Burnt along with the entire house.
Married to six men, and strangely
all of them are dead.
I'm sure you've seen what
we've recovered.
We need to do a DNA profiling.
Hope you're not too busy.
It's a priority case.
Arun?
What are you doing?
How come you never
showed this to me?
Why?
Is this Susanna?
Saheb.
Now, she's no more.
Detached from life, and
torn apart by love,
My Saheb was melancholic.
All her life, she was in search
for her eternal love.
She was very lonely.
Just an infant when
she lost her mother,
and before she could become
an adult, her father died.
My senior Saheb, her father.
He was her everything!
Friend, mother, and brother.
And after he was gone
she tried hard to find
him in every man she met.
On the day of her father's funeral
in full black attire, she
reminded me of soft snow
rolling off the mountain
on a silent night.
No wonder she radiated in black.
And soon, it became her colour.
Uncle Goonga!
He was dumb but he had a lot to say.
I was born an orphan!
Don't know if he adopted
me or I adopted him.
My first real competition.
And senior Saheb's last wish.
The first husband,
Major Edwin Rodriques.
Goonga!
How much longer?
Ghalib!
He says, everything will be
ready in the next half an hour.
I don't want to see any
of his boys around.
Ghalib.
Poet by name, butler by profession
and mocks a Bollywood villain.
Anything else, sir?
What did he say?
Thank you, sir!
If he knew you were calling him
a fucker he'd pull your eyes out.
Ghalib.
The third ace in her trio.
Maggie aunty!
Under whose care Saheb grew up.
She became her mother
and her best friend.
She had a few other friends too.
Venomous, dangerous...
but faithful like no other.
Goonga was daddy's favourite jockey.
Why don't we hire a professional
rider from abroad?
What do you think you're doing?
Stealing!
Show me your hands!
Whose rascal is this?
I picked a few for Candy, Sir.
Who's Candy?
Your new horse.
How much have you studied?
Anything else?
Miss Saheb, forgive me!
Thought I'd help this orphan.
Will send this fool
back to the village.
You won't see this rat anymore.
He won't be seen here anymore.
Because he'll be starting
school tomorrow.
Saheb, thank you!
Snap! My life changed
in a split second.
Saheb picked me up from
a bed of thorns
and placed me on a bed of roses.
This is the new admission
I was talking about.
She was my goddess.
And I, her blind devotee.
All said and done Arun, the
Major was pretty handsome.
The perfect Indian husband.
Boring, possessive, insecure
and a doubting Thomas.
Mr. Stinker!
-Cheers!
All throughout operation Blue Star.
I can't figure out if you're getting
older or younger by the day.
Edwin is greying fast
but you look the same.
Really, since when?
Since yesterday.
Every morning, I quit drinking.
Really!
"I quit every morning."
Stop fluttering around.
Why do you keep reminding
me of my disability?
It's high time we had a child.
Once you're a mother, you'll
learn wifely duties too.
Did you visit the gynaecologist?
All tests are normal.
The doctor says, there's
nothing wrong with me.
So now...
I'm disabled in bed too?
How often have I told you
to knock before entering?
Next time, I'll bury you alive.
This was bound to happen,
my friends!
Marry in a haste and...
Repent at leisure.
You want to break his other leg?
Sir! Are you alright?
Goonga! Goonga!
Goonga, what happened?
What happened?
Ghalib... Ghalib!
He will survive.
But we're sorry, we couldn't
save his eye.
One eye is enough to witness
what's going to happen.
The next time I saw the
Major for the last time.
Going to the dense forest
looking for a man eating panther.
Or the animal won't come.
The beast in me is already here.
Major sir.
Major sir, panther.
The panther wasn't interested
in the goat.
He was looking for humans.
Can't tell whether the Major
lost his balance...
or whether someone pushed him.
Nevertheless
it took the forest officials
two days to find the Major
or whatever was left of him.
I just couldn't get myself
to mourn for the Major.
Fate had given me another chance
to woo my Saheb.
Like a balloon,
my hopes went soaring.
But she chose the guitar instead.
Indian women fall for
a guitarist over a riff.
And this asshole had
the vocal chords too.
Before the wedding this creature
was called Jamshed Singh Rathod.
From now I'm Jimmy.
Made for each other, that's right!
Her lips were ripe and so close
Oh Mama
I looked at them
And all but froze
Oh Mama
You wrote this for me?
No, it sprung from within.
Oh Mama
My heart now only thinks
From the heart
Oh Mama
My heart often bangs my head
No stranger to me
May my fall be her rise
She, my nemesis, too,
Is no stranger to me
A beating heart forever
Stays beaten
Oh Mama
Oh Mama, she shoots at me
This marble-eyed meow-like girl
Oh Mama
She steals on me, not
A sound she makes...
Oh Mama
She smuggles herself into my dreams,
Pray it doesn't stay a dream
Oh Mama
There isn't hope
But hope remains, still
How I languish in the
Anguish of love
Something's being ripped out of me
Oh Mama
Oh Mama, she shoots at me
This marble-eyed meow-like girl
Oh Mama
Welcome back to
'Cultivation Today'.
Many farmers...
Okay that's enough!
What's the proof this is yours?
This was my college composition.
Jamshed was the backup
vocalist in my band.
Bloody thief.
Where the hell is he? Call him.
Here's proof.
It first came out in English, now
they're launching the holy version.
Now what do you want?
Respect.
Shall we?
Thanks man!
Here's a new composition.
Interested?
At heart, At heart
At heart, the heart's a heart
Full of tricks and illusions,
Simply a smooth operator
The heart's heady at times
And at times, take heart
Full of tricks and illusions,
Simply a smooth operator
The heart's heady at times
And at times, take heart
It's a gentle whisper,
At times and at times
An uproarious drum roll
At times, it's the raging fire
In your veins
At times it is the calming coolness
Believe it or not
Is only a matter of the heart
At heart, the heart's a heart
The shore for drowning men
The ignorance of the boor
A hundred heavens, that's
What it's worth
At heart, the heart's a heart
Where are you, boss?
The Berlin wall has collapsed.
So has the government.
And you're stuck on cocaine?
This is what you call heroin!
No one has the balls to
behave in this manner.
This is Bappi's song!
You know how many musicians
are waiting for him?
A hundred! Who is going to pay?
Your father?
At heart, the heart's a heart
Ladies and gentlemen, Jimmy
will be here soon.
Please remain calm.
He will be here soon.
Please remain calm, please.
A heart which beats
At heart, the heart's a heart
Susie, what are you doing here?
When did you come?
Why didn't you inform me?
We were playing a game!
Cops and robbers!
You wanna play?
Jimmy is a robber.
Cops and robbers!
FBI, dead! CBI, dead!
Sahib was stubborn this time
to save her marriage.
This time she wouldn't give up.
Why are you doing this to me?
I won't go back to drugs!
I swear.
Please, Susie!
I will choke you to
death once I'm free.
You are messing with
Jamshed Singh Rathod.
I am of royal blood.
I will cut you into pieces
and feed you to the dogs.
Susie.
I can't leave him alone.
He is my life.
By now Saheb's life
began to settle.
Jimmy was getting better.
But she didn't realize
that drugs addicts
become sly once they're caught.
'Champions of deception.'
This was confiscated from
a drug peddler yesterday.
Who else could own such
a beautiful piece?
I recognized it as soon as I saw it.
It's priceless too. How much?
You never put a price on priceless
things, Inspector.
'Keemat.'
Inspector Keemat Lal.
Was a favorite in my father's
antique collection.
I'd like to question your servants.
A marble-eyed meow-like girl
O doggy
Servants here are loyal
more than their owner.
You can call me by my name,
if you please.
Susanna.
How dare I, madame?
Thank you. Nevertheless.
I don't think I would ever...
maybe another time.
Right now, it's not appropriate.
Jim.
Careful, sir!
These snakes are venomous.
The snake temple.
Snake temple?
But madame is a Christian.
Yes, she is!
Her father was a Christian,
but mother, a Hindu.
She set it up.
Saheb feeds them milk, every
morning without fail!
-How?
-She goes down.
Isn't she scared?
No! They're her pets.
She thinks humans
are more poisonous.
Wow!
That's great.
Sir, snake!
Are you alright, sir?
Yes, I'm fine.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Six, five, four, three, two, one.
Whose footprint is this?
-Could be anyone's.
-No, no.
Not just anyone's.
It belongs to the murderer.
Murderer?
-Is anyone left?
-Yes, there is.
Who is it?
It's me.
Why do you bother, Madame?
You've gotten your feet all muddy!
There is no need, Madame.
Not madame, Susanna.
You are just. I mean...
how will I?
Really. I mean.
Joking!
Not right. Who am I to say!
Just as you wish, the next time.
But it's fine, not a bad thing.
I'll try next time.
But how will I?
It is believed that Jesus spent
his last days in Kashmir.
Saheb left for Kashmir
in search of the Lord.
Instead of Jesus,
she met "Mohammed".
Hail Allah!
Mohammed Wasiullah Khan.
A.K.A The Traveler.
From the soot of spiraling
everyday smoke
a patch of sky, now
remains blackened
all day long.
-Great!
-Wonderful!
Do not bow your head beneath it
for now when you do so,
God yanks His feet away.
In the mounds of rotting rubbish
heads of bodies gone
cold still smolder.
Wonderful! Wonderful!
Hungry four legged animals, fight
over the bones of arms and legs.
The flesh and the bone
belongs to the one
who first digs its
teeth into the flesh.
I would like to have
your attention, please.
The flesh and the bone
belongs to the one
who first digs its
teeth into the flesh.
The men of faith now ask, who first
dug his spade into this earth!
Some say there was
a mosque here once.
Some say no,
once a temple stood here.
But when you touch your
forehead to the ground.
God yanks His feet away now.
He cannot bring Himself to believe.
He cannot bring Himself to believe
that He once called
this place, His home.
-Wow!
This time, Saheb not
only had a new lover
but also a new name and religion.
Susanna Anna Marie
Johannes was now.
Sultana Wasiullah Khan.
Thank you.
One more, please!
Don't go!
One more verse!
-My next verse.
-Yes, please.
A day shall dawn
bringing with it a calm
the heart bereft of desires,
the mind devoid of passion.
Shoreless, totally fathomless
Close your eyes, please
I have been drowning
I need to breathe
Shoreless, totally fathomless,
Close your eyes, please
I have been drowning,
I need to breathe
Lillah!
Turn your face away from me
It'll be a great kindness.
-Turn your face away from me
-Sultana?
It'll be a great kindness
Ever since I saw you
My breath has stopped
my breath has stopped
Shoreless, totally fathomless
Close your eyes, please
I have been drowning
I need to breathe
-May I?
-Proceed.
If a flitting glance of yours,
were to graze me.
That would be greeting enough
and I'll keep my
eyes forever lowered.
Wow!
Ever since I saw you.
My breath has...
-Stopped.
-Wow.
Encore!
Who is that?
Your uncle!
Pray, take a look
At your feet
Something's stuck, it seems
Please ask Time to move on
If a flitting glance of yours
Were to graze me
That would be greeting enough
And I'll keep my
eyes forever lowered
Ever since I saw you
my breath has stopped
Shoreless, totally fathomless
Close your eyes, please
I have been drowning
I need to breathe
Lillah!
As tender and romantic in his poetry
as brutal in bed.
Unless he beat the shit
out of the woman
he remained soft.
Come on, bite me.
Come on, let's lose ourselves.
Initially she tried hard
to conceal her scars.
However, her wounds grew deeper.
Love became a myth.
A mirage. You think it's there,
but it really isn't.
Prayers, offerings and sacrifices,
she tried it all.
But nothing worked.
Is it coming from the
heart or the being?
These fumes,
from where do they come?
Love is a heavy stone.
Not for the weak ones.
What does 'Natawan' mean?
'Debilitated.'
Weak.
Feeble.
Sultana!
Cold-blooded!
Why kill someone?
She could've left him and come home.
Who would've stopped her?
As a child, Miss Saheb
would walk to school.
There were two paths.
Both equidistant.
Neither were different.
And one day, there came a crazy dog,
Who scared her every single day.
She could've taken the other path.
She hid her father's
pistol in her bag.
And bang!
Saheb always gets her way.
And the dogs are blown off!
Namaste
I'm grateful to you.
Then I must be Anna!
In Hindi, please.
I'm learning the language.
What else have you picked up?
My love for you is eternal.
Let's go, Saheb.
Anna.
Please have dinner with me
at a nice restaurant tonight.
I am very rich.
Can I at least drop you
to your mansion?
I have my car.
"But I have something better,
a mother."
Amitabh Bachchan.
From the movie, Deewar.
Goodbye, sweethearts.
From now on...
Russia and me! Why?
Because you, my friend,
are headed to Russia.
To study at St. Petersburg
Medical Academy.
Cheers!
Why?
Because, Nik loves me.
To hell I'm going to Russia!
Why not?
Because, I hate vodka.
It's because...
Quite a distance he has walked
A thousand distant miles
Another Pushkin from Russia
Who's left Moscow
Only to be with me
Something like this is
Possible only in love
Darling
Let your eyes feast on mine
Darling let the passion rush
Don't hold it
Back let this love gush
Darling let
Your eyes feast on mine
Don't hold it
Back let this love gush
The Spring's joyless
The beloved's heart's restless
Hold back the songbirds
Darling let
Your eyes feast on mine
Anna?
That hillock enveloped in mist
Where the fairies once lived
You'll find it across
The high Khyber
That's what all
The fairies still say
Darling
I'm merely a serf,
Let me groom the Princess
Let this restless heart
Steal a little solace
Let me conquer
The heart of my beloved
Darling let your
Eyes feast on mine
The Spring's joyless
The beloved's heart's restless
Hold back the songbirds
Darling let your
Eyes feast on mine
Don't hold it back
let this love gush.
Darling let your
Eyes feast on mine
Don't hold it back
Let this love gush
Darling let your
Eyes feast on mine
Yes.
Who were you talking to, Nik?
A colleague, from Moscow.
Woman?
What do you think?
Your last words of the
conversation meant...
"Darling, I will be back soon."
You are hiding something
from me, Nik.
When I say I go to Kanyakumari.
I don't go to Kanyakumari.
I go to Koodankulam, instead.
Koodankulam?
Yes, Koodankulam.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nik.
You are a spy?
Come on!
No.
No!
I am your friend.
And...
my love for you is eternal.
A kilo of this, please.
I'm just not ready for
another marriage.
Why not?
Marriage is the worst thing
that happened to mankind.
I'm pregnant...
with your child.
A shocking incident.
India had finally accomplished
its nuclear test.
And instead of Hiroshima,
it was now, my heart!
Saheb dropped two bombs.
First, to get married!
The other, to send me to Russia.
It was my fault.
I should've kept mum.
I made a trip to Moscow to
attend a college seminar.
And what I saw there...
blew my mind.
Nikolai Vronsky, in fact had
two Annas.
One in India and
the other in Moscow.
I still blame myself for his death.
I shouldn't have sent
her those pictures.
Where's Anna?
She's at the market.
-But why?
-For her new wedding gown.
Goonga! Great job.
Lovely!
Feels so good.
The late Major,
her first husband.
He was eaten by a panther,
wasn't he?
Shut up Goonga!
He says we pushed the Major down.
Don't believe him, sir.
He is a big liar.
Goonga, shut the hell up.
Why are you telling me all this?
Because he too, had a mother.
No, not at all.
Don't believe them,
they are just lying!
They say, that we gave him
an overdose of heroin.
Husband number three.
Wasiullah Khan a.k.a The Traveler!
We dug his grave in the snow
and buried him alive.
Where is Anna?
Anna is over here!
Look!
Anna's here!
And that is you,
Nikolai Vronsky!
My husband number four
with his wife number two.
Cheers to that!
Four, four...
R. A. W.
R. A. W...
A wife in every country!
Darling let your eyes feast on mine
Run away! Run fast!
He ran away!
Believe me, we were just acting
like husband and wife.
I know you can play
a very good husband!
But to play such a great daddy.
My love for you is eternal.
Come on, you've been called.
There she is.
Have a seat, please.
How're you doing, madame?
-It's you.
-Yes, it's me, Keemat.
Inspector Keemat Lal!
This time, you're in real trouble.
-Look, Mr. Keemat.
-No 'Mr.' please.
Just Keemat.
I've gone through all your reports.
The local police is convinced
about your involvement.
According to them it's a
clear cut case of murder.
But the case is sensitive.
The Ministry of external affairs,
Russian embassy, are all involved.
You are an intelligent woman.
But, this time...
there is a certain item missing
from your husband's belongings.
If only I could
get my hands on that.
You get it?
That's it!
Just leave the rest to me.
Great!
By the way, what are you doing
this evening? Must be busy.
I need to inspect the
scene of the crime.
Maybe, some other time then.
Do you prefer vegetarian
or non vegetarian?
Don't bother.
Non vegetarian.
And what would you prefer to drink?
Nothing in particular.
What do you prefer?
Anything but vodka.
You're going to get me killed,
madame.
Sorry, Sunaina.
Wow!
I think I've had a bit
too much to drink.
Never mind.
You'll sweat it out.
Where?
At the scene of the crime.
It is pretty deep.
In the dark anyone could
miss his step.
It was a full moon night.
Mind you, he didn't slip.
He climbed down
on his own.
Must've been slippery
because of the rain...
and moss.
The rain?
In this season?
A lot of accidents can happen
when one is drunk.
He had quit drinking.
Alcohol!
How do I...
What should I say?
Forget about it.
Sorry?
Madame!
Darkness!
Pitch black!
Raining...
cats and dogs!
And...
the white man slipped.
Died!
Reached hell.
The bastard deserved it!
Madame!
I'll never forget this favor.
'Pure satisfaction.'
Like I've bathed a hundred
times in the holy waters.
No need to worry anymore.
If you ever come to Delhi...
I'd like to return the favor.
Should I go?
Yes!
Keemat left, only to return sooner.
He definitely reached Delhi
but left his heart behind.
He'd come back for it every time
but always managed
to leave it behind.
Come Madame.
Come.
But Keemat kept on coming.
Saheb was left
with no other option.
His quest for 'pure satisfaction'
knew no end.
I confessed to my wife.
Why?
I wanted a divorce.
And I got it too!
Here, look!
I can't live without you anymore.
I'd rather die.
I will die.
I swear on the Lord himself!
Oh my God. There was poison
in the Viagra bottle?
The bottle contained Viagra pills.
What was it then?
Accident? She killed him.
And you knew it.
How would I know?
Of course, you wouldn't. You
were blinded by her love.
Some years later, I returned
from Russia, a Doctor.
But Saheb had turned into
'a patient.'
What has the world done
to my little bunny!
What are you looking for?
I know there's one
hiding somewhere.
I just can't seem to find
the rascal, when I want.
White hair?
Don't say it aloud.
It's a bad omen.
Here it is.
Show it. Let me see!
Fetch the scissors.
There on the record.
Snip it at the root.
See?
How much I need you.
Right there. Put it in the box.
I hate New Year's Eve.
When did you see me last?
It's been two years.
Do I look any different?
You've become
a little more beautiful.
I haven't changed at all?
Sure?
You've grown up to be shy.
Please don't, Saheb.
Why not?
It's my responsibility
to educate you.
The delicate thread between
us had snapped.
That was the last time
I ever saw her.
The next morning
I took Goonga along
and left her forever.
No one to fear, and no
favors to be returned.
You still miss her, right?
Get some sleep. It's pretty late.
It's an early morning flight
and you need to be in time
for security check.
Hello!
We'll find out right now, details
about his last call.
Please calm down.
Here, have some water.
I told him you are very angry.
Hand me the phone.
I tried calling you a hundred times.
There is no conference in Delhi.
Arun!
Nandini, I'm fine wherever I am.
I'll be back in a day or two.
For what?
I can't believe you would
betray me for anyone.
But there is someone.
Is she alive?
Arun?
Is Susanna alive?
Do you need more time
to think over it?
No. I've already made my decision.
Alright then.
See you in the church at 11.
I've repaid your favors, Saheb.
Your Saheb is no more.
I kept looking for reasons to
live, after you were gone.
And one day, I heard
about your wedding.
What better reason could
I have waited for
to end my life.
The phone and car, are
both out of order.
My mistress needs to
get to the hospital.
Please, sir, for God's sake.
Please help, sir. Please!
Otherwise my mistress will die.
I was desperate to finally
rest in the arms of Jesus.
Looks like Jesus changed his mind.
Maybe in guilt,
he sent me an angel.
I was dead in my head.
But when I woke up, felt
a little strange.
A pair of spectacles
on God's nose?
You are...
Tarafdar.
Dr. Modhushudhon Tarafdar.
Who slowly became the big
brother of the house.
He was considered some
kind of Miracle Doctor.
A strange concoction of allopathy,
naturopathy
Ayurveda and spirituality.
Ridiculous!
This mushroom is called
Jack O' Lantern.
It has a number of uses.
Very useful mushroom.
A bit could cure,
too much could kill.
There is plenty of evil all around.
And even plenty is never
really enough.
It's always scarce.
But for the one who survives
even in scarcity,
nothing seems scarce.
Less, more, more,
less, that's life.
So would you prefer less
or more in your soup?
For a healer like him, I was willing
to remain ill all my life.
And I would've but Modhu promised,
he wouldn't go back to Calcutta.
Marriage wasn't on my mind.
But Modhu wanted me to be
the heir to his wealth.
He was afraid that if he were
to leave this world before me,
then his ex-wife and daughter
would harass me.
My life was grounded
but I was flying.
Modhu.
Khan!
What happened to the lights?
Khan! Maggie aunty!
There's a robber upstairs.
And he has a knife.
Be careful!
News is just in that in shootout
at the Taj hotel.
NSE Major Sandeep Unnikrishnan
has been killed.
At the Trident Oberoi
and Nariman House...
Don't worry!
Everything will be fine, come.
Modhu.
Towel.
-Thank you.
-Let me see?
I was destined to be with
all the wrong men.
At first I was completely shattered!
But slowly I began to fear him.
For the first time, it was
my life that was in danger.
Look what I cooked
especially for you.
How can you think such a thing?
Have you lost it?
What are you doing?
Susanna, look.
This is a big misunderstanding,
Susanna. And, even if it isn't...
Please, darling,
please listen to me.
It's your turn.
I really needed it.
I lost a lot of money in business.
I truly love you Susanna,
believe me.
I wasn't even destined
for a peaceful death.
I had forgotten all the bullets,
next to Tarafdar's body.
Sleeping pills had failed once.
I didn't want
to hang on a noose.
I'd lost respect for myself.
I was shattered.
For a professional swimmer
drowning isn't an option.
I was punishing myself
for my cowardice.
A new death every moment.
And then I found out
I was dead for the rest of world.
I couldn't let Maggie's
sacrifice go in vain.
She forced me to take
on life,
one last time.
Of course, you were forced
into everything
into marriage, into murders!
Did you ever stop to wonder, why
you committed all those sins?
For whom?
For my heart!
Your heart.
-The heart!
For the sake of your heart
you sent six people to their
final abode before their time.
You won't understand, sugar.
Here's a little fact.
Every single wife
has at least once in her
life entertained
the thought of getting
rid of her husband.
Why don't you ask your wife?
I'm sure she's thought
of at least one way
to murder you.
Any idea why you've survived?
A child makes
the husband more acceptable.
That's the reason why
you never had a child!
You fulfilled that desire of mine.
Never have I shared our
love with anyone,
nor will I ever in the future.
In the future?
Now you won't find a sacrificial
lamb, Saheb.
Your beauty...
You've become a little scary.
He has accepted me for
the person I am
with all my sins and virtues
and this scary...
scary face of mine.
Who?
My seventh husband.
There's a beautiful church,
in the old city.
Will you come?
Tomorrow morning. Eleven o'clock.
I won't let you take
another life, Saheb.
Hey sugar!
You won't be able to save him.
He has already sacrificed
himself for love.
The world, the universe
and its radiance
aren't enough to satisfy my soul.
This peace, this joy, can be attained,
only through Jesus Christ.
Who is very dear to me.
The Lord of the Universe.
I, Sister Anna...
in the presence of Mother Mary
solemnly vow to Lord Jesus
that from now on I belong to Him alone.
From today He is my only master...
my spouse.
There is not a soul in sight now
Come, acknowledge me now, at least
Not a soul stirs this moment
Come, embrace me in your fold
Embrace me just this once
Then take me along
Hope there is no misery
On the other side
Jesus
You hear the tolling
Of the church bells
Jesus
Yet all you choose is
To keep your quiet
Jesus.
How do you pick who amongst
Us is worthy of your grace
Jesus.
You hear the tolling
Of the church bells
Jesus
Yet all you choose is
to keep your quiet
Jesus
I want to confess my sins, Father!
My seven sins.
Arun! Arun!
Stop the car! Right now!
Did you say anything to the police?
I haven't told them the truth yet.
Or you'd be in jail for
the rest of your life.
If you ever...
try to see her again
What happened to your spectacles?
Someone cast an evil eye.