MAN:
Stop!
Stop or we will fire!
Run, you idiots!
Don't let him get away!
[COWS MOOING]
[PANTING]
He's disappeared, sir.
That's impossible. He's got to be here.
Search the huts again.
JHUNKU:
Apu.
You managed to escape!
Did you get shot?
[THINKING]:
Will it all end here?
Are we headed for
failure yet again, Aparna?
Apu?
I can't lose you now.
Not after all these years
of tireless efforts.
JHUNKU:
Our worlds were so different.
I still don't know
what brought us together.
Get away, heh.
APARNA:
Jhunku, don't be scared.
We have white cards.
-Get moving.
-I didn't do anything.
Are you with them? Move it!
BOY:
I am not a revolutionary!
OFFICER:
I'll teach you a lesson.
-British.
-Leave India!
-Long live.
-Jatin Das!
-British.
-Quit India!
-Long live.
-Jatin Das!
JHUNKU:
You gave me such a hard time...
...for I'd visit
the District Magistrate's house.
But the thing is,
I trusted him.
And everything he'd say.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello. Wilkinson here.
And that's a D minor,
not a major.
You'll have to
concentrate, Jhunku.
WILKINSON:
You tell Johnson to stand down.
Yes, you heard me right.
And tell him to return
to police headquarters.
Immediately.
Sir. Sir.
Mr. Wilkinson order. No action.
JHUNKU: For you, he was
only a political leader...
...no doubt, a visionary one.
Guns down!
Company, about-face!
March!
-Long live!
-Jatin Das!
JHUNKU: But for me, Masterda was
much more than that.
He taught me to
question everything.
Even him!
He is not Johnson, he is Farmer.
Mrs. Farmer.
He is not Johnson.
I couldn't come.
I mean, Dad didn't
let me go to the rally.
Did I even ask you about it?
I have got some detective
stories for you.
-Byomkesh Bakshi.
-Yes.
I kept it inside.
Even a dog has a better life.
A dog can wander
where it wants to.
Go on. They won't bite you!
Sukhendu is also there.
We should have cornered Johnson.
No problem,
we'll get him next time.
Next time? We have to do it now!
BOY: As if killing one Britisher
will bring down the empire!
Arrest him.
Ganesh Ghosh.
Anant Singh.
Ambika Chakrabarti.
Lokenath Bal.
Nirmal Sen.
And Mr....
Surya. Sen.
So what is this sudden
interest in geography?
These areas that you circled.
Why?
What do you plan to do?
I was hoping
you wouldn't tell me.
I'm giving you one
last chance, Mr. Sen.
[SURYA GASPING]
What is your plan?
[SCREAMS]
[GROWNING]
Shall we try again?
What is your plan?
Johnson!
All this must stop at once.
But I'm very close to results, sir.
[GROANING]
Let them walk.
Walk, sir?
Yes.
I want them tailed.
I want details.
Who they meet?
Where they go?
What they do?
You are trained in surveillance...
...I presume.
WOMAN:
Subhash.
You haven't told me
about your day at school.
MAN:
Jhunku, come here!
What?
-Please.
-Who gave you this book?
-But, Masterda....
-You know the book is banned.
See the rubbish your
beloved son is reading!
Sarat Babu's writing is rubbish?
I mean....
It's filled with patriotism and....
-Dad, I don't think--
-Don't you dare talk back!
I didn't become a barrister...
...just so I can bail you
out of jail.
I'm trying my best to get
my son to go to England.
Wilkinson has gone out
of his way to help you.
Is this how you show
your gratitude? Disgraceful!
Run, Ganesh!
Faster!
Come on.
MAN:
They are utterly shameless!
I was peeing the other day...
...and the constables stood right
behind me. He kept on staring!
I said okay, check it out.
The color of my piss shows
I am a revolutionary.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
So what's the report,
Ambikada. Nirmal?
What's wrong?
Nobody is ready to assist us.
Didn't you explain properly?
Nobody believes it can be pulled off.
Not here, nor anywhere else.
Purely a pipe dream!
Pipe dream!
Our plans are useless?
Who says our plans
are just pipe dreams?
If we try, they can come true.
What are you saying, Surjo?
Taking over
the entire Chittagong...
...just by ourselves,
without outside help...
...that's sheer lunacy!
Precisely! That's exactly
why we should do it.
Because nobody thinks
it can ever happen.
Everybody thinks the
British are unconquerable.
That they cannot be defeated.
But why can't we destroy
that myth here and now?
What if...?
What if we don't succeed?
And what if we do?
The British aren't as bad
as you think they are.
I wonder why I tolerate
you so much.
Apu, do you think only
Masterda knows the way?
Why? Certainly not!
We're waiting for you
to show the way...
...after you return from Oxford.
We'll get along better
with the British...
...if we understand their ways. Right?
Of course. The British are just
waiting to hand us freedom!
All that's missing is you!
Go to that side.
You should come to this side.
-Well done.
-No, not here.
Don't expect help from Calcutta.
And weapons?
First, hit him on the head!
I think Masterda is planning something.
Something radical and momentous!
Whatever it is, I want to join in.
You can't even watch a goat die
and you'll kill the British.
A goat is innocent.
Come on.
Priti.
Nirmalda is totally
checking you out.
You think everyone's
checking me out.
Come on.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Come inside.
Come on.
Nobody else is here.
I just wanted to make
sure you are all right.
See? All in one piece.
Except I'll never be
able to write.
Sit down.
Will you please tie the bandage?
So difficult with one hand.
Masterda, wouldn't you be
better off...
...if you stayed away from
shootouts, encounters...
...from all this rebellion?
[LAUGHING]
That's why I like you so much.
You come up with the most
remarkable ideas.
But aren't you chasing the impossible?
Have you seen an elephant in a zoo?
Of course, many times. Why?
The elephant is far stronger...
...than the chains on its feet.
Yet it doesn't break free.
Do you know why?
Because it's grown
accustomed to the chains.
Binode, look over there.
Hurry up!
-Pour it right over there.
-Where?
-Johnson's coming. Hide!
-Get away.
Run! Get away!
Tell me how your education
is coming along.
Oh, good.
-I came first in the class.
-Really?
You know I'd promised
your father...
...every assistance for you
to go to England.
You'd like to study in England,
wouldn't you, Jhunku?
Yes, yes.
I want to be a lawyer
like my father.
Splendid!
By the way,
I wanted to talk to you about...
...what happened to Johnson.
Do you know who did it?
Look, I've made a list
of names of the boys...
...and...
...perhaps you know them, Jhunku.
Amar Nandi.
Tun Chowdhury.
Sukhendu Guha.
JHUNKU:
Autumn was my favorite season.
The gentle, cool breeze...
...brought relief from
the sweltering heat.
Pass me the ball.
BOY 1: Pass it to me.
BOY 2: Take it.
Goal!
JHUNKU:
Even I'd come out to play football.
-Penalty!
-Come on.
Come on.
It's all right. Come along.
JHUNKU: By then, the Johnson
incident was a distant memory.
Pass it here.
WOMAN:
I'll donate my jewelry to Masterda.
MAN:
Rajat.
-Jiten is also with us.
-Rajat, give him the list.
Give it to him.
Masterda, let's go.
[MEN PLAYING TRADITIONAL MUSIC]
Who's the girl
you want me to meet?
-Oh, come on!
-Who is she?
Who is she among them?
[ALL CLAPPING]
Hey.
-Let go!
-Come on.
-Who is he?
-What's going on?
-What happened?
-Hey.
[GUN SHOT]
Sukhendu.
-Sukhendu.
WOMAN: What happened to him?
[SUKHENDU GASPING]
Sukhendu.
Hey.
[CHATTERING]
[SOBBING]
Tell us what to do...
...or we'll deal with the British.
He killed a boy.
It was an accident.
The unintended consequence...
...of overzealous law enforcement.
You can't justify this, darling.
[SIGHS]
So when do we take over
Chittagong?
But you said it was impossible.
I can get more like these.
Who's going to use them?
Those who know how to shoot
are under surveillance or in jail.
Then we recruit those...
-...who are untrained.
-What do you mean?
Only the white card holders.
No more red cards,
no more suspicion.
No, he can't do that.
You bastard.
Sukhendu is dead because of you.
Why did you tell them
about Sukhendu?
Didn't you know
what they would do?
You dirty double-crosser!
[WATER SPLASHING]
I knew I'd find you here.
You must believe me.
I.... I....
I'm not a traitor.
Says who? Of course not.
I liked Sukhenduda a lot.
Yes, I know.
That Wilkinson...
...made a complete fool of me.
I feel ashamed of myself.
-I can understand.
-No, you can't.
Because you've never
let anyone down.
I have to avenge
Sukhenduda's death.
I won't spare Johnson.
MAN 1: My leave has just
come through, you know.
-Really?
MAN 1: Yes.
Here's to a white Christmas.
MAN 2: Evening.
-Good evening.
MAN 3:
This is by far--
The governor general in Calcutta...
...asked me to give this to you.
I can't--
But I requested Johnson's transfer.
WILKINSON: Ladies and gentlemen,
may I raise a toast...
...in honor of our new
DIG of police, Chittagong.
Here is to Mr. Charles Johnson.
Sir.
Yes.
Jhunku's looking for you.
downstairs.
Excuse me one moment.
Yes, Jhunku, what is it?
Johnson is DIG?
Chief of police?
So he's been rewarded
for murdering Sukhendu.
Jhunku, I think you'd better go home.
This is the British justice
you'd brag about.
You liar!
You hypocrite!
This belongs to my dad.
I stole it.
But why?
I want to join you.
You are always with me.
Not that way.
With the gun.
Do you know what
we intend to do?
You want to drive the British out.
That's good enough for me.
You look tired.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Not tomorrow. Right this minute.
If you don't take me in
right now...
...I'll go on a hunger strike.
JHUNKU:
Preparations had begun.
Everyone watch carefully.
Close one eye and aim
with the other. Fire!
JHUNKU:
I left home at the crack of dawn.
But I pacified my mother by saying...
...I was selected to join
the football team.
MAN:
Aim carefully.
JHUNKU:
Imagine me on the football team.
Fire!
Don't worry!
JHUNKU:
I rarely saw you those days, Aparna.
[WHISTEL BLOWS]
MAN:
Easy does it.
Squat here.
Sit down.
Carefully.
Backs straight!
Together. Breathe in.
-Breathe out.
-Jhunku, back straight.
He is coming.
Inhale.
Exhale.
What are you all doing here?
-Yes.
-What's going on? At this unearthly hour.
Preparing for the upcoming
football match.
Some yoga, meditation,
concentration.
-Want to try?
-Just shut up.
Keep your boys under control.
Show me your identity cards.
Check it. Nothing but white.
[SCOFFS]
-Satisfied?
-Let's go.
Inhale.
Exhale.
Breathe in.
Bullets out!
[ALL CHUCKLING]
Guns in.
Bullets out!
And backs straight.
They're going away. They're gone.
SURYA:
Listen carefully.
There are only two British
strongholds in Chittagong.
Police lines...
...and the Auxiliary Forces Armory.
We capture them and break their back.
Two sentries outside,
four more inside.
The British officers
won't only be in these two places.
Then let's attack
where they all gather.
Right. European Club.
All captured in one go.
It's not that easy.
They'll get help with one phone call.
-From where?
-From Calcutta.
Then we blow up the train tracks.
It's all over.
And the telephone lines too.
Thirty boys and
with zero experience.
Experience.
How old were you
when you beat up the Britisher?
Hello, Mom? Yeah.
Come here. Come on.
Come on. Pin him down.
-Come on.
-Show him.
Apu, I....
Surjo?
We lost our firearms supplier.
So how many guns do we have now?
Five pistols.
Seven rifles.
A total of 12 in all.
Fire!
Go back. Jhunku, Bidhu, Hari.
Fire.
What's in store for them?
Not one of them has reached 20.
Do reconsider. Let's postpone a bit.
Absolutely not. It's now or never.
Thank you.
Darling.
What's happened to your
idea about returning home?
There would be no one
to make you chicken there.
Well, I quite like cooking.
A letter from my brother.
One third of
Glasgow is out of work.
This seems to be
the right place to hide.
No?
I wonder why Masterda
made you a part of this mission.
How are you, Priti?
Fine.
I wanted to ask you something.
Sure.
Priti, I wanted to tell you....
I mean, what I wanted to say....
Do tell, please.
I love you very much.
I mean, how you love me--
I mean your fighting spirit.
It's just exemplary. Inspirational.
You must keep it alive forever.
Then take me along with you.
How do you know
I am going somewhere?
-You are going somewhere?
-No.
I'm getting late.
-Nirmalda?
-I'll catch you later.
[GASPS]
JHUNKU:
Fine. I'll eat later.
Jhunku, listen.
[SIGHS]
Jhunku. What's the matter
with you these days?
You're behaving so oddly.
SURYA: One thing you should
never forget...
...is that we are not trigger-happy...
...bloodthirsty mercenaries.
Mother's looking for you.
We have no right
to behave the same way...
...as they have with our families.
Leave all civilians alone...
...whether Indian or British!
SURYA:
It's time.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
The train arrives in 15 minutes.
Can it be done?
[METAL CLANGING]
[MAN GASPING]
Boys!
Break it!
ALL:
Long live revolution!
JHUNKU: Only a few sentries
stood guard at the armory.
Glory to motherland!
Long live revolution!
JHUNKU:
The British never imagined...
...that the Indians would dare
storm their establishment.
[BOTH GASP]
Run, you cowards!
-The revolutionaries are here!
-Where did they come from?
-Weren't they all in jail?
-Come on, hurry up!
MAN 1: Save yourselves.
MAN 2: Run!
MAN 3:
They have our guns!
You two, go to the armory. Hurry.
You two, get out of here.
Tell the magistrate that Chittagong
belongs to the revolutionaries.
Yes, sir.
-Let us wear our uniforms.
-I'll take off whatever you're wearing.
-Buzz off.
-Sure.
JHUNKU:
Not a single bullet was fired.
Intruders, run and save yourselves!
JHUNKU:
I'm glad we didn't have to.
My hands were so clammy...
...that I couldn't hold my rifle straight.
-You bloody bastards!
MAN: Hands up!
JHUNKU: Lokenath and Nirmal
had gone to the AFI Armory...
...to fetch the machine guns.
[ENGINE STARTS]
It's open!
[LAUGHING]
I'm sorry to barge in like this, sir.
But the AFI armory
has been taken over.
What are you talking about?
-Sir.
-Sir, terrorists, sir.
Where are your uniforms?
Sir, guns.
They took over. Surya Sen.
Ganesh Ghosh and Anant Singh, sir.
-I'll call the train.
-It's no use, sir. The lines are cut.
Railways lines also.
No train can come.
But I told you to have them under
constant surveillance.
-We expected them to--
-No point in going over that.
-Have they come to the cantonment?
-No, we're safe.
Let's not fool ourselves any further.
We have to flee this town.
They have taken over Chittagong.
Masterda, Nirmalda and the boys!
-Jhunku is with them.
-Jhunku?
-The club looks deserted.
MAKHAN: Yes.
Guys, wait here.
Come on, Makhan.
Where are the officers?
-Speak!
-Where are they?
Today's Good Friday.
The club's closed.
What?
We checked all the rooms.
We didn't find anything.
It's supposed to have been right here.
We won't survive even two days!
Forget about taking over the town.
MAN: I'll recon around the town
the British might counterattack.
BOY: Have you ever seen
a machine gun?
SURYA: What's wrong?
-Forget about guns.
Where are the weapons?
Couldn't find the machine guns.
We searched everywhere.
-I'm sure they kept them somewhere else.
-So it's just a big failure.
-How will we face Chittagong?
-Uh-huh.
No need to fly off the handle...
...or get distraught.
Listen.
Right here...
...right now...
...what happened here...
...is truly staggering...
...truly momentous.
The British rule has been shaken
to its foundation.
They are agitated.
A trained army didn't achieve this feat.
It was the handiwork of a few teenagers.
Yes, by each one of you.
All of you are part
of this historic achievement.
What history will remember...
...is this glorious achievement
and nothing else.
ALL: Long live the Indian
Republican Army!
Long live revolution!
What you need is to strike terror...
...into the hearts
of every resident of Chittagong.
Go after anyone...
...who is even remotely
sympathetic to the rebels.
Begging your pardon, sir, but...
...we'd lose every bit of credibility.
In India, one rules firmly...
...or not at all.
Sir, everybody, even within
our own administration...
...is upset with
the Bengal Ordinance Act.
Don't you see, Wilkinson?
We need to stop
a spread of this disease...
...at any cost.
You are a fine and upright fellow.
I would hate to lose you...
...over this nasty mess.
PRITILATA:
For the first time in our history...
...the British police and army...
...have hung their heads in shame.
Who made this possible?
A bunch of youngsters
like you...
...led by Masterda.
Our Masterda. Masterda Surjo Sen.
JHUNKU:
For that one day...
...Chittagong was free from British rule.
Independent.
But the excitement
was short-lived, Aparna.
We didn't have the machine guns.
Our military commanders Anantda
and Ganeshda were missing.
We were forced to retreat.
Halt. We'll stay here.
Masterda sent Anant and Ganesh
to town for reconnaissance.
Did they get caught there?
Police lines were the rendezvous point.
So where are they?
We were reconnoitering Chittagong,
not having fun.
-I told you to hurry up.
-Who asked you to come with me?
Only I was to go.
Hold off your lecture now.
Save it for Calcutta.
JHUNKU:
The British returned to Chittagong.
Now accompanied by Ahsanullah.
The dreaded CID officer.
Now the town would pay.
Where is Surya Sen?
For everything.
Line up!
Listen carefully.
I need names, all of them!
Of all those involved
in the armory raid.
I said names!
Put them all in the van!
OFFICER:
Get off the cart.
Come here!
Hurry up!
Which village?
-Gahira.
-Dhalghat.
Gahira. On the way from Dhalghat.
-Dying from starvation.
-My mother's dead.
We haven't eaten for a week, sir.
-My wife's died.
-What's in the bundle?
-Only clothes.
-Show it to me.
-Some blankets.
-Some medicine.
-We are looking for work.
-It's nothing.
See, nothing here.
Rajat, Makhan!
Get them off the jeep.
-Get them off.
-Yes. Don't kill me.
-Tie them up.
-Yes, very tight.
Come on.
[ENGINE STARTS]
-What should we do now?
-Straight to Calcutta.
[BOTH LAUGH]
JHUNKU: We failed to make contact
with Anantda and Ganeshda.
SURYA:
It's all my fault.
JHUNKU: We were running
out of food and water.
SURYA: Please don't think like that.
NIRMAL: We don't blame you.
JHUNKU: Masterda looked perturbed and
indecisive for the first time.
We can't wait around for them.
And that made all of us
very apprehensive.
Hello.
Please give us some
biscuits and snacks.
-Sure.
-Some rice puffs too.
Add this to the bill, please.
We need food.
How much?
Do you think I don't know
who you are?
Every newspaper has
written about your mission.
If I make you pay...
...even hell wouldn't take me in.
Every day I pray
for your well-being.
Today I'll pray harder...
...because I have now seen you...
...with my own eyes.
May God help you
succeed in your battle.
-May Allah be with you.
How long can we wait around?
Let's just go and
attack the European Club.
Patience!
-Try to understand.
-Masterda!
The British have found out
about our location.
Don't worry.
It's our turn now.
No more agonizing wait.
This is where they were last seen.
They are cornered. They can't escape.
Our strategy is simple.
We overwhelm them.
If that fails...
...we have all those guns, don't we?
That is going to be
a guaranteed bloodbath.
This is a war.
You know, most of those rebels
are under 18 years of age.
NIRMAL:
Feeling scared?
Are you missing your homes?
Hmm?
Anybody who wants to leave,
now is the time.
I know what you all are thinking.
I know that.
You feel we don't
stand a chance tomorrow.
Let me tell you that we will win...
...and win hands down!
Because you have...
...what these foreign mercenaries
can never have.
You have self-belief.
And the courage
to stand up for your conviction.
Don't weaken your resolve...
...and we'll win this war.
-Are you brave enough?
BOY: Yes.
SURYA: Are you?
ALL: Yes.
SURYA: Sure?
-Then say it out loud.
ALL: Yes.
-Louder.
SURYA: I can't hear it!
ALL: Yes!
JHUNKU:
I didn't think I'd die.
I was certain I would.
But it was better to die, Aparna...
...than to live like a coward
in your eyes.
Aparna, I was truly surprised...
...when Masterda
put Lokenathda in charge.
He was only 23 years old.
My friends...
...the day of reckoning
that we've been waiting for has come.
We'll show the enemy...
...that 50 of us are more powerful
than 50,000 of them.
-Can you see that rock?
-Yes.
-That rock I say.
-Yes!
The enemy must not cross that rock.
We'll push them back from right there!
Men, get ready and take your positions.
Move!
My brother!
Are you scared?
Follow your orders.
Last night, I was scared.
I had almost decided to leave you.
I know.
But I also know...
...you won't leave me now.
Now go.
LOKENATH:
They are firing from both sides.
MAN:
They are firing from this side!
BOY:
Jhunku, fire!
[GUNFIRE]
Palmer, lead the charge! Now!
Smith, start the machine-gun fire!
-Outflank them!
-Yes, sir!
-Everybody down!
NIRMAL: Behind the rocks!
Behind the rocks!
Masterda!
-Bastards have hemmed us in.
-We'll get stuck here.
Nirmalda, give cover to Masterda.
It's machine-gun fire!
Everybody stay down!
-Hey.
-Sit down.
Hari, sit down!
Ambikada!
Ambika!
Stay down!
Stay behind the rock!
The bastard keeps firing!
Tegra. Tegra!
Tegra!
SURYA:
Nirmal.
Hold the rear attack.
Give me the gun.
-Stay low.
-Bikram.
Be careful!
Down.
Stay down.
Tegra?
Jhunku, where's Tegra?
[GUNFIRE]
Fire!
[ALL GRUNTING]
SOLDIER1:
Captain Palmer is hit, sir!
Major Smith is down, sir!
SOLDIER2:
Machine gunner down, sir!
Retreat!
[ALL CHEERING]
Ambika.
We are leaving.
Go. As fast as you can.
I'll stay.
Attention, Indian Republican Army!
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
After four days of disruption...
...train service between Calcutta...
...and Chittagong has resumed
from today.
Even though peace and order
has been restored in Chittagong...
...the rebels, led by Surya Sen--
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[CHATTERING]
We'll send you boys home.
Because nobody knows who you are.
Security reasons dictate.
-Listen to me.
ALL: No. No!
Just listen to me.
-Masterda.
NIRMAL: Long way to go.
BOY:
No, no.
We have to do so many things...
...but we have to stay with you.
We won't go back.
We need people in the cities too.
The battle is not over.
It will carry on!
And who says that
to be a revolutionary...
...you have to be
on the run all the time, huh?
Some revolutionaries
are headed this way.
Actually they are
bandits and dacoits...
...nothing but hardcore criminals.
Most importantly,
all of them are Hindus.
Don't worry at all.
It's a Muslim village.
-They won't be allowed here.
ALL: Right. Right.
I expected nothing
less from you, Rahim.
-Goodbye.
ALL: Goodbye.
-Any news?
-Why should I tell you?
It's for Masterda's ears only.
Hope nobody followed you.
-You still have no faith in me.
-Of course, we do.
That's why we chose
you for Calcutta.
We?
Yes.
You tell me.
Do you have faith in me?
Priti.
Our world is filled with danger.
We might get captured
at any moment.
-I don't want--
-But you...
...will always be with me,
won't you?
NIRMAL: It's time you learnt
how to use this.
I'll teach you.
[DOOR OPENS]
Jhunku.
My darling son.
[MRS. ROY SOBBING]
Jhunku.
Son, here's your
favorite fish curry...
...and sweets.
Eat this.
[CAR APPROACHING]
AHSANULLAH:
You two, go to the back.
Auntie, police!
NILESH:
Yes, Mr. Ahsanullah?
What's the problem?
-Search the house.
-Yes, sir.
Where's your son?
Do you have a warrant?
Warrants are no longer needed.
Surely you know that!
Mrs. Roy...
...where is your son?
He's nowhere to be found, sir.
So you want to play games?
Hey.
-Stay back!
-Mr. Ahsanullah!
-I'll blow his brains out!
-You're holding a gun.
Stay back!
Mrs. Roy...
...choose between your two sons.
I don't have time to waste!
You get till the count of three.
-One.
-Please let him go.
-Two.
-Please listen to me.
Sir.
Please.
My son hasn't eaten for two days.
Please sir.
At least grant him bail.
I'm sorry, Roy.
It's a far too serious an offense.
He can't survive in jail.
He is too delicate.
Not that delicate that
he couldn't take up arms...
...against the British Empire.
[SIGHS]
Look, Roy.
You get him to talk...
...and I'll see what I can do.
Good night.
[DOOR OPENS]
Jhunku.
Dad, please get me out of here.
Please, Dad.
I will get you out of here.
You just have to tell them everything.
Magistrate Wilkinson has promised.
What?
You went to him?
Why don't you try to understand?
Only he can save you now
and no one else.
I don't want his help!
But you have to
think about your life ahead.
I have.
Tell Mom not to worry about me.
Jhunku, don't be so stubborn.
I am not being stubborn.
It is far beyond both our control.
Any news of Jhunku?
No.
Jhunku, look at me.
What has happened to you?
Why have you given up on Oxford?
Do you realize what a mess
you are in?
We know who the leaders are.
What we need you to tell us...
...is where they are.
Where did you last see Surya Sen?
Jhunku.
I'm your best chance.
Give me something.
And I'll see to it that you are spared.
All right?
So let's try again.
What were your instructions
after you returned home?
Speak up, lad. Speak up.
I know what Ahsanullah
and Johnson are capable of.
I don't want to have
to hand you over to them.
AHSANULLAH:
He can tell us everything.
WILKINSON:
All right.
Remember he is only 14.
Jhunku.
No one wants to see you hurt.
But I need to know.
Where is Mr. Sen?
Jhunku.
Where is Surya Sen?
AHSANULLAH:
Where's Nirmal?
[YELLING AND GRUNTING]
Damn him.
Where is Ambika hiding?
Damn him!
WILKINSON:
Stop!
You didn't have him tortured,
did you?
Have you lost all sense of decency?
[DOOR CLOSES]
[GRUNTING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
WILKINSON:
Johnson!
I want results!
You have exactly one week...
...to find those bloody terrorists.
I don't care how you do it.
I want to
see them behind bars.
-Anantda, police!
ANANT: Nasser, run! Ganesh!
Rajat?
AHSANULLAH:
Where is Surya Sen hiding?
I said where is Surya Sen?
Bengali.
We are so proud of you.
[ALL YELLING AND GRUNTING]
Guards, come quick.
They are fighting!
GUARD1:
Let him go.
-Stop.
GUARD2: Let him go.
Stop.
MAN: No.
GUARD 1: Let go!
Let go.
Back off.
-Hey.
-Back off.
Move.
JHUNKU:
We were going to break out of jail...
...by digging a tunnel.
And launch the second uprising.
I was so proud that Masterda
chose me for the job.
We dug for 30 days.
The bombs were in place.
All we had to do
was to detonate them.
SURYA:
The boys must be saved.
I can't just stand by
as a spectator to their death.
Then don't hesitate.
This is only way to bring
the British to the table.
We have to have something
to force their hands.
NIRMAL: They are killing our boys
one by one...
...and we're just being
a mute spectator.
PRITILATA:
They deserve nothing but death.
Ahsanullah and Johnson have committed
many atrocities. They have no right to live.
[DOGS BARKING]
[GUNSHOT]
NIRMAL:
Police!
Masterda, leave with Priti!
I'll stop them.
No way!
-Nirmal, you come with us.
-Masterda, go!
JOHNSON:
Fire!
[GUNFIRE]
NIRMAL: Masterda, go!
-Not without you!
-Masterda, go.
-Nirmal, I am ordering you!
PRITILATA:
Nirmalda!
Nirmal.
Masterda.
This movement must go on!
Priti!
Priti, let's go. Priti.
Priti, now!
-Come on.
-No.
JHUNKU: Nirmalda's death
affected everybody.
For the first time...
...I saw Anantda,
Ganeshda and Lokenathda cry.
Was our mission worth this?
Nirmal would have wanted you to lead.
I'm so glad...
...that women are
a part of our movement.
I left...
...my new bride to fight the British.
She begged me to take her along.
But I wasn't sure.
Why don't you bring her in now?
-What's the hesitation now?
-Wish I could.
People seem to disappear
after their death.
There's no dearth
of brave boys in India.
The land is drenched in their blood.
But a new page will
be added to our history.
The world will find out...
...that the daughters of India...
...do not flinch from death either.
JOHNSON:
Ladies and gentlemen...
...there may be some here among us...
...who believe that our methods
have been less than effective.
The fact is...
...a great of deal of headway has
been made against Mr. Surya Sen.
Hey!
What's going on here?
This could not be further
from the truth.
Make no mistake.
Before--
[ALL SCREAMING]
[GUNFIRE]
[SCREAMS]
[PRITILATA GROANING]
We did it! Everybody leave!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
APARNA:
But Jhunku...
...sorry to pass on the bad news...
...Pritilata is no longer with us.
MAN: A chit of a girl
took over the European Club.
Johnson and Ahsanullah
have been killed.
And you haven't got a clue
where Surya Sen is hiding.
It's preposterous.
He can't elude us for much longer, sir.
Heh. You've been telling me that
for the last three years.
We have an offer from Surya Sen.
He will cease all attacks against us...
...provided we spare the lives
of all his boys.
I can't pull back now!
It would be positively humiliating!
I will let you know how to proceed.
JHUNKU:
None of us were executed.
Thirty boys were freed.
CROWD [CHANTING]:
British! Leave India!
JHUNKU: But 12 of us, including
Anant, Ganesh, and Lokenath...
...were deported to
the Andamans penal colony...
...the dreaded Black Waters.
All the way across the ocean...
...for life.
My brother!
Was our uprising
just a flash in the pan?
Did we make any difference at all?
Or was it all a big mistake?
APARNA: The peasants are getting
inspired by Masterda.
Jhunku, the peasants are
starting to resist the British.
Don't you give up. Yours, Aparna.
My time is up, Rahim.
I don't know how history
will judge me...
...for bringing these youngsters
into the freedom movement.
I still don't know...
...if I even managed
to give them a new vision.
JHUNKU:
Protests outside led to my release...
...after a long seven years.
"Black Waters."
The dreaded penal colony...
...a dark history
of my adolescent days.
I was returning to Chittagong...
...wondering if there's
anything left in me.
APARNA:
Jhunku?
JHUNKU:
Why didn't you get married?
My wish.
But where are we going?
BOY: Let's go to Johnson's house
for tea.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[CHUCKLES]
The battle's not over...
...it will carry on!
Masterda, run.
The police have surrounded us.
OFFICER:
Surya Sen, you're under arrest!
SURYA:
Organization.
If you let it fall, it would be all over.
You have to care for it.
Nurture it...
...like you do for your own crops.
Make no mistake...
...when the time is right...
...it will give wings to your dreams.
Apu?
Was Masterda's sacrifice in vain?
Was our uprising
an exercise in futility?
It will be, if you give up.
I feel so isolated.
Jhunku, I have to show you something.
Yet again,
the British and landlords...
...have taken away our grain.
There's the granary
where our grain is stored.
But the peasants
are in a defiant mood.
Twenty villages are ready.
The time is now
to fight to reclaim our grain.
JHUNKU: The excitement in your eyes
was unmistakable.
But Aparna,
I wasn't ready for it yet.
Stop. Right there.
Go back!
The peasants are cornered
in their villages.
Come on, Jhunku. Let's go.
The police have surrounded us.
It's only police.
Let's take them on.
Don't be absurd.
No more than five people
are allowed to gather in one place.
How can we even reach the granary?
Tunnels.
Yes, tunnels!
-Tunnels?
-Meaning...?
We'll dig tunnels from each village...
...and use them
to emerge next to the granary.
Nobody would be the wiser.
We can do it.
Masterda used to say...
...that confinements
are meant to be broken.
Our strength is in numbers.
If we work together
around the clock...
...with determination...
...we can finish it
before anybody has a clue.
The British would be hoodwinked.
Yes, it can be done.
Shall be done.
We are ready!
The police are after you.
Run!
OFFICER:
Stop!
Stop, or we will fire!
[APARNA SCREAMS]
Stay awake. Don't drift off.
-Keep your eyes open.
-Don't worry about me.
Go now.
Everybody needs you.
Go. Find them.
I will be back.
I never lost faith in you.
I'll come back for you.
Jhunku.
How are you?
We know what you're up to.
Today nothing will stop us
from reaching the granary.
I am giving you a last chance.
Turn, and return.
I'll pretend that you weren't here.
The crop belongs to the peasants only.
I want to help you.
Like you did when I was young?
Then you're under arrest.
Listen.
Carefully.
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
Because I think that
it is the most glorious...
...episode...
...in my life.