"Golmaal..."
"Hello...Hi...Namaste...salutations!"
"We're back to have a blast."
"We'll turn your boring
moments into something colorful."
"The celebrations wont stop."
"Our friendship is
the talk of the town..."
"...and even you can join the gang."
"Stop being shy from the
world...and scream and shout."
"Go...Go...Golmaal"
"Everything's gonna
be Go...Go...Golmaal."
"Go...Go...Golmaal"
"Everything's gonna
be Go...Go...Golmaal."
"Fool your sorrows and smile openly."
"Stop ringing the
bells of your worry..."
"...and let your heart beat loud."
"Whistle loudly ..."
"...and have a blast daily."
"Show your zest..."
"...and scream and shout loudly."
"Go...Go...Golmaal"
"Everything's gonna
be Go...Go...Golmaal."
"Go...Go...Golmaal"
"Everything's gonna
be Go...Go...Golmaal."
People are right.
I shouldn't be working here.
It's a weird place.
Anna madam.
I've kept all the books in its place.
Shall we leave?
- Hmm...
Keep the lock here, I will go later.
Madam, it's quite late...and dark too.
Don't worry, Peter.
I'll manage on my own.
Keep it.
- Okay, madam.
What is your problem?
You can see me?
Myself Ram Krishn Iyer.
Born 1956, Died 2016.
Can you see all kinds of spirits?
When I was a small,
I always prayed to God for a gift.
And this became my God's gift.
Maybe that's why...
... after I died,
I wandered to this place.
Can you please help me?
- Yes.
We belong to a strict Brahmin family.
But my daughter Prerna,
she loved a Muslim boy.
How can I accept that?
So I disowned her.
For years I did not talk to her.
But, for her every birthday
I wrote her a letter.
Because I realized
how much I missed her.
But, I could never muster the
courage to post those letters.
Before that, I died.
I want you to deliver
those letters to her.
Let my daughter know
that I accept her.
I love her.
'How is it possible?
How can I see them?'
'How can I talk to them?'
'Soo many questions.'
'Well, the bottom line is...'
'...when it's God's will , there
is no logic in things, only magic.'
'But, then there are some spirits...'
'...whose wishes remain unfulfilled.'
'Maybe that's why God chose me...'
'...so that I can act as a medium,
a path to fulfill their wishes.'
'And their spirits
can attain salvation.'
'I've helped many such
souls since my childhood.'
'But, there was a spirit...'
'...whose story was
connected with my life.'
'It is a story worth listening to.'
'The story begins
from Jamnadas Orphanage.'
'Jamnadas was a successful
businessman of his time.'
'He was so committed
towards social work...'
'...that one day he wrapped
up his entire business...
...and built an institution
for the orphaned children.'
'Jamnadas Orphanage!'
'The first child at
the orphanage was Gopal...'
'...had sold his brain off
and bought anger in wholesale.'
'And this is Madhav.'
'He enjoyed sticking his
'finger' into others business...'
'...just as much Gopal
enjoyed breaking them.'
Aaahh Sh**
'During night,
Gopal was very scared of the dark.'
Oh.. Relax, it's Laxman.
'And that's why Gopal clung
on to Laxman's finger.'
Laxman.
Me?
- Not you, him.
'There was another Laxman here.'
'And this is Lucky.'
'This Poor child couldn't speak.'
'Amongst the orphan kids...'
'...Jamnadas' favorite was Pappi.'
What's wrong, Pappi?
Pappi? Shameless!
'And then, one day.'
The baby has fever.
There the girl smiled and that
Bought a smile to everyones face.'
'And Since then the kids named
her 'Khushi' (Happiness)'
Khushi.
- Yes...Khushi.
'Usually, human beings look
for love and care in their own...'
'...within their family
and relationships.'
'But if you look here.'
'These kids don't share
any bond or relationship.'
'Except for love.'
'That is me...Anna Mathew.
This is my dad's library.'
Where the children from the orphanage
would often come over.'
"Since Childhood
I could see spirits ...'
'...and these five knew all about it.'
There you go again, Anna.
Who is it this time?
Stella Aunty.
She passed away three days back.
- What?
See! She's right next to you.
- Laxman!
Relax, Gopu.
'Ghosts, spirits, souls... Gopal
was scared of them all.'
'And Madhav would always
take full advantage of it.'
Gopal, you hit the ball.
You'll only have to go get it.
'Adjacent to the orphanage...'
'...was Jamnadas' close friend Col.
Chouhan's bungalow...
...which was locked for many years.'
'Madhav, Lucky,
Laxman and Gopal never got along.'
Gopal, I've told you this many times.
You're always picking
a fight with someone.
Go...stand outside
the orphanage's gate.
Madhav started it...
- Go!
Gopu, I'll also come with you.
'Jamnadas scolded the kids a lot.'
Laxman, we won't stay here anymore.
'Gopal and Laxman decided
to leave the orphanage.'
Madhav, Lucky,
and Laxman also left the orphanage.
'Jamnadas would often miss the kids.'
'But the person who missed
those five the most was Khushi.'
'And finally, the day arrived
when someone adopted Khushi.'
'But one thing always
bothered Khushi...'
...where would they be,
and what were they doing.'
Aye..Babli. ..we've seized this plot.
And you can't ...
- Quiet you stupid numbskull cartoon!
I'll get this plot vacated,
My poor man's prince Charming
I see...you'll vacate this place?
No, you moron.
This 'plot' P I L O T... PLOT
...will be vacated by my buddy Gopal.
I see...so he's Gopal.
What can this skinny boy do?
Just like nine comes before ten...
...similarly,
before the leader comes the follower.
Understand.
- Sons of pig...he's coming.
100 percent he's going
to hang you by the noose.
200 percent he'll
send you to your graves.
300 percent he'll
erase your existence.
What? Finding it hard to breathe?
Maybe, but why are
you gasping for air!
Insult! Insult!
Gopu...smash them,
bash them...finish them!
Gopu!
He doesn't sleep at night
because he's afraid of the dark...
...and dozes off during the day.
Gopu...get up, Gopu.
This sleeping beauty
bit is bad for business.
He's the one insulting me.
Gopu, if this continues...
...then no one will respect
us in the society.
I have an idea.
So... Swami sent you to
evict the plot from us, huh!
Get lost.
"Finger...Finger...Finger..."
Hospital.
OH! Come.
You really cleaned
Them up well, my boy.
Gopal...here's your payment
for clearing the plot.
Enjoy.
Send this to Jamanadas Orphanage.
Uncle Sam was right...
Charity begins at Home-work. buddy
Gopal, you have a big
heart and a lot of courage ...
I'll go to Ooty right away
and give this money to the orphanage.
And anyway, soon it will be dark.
Dark?
When darkness spreads over Kunnur...
...even the postman doesn't
step out of to deliver posts.
Understood.
Where's my He-man!?
I am running out of patience, Sweety.
Come urgent.
No, not to Argentina,
come urgently. fast
For my sake.
I went through a lot of trouble...
...to secretly build this costly
house which my family unaware of.
Come, Sweety...we'll have a ball.
Not football... Celebration!
you coming?
I'll take a cold shower, and get hot.
Lucky, He's in the bathroom,
you go upstairs.
Laxma-
Blood! Blood!
Blood!
Ghost! Ghost!
There's only one way, Mr. Naidu.
Sell your house for 20 million.
That house is worth 40 million,
Vasooli bhai.
It's a total loss.
Everyone in Ooty knows
that your house is haunted.
It's only my humbleness that
I am offering you 20 million.
And anyway, your real
motive is all about having fun.
There's another bungalow close-by...
...and it's price is
increasing by the minute.
30 million.
- How much?
31 million.
- One million in a minute?
Like I said...the price
goes up every minute.
Then seal the deal.
- Okay.
Done.
Sweety, address change.
Boys!
Long Live Vasooli Bhai!
- Enough!
Here's your money.
- Thank you.
Tell me something, Madhav...
...what makes people believe
that ghosts really exist?
Simple logic, Vasooli bhai.
Where there are humans,
there's fear.
Where there's fear,
there's blind-faith.
And, where there's blind-faith,
there are ghosts. - And.
Where there are ghosts,
there are spirits.
Where there's lentil, there's sauce.
If you stretch too far,
your pant is going to tear.
Shut up!
Here you go.
Donation...Jamnadas Orphanage.
Vasooli bhai, people never
forget their first love...
...how can we forget our first home?
- Yes.
That reminds me...
...what about Swami's
plot which someone had seized?
Oh man...your childhood friends,
Gopal and Laxman.
They cleared that
plot long back with Babli.
Childhood friends?
We'd rather have enemies,
than friends like them.
Madhav.
- Yeah...
Gopal always foils our plans.
- Yes...
What do we do about him?
When a guy like him
gets out of hand...
...then we must press his weak point.
Weak point?
Yeah...
Fear...
Darkness...
Ghost!
Save me from ghosts and spirits.
Protect me from evil powers.
Don't let bad spirits or
witches come anywhere near me.
Mummy...
Gopu, it's me Laxman. Relax.
You're soo unbelievable.
You beat up a dozen by day...
...but, sleep like a coward at night.
Just relax.
Come, let's sleep.
Laxman, ghost.
What! what happened? Gopu.
Gopu It's Sudari .... Sundari.
Our neighborhood dog Sundari. Gopu
I've told you this soo many times,
there's no such thing as a ghost.
Gopu, please.
Just like on Christmas,
everyone says...
...Santa's coming, Santa's coming.
But everyone knows,
he's not coming, period.
Similarly, there's no
such thing as a ghost, Gopu.
Come here... come here..
come On my lap. Come on my lap.
I know you're a naughty boy.
You won't sleep until I
sing you a lullaby.
"The apple of Jamnadas' eye..."
"...and Laxman's Gopala."
"There are no ghost's
relatives here..."
"...nor any spirits friends."
Gopu! Gopu!
All the lights went off!
Gopu Don't be scared,
Don't be scared!
I'll go have a look.
- Yeah.
Don't go anywhere.
- Yes.
Don't go anywhere, Gopu.
I see...so you guys were
Pulling the prank.
Yes! My DJ wale Babu's disc.
Insult!
Gopu! Gopu, come here.
Come out. Come here.
Come here, Gopu.
Smash them, Gopu. Smash them.
Come, Gopu.
- Yes.
Come Gopu, come.
Gopu, don't be afraid of the dark.
I am right here, Gopu.
Go, smash them.
Gopu, if you stick your
finger in our business again...
...you will only see
darkness in your life.
Stop threatening Gopu.
First Turn on the lights.
- You two come out first.
Turn on the lights first.
Turn it on.
- Show us.
Turn it on...
Gopu...Gopu...
- Qui..et!
Qui..et!
Stop it!
Stop prancing around
like little kids.
And you, you sly man what are you doing
here with my strongest of the strong men?
There's bad news for all of you.
- What? what happened?
Gopal, I went over to the
orphanage to donate your money.
found out there, that
Jamnadas is D U D E... is Dead.
His memorial service is tomorrow.
I think you all should
go to the orphanage.
We'll go.
- We'll also come with you.
Alright.
- Gopu, these guys.
Go and sleep, children.
Tomorrow is Friday the 13th
Mr. Jamnadas' memorial service.
all five left together
but none of them knew how..
..their life was going to
change from that point onwards.
Excuse me. Is this where Mr.
Jamnadas' memorial service happen?
There's still some time
for the rituals to begin.
I see...
Let's take a look
around the orphanage.
Yeah... it's been 25 years.
I wonder what all
has changed around here.
Nothing has changed.
Everything is still
the same till today.
Yes, Gopu.
But someone made paintings everywhere.
Superb, right?
Gopu... The Haunted Home.
Remember?
There's no way he can
forget this haunted house.
It used to scare the crap
out of him when he was a kid.
Back to your old tricks, aren't you?
Getting all emotional
when you needed a lift.
Gopu, please.
We were kids back then.
But Gopu isn't scared of anyone now.
- I see...
If nothing scares him,
then let him prove it by going inside.
Let's see if he can
really man up and go inside.
Gopu, show them. Show them, Gopu.
Show them how strong you are.
Show them, Gopu.
- Show...
See...see
Okay, Gopu. You are strongest, Gopu.
You are strongest.
Yes, Gopu. Show them.
Show them. Come on!
Stop wasting time.
We've come this far.
Have you met Mr. Jamnadas yet?
It doesn't look nice
- Oh s***
You're so right.
- Go.
I'll just come.
- Say hello from our side.
I hope he recognizes me. Ja..
Bloody liars.
What a wimp.
Got scared by a girl.
Who is it?
Whose voice is that?
- Chinese cat!
Who are you guys?
And, how did you get in?
What did you do?
- We haven't done anything.
Who are you guys?
We're here for Mr.
Jamnadas' memorial service.
Yes, we spent our childhood here.
We were the first
batch of the orphanage.
Yeah.
- Hold on!
Lucky, right?
- Yeah...
And, Madhav.
Gopal.
And, Laxmans.
- Woah...
...how do you know?
- You know us?
Of course.
Baba, I know them.
What? Didn't you guys recognize me?
- Who you?
Not who? Anna...Anna Mathew, librarian.
- Anna!
Oh! Anna Mathew, guys.
- who Anna?
Our very own 'Google' for the ghosts.
Library...
Oh yes...
How's your library?
Even if it's empty, she will
say it's infested with ghosts.
she thought we were ghosts.
Who did?
- she did.
She did?
She did ...
She got scared of us...and
we five got scared of her.
One minute!
...who are you talking about?
Baba, they are talking about Damini.
Damini.
You don't have to be scared of her.
She's the house caretaker.
Oh, she's the maid.
- Maid...maid.
Forget her.
Anna, you've grown so tall.
Yes, double of you.
Tall, dark, and handsome.
Yeah.
- Alright .. Come on, guys.
The rituals are about to begin.
Yeah, we'll talk later.
Good morning, ma'am.
- Good Morning.
Anna.
- Yeah...
Do you still see ghosts?
- Yes, Gopal.
Gopu.
- Hello, Baba.
Baba, its Dande.
Dande, how are you?
- I am fine.
It's a good thing you're here too.
Come on, let's go.
- Go ahead, I'll join you.
Look Dande sir, regular
customers of our Police Station.
We're really sad to see you.
- What?
I mean...when we heard
about Mr.Jamnadas.
It is very sad.
I know you guys...
Try to act too smart...and I'll
throw you behind bars.
Madhav, Gopal, Laxman...
did you recognize me?
No!
- Didn't recognize me?
- Pappi!
Not this Pappi (kiss), Pappi bhai.
- Pappi bhai.
Pappi bhai...
Did you get over your absent-mindedness?
- It was cured long ago.
But, Mr. Jamnadas...
There's nothing we can do.
Jamnadas was a close friend.
We'll always miss him.
Today, on his memorial service...
...I would like to call Mr.
Jamnadas' well-wisher,...
...Mr. Vasu Reddy from NV builders.
My mother always used to say...
...everyone's goes to
heaven after they die.
She was absolutely wrong.
Mr. Jamnadas built
a paradise while living on earth.
This orphanage.
You know, we builders build houses.
But he made a home.
And, for a better future
for the children of this orphanage...
...before Jamnadas died,...
...he transferred over the
orphanage to our company...
...and gave us a big responsibility.
Which was that we relocate this
orphanage to a big city like Bengaluru...
...and bring a change in
the progress of these children.
More incentives, more opportunities.
Jamnadas ji, He treated every child
in the orphanage like his very own.
But his most favorite was...
Pappi.
Pappi bhai, few words.
Please.
- Come on.
Go on... What will I say?
- Go now!
Jamnadas ji.. to me.. was...
He used to feed me
milk with his own hands.
He's the one who
raised me since birth.
And, he was so naive that...
...he passed away while
taking a stroll on the terrace.
This is not done.
Anyway...
This is how I would like to pay
my respects at his memorial service...
Today is Mr.
Jamnadas' birthday.
Call the DJ.
Cook a feast...look...
Look at Mr. Jamnadas...
He's on live-chat with us.
Look at him smile.
You guys are here too.
Dande... Rascal! You're only one.
But you keep saying
you're a sub-inspector.
Gandhari, my burnt toast.
Madhav, you're
spreading like a fungus.
Lucky...
Happy Birthday to You!! Sing sing
Laxman! My Little Bheem.
Even the money plant outside
the orphanage is growing up...
...but, you're still
where you started.
Laxman no. 2...my slipping tongue.
Gopal...when you were a kid,
you looked like Murugan.
But now you look like Devgn.
So that was our Jamnadas ji.
Reddy sir, it's a nice thought
to shift the kids from here.
In fact,
I have been thinking the same for you.
How will you live here
alone...without your daughter?
Take my advice, and go to Dubai.
Stay with Nikhil.
My company will look after
your house and business.
No, Mr. Reddy.
My daughter's memories
dwell in this house.
And Damini's here too.
Anna lives with us as well.
In fact, Anna and I have decided...
...that we'll rent out two rooms.
Even I'll feel better with the
hustle and bustle around the house.
See you.
Bloody old man!
I'm trying to empty the house out...
...and he's filling
it with more people.
Gopal, Mr. Jamnadas wanted only the
best for the children of our orphanage.
And, all thanks to
Nikhil and Vasu Reddy...
...who have taken upon
this big responsibility.
What more can one ask for from god?
Just that God gives you
the strength to remember all this.
Quiet!
Jamnadas left these for you.
Some old memories.
For me?
- Yes.
You were the 'Boney Kapoor'
of this orphanage.
We started this venture with you.
He was the first child.
- I know, but what is this?
Yeshwant,
Mustafa, Ankush, what is all this?
Jamnadas was a big fan
of Nana Patekar.
How can you forget?
You're so forgetful.
He isn't with us anymore,...
...but his spirit is watching over us.
I feel like he's...right
in front of me.
Jamnadas... he's listening to me.
Gopu, let's go.
It will be dark soon.
Come on.
- Let's go.
Hey...what's wrong? Let's go.
That chair...
What?
- It was swinging on its own.
On its own? Really?
Must be the wind, stupid! Come on.
On its own...
Listen...Laxman.
Gopu.
What's happened?
They came as five, but while
leaving they weren't five but...
Laxman, I've put
in a CD of 'Krantiveer'.
Let's watch it together.
Come on, Laxman.
Come quickly, Laxman.
Nana's going to start talking.
Gopal.
Jamnadas was murdered.
- Jamnadas?
Come, sit.
- Gopal, listen to me.
No, I will listen to Nana first.
Gopal.
- Na-na.(no-no)
- Na-na.( no-no)
Gopal.
GOPAL!
So now you will only listen to Nana?
Nice...nice... A single mosquito
Can turn a man into a eunuch...
...similarly it makes
a dead man into a spirit.
A single mosquito.
Laxman, all that mimicry
of Nana has cleared your tongue.
What Laxman? Laxman! You are on with!
This is not a mimicry.
Born with a defect in your
thinking you slum dwelling parasite!
I am not Laxman.
Laxman, look...stop scaring me.
Or else I will hit you.
Nice...nice...
What is fear, I'll show you.
look...this is called real fear. Look!
People with big houses
have small hearts!
Jamnadas was murdered,
He was killed
Nice...Nice...
Just because a woman is
fat doesn't mean she is pregnant
"The apple of Jamnadas' eye..."
"...Listen to what's
going to happen next."
"You're going to now..."
"...avenge Jamnadas' murder."
Nice...
Anna...
Let me handle this.
You two wait here,
I'll go take a look inside.
Gopal, it's okay.
Why are you scared me?
Last night you were
sprinting on the walls.
I admit that my tongue sticks out...
...but that doesn't
mean I am a lizard.
How can I sprint on walls?
I am not a ghost,
I am your friend.
I am real, look.
Touch me. Touch me.
See...I am real.
It's okay.
There is a spirit.
There is a spirit?
So Gopu was telling the truth.
And, in order to drive
this spirit out of here...
...I must coordinate with some people
who perform prayers, counseling...
...in short,
this process is going to take time.
How much? How much time?
At least 40 days.
- 40!
In that much time Gopu
will die 40,000 times.
Not acceptable.
Then, there's only one
way to handle this situation.
What?
- Speak.
Till the time the spirit
matter is not solved...
...you must stay far away from here.
Yes... But where?
Remember the Colonel's bungalow?
That haunted house.
He's renting it out.
And, for the past few days
even I have been staying there.
If you want I can speak to him.
Gopu, she's also staying there.
Yes! yes please speak to him!
Till this spirit crisis isn't solved
we will stay with you only Anna.
We'll stay with her, Gopu.
- Okay.
You scared me.
What's wrong?
Vasu Reddy's man had come.
He said two men are living
at Colonel's place as paying guests.
We've to get them out of there.
I suggest that Laxman, Lucky and me...
...will go over there
as paying guests.
We'll scare them out of there.
Call Vasu Reddy and tell him.
Nice idea.
And, you're already
in your scary character.
"Call him and tell him."
Hello.
- Reddy sir, it's Vasooli.
Those two men at Colonel's place...
- Hold on...just hold on.
Did you send those two men? rascal
No no... I want to send my three men.
- What?
First two, now three more.
Will you make the Colonel's place
into an orphanage as well?
No, no Reddy sir.
My three men will
go there posing as PGs...
...and scare those
two out of the house.
I see...I see...
Very good idea. I'll make you rich.
Thank you, thank you, sir.
Vasooli, just do this job for me.
Consider it done.
What?
- What?
What? Wha?
You three go to
Colonel's house as PGs.
And scare the other two
PGs living there out of the house.
You mean we've to scare
those two PGs out of there.
And, we've to go over
at the Colonel's house.
Ooty.
Consider it done. Consider it done.
What's wrong with him? Has he lost it?
Why are you moving on your own?
Took all the luggage?
Lucky...Madhav...
Woah!
It's the same car.
So Gopal and Laxman are inside.
So the two paying guests are
none other than Gopal and Laxman.
'Baba said he had no problems...'
'...in letting them
stay in his house as PGs.
But Baba didn't know the truth.'
'That they actually had
a problem with each other.'
I am leaving, but Anna will stay here.
You can think that this is her house.
And Damini's here...to
look after all of you.
But, where are you going?
It's been 15 days since
my daughter passed away.
I'm taking her ashes to Rameshwaram.
Laxman...from wherever we are passing,
someone is passing away.
Gopu, relax.
Baba, the car's here.
I should leave now.
But your car's here.
Come on.
Gopu...
I'll see him out.
Baba, drive safe.
- Baba...
I guess Baba can't see.
So, Gopu...what are you doing here?
Don't you have your own house?
Eh First!
it's not a house, it's a bungalow.
Yeah, and we're converting
it into a flat. That's why we're here.
Who converts a bungalow into a flat?
He means...when you see our bungalow
after we've upgraded our interiors...
...you'll fall flat on your face.
Understood.
What are you guys doing here?
Even we have a status.
Status?
Even we are getting our interiors done.
- Yeah.
Italian marble, Persian carpet.
And, at the entrance...
Water fountain.
You can't even buy a fountain pen.
Getting a water fountain?
Relax, guys. Relax.
Come on, pick up your stuff.
Maid... is it free?
The wifi?
Yes, it's absolutely
free... Like you, jobless.
Maid...do we get water in the house.
It will if you turn on the tap.
- Superb answer!
Okay, I'll tell you
who's going to stay where.
You two, up there.
Not that one,
the room next-door is mine.
Which one?
- The room next-door.
And you three, down here okay.
- Woah!
Woah! Woah! Woah!
Excuse me...why will
we stay down here?
And why not upstairs?
- Are you in a hurry to go up?
Gopu, help him.
- Hold on...
We're paying rent too.
- Go to hell.
Get lost...
Guys! Everyone has to adjust
somewhere, okay?
Hey, Ms. Adjust...
Don't poke your nose when the
elders are talking. Understand.
Don't touch me.
- Hey, don't touch.
Why are you coming
In between us for the girl?
Yes, why are you in between?
- Yeah...
You're a maid. Maid!
- Yeah.
Your job is to do odd
chores.
To Salute, clean the place.
Lift our luggage.
You're a maid. Maid!
Why are you pushing me?!
Should I give you one?
I'll punch you.
- Punch.
Punch. Am getting angry
Punch you... On your face.
stomach...everywhere.
Should I? Should I ?
Woah...
Went deaf, didn't you?
Spare me!
- Huh!
I mean I am sparing you today.
- Why? What's today?
It's my sister's wedding.
- Huh?
Which sister? What wedding?
It's my namesake sister's
legit wedding.
Yeah... And stop clinging to me.
Avenge your friend.
Go on boy go...
Yes...
He got scared. He got scared.
Yes...yes...yes...
Kill you.
What's going on here?
Look, if you guys want to stay here...
...then, we have to all
live together peacefully.
Understood! This is not done.
Gopal, Anna is absolutely right.
Don't be angry. Just relax.
Okay, Gopal.
- Gopu, let's go.
Relax.
Relax. It's me, Gopu.
Come, let's go.
Come on, I'm right here.
The family that eats together,
stays together.
Let go.
- Exactly...let go.
Gopu, my fingers have surrounded
the fritter from all sides.
And, my fingers...
...have surrounded your
fingers from all sides.
Don't be scared, Madhav.
Let go, Gopu.
Otherwise...I'll turn off the lights.
Don't be scared, Gopu.
If you turn off the light,
I have a candle.
Oh sh**
Even if we've to go
over your dead bodies...
...this fritter will be ours.
- What is this?
You guys are fighting over a fritter.
This is not just about one fritter.
It's about the sauce too!
Let go, Gopu.
- Let go. Let go!
Oh sh**
Gopu.
Gopu Ching.
I love Desi Chinese...
- Laxman... Behave yourself.
...with my fritter.
You're dead.
Gopu, smash...smash them.
- Gopal.
Gopu.
Gopal.
[gibberish]
Oh sh**
He has no feelings!
Gopal.
- Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it! What is all this?
Have you guys lost your mind?
Who fights in the house like this?
And you Gopal...I am warning you.
You're not going to do this again.
Understand.
This is a house,
not some wrestling match ring.
I am talking to you, understand.
- Lower your finger.
Gopu, spare me, Gopu spare me.
Look, I raised you, cared for you.
I fought for your fritter.
I'm your baby brother, bro.
For the sake of your brother.
Hey, Laxman, Your words are like
yesterday's rotten pasta to this maniac.
And Gopal, I know you're
like the father figure of us all...
...but he, he is like your
mother... Your mother.
Does one break their mother's finger?
Breaks a finger?
Let go his finger, you madman. Oh shit
Gopu... Gopu, no.
Gopu...
- Gopu...
Gopal. Gopal.
Gopal! Get down.
Just get down. Just get down.
Get down.
They all deserve it.
Jackpot!
Stop it!
What are you doing, Gopu?
"I looked at you..."
"...and flung my heart at you."
"You're like an angel from heaven..."
"...so say my eyes."
"I looked at you..."
"...and flung my heart at you."
"You're an angel from heaven..."
"...so say my eyes."
"Your face makes the moon conscious."
"Your beauty's intoxication
is touching my heart."
"Who stole your slumber,
sweetheart..."
"You did."
"Who stole your peace, sweetheart..."
"You're...a madman."
"Why are you after me?"
"All lines from this route are busy."
"Lock eyes with me..."
"...let the news spread."
"I can't control myself any longer..."
"...because you're so amazing."
"There are no sorrows
in your life right now."
"But he will make your
days and night empty."
"Who stole my slumber, sweetheart..."
"You did."
"Who stole your peace, sweetheart..."
It's okay, Lucky.
It's okay,
don't worry I'll fix it now.
Okay.
What? From ten your
fingers became eight?
He's saying its straight not eight.
But hello, how did you do it?
Magic.
Laxman.
- Gopu.
Laxman! Laxman! Laxman! Laxman
- What happened, Gopu?
Baba's dead daughter!
Where?
Gopu.
- What?
Did we turn off the gas back home?
Sorry, sorry, sorry...I forgot. sorry
Let's go back to sleep. Good Boy
Don't be scared. Come here come here
Gopu. gopu
Okay.
Okay, Gopu.
"The apple of Jamnadas' eye..."
"...and Laxman's Gopala."
"Our very own ghostbuster..."
"...Anna is downstairs."
Hey, maid...listen.
Don't you get paid?
- Why?
You wear the same dress every day.
- Yeah.
This is my uniform.
Colonel sir gave it to me.
The Colonel.
But the Colonel is blind.
You can change, he won't know.
Just shut up.
Lucky, there's definitely
something between her and Anna.
Not like that.
But these two are definitely
Some planning.
O Sun Lord, protect me from ghosts,
spirits, black magic...
...and also Nana Patekar that sprint
on walls, and open hair witches.
Got Scared?
- No.
Oh! my my, what is
this madman doing with the house maid.
What are you doing
here in the morning?
Morning meditation.
It's so spacious out here.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
Come come...
Tell me something, Gopu.
The five of you grew up together.
You and Laxman are soo close also.
So, what is your problem
with the other three?
They are not all that bad.
Yes, Damini. You're right.
They are not that bad.
But They are very bad,
rascals and scoundrel type of people
Why you...fool
Gopal, I have to say...
Whoever you marry, that one will be Lucky.
- Marry Lucky?
Not that Lucky,
I meant extremely fortunate.
You got safe.
- Why?
Because every girl wants a tall,
dark, and handsome boy.
And, you have all these qualities.
you're innocent too.
Oh no, I completely forgot.
Anna's has been looking for me.
I will see you later, okay.
Bye.
Gopu's falling
head-over-heels for her.
Come come come ...
Gopu!
Gopu! Gopu!
Gopu, This situation
reminds me of a poem.
Please...do tell.
"When early in the morning..."
"...someone says make me yours."
"It clearly indicates
the time has come..."
"...open a pack of hair-dye,
mix and apply."
Wow!
You like her?
No-no.. It's nothing like that.
We're just hello - hi.
- What kind?
hi...or hiiiii.
We were watching everything.
Quiet.
Laxman, I think Damini
is in love with Gopu.
Lovely...
- No, no, it's not...
It's exactly like that.
She's been going crazy looking
for you since morning.
Where is Gopu? I don't see him. where?
- Can't see.
She's been driving us crazy Gopu.
She's pining for you.
What?
I want Gopal. I want Gopal.
You guys are too much!
We got this madman
bowled over romance.
Tonight he'll be visited
by the ghost of love.
Tangabali Kita verede
"But love never obeyed
any age restrictions."
"One of the partner's
has to be younger."
"Prince..."
"Please don't hesitate
in telling me that you love me."
Lamhe...exactly your story.
Meaning.
Childhood...old age...
I am only joking.
That girl Damini...she's called you.
Me?
- Yes...in the basement.
In The basement?
- Oh, what happened Gopu...
Won't you go alone in the basement?
Says who?
He's coming.
We'll scare him so bad today...
...that he'll will leave
the house and Ooty also.
Damini...
That was nice... Very nice...
But it's going to
be bad for you... Very bad.
No...
Gopal!
Greedy boys... Our own
dogs are biting our flesh!
And distributing us like bones!
Gopu, let us go.
Reddy sir,
I don't know what's wrong with Gopal.
We tried to scare him...
...but he scared us more in return.
- Please do something.
My mother always said...
Your mother was always spoke wrong.
Forget her... Just tell us what to do.
Burn that house down.
What?
- Burn it down?
I'm only concerned about the plot.
Burn it down.
- How can we just burn it down?
Payment doubled.
You think we'll commit this sin for money?
- Yeah...
There are people in that house.
You know, my mother used to say.
- Let your mother be...
Consider the house burnt.
What's with you?
Why are you quiet?
You've lost your mind, Madhav.
You're risking everyone's life.
Yeah...
- Burn that house down.
There's Gopal, Laxman,
Anna... and that maid in that house.
What if something happens to them?
Everyone will be safe.
There's a birthday party tomorrow.
- Whose birthday?
Everyone.
- Everyone?
Don't you remember, Lucky?
Mr. Jamnadas would choose one day...
...to celebrate everyone's birthday,
remember?
I remember.
- Correct.
And, there's a similar
birthday party tomorrow.
Understand.
So, when Gopal and Laxman
will be busy decorating...
...we'll sneak out and burn
that old man's house down.
And there won't be anyone.
- Woah.
Okay!
kids, am going to sing you a song,
listen closely to the tune,...
Where are you going?
Come back.. listen to me.
Look where you're sprinkling that
thing. Do it properly...go there.. go.
Madhav...fire!
Oh shit!
Lucky crazy, have you gone mad?
Setting your brother's bum on fire.
What have you done?
Lucky, have you lost your mind? Lucky
Has some ghost possessed your brain?
- Not just my brain, you greedy boys.
Its controlling my entire body.
He spoke.
- Lucky spoke.
Lucky spoke.
- Yes, he spoke.
He spoke well. Spoke well!
I'm sitting right here.
Let's see who burns this house down?
Run! Run! Ghost. Ghost.
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
- His's bum on fire.
Gopu...Lucky's been possessed.
He's talking.
Madhav, I admit I am not very smart.
But this is too much.
He's talking... He's
turned into Nana Patekar.
Lucky's talking.
- he is Speaking.
I'll take a look.
- Don't go, Gopu. I am warning you.
Gopu, he's been possessed.
- Relax, he's Gopu.
He's not scared of anyone.
He's strongest.
He's been possessed.
- Shut up.
They say you spoke.
That you've been possessed.
Say something...
Hey...what are you saying?
Madhav, he's stopped
talking even in sign language.
Superb, Gopu. superb
You guys are uselessly trying to scare me...
- now you will hear my voice now?
Oh, s***
What? your eyes have popped out?
Soon your tongue will also stick out.
And what are you saying speak speak!
Do I look like All India radio that will
keep playing for you the whole day?
Papa Natekar's is here!
Anna! Anna!
No, no I cannot stay here.
- Hold on, Gopal. Wait. One minute
No, please.
- Wait, Gopal, listen to me.
Listen to what, Anna?
That spirit has followed
me all the way here.
First, he possessed
Laxman and scared me.
And now I wonder what
it was going to do to me...
...after possessing Lucky's body?
Sooner or later this
spirit's going to kill me.
And, you guys will
also die because of me.
Look at poor Lucky's condition.
I don't think after today he
will ever get up again.
Laxman, water.
He's awake, I meant water to drink.
You...
Madhav, Gopal, what's happened?
You were possessed by a ghost.
Gopu, why are you talking like him?
Why am I talking like him?
You were possessed by a ghost.
Madhav, Laxman...I am
responsible for your plight.
I admit that we never got along...
...but, at least we share a bond.
I cannot risk your lives.
I cannot stay here, Anna. Let's go, Lucky.
- Wait, Gopal.
If anyone should leave,
then it should be us three.
We were going to burn this house down.
Remember Vasu Reddy, the builder...
...he was at the memorial service too.
He has his eyes on this plot.
He paid us to burn this house down.
And, you guys agreed.
Anna, I didn't know that
things would get out of hand.
Sorry, Gopal. You won't leave alone.
We will all go with you.
Yes, and if that spirit returns...
...we...we... will run together.
- Superb idea.
Yes, Gopal.
We're together.
- All together
Anna, don't worry about Reddy.
We'll handle him.
And Anna, thanks for
everything you've done.
See you soon.
- Hold on.
If you guys really want to leave...
...then,
why don't you all leave tomorrow.
Right?
- Yes.
Along with you guys,
It's the children's birthday.
They will be sad if
We aren't there with them.
Just for one day, stay.
Gopu.
- Yeah.
When a beautiful girl says 'stay',
then it clearly indicates...
What? - Just like we tell our dogs,
'Moti, stay'...
... she's telling you 'Gopu, stay'.
Gopu.
Let to.
- Gopu...
"We're stubborn."
"We aren't going to Agree."
"We will continue doing mischiefs."
"Tell the world..."
"Don't take away...our freedom."
"I want to say what's in my heart."
"We're going to stay the way we are."
"One life...not too much, but..."
"...we're going to
be a little naughtier."
"We will never change."
"We'll get naughtier."
"We won't lose...these
moments of mischief."
"We'll never let sorrows...
get in the way of our happiness."
"We'll let life smile."
"We won't lose...these
moments of mischief."
"We'll never let sorrows...
get in the way of our happiness."
"We'll let life smile."
"We'll drench ourselves...
in this deluge of dreams."
"We're gonna do...
what we've never done."
"We will never change."
"We'll get naughtier."
And then, that day also came ,
when I was about to tell..
..them something that was going
to change their lives forever.
Gopu, before we leave...
...you must do this.
- What?
Say "I love you" to her.
- Yeah.
Are you mad?
- What are you scared of?
Age difference.
Gopu! Every girl looks for a
father-figure in her companion.
She's got the figure,
you're the father.
Madhav...
- Don't be scared.
Go, confess Gopu.
Propose to her. Gopu...don't hesitate.
Go...go...you have to go.
- Go Gopu go...good boy.
What I was saying, child...
- Huh!
My coffee's still left.
Oh, that reminds me..."Cheeni"
Have you seen 'Cheeni Kum'?
What?
The love story between
the hero and heroine was amazing.
Yeah...
- Madhav.
Laxman, Lucky, where is everyone?
Madhav, Lucky, Laxman...
It's such a big house,
what are you guys doing outside?
The person lost in the
morning returned home now only
Pappi, what are you doing here?
I'm here to show you guys something.
Take a look at yesterday's photographs.
- Show me...
Superb.
- Nice.
look at this one.
- That shirt's looking nice.
You're there, you're there...I
am there, so are you and you...
...but, where's the kid?
- Where's the kid? Oh yes.
She's not there.
- Yeah.
Even his camera is
absent-minded like him.
Forgot to take her pictures.
Whose picture?
Damini.
- Damini?
Yeah.
- Damini, who? Whose Damini
Gopal's girlfriend, Damini.
- Damini is my girlfriend.
Woah...
- Madhav. Madhav.
He's forgotten again.
I haven't forgotten anything.
My wedding's been fixed with Damini!
The wedding is next month.
He's definitely forgotten.
I haven't forgotten anything.
She! She! She's my Damini.
- Pappi bhai...
Pappi bhai, what are you doing?
- Who hung my darlings photograph like this?
Pappi bhai, she isn't Damini.
That's the Colonel's daughter
who died in an accident.
She is not that Colonel's daughter,
She is Damini, she is the caretaker.
And she's alive.
Look.
You took this snap when she was alive.
Yes! .. You forgot
- I see...
Then let's talk to her on video-call.
Sweetheart Pappi... Do you
want a kiss on video-chat again?
Don't waste time...
Now get lost.
If she's Damini, and she's alive.
Then who's that Damini with Gopu?
- Where is she?
Outside.
- I'll take a look. Come on.
Who is it?
Where is she? He's sitting all alone.
Look.
There's Damini sitting with him.
You guys have lost
your mind like Gopal.
We just spoke to Damini on video-chat.
He forgot again. Come here.
I haven't forgotten anything.
- Oh Shit.
Gopal's is sitting there alone.
I haven't forgotten anything.
Damini, the care-taker of this house
is my girlfriend.
She isn't in this house,
or the courtyard...or the garden.
I haven't forgotten anything.
Madhav, if that is
Damini the maid's picture.
And she's Damini the maid.
Then, who is the Colonel's
daughter that's dead?
Colonel's daughter?
- Yes.
She is the Colonel's daughter.
That's...that's...
- She is dead!
I attended her cremation 17 days ago.
- What?
If you don't believe me,
then search on Google.
I'll check on my phone.
Excuse me!
Show me...
Pappi, for the sake of your mother...
...you really don't see her?
There's no one out there.
Gopal's all alone.
But we can still see her...
That means she's a ghost.
And my Gopu, who's afraid of ghosts...
...is going to say I love you
to a ghost. - S***
Someone stop him.
Gopu...Gopu...Gopal.
What happened?
- Gopu...
What?
- Come here.
Come here.
Just a minute.
What is it?
First, you guys send me
out there and then call me back.
How are you Pappi?
What is it?
- Listen...
Gopu...that Damini, she's not a girl.
Is she a boy?
- She's not a boy.
Is she both?
- She's neither. Gopu
Then what is she?
I'll tell you. She's a spirit.
- A ghost.
She's a ghost!
- Yes.
Madhav, just because
I am scared of ghosts...
And, you too Laxman.
Seriously, it's very important. Show him
- See...the Colonel's daughter.
Ghost.
Accident... Kunnur Ghat.
Trying to scare me
with this fake Google.
Here, only she is standing Damini.
Stop over acting you guys.
And you...you're trying to scare me...
Did you miss, Gopu?
Try again...be sure, Gopu.
- Please, don't do this.
They are speaking the truth, Gopal.
I am the Colonel's daughter.
And, I died 17 days ago.
Please!
Mummy!
Gopu...
Gopu, relax... It's a ghost!
- Gopu.
Ghost.
Listen to me, Gopu.
- Ghost.
Listen to me, guys.
Please let us go
What wrong have we done to you?
Guys listen to me please
Don't be scared, Madhav.
Enough... enough Madhav.
Wait... I know how
to deal with this banshee.
What? What?
- Let me show you.
WOAH!
- Is this Star Plus?
Be Quiet.
Every Diwali is not a bonus.
Every pimple is not a puss.
And every cross is not Star Plus.
It's a Cross from the Hollywood horror films.
- Cross.
And these ghostly people can't cross it.
- Really?
But where is this ghost person?
Is it on the Left or the right? Where?
She's right here in front.
Now don't disturb.
Concentrate.
Hoo-ka-baa
Hoo-ka-baa!
She's scared.
- It's working.
Very good.
- The power of the cross.
Go on...
- Hoo-ka-baa
I will destroy you, demoness.
Run away you vampire.
Witch... Once there was an enchantress
Conjuring Part 1, part 2.
Get lost from here.
Woah!
Are you okay? Laxman
Laxman...
- Why aren't you guys saying anything?
Why are you silent?
Hello-hello-hello...3,
2, 1, testing...
Rampur's Laxman.
Pappi...even you lost
your voice like Lucky.
We have not gone mute,
you've gone deaf.
Hoo-ka-baa! Hoo-ka-baa
I know she's gone, but why
are'nt you guys saying anything.
That's what we are trying to do
He's deaf, he's dumb, I am blind.
I can't see the banshee.
What do we do, Pappi?
I'll try talking to the banshee.
Leave this on me.
Smash it on you?
Tie him up. This deaf man
Let me talk to the banshee.
She's also someone's sister,
someone's daughter.
My dear banshee...
My dear banshee...show
some ghost-anity.
Ghost-anity?
Just like humans have humanity.
Ghosts have ghost-anity.
Trying to fix this
Look, daughter, I just...
- Right-right...
left...left. Yeah...
- right...right...
left...left... - Right, right...
daughter...
- Right-left...right...left...
"Train...train..." Railway train
Railway train goes round and round
Do I look like a Jiant bell...
Or a table-fan, or a viper? Who am I?
From there to here and here to there.
Gopu...what are you doing
in the middle of the road, Gopu?
Waiting for Rohit Shetty
to arrive with his cars?
There's a ghost inside.
- What?
A female ghost.
- Daam those three..
What?
I said those three are
up to their old tricks again.
Madhav, Lucky, Laxman...
...it's their job to create
fake ghosts like Ram Gopal Verma.
There's a real ghost inside.
- Gopu,...
I know you don't stay up at night...
...but those three made
you look like an owl. F O O L. owl
the girl who died 17 days ago. It's her ghost
- Gopal, son...
...I'll go inside and
clear your misconception.
My buddies (Vikrams
kids- Vikram ke Bhatto)
Please leave
Look, Babli's here.
Babli bhai...
Babli sir...you shouldn't
have come here.
Quiet!
My ugly duckling (my
Jimmy Sherrgill of mice)
Do you also believe there's a ghost here?
- Of course...
There is...there
is...she's right there.
Is this Planning, Madhav?
Planning for what?
Madhav, if there's
a ghost here then tell her...
...that Babli's here
in a guest appearance.
She must take good care of the guest.
Where are you my
banshee's Bipasha Basu?
I think even he can't
see the banshee like me.
listen carefully, if you're the
caretaker than I am the Undertaker.
Babli sir, please leave now!
- Nonsense, why tomorrow?
I'll have tea today.
So far, so good.
Call that banshee. Hello, ABCD.
A for Aatma (spirit),
B for Bhootni (banshee)...
...C for Chudail (witch),
D for Daayan (enchantress).
Come on baby banshee, show your moves.
Oh shit!
Mummy! mummy! Am I going up or
is the ceiling coming down? Save me!
Vasooli bhai.
- Gopal, what are you doing like this outside?
Vasooli bhai, there's a ghost inside.
- What?
I think my boys have done their job.
This is a very bad news, Gopal.
Now I must go inside
and save everyone.
But that can be...
- I know it's a life taking situation, but...
What happened?
- Gopal, someone's pulling me inside.
Now that's called scaring.
Gopal, save me.
That's Vasooli's punch. Gopal,...
- Vasooli bhai.
....please tell everyone
how Vasooli died.
Someone is infamous...
Madhav.
- Vasooli bhai, ghost.
Ghost? (camel)
- Ghost?(camel)
Okay.. Alright.
I know there's a ghost here.
Vasooli bhai, he's telling the truth.
There is a ghost.
look, she is standing there.
Where?
There.
- Vasooli please, understand.
Madhav, you're so engrossed
in trying to scare them...
...that you started believing
there's a ghost here.
You guys don't even know
how to scare someone.
Now Learn from me.
I just scared Gopal outside.
I said someone is pulling
my arm... pulling my arm...
Madhav.
Babli... This place is haunted.
My flying Jatt...I know.
This place is haunted.
B O O T Y... (bhoot) Ghost.
Anna.
What happened?
Damini is a ghost.
Come with me.
- No no, I won't.
Whoever goes inside doesn't come back.
Don't worry Gopal, I am here.
- But Anna
You trust me, don't you? Come on.
No, Anna.
- Come on.
Anna.
No, Anna.
- Come, Gopal.
Come on.
Gopal, I am right here. Let's go.
Ghost...she's a ghost.
Gopal, come with me.
Run away...
She's a ghost too.
- She's a ghost.
Shut up.
I'll beat you all you into ghosts.
-What?
Come out all of you... Come on.
'They were all in shock...
They had thousands of questions.'
They all were sacred...
'I explained everyone
that she was just a pure soul...'
They were all stunned when
I told them who the spirit was.
'I told the spirits real name.'
Khushi.
Didn't you all recognize her?
She's your Kushi...
...who you had picked
up from the streets.
Saved her life.
You must be wondering
how can she be with us...
...even though she's dead.
This is not possible.
How can we believe this?
When it's God's will, there
is no logic in things, only magic.
Meaning Khushi?
- Our Khushi.
Same Khushi.
- She's our Khushi.
She's our Khushi.
Khushi.
Madhav, we used to rock her in our arms.
- Yeah...yeah
Ohh... Gopu...
Gopu, your to-be wife turned
out to be your has been daughter.
"The apple of Jamnadas' eye..."
- Quiet!
Is he sleeping?
- Hold on. Leave all this
After all these years,
Our Khushi... And like this?
How? I don't understand any of it.
Will someone tell me whether
she's on the left or right?
...where is she?
She's like Anil Kapoor from Mr.
India for us.
Yes.
But how could our Khushi die?
What stupidity is this!
Anna, please explain.
We don't understand anything.
Yes.
After you guys left.
The Colonel and his wife adopted me.
Father and Jamnadas
were close friends.
Father also had a tea-estate in Ooty.
He wanted me to take over
the tea-estate business in future.
Since childhood I was interested
in art and craft.
Whether it was at
home or in the orphanage...
...I would start painting
wherever I got a chance.
I knew Anna since then.
She was like an elder sister,
a mentor to me.
I grew up...things were going normal.
But then,
one day mother passed away...
...and father lost his vision.
I took on the responsibility
of my father and the tea-estate.
Like they say,
time is the greatest healer.
Slowly things got better.
Life was back to normal.
Khushi.
Khushi. Did you recognize him?
- Oh my, God. Nikhil.
After 7 whole years.
When did you arrive?
And why didn't you inform?
I met your father in the morning.
But you weren't there.
Yes, I was out for
some tea estate work
So finally, Dubai kicked you out.
No, no, he's got a huge
construction business in Dubai.
And now, he'll start a construction
business in Ooty along with Vasu Reddy.
And Khushi, he has big plans...
...for the children of our orphanage.
I've no one in this world.
I never got along with my brother.
He's all that I got now.
My nephew, Nikhil.
And, this is why I've decided...
...I'll give him the orphanage.
'It didn't seem like Nikhil
and I were meeting after many years.'
'I could feel a special
connection between us.'
'We started spending
a lot of time together.'
"coming and going..."
"laughing and singing..."
"...I imagined this
in my mind many times."
"The first glimpse..."
"The slow effect..."
"Why does it make the heart restless?"
"Stopping and walking."
"Walking and stopping."
"no idea who you're waiting for."
"Could I be...the one you believe."
"why do I feel like
that all the time?"
You guys played a big game with me.
Don't get so hyper.
Let us explain.
- What will you explain?
Explain me what?
You two only want to
build your dream project.
I went over to your
architect's office...
...and saw the blueprints and model!
You've nothing to do with
the future of my children.
No, uncle.
- You usurped my land by wrong means.
I will change my will
and give it to Pappi instead.
Uncle, please don't
let my efforts go to waste.
What effort?
- I worked really hard, uncle...
I lied...scammed...convinced
you to give me your land...
...spent so much time
with those orphans.
Even convinced Khushi
to marry me for that bungalow.
Asked Baba for Dubai..
I worked really hard
for my Adventure Land Project.
If you change the will, old man...
...I'll change your expiry date.
It's not your fault.
your blood is only filthy.
Your father cheated me for money.
And you cheated me for the land.
You're a scoundrel
son of a scoundrel father!
No...
Mr. Jamnadas. Mr. Jamnadas.
He's dead. You killed him.
Khushi.
Hello?
You should've called.
Oh, you got the wedding cards.
You did the right thing...you
shouldn't have called.
This had to be a surprise.
Khushi weds Nikhil.
- I'll tell the Police everything.
Don't be so unreasonable, Khushi.
I won't let those orphanage
kids loose their home.
Just try and understand.
- I will tell the Police...
This is unbelievable...this
is too much.
What did I ask for?
A poor guy is trying
to fulfill his only dream.
But, no...
Everyone wants to
meddle in his business.
Think practically, Khushi.
This old man had already
lived beyond his age.
You've your entire
life in front of you.
There's just a murderer
in front of me.
Nikhil, what are you doing?
Vasu, take his body to the orphanage.
Throw it off the roof and
prove that it was an accident.
And you, my gorgeous.
Let's go for a drive.
What? She left three hours back.
Okay, alright Nikhil.
I'll call you once she arrives.
Okay.
What did he say?
Nikhil said she left long back.
Anna sister...
Mr. Jamnadas fell off the roof.
What?
What's going on, Anna?
There's no trace of Khushi either.
What time did she leave
home in the evening?
At around 6 pm.
I am worried, Dande.
- Don't worry, Mr. Chouhan.
We'll do whatever we can.
The next day Nikhil left for Dubai, I thought
of stopping him but what would I say to him?
I even thought of telling
the Police everything.
But how would I make them believe me?
I was thinking about all that...
...when I met you guys at Mr.
Jamnadas' memorial service.
God answered my questions.
Only you five can see Khushi.
Why?
It's a sign.
Sign from God.
He wants all five
of you to help Khushi.
And for that,
I had to get all of you here.
You guys got here...
...but we were waiting
for you to unite...
...so that we can tell you everything.
And then you can
get justice for Khushi.
And save the kids of the orphanage...
...where you guys
spent your childhood.
Madam.
Oh brother!
What was all that drama inside?
Yes... They turned out to
be like Thakur from 'Sholay'.
They were planning
to make a gang all along.
At least Thakur was
still alive in that.
Do we have to be like
Jai and Veeru for the dead?
Till now we heard
'Wanted dead or alive'.
Now, we've to catch
a living for the dead.
What nonsense?
But I understood everything, Lucky.
- What?
We should not meddle in this
whole "Justice for Khushi issues"
Yes...
- But why?
Because she's born unlucky.
Look...when she was born,
her parents passed away.
When she came to the orphanage,
we all parted ways.
The colonel and his
wife adopted her...
...but the mother died
and the father lost his eyes.
Eye for an Aai (mother)!
One poor guy fell in love...
... he had to commit two
murders and run away to Dubai.
Look, bro, helping her is like...
Stepping on an axe...
Black money with tax...
...and in the interval,
comes...climax.
He is right.
What nonsense.
I think...
None of your antics, Pappi.
There is enough confusion already!
Say something, Gopu.
You haven't said a thing.
Poor guy what will he say.
His to-be wife turned
Into his daughter.
then, from daughter into a banshee.
And now, for that banshee,
we fight against humans?
Look Gopu, it was fine as long
as it was about evicting the house.
Now we shouldn't get into
all this ghost- justice - mess.
And that Nikhil... you heard na he's
a bloody murderer.
Yes, Gopu.
You know what,
I think we should run away.
There can't be better...
- Shut up, Madhav.
What's wrong with all of you?
Didn't you hear what Anna said?
Those guys killed Khushi.
Same Khushi...who we
all loved so dearly.
And Mr. Jamnadas,
if it wasn't for him...
...we would be lying
on some road side.
How can we watch these
children lose the orphanage...
...the same place where we grew up.
No.
Khushi gave her life for those kids.
For those kids.
And, I'll do anything I
can to get justice for Khushi.
Whether you guys help me...or not.
Gopu... listen...
- Gopu. Gopu
Listen, I need to get some of Khushi's
stuff removed from the closet.
Can you please give me a hand?
Be careful. What did you drop?
It's a diary, Baba.
Something's written in Arabic.
You're holding it upside down.
- Sorry.
Must be Khushi's.
She would write in it daily.
Sometimes she would
read it out for me.
You're Gopal, aren't you?
The guy who's been forcefully
staying in that bungalow.
Take your brother and leave.
Or else, along with you two
will throw the old blind man out.
You don't know Nikhil
and Vasu Reddy yet.
For land, they can take lives!
Who are you? The local hero?
Robin Hood? Messiah?
I am a crack.
"In the orphanage, I
never felt like I am an orphan."
"Gopal would break fingers,
but he always held on to mine."
"the first Laxman
would cry along with me."
"And the second Laxman would
make me laugh Whenever I cried."
"Whenever Lucky would
get any money..."
"...he would first get clothes,
toys, and gifts for me."
"And, a day never went by
when Madhav didn't tie my hair."
"Whenever I asked
him why he did it..."
"...he would say today
is 'Baal-Diwas' (Hair Day)."
"After mother passed away..."
"...I thought I will never
be able to handle myself again."
"But sister Anna
supported me a lot..."
"...and gave me so much love,
that frankly I don't miss my mother at all."
"Today, I met Nikhil. I felt
an instant connection between us."
"He's really nice."
"Father agreed... My wedding's
been fixed with Nikhil."
"All my dreams will finally come true.
Even I will have a family of my own."
"Those five gave me the correct name.
Khushi (happiness)!"
"They knew that I was destined
for only happiness, all along."
Gopu...
- Stop it, Gopal.
Beating them up is not the solution.
This orphanage belongs to Nikhil now.
So we must get him here.
Only then can we take
this place back from him.
Gopu, Anna is right.
Let them go.
Dande sir ...get used to it.
We already have.
Dande sir, we found out that
Nikhil's coming here from Dubai.
I suggest that you should
arrest that Nikhil and Vasu Reddy.
How can I arrest them?
We have no evidence to prove
that they committed these murders.
But, if Vasu Reddy
confesses to these crimes...
...then we can register a case
on the basis of his statement...
...and issue an arrest warrant
against Nikhil. That can be done.
Arresting Nikhil is too far-fetched.
We must first think of a
way to make Vasu confess.
What to do, what not to do.
Do what do we do...Scooby Doo.
I was saying...
Katappa uncle...
As long as you're with me,
there is no one alive who can kill me.
Mother Sivagami!
Bhallal deva!
When someone raises
his hand on a woman...
...his only punishment can be death!
- Pappi.
Where's my tea?
There it is.
- Stop it guys!
I have an idea.
Just like Khushi possessed
our bodies and scared us...
...similarly we can take Khushi's
help to scare Vasu Reddy, isn't it?
But how?
Madhav, you always said...
Where there are humans, there's fear.
Where there's fear,
there's blind faith.
You guys scared soo many
people without any ghosts.
And now you guys have
a live and legit ghost.
Live ghost?
- Yes, ghost.
G S T...Ghost.
That's a fantastic idea, but...
...how will we make him believe
that there really is a ghost?
We all five are already in his radar.
Quiet...stop abusing.
There are ladies in the room.
He's not abusing.
- Then?
He's saying only
one man can do this job.
Pandu!
- Pandu!
Hey...
What's all this 'Pandu-Pandu' about?
I came here thinking
I'll get some rest.
But blah-blah-blah...
- Nana Patekar.
In the flesh!
You can see Nana, but not the library.
Hey librarian...do you
also sell fish on the side?
Why are your eyes popping out?
Did you see a ghost?
Close your mouth... Or your
tongue will stick out too?
Hello...yeah, get the shot ready.
What?
Where am I speaking from?
Where does your father speak from?
Come on...step on it, step on it.
Everybody just chill. Call Pandu.
So there's a ghost
around here somewhere.
You five can see it,
but these three can't.
Snap out of it! Snap out of it!
I look like one...even
sound like one...
...but, I am not that stupid.
I don't believe in all this justice,
benshee, spirits, and salvation.
I just don't believe it!
Fine...Khushi, demonstrate.
Khushi.
What a joke.
Somebody is holding me.
Show him your moves, Khushi kiddo.
M T V Moves.
What's the plan to scare Vasu Reddy?
Come on.
Ae Mongoose!
You're a sinner... An evil soul.
- Who who are you?
"Double Double Toil and Trouble..."
"...fire burn and cauldron bubble."
"Your time will come soon."
"You're sleeping
soundly like a sleeping beauty ..."
"...but, soon you'll
be lying in your funeral fire."
Bahadur!
"You'll suffer like
a beheaded chicken..."
"...and be buried 6
feet under the ground."
"You'll be punished for
your deeds and your scams."
"That Adventure project
will never be yours again."
Adventure?
You killed a girl and an old man.
Their spirits will
come and take revenge.
Janardhan,
Bahadur, there's someone in the water.
There's someone in the water.
find him.
What happened?
That's baba's in the water, find him.
But, there's no one here, sir.
- He is...
look that way...look look
Believe me, Nikhil.
I don't know who or
where that Baba came from.
But everything he said was true.
Relax, Vasu.
It could be a coincidence.
The land, two murders...adventure
project, everything.
He even mentioned you.
He said your partner
will have to pay too.
I've told you Vasu, never
discuss these things over the phone.
Anyway, what about Gopal?
There's a farewell function
at the orphanage for the kids.
I'll deal with Gopal there.
But my trouble is this Baba...
- Just shut up, Vasu.
Just Shut up.
Don't mention about this to anyone.
I am arriving on the 30th.
And, I want the orphanage
empty before that.
That's it.
Brother Gopal,
I want to stay here only.
I don't want go to Bangalore.
Don't worry,
what you want that will only happen.
Go play.
Gopal, Vasu Reddy.
Reddy sir, that's Gopal.
Gopal, I'll handle this.
Stay cool, please. Come lets go
Yes, calm down.
- Just relax, okay.
Cool...cool...
- Don't get angry.
Madhav will handle him.
- Chill...
Relax.
- I am cool.
Stop...wait...stop.
Peace...non-violence...peace... P I S S
Reddy sir, he was your enemy...
...but now he's your friend.
What do you mean by a friend?
- Means he's ready to join our gang.
And, for 10 million rupees...
...he won't just get you the house,
but also get rid of the kids.
And the Colonel...out of the way.
Don't think too much, Vasu sir.
Let's join hands with him.
Gopal, come on.
Come, Gopu.
- He's normal now.
Gopu, let's go. Let's go.
He's just shaking your hand.
Shake hand. Shake hand.
Come, Vasu sir.
The kids are waiting for you.
Farewell.
First and foremost,...
...a huge round of abuses for Mr.
Vasu Reddy.
Ae...
- I mean applause...applause.
So, without wasting any time...
....I would like to invite Mr.
Vasu Reddy to take the mike.
Mr. Vasu.
My mother used to say...
Children are the image of God.
She was absolutely wrong.
In fact, Gods are an
incarnation of you kids.
That's why it's always said...
Children are always pure souls.
And today...
What happened, sir?
- There's current in it.
Let me check.
See...
- See what? I was just joking.
There's no current,
just my talent. talent
Come on.
Children, we should never
deviate from our goals.
Otherwise, we wont belong here...
...neither there.
You'll come across many
speed-breakers in your path.
But we should never stop.
We should overcome those...
What happened, sir?
- That mic punched me.
It's just a mic,
not Mike Tyson to punch you .
I don't want the mic,
get it out of here.
Take it out...fine, I'll get it out.
In order to relocate the orphanage...
...I met with the Education
Minister and told him,...
...that our new orphanage
will have only one slogan.
Only one motto, which is...
Vasu Reddy is a dog!
Repeat after me...
Vasu Reddy...
- Is a dog!
And this dog won't let
the children go anywhere.
No relocation.
Music. Dance...Party.
Play the music!
Play the music! Play the music!
Your daughter's been
possessed by an evil spirit!
...evil spirit!
- No!
Your daughter's been
possessed by an evil spirit!
No!
Now, do you believe us?
Donkey, dog, monkey...
You danced like every animal.
What was wrong with you, silly?
I am calling you silly.
If you didn't want the
bungalow and the orphanage...
...then why waste our time?
Mother swear I want the
bungalow and orphanage.
But I never danced
like this in my life.
I don't know what happened...
Hold on. Hold on.
Was he there too?
- Who is he?
He's the guy who came
to my house that day.
He cursed me.
What?
- He's saying you should've drunk it.
It wasn't alcohol...
I meant cursed me.
He was saying that I
will die because of this land.
My death is near.
Revenge... spirit...
- Hold on.
What happened?
If that's true,
then something's fishy Daya.
Where's Daya?
- In our heart, for you.
If you weren't the one dancing...
...and, that baba was warning
you about the land and revenge...
...then, there's only one logic behind it.
- What?
You have been possessed by a spirit.
What are you saying?
He's been possessed by ghost, witch, spirit,
demons, evil spirit, devil enchantress...
That's enough, stop it.
But it's true, these things happen.
Ghosts are common in land matters.
Remember Babli's
neighbor...Lopa Mudra!
What happened to Lopa Mudra?
She moved heaven and earth...
...but, she didn't give her
piece of land to the landlord.
So the landlord buried
her under the same piece of land...
...which she fought for.
till today Lopa Mudra's
spirit comes out of that land...
...in different
positions and screams...
"Zameen (Land)!"
- That's enough, stop it.
Laxman, that was a bigger problem.
Lopa Mudra was murdered...
...and, she came back for revenge.
- Right.
Vasu sir, did you kill someone
or got someone killed for the land?
I... no-no-no, not at all.
Then there is no problem.
Let's go.
No...No...No...
- What no?
Nothing...we just wanted
to check the time.
Nine minutes past nine.
Raghav! Raghav.
Raghav, fire.
Put it out. Fire extinguisher.
Fire. Put it out. Put it out.
'We had all planned for tomorrow.'
'But we were also afraid
that our plan might backfire.'
What are you guys doing here?
- Listen up, come here.
We've come up with some
options to kill the Colonel. - Yes.
The first option;
we'll hang him upside down...
...and loosen him loin-cloth.
Then, we'll make a noose
out of it and hang him.
Nonsense. Nonsense. - No...
The second option;
he was a colonel, so we'll tell him...
...to teach us how to fire a gun.
When he picks up the gun,
we'll turn it around.
Bang...
no, no, no...
- Okay, the third option.
We'll take him out to light a candle...
but instead take him to a petrol station.
"Light a match...and up he goes in flames."
- Nonsense. stupid, stupid, stupid.
Fourth option;
Electricity on.
Don't translate that, its absurd.
Next option, please.
- The fifth option;
...we'll call the
Colonel to your office...
...and strangle him to death.
After that,
we'll put his body in a car...
...and throw it down the valley.
No, no, that's not possible.
- That's the best idea.
It's already been done.
- Done?
I mean...you guys are out of options,
now let me think.
"Don't knock on the door, beloved."
Just come in straight. beloved
Vasu sir,
there's a chick in your bedroom...
...looking for some good time.
- I don't have a sweetheart.
"Don't knock on the door, beloved."
Just come in straight beloved
Vasu sir,
can't say whether you're possessed...
...but the animal inside
you is definitely coming out.
Quite.
"Come come..."
Hey...
"Double Double Toil and Trouble..."
"...fire burn and cauldron bubble."
"You may be sleeping soundly
like a sleeping beauty you pig..."
"...but, soon you'll be lying
on your funeral fire for sure."
He's that baba.
Just like there's a baby-shower
before the child's born...
...similarly,
this is your shower before you die.
Where are you going sir?
Even I want to kill you!
Today You're going to die, Vasu Reddy.
We've caught him, Vasu sir.
No need to be scared.
Everything he said
turned out to be true.
That spirit is everywhere.
She will kill me.
Save me. - listen If you want
to get rid of that spirit...
...then, we must go to sister Anna.
- Yes.
Why Anna?
Because Anna doesn't
just see and talk to ghosts...
...in fact, she also executes
them with her powers.
Let's go, let's go.
- Save me. Save me.
Come on, Gopu. let's go.
Eeem-Breem...Hocus-Pocus...
spirits-ghouls...Plasma...
Plasma 32 Inch.
What have you guys written?
Anna Aunty, I wrote this.
The spelling of ghosts and spirits.
P L A S M A...
Ghost and spirit.
Shut up, Babli.
I am already very nervous.
They will be here
any minute with Vasu.
And what do you guys think?
Making a circle of
lemons and chilies...
...and putting a voodoo doll in the
middle and all the hamming...
...will make Vasu believe all this?
Of course, he will.
There's only one thing everyone
believes in... Blind Faith.
And, we'll just scare him out
of his wits and record his confession.
He'll be here any minute.
Come, Gandhari.
let's hide behind the books.
Why you... this way.
Spirits...ghouls...and ghosts.
Deeds misdeeds punishment indifference
Eem Breem Cold Cream.
Spirituality attainment
pleasant morning
Naughty naughty naughty talks
Shut up, Lucky.
This is serious work.
Sister Anna, please continue.
Do something, save me, please.
- Hold on...
That spirit is somewhere here only.
I can feel it.
Hello...
I am air hostess Shabbo...
...welcoming you to
Hyderabad Airlines,...
...and let's quickly go
over the safety instructions.
When the air pressure reduces...
...the oxygen masks will fall
down from the compartment above.
Don't start screaming 'Snake-Snake'
when you see the oxygen masks.
Don't scream and yell like idiots.
Don't behave like illiterates, I say.
Two doors in the front,
and two at the back.
And, if the roof blows off...
...Then its gods court.
Hey, mister, fasten your seat-belt.
Have you come to a wedding?
Hey, madam,
what all are you sitting here with?
Put all these lemons and chillies in the
luggage compartment... Who let her in?
Pappi...
- Sit! Sit
Understand the seriousness
of the situation!
Quiet everyone...quiet.
Tell me...
Tell me what do you want.
What?
I see...
Vasu, (yes) this spirit
will leave you alone only...
...if you confess to each and every
crimes so that we can record everything.
What...
She means confess to your crimes...
...so that Anna can get rid of
the ghost in record-breaking time.
Yes...
Fine.
In order to get Mr. Jamnadas'
orphanage and the Colonel's bungalow...
...Nikhil and I first Jamnadas ...
Get out and close the door.
The library's closed today.
Anyone just barges in here.
- Nikhil.
Nikhil?
What's going on, Vasu?
- These people are helping me...
...in getting rid of the ghost.
Remember, I told you over the phone.
It's not an illusion.
It's a real spirit.
And it's here only somewhere
Anna just spoke with the spirit.
And that Baba is a very powerful guy.
Everything he said came true,
ask him yourself.
If that's the case,
then please tell me...
...if the spirit is here,
then where is it?
And, why is it here?
That spirit is here to
destroy all sinners and evil souls.
Double Double Toil and Trouble.
Fire burn and cauldron bubble.
Vasu, he's not any
baba...he's an imposter.
There is no spirit here.
Since the time you have called me,...
...my men have been keeping
an eye on all of them.
This is their game-plan, Vasu.
They are trying to trap
you in one of their plans.
I'll deal with you guys later.
Let's go, Vasu.
Where are you going?
It's a good thing you came down here.
Now he wont tell us the truth,
you will tell.
You killed her.
You tortured her to death.
Nikhil!
Inspector Dande.
So the police is
also involved with you
The police isn't taking
any sides, Nikhil.
We know the truth. That's all
You killed Khushi and Mr. Jamnadas.
I see...
And you all have gathered
here to collect evidence.
So, tell me what
evidence did you find?
Come on, tell me what's the proof?
You guys can't touch me.
That orphanage belongs to me...legally.
I'll throw those kids out like that.
Soon I'll have this
piece of land as well.
Who can stop me?
You, Mr. Dande?
Or you guys?
Who will stop me?
You? You Gopal? Or your friends?
Nobody can ...
Khushi is digging your grave.
Educating girls imply progress.
Khushi! Khushi!
- Khushi, please stop it.
Don't let go. Don't let go.
- Stop encouraging her.
I mean don't let him go. He'll
die if he falls from this height.
Khushi.
Khushi, please stop. Don't do this.
We want justice through punishment,
and not by killing him.
Khushi.
Khushi, wherever you are.
Please forgive him.
Tell them, Nikhil.
Confess that you killed
Khushi and Jamnadas.
Killing him won't
get us the orphanage back.
Think about the orphanage
and the children.
You know, we found you at that gate
There?
'It's said that when a person dies...'
'...and his soul attains salvation,...
...it's the beginning
of a new journey for him...'
'...which we call the Afterlife.'
'There are no sorrows
or pain in this Afterlife.'
'Nothing right or wrong.'
Just a soothing light all around us...'
'...and, we all converge in it finally.'
'We don't know whether
it's true or not.'
'But yes... When God's
will is involved...'
'...there is no logic, only magic.'