Chicago 1990
That's it
Today there is going to be a storm.
It's a challege
The whole world will be sunk
Where is he
What is this?
Magic!
Papa, it's $25 i have...
I know, the bank loan is alot!
This will help us to save our circus
This $25 you keep it
The bank loan is alot!
Till you have this $25
No, bank can shut us down!
Papa, why is the bank not
agree with your...
Papa did speak to them
Cause you are a specialjoker
If, you Iike our act
Do not shut our circus
Papa might if they do'not Iike
my actig... how dare you
They must agree with me
Everythig will be fine
Cause you are my magic
Do you know who is he
Yes!
Me, sahir
Please show your magic to them
Bank owner's will be happy
We are god's grace
We must not loose hope
Sahir,don't apolagise to our enemy
Do not g ive up hope
We must respect our honour
This circus is my only hope
You are tearig it apart from me
Bank owner's
Papa
We are god's g race!
What?.
He is not answerig his mobile
It's a pressure cooker
They asked me to hold
You finally decide to kill me
Yes?.
Short cut i am a hero
Have you not see how handsome
i am
Why kill a policeman
Your gun must be saying
How handsome i a m
Let hi m go
Listen to your gun
Why come to my area and arrest me
How dare you think Iike that
Must i tell you the truth
Please!
Every year on the 15th august
independence day
Every person must have
equal rig ht's in our coutry
Do you thik we are equal
My aunty... hema malini
Equal
No... boss
No chance
Why spoil the reputation
for our coutry
Like good people Iike me
And bad goons Ii ke you
Who is gona win the match
The day you are behind jail
Have you think so much
Before coming to me
Actually its jai brother's idea
But jai fights and then q uestion
When he punches you feel pain
No,sir
I only need one back up
When he comes it's Iike a storm
Ali
Hey kill them!
Ali, come
Stop!
Can not apply brakes
Mummy help
Come, i'll chop you both!
Ali...yes brother
Run
Papa, i know the bank loan is alot
to return
As long as you have this $25
No bank can shut us down
Our circus is the greatest
on this planet
Circus is my only dream
But, you are tearig it apart from me
I, am back home papa.
Ali, you at a new city
Do not try and woo any gi rl
Stop your glazig at girls
No, brother
Ali became a internatioal police
Ali' s eye is only on the thief.
And, ali's ea rs... motor bi ke
4 cylider... bmw
Confirm
She can't speak hind i
Whatever english i knew
I spoke it
How will we go
Three, is not allowed to ride a bi ke
He is go with victory
Three days she will be mine
Only ali
Will it be done
Yes sir
We practice for so long
Did not ever think we will be on platform
No idea how you done this
But it's a masive
I did not work alone
I borrow from the bank
Where is my actress
All the girls audition is taken
What are you looking for dude
A gil must come Iike fire
Must be brave and courage
Must be have some madness
We need brain to find her
Who is she
She is crazy man
I won't return today
One chnace
please
This is not a reality show
Oe minute
Put me down
Who are you?.
The one you are in search
Please, give me a chance
only one audition
You have just 5 minutes
Five minute if my eyes is out
of you... then you out
And do not return ever again
Promise, i swear  my unborn children
My five minute is up
Can you remove your eyes
I'm trying that from a long time
Liar
I swear on my unborn children.
Aliyah
Welcome to the great indian circus
aliyah
You are fired!
Chicago police thinks the thief
is asian
Mr. dixit what have you got to say
about the thief
In, few days two robbery
I, don't think he is a true thief
No, thief leaves so much of evidence
He Iikes to run
My advice to hi m
Escape from this city
Do you think he will loot again
If he has the courage
People are afraid
I don't think we must fear
this thief
He is a clown
When i get him
He will entertain in jail
Do you think you can get him
Destiny is always in police hands
This clown is in my hand
I Iike to meet
Mr. dixit
I am very pleased to meet you!
Sahir khan
Wanting to tell you something
I am the thief
No one knows about it...
only you
I did not understad
The great indian circus
Is the name of my show!
The thief you are in search for
I have a trick for him
Which i'll be showing at my show
2005 circus fantastic
That is me
And behind is the thief
We are only clowns at a circus
And he is a magician
He had no enemy
And he won't speak to anyon
After the show he  dissapeared
in his room
He is known as charlie
I, want to take my magic elsewhere
Robert... sir did not Iike the idea
I heard him speak for the first time
What ever he said
I still remember the words
What
A saying must not hurt your enemy
How do you know charlie
is behind the robbery
Read in the newspaper
That he leaves his joker evidece!
How many circus clowns are there
Why the bank
If i show you suspects will
you identify them
He is alway's in clown uniform
Untill today no one seen
his face!
I can hel p you
We both are circus clowns
Difference is i am on stage
And he is on the rope
Charlie is a genious
I can think Iike him
Why do you want to hel p me
I want him to be caught
He is not a thief
This is the last hope
to get him
No robbery or thief will exist
Sahir what ever you doing
it's a help
At 9a m we will meet
joker a clow
That is my name
Let me help you
To become a clown it's serious
Everything that i do
Must be with honour and pride!
My work is not ajoke
It's a battle
Victory must be Iike the audieice is winnig
But i am always the winner!
He come's from oe place and return
from another... how is it possible
If i was charlie the loot
will be happen today
Why
What is it today
1st a pril
clown's day
Today is my 1st show
my mobile will be switched off
Brother he dissapear Iike a wind
How fast he escape
I'm a fan of hi m
Come
Where to
Where he can't run
The great indian circus
You quite brave to act strong
What is this jai
Quite cha rlie!
Mysterious clown
Whom no one knows his identity
Your story was very good
My job is to com plete the mission
But i have to concentrate on the story
I must trust those who is infront
of me!
You had a very good idea
Enter the bank and know all
the security codes
Only three men knew about the codes
Two police officers and the other thief
Me... remove your clothes
What
A 9mm of bullet
Leaves a clue behind
Jai you are doing mista ke
Brother, there is no evidence
It' s clean
Officer body scan
Jai how, is it possible for a bullet
to be clean on my body
I'm a circus clown
Trick is always within me!
I had shot you with my own hand
I only wanted to be friend with you
Thief and a police are enemy
Brother,we need to go
I feel pity for myself
That the bullet was not shot on your head
Next time i won't let that mistake happen
How did you do this?
Sorry we are not friend's
If we were
I should have told you
Is the pain too much
You won't find aything
Take this and go
Let it go
Do not try and act smart
We are god's grace
We must have faith
Papa has two
One is intellegent
And the other is weak
I was the secret for papa
That day papa had one more secret
No one knew about
You said i am the secret
No, one must come to know about me
Papa i was inside the box
I had no fear
Who is goig to stad on you r back
Who is going to tell you
Your beard is wh ite
Everything i notice
That is why, i hide you
You are my secret
Oly ca rry h i m
He is grown up... he is not a child
I am papa's angel
Angel don't walk on the ground
Say thank you
Sama r, do't let go
Don't ever let sa hil ' s had
Not ever
No one can fight the bank
Bank is Iike a rock
That day we knew we drop the bank
It's the bank or we survive
Papa, alway's said I'm his angel
I have magic in my hand
This is my blood
The passage is very narrow
It's a secret
Sahil don't even know my secret
My secret is...
Aliya h
There is no good man for her
in this entire world
She is the best
Her name is very cute
[ Skipped item no. 257 ]
When she is not close to me
I feel happy
Her name is cute
I feel good to think for her
Goodnight aliya h
Where are we going
Going back home
Remain quite and come with me
know the train to the airport
Cancel our trip
Let's begin with our operation
We are not in our hometown
But we are international police
We came with respect
And we shall go creatig chaos
Brother we stayed behind
Do you remember his circus trick
The way he loots
We need to understand
You tell me
What can i do
Our answers are hidden behind
Sahil is hiding something
Playig the game is fun for me
Why did you wear my costume
I did not have time
What's the difference
Your costume stinks
Don't try and act smart
Why can't i be smart
Tomorrow is sunday
Why are you so stubborn
Hello, you must send the box
Nowadays you forget alot
Twins
One brother goli and the other boli
One brother is weaker
I'll take care of him
You concentrate on sahil
The case is much easier
Iike a waterfall
Now we know their secret
Have you not seen
They are twins
Been twins is not a crime
How will we get them
Sahil's strenght is his brother
And his weakess too
Tell me direct
What should i do
Sunday, 14th may
Sahil always tell me a hip hop
A day i want to be samar
Cause i go alone
He is afraid for me
I have no problem
I can take care of myself
I have alot of fun
I Iive in a box
Only sunday i feel the fresh ai r
My nose is funy... when it's cold
Writing my name is fun
Only my name!
For two minutes i'll let out my secret
Thief thief
Hey you stop!
Stealing is very bad!
I am not a thief
Did not eat for 5 day' s
Happy burger
Whom eat burger be happy
Do you know who is the biggest thief
Everyone is a thief within
What do you Iike
Fun
Where are you going?.
I only come on sunday's
Can we meet the next sunday
My circus
I did not make any friend
Papa i always think i can
not be a fried
If, i tell sahir he won't Iike the idea
Where do he have the time
I have two secret' s
Aliyah and a friend
Victoria this is call brain
Do you know Karim bhai
You need to research
Ali you are here to find the thief
Think about work
Not Kamasutra
Mr Iqbal khan
How are you?.
Untill i have this $25 on me
No, bank can't shut us down
Papa this is the last bank
This bank will be finish very soon
Yes i found ajob
I will buy you a burger
I did not see aliyah
The wonder girl
Aliyah is not my gf
Why
The way you both react
lt's Iike gf and bf
Why don't you kiss her
Hey, she is not that type girl
I love her
I told you
But she is not my gf
She don't even know i Iike her
What nonsence
This can't be
When she is near you
lt's Iike you lover's
When she looks at you
It's Iike she is with sah i r
When aliyah look's at sahir
Today's performace
I will act
You take my place
And i will take your place!
What
Are you crazy
No
I want to perform
You are crazy boss
Must i do the thinking
You had over reacted today
Something happen today
A lot happen in a big way.
Something electric... between us
I still can feel it
What can we do about this elecricity
Boss there are something in Iife
we must get hold
Everything has a moment
If you are late
Everything is finish
Can we go on a date
Are you going
Yes
Today is not sunday
Going on a date with aliya h
So do you Ii ke her
Doe's she Iike you...yes
But who do she Ii ke
She only knows me
Can use i did not given her place
We are this much from our plan
We have to suceed
And the bank needs to close
You are papa's secret
We have only one plan
Please do not break our plan
It will cause chaos
If, i do't go she will feel bad
It's only for one night
What do you think
If you go she will be crazy for you
How will you speak to her
You are a secret
Remember you are weak
This is why you are inside
I am outside
Two minutes she will come
to know you are not sahir!
Just fix your brain
You a burden... bloody idiot
I am not a burden
I am samar
And either weak
Papa has two hand
Sahir and samar
I do the ha rd work
Applause go to you
And you want to become mastermind
Why me?.
You are weak
Why
Do not date guys with open
shoelace
Might if i tell you
Ican't tie lace!
Nice trick to woo a girl
to her first date
It's a fact that I don't know
how to tie a lace
What happen
Elecricity
Brother from Ram ad Shaam
There is one going
Follow them
If you speak Iike that
Everyone will think we both bf ad gf
Let them think
From both who is my bf
There are two off you
You are one
And the other is my boss
Very nice ego
Who do you Iike
If you was not around nothing
should happen to me
Do you consider me as your pal
I will tell you a secret
Remember we are friends
Don't be afraid
This was a Iie
Friendship was true
Friend's don't speak a Iie
You Iied to me
The bank of chicago
They have been punished
The bank is not sh ut dow
And papa is not alive
This should come to an end
I,know you and sahir are brothers
The great Indian circus
You are the secret!
Samar you need to help me
Come with me and give a statement
to the police
I, will try and plead with the case
You are the one can save sahir
Save aliyah's love
Sahir the wizard
I am a clown
We cheat death
I Iike your trick
Observe and cheat
When the three meet it's mag ic
What everthing you done to samar
It was not right at all
You played with his emotions
I should have stayed to see you dead
It's my last bank loot
Our last and dagerous loot
This is going to be a storm
We are going to shut down the bank
The first time I caught a thief
durig the night
If I was not a police
Surely should write a poem
Brother, let them go
We can't get them
At nig ht it's always victory for a thief
And when the sunlight it's mine
I have a plan
Samar
Jai,I'm very tired of running
And there is no place to run
I am a rrested... but the court
Can't prove me guilty
This is all the evidence
This is all my crime
Let Samar go
Each off you must get punish
Not Samar
I was the mastermind
Playing was mine
Samar is innocent
Let him go
It's a deal
You prom ise
From now onward's you do not hide
You not a burden
You are Samar
You are not weak
We were two
We Iived as oe
Where are you going?.
Let go my hand
Papa said  I can't let go your hand
We are god's grace
Ou r destiny is decide by god
The last day of chicago bank
remain's hope
Last day for western bank
There are some rule's to be broke
Victory only meant for one
Real victory are the hero's
The great Indian circus!