Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
India and pakistan has fought
4 wars until now
but india and pakistan's government
agencies and fighting daily
normal people dont know about it
they hide it for country's security
but some stories cant be hidden
but its a story that shocked the world
its a story of a tiger
they will find me
they have found me,
you kept me here since 1 month
tell me what to do?
I'm reached here.
You come
you are breathing like a dog
how much governmentjob gives us?
What is the rate of purchases agents?
They need it. You sold our
information to isi
you also have killed so many isi
agents in your career
we are just players in this game
will raw give this to us?
Come with me.
It has lots of money
i will not come with you
you have come at so many days
look he has come back again
why are you happy?
I'm not happy.
I was just telling you
he must have fight with someone
why are you staring him?
What does he do?
Son its 9 am.
I give you lift to office
sir is very punctual to time
ravinder was kept at northen border
of iraq
your face is totally changed
i will be fine.
I dont need leave
dont use your luck so much
tonight make a good food for me
then i will find a new enemy for you
this is for your food and
madness
how you live here?
You dont have anything
good in house
since 8 years your salary is saved
in agency's account
if i live here then i will use money,
since 12 years i'm on government tour
how much you have saved?
They will be spoiled in agency bank
when i will be retire,
i will use all money
why you never had any girlfriend?
What is the problem in yourjob?
When someone asks what is yourjob?
I still have sometime
i was a poet when i was young
i will live whole life for her
my work came between
you still feel regret?
I think i have found your
next mission
only india has an anti missile
technology
from which we can stop most of
incoming pakistani missile
one man made this technology
he is one of the famous scientist
of the world
since few months we have a doubt
that he is sharing his knowledge with someone
that person is working for pakistan's
defence establishment
so i have to stop him?
We just have a doubt
someone will be die when
you go on a mission
only 1 girl has a access to professor's
house
she is trinity dance academy student
since 1 year
and care taker of professor's house
they dont have any fixed time
when he will come back
he go with rocket for a long walk
i meet him there
i dont know anyone here,
is there any hotel here?
Its on my way
its was a bad joke
my hostel has come,
there are 2 more hotels ahead
not from there,
come from here
what do you do?
Do you want to sleep
in that room?
It belongs to my friend but
she is out of town
its more expensive than hotel
money is in the pocket
of my jacket
what do you do?
I'm a writer
so you want to take interview of professor?
Will it be ok if you take my
interview later?
Why are you talking on the pipe?
Are you married?
You will not ask do you have
girlfriend?
Now your age is for marriage
i'm not married
i cannot find any good girl
what do you want?
For whom i live for whole life
first time someone called me this
they sponsor the show and i
do choreograph
you want to spend sometime with professor?
I will try to talk to professor
you enjoy eggs and indian
government pays for it
manish chandra is a boring name
look at his hair
shanoi sir told us we dont
want professor's computer
we have to know with whom
professor meet
i'm thinking to go in his
house with girl
i'm a mad scientist
indian government thinks this
tell me what i have to do?
I want to spend most of time
with you
when you make notes in the morning
i go with college with you
you want to write book on me
or you want to marry me?
Why he always bark on me?
Because you called it idiot
you dont like dogs?
Tonight i'm going with my friends
you will not come like this?
Have you ever thrown darts?
She is effecting you alot
your mother was on the phone?
I want tangri kabab
you dont look like writer
your hands are like body builder
why you become writer?
Very few people listen to
their heart
most important thing they
always think from their mind
like he hold me seems like
he belongs to our work
someone is becoming angry when
i go near to professor
we have to finish it as
soon as possible
you have never buy a gift
for any girl?
Its neccessary to impress zoya
for mission
you have bring this gift for me?
First time i'm giving gift
to a girl
you dont like it
i like it
it reminds me someone
will you help me?
I dont know dancing
what happen?
Leave girl and catch rocket
1 dog has made me cat
what happen?
Can we meet tonight?
Its very important
you have also bring professor
on a date?
I told you i will make rocket your friend
now he will not bark on you
i want to show you something
you bring me here to show this?
It happens in 25 years
do you when this shower happened
last time?
16 june 1991
my father had an old police jeep
he bring me outside city in it
he always used to say a person
feel happy to look at stars
because 1 day our all loved ones
become stars
i felt so happy from
these things
where is your father?
What was the name of your father?
I cannot hide from you
i'm dumb in it
thats why your daughter call me dumb
i want to say something to your daughter
i dont know how to say
what do you want to say?
What are you saying?
We cannot love
when we are not on mission?
She loves writer manish chandra
neighter i'm manish
nor i'm writer
i have changed so many names,
i dont remember my real name
tiger is a name of a dog
i told you dont fell in love
its 5 am morning
you have created hell in dubin and
that agent also ran away
she knew i'm not a writer
he must be there
you will be saved from police.
I will talk to sir
after creating hell you watch
play with your girlfriend
thats what i'm saying,
go there
you know it
what we do in these situations?
You have 2 options
work for us
and give us all information
i cannot cheat my country
then i have only 1 choice
neighter i'm writer
nor i'm manish
expect these 2 things i told
everything true
i just wanna know
you dont love me?
I was doing my job
you kill someone on your every
assignment
we did not want this
police found their agent's
dead body
you did not left any trail.
I have bring back hard disc
i'm tired from this operation
only few people listen to
their heart
you are packing your stuff?
We caught a message
pakistani deligates wants to raise
kashmir issue
monitor all pakistani sources,
i'm fed up of catching all messages
they are using our actors names
we have gulshan grover and amrish puri
daily they put 1 messagae.
Zee tv is coming, doordarshan is coming or not?
What are you searching?
You wanted a leave.
Why you want to go istanbul?
Take out your sweeters.
Lets go to istanbul
tell zoya. It was very easy for you
to say i love you with gun in hand
if you had gun in your hand,
i would say same
on that place where you killed agent feroz.
He was also there
a girl whose duty dont allow her to love,
she says that she love him
to a person whom she does not
know his real name
if she said then what will happen?
We cannot live together
daily we will request songs for each
other on all india radio
we are enemy.
Our duty will not allow us to live together
our people will not allow us
to live together
what tiger is doing?
All deplomats of the world is
dancing with each other
why indian and pakistani?
This world will not let us live
then why dont we make
our world
lets run away zoya
dont know until when our countries will fight?
We cannot wait for them
it will be hard to run in old age
you have to decide what will happen
with us its in your hand
where are you?
Its time to go airport
i think pakistani have kidnapped him
dont leak this news
how much money he has withdraw?
Around 23 lacs
when i will retire from job,
i will withdraw all money
tiger has very sensitive information
if someone will get this information
then all our agents will be in problem
i dont know what tiger is doing
but tiger will not give this information
to anyone
1 pakistani deligate is also missing
this is his friend's hotel
do you know how many countries in the world?
201 countries
but tiger only found a pakistani girl?
Why you called me here?
Our plan will be ruined like this
he is a very dangerous agent.
But you have to wait
its not easy to make him fool
we should know what are you doing?
He dont have any doubt on me.
I cannot bring him here
there are lots of indians searching him
i'm bringing him here.
We will take 10:30 flight to kazakhistan
you take our photo on airport and
send to kazakhistan station
i did not recognize you
that person having coffee is an
isi agent
the person talking on the phone
is also a isi agent
lets go
but there is a 1 hour time
in our flight
we will see.
Lets go
but i had to do this
that you created there
he made a plan to trap you
if you saw me with captain abrar
then why you came with me?
First time i did something with heart
i wanted to see where it bring me?
I'm laughing to think what is
happenning in kazakhistan?
He is looking like a pakistani
its already 3:45 since flight landing.
Nobody came here
kazakhistan information is wrong
there were 2 big flights from istanbul
they can travel on any nationality
passport
find them
we have to find
if tiger has decied it then
it will be hard to find him
raw was running before him and
still raw exists
tiger knows so much things about us,
before this information isi will take
we have to find him and
bring him back
and if he dont want to come back
then you better know what we
have to do
remember 1 thing nobody will
recognize his body
lets go from here
dont send these type of correspondence
you handle somethings by yourself
they are keeping an eye on us
they need manager authorization
for big amount
they can give half of that amount
manager will be here in 20 mins
i buy car from this money.
You withdraw all money
you ran so much
look what i found
sorry i remind your father again
they all were waiting for you
dont do anything here.
They can kill us here too
kill him if you need too
you will kill me?
Do know how countries in the world?
How can you run with a pakistani girl?
Do you know how much information
zoya can give?
She is ready to come to india
i need your men's help
she is with some people.
They will not allow her to come
you want us to attack isi in cuba
if she is a pakistani then you
call her a girl
they are taking her to pakistan by
morning flight
we have to do know
you will be here
you will block them from here
to arrest me you bring an army
we come here to arrest our teacher
our flight is taking off
you indian friend ran away
i will reach.
Dont worry about me
we will have only 1 chance to take off
bring us to a safe place
you call me from my real name
you have shown me your reality
first time i did what my heart told me
you are fogetting your duty
its not easy to live with regret
its cheating to love with enemy
when i was felling in love nobody told
me its wrong
until when you will run?
When india and pakistan will not need
isi and raw, we will come back
they both are missing in raw and isi files
but still we are getting news to
see them in different countries of the world
but nobody is sure they are
tiger and zoya
raw and isi still searching tiger
and zoya
first time in history raw and isi did
work together
wherever they are, after getting this news
they will be happy
www.nieco.com
text nieco nieco