I am 40 years old.
Normally at this age
in one's life, there comes a big twist.
There came a twist even in my life.
I mean, really big.
One that changed my life.
Actually, let's start
at the very beginning.
Since I was a kid I have been living
in this house with my
grandpa, grandma, mother and father.
My parents passed away when
I was eight years old.
My grandparents took care
of my upbringing.
When I was a child
I was very cute.
People would pull my cheeks and say...
So sweet!
And this sweetness was even running
in my grandpa's business.
Y. Y. Confectioners
In Mumbai, the outlets of our shop
surpassed the greenery.
Please pack samosas
and half a kilo of Jalebis, brother.
Brother!
Y. Y. Confectioners!
My grandpa always interfered
in my love life.
At times he would call
and at times he himself
would show up in person.
I never had a relationship
so, clearly marriage was out of question.
Six!
Did you see, Rahul?
Sachin plays so amazingly.
Though my grandpa was a die hard fan
of Sachin Tendulkar...
he never applied the word "die"
in his life.
Time passed on but he did not.
All my relatives settled abroad.
And then, it was 2013.
My grandpa's 100th birthday!
All of my relatives gathered and,
even the two tragedies of my life came.
My two friends, Bobby and Salim.
Once you reach there
don't be naughty at forty!
And both of you, mind your own business!
- Tanu, help me with the decorations.
- One second.
What are you two planning to do?
Not just the two, it includes all of us.
Rahul, although it's grandpa's birthday,
we have a gift for you.
Hot NRI women!
I've already spoken to them.
We'll be with them in Goa for
six days and seven nights.
What sort of friends are you?
For a week!
How will grandpa let me go for a week?
I'll be back.
He's an idiot!
- You are also an idiot...
- Rahul...
Come here.
Grandpa.
Sir, you come with me.
Yes, Grandpa.
Did you bring me a gift?
You haven't yet opened the gifts given by
Vimal, Renu and the others.
They are others', not ours.
I am going to be 100 years old.
I will say wise things.
They like me because we're related.
You love me which is why we are related!
I wonder what will happen
to you once I'd be gone.
No, Grandpa...
Here we go! I've also begun
to talk about dying.
Well, I am still young.
Why should we talk about what is
to happen 20 to 25 years later?
Come on, show it to me.
A bat autographed by Sachin!
Come on, hit!
Grandpa, Rahul is thinking to open up
a franchise of your shop in Goa.
Yes, go ahead and open it.
Why is he playing like this?
Grandpa, we have already seen
an amazing plot in Panjim.
Grandpa, can we go with Rahul
to finalize the plot?
- Go!
- Okay.
Come on, Sachin!
Hit it beyond the boundary!
Six! Sachin is on 99.
Hey, old woman.
Look, Sachin is on 99.
Oh, Grandma!
Such excitement for a century!
It's just a game.
He will make it again.
Grandpa!
Both grandpa and Sachin
were knocked out at 99!
It was a strange feeling.
But then I read that...
a person's death is already
predestined before his birth.
I thought to myself if what has to happen
has already happened then
what difference does it make?
After all, grandpa lived since the era of
All India Radio to the advent of Twitter.
He lived a good life.
That's it!
At that very moment...
I had made a decision.
Goa is on!
Grandma, I want to do something
more in life.
I want to do something
by my heart.
I cannot handle
grandpa's business anymore.
Grandma, even I have some dreams
which I've not been able to fulfill.
But now I want to see the world
and learn things.
Grandma, I really want
to live on my own terms.
Rahul, along with the property,
you're free to do whatever you want.
Live your life the way you want to,
nobody is stopping you.
But you will have to do me a favor.
Tell me, Grandma.
It was your grandpa's last wish...
that after he died...
half of his ashes should
be immersed into the Ganges...
and the other half in Rameshwaram.
Rameshwaram?
Yes. I will go with Anshu
and immerse his ashes into the Ganges...
but you will have to go to Rameshwaram
to pour the other half of his ashes.
Grandma, me?
Yes, you!
This was your grandpa's last wish.
You will have to fulfill it.
Rameshwaram is at the end of India!
That too in the exact
opposite direction of Goa!
One minute, guys!
Salim, give me that.
The waters of Goa must be flowing up
to Rameshwaram, right?
What do you mean?
Means if we pour out
grandpa's ashes in the waters of Goa...
It will eventually float
and reach Rameshwaram.
Yes, but Goa and Rameshwaram
are miles away.
Oh, we are going to make
them coincide!
Which means...
Goa is on!
Yes, Rahul.
Bobby, change of plan.
What? You're coming to Goa, right?
Of course, I'm coming.
But to fool grandma we have
to begin our journey by train.
What?
Grandma is going to come to see me off.
So in the next two hours I'll buy a
ticket of any train going to South India.
I will get on the train,
and I will get off at Kalyan.
You guys wait for me there,
we will travel by road from there.
Which means, Goa is on!
Let's go, grandpa.
Chennai Express?
Yes, Chennai Express.
As much as I know, I don't think
Chennai Express goes to Rameshwaram.
You did not understand.
Didn't I tell you that I want
to spend more time with grandpa?
So I am taking the long route
not the wrong route.
I will get off at Chennai
and take the road to Rameshwaram.
Rahul...
Do you know why am I taking your
grandpa's ashes to the Ganges?
It's because I don't trust anyone here.
But I have complete faith...
that you'll immerse your grandpa's ashes
in the waters of Rameshwaram.
I did not like lying to grandma.
But by then, I had already done that.
Where are you, Rahul?
We have already reached Kalyan.
Yes, I just took the train
after bidding farewell to grandma.
I will be reaching shortly.
Rahul has arrived.
Rahul, where were you?
I've come, right?
- It's going to be fun!
- Yes!
- Ash!
- What happened?
The ashes!
Grandpa's ash!
Rahul...
Rahul, listen to us!
I've done this before.
Actually... Sorry, I have to go.
Meenamma, what did you think?
That you could get away from us?
What you are doing is totally wrong!
Don't try to preach to us.
What are you guys fighting about?
People miss trains and because of
you people I missed my platform.
Meenamma.
Please relax. Don't be upset.
Chennai express
That's my seat.
I'll take off the bag. Nonsense.
Rahul, where are you?
I am in the train.
In the train?
I didn't have the chance to get out.
So, this is what we are going to do...
We will meet at Karjat Station.
And listen...
Don't worry about me.
I've got great company.
So, you finally found her?
Yes, she is sitting right in front of me.
What hair!
What amazing eyes!
What lips!
You're objectifying her!
Won't she beat you?
She doesn't understand Hindi.
Hey, wait!
She's looking at me.
She's probably looking at me with love.
Make sure she's not blind.
But its possible that
she'll fall in love with me.
Listen, let's meet at Karjat Station.
Till then I will keep myself busy here.
Hopefully, I should be able
to get her along.
When I saw you I knew my dear
That love is crazy my dear
Now where do I go
What makes you think I
don't understand Hindi?
The ones whom you helped
Are here to kidnap me
Kidnap?
We're in big trouble
So will you help?
So that they don't suspect anything...
Talk to me through songs
Grant me forgiveness,
For what I've done
I had no idea you knew the language
I will do as you say now
Since I've made a mistake,
I should pay the penalty
Don't you worry!
I am here!
Meenamma.
You sing.
So you go to the toilet
Toilet!
But why are you sending me to the toilet?
What is it that you intend to do,
Tell me?
Your...
-I will use your phone to make a call
-Okay
I will inform my friends
Go to the toilet
Toilet!
You must not have heard
the name before.
Can I make a call from this?
Of course, you can.
Meenamma, what did you think?
You would call and we
wouldn't notice?
That was my phone.
My friends are waiting at Karjat Station.
How will I contact them?
That was my phone.
My phone!
Meenamma, what is he saying?
It was his phone.
If I knew that earlier
I would have thrown him out
with the phone.
What is he saying?
He's saying that had they known
the phone belonged to you
they would throw you out
with the phone.
Is this your father's kingdom?
Are you trying to scare me?
Are you threatening me?
Meenamma!
Enough! This is too much.
You have made me so angry that
I will sit down.
And if I sit down don't think
I won't be able to stand up again.
And if I stand up don't think...
I cannot sit down again.
And I forgive you for the mobile too.
I can buy the entire mobile company
if I want to.
4G, 5G! I have a lot of money.
Poor people.
Brother, show me your ticket.
No.
What no?
If you don't have a ticket
then you will have to pay a fine.
I have my ticket.
This is a ticket.
If you don't have a ticket
then you will have to pay a fine.
From where have you boarded the train?
Are they with you?
Listen to me very carefully TC
Don't take it easy on these hooligans
I swear all four of them
Are carrying long weapons
These four friends have abducted this girl
And taking her very far
Very carefully
Come on, get up.
Come with me.
Come on.
Now you will be in trouble.
You can go to jail and
play ping pong!
You think you are King Kong?
What?
Why aren't you answering?
And Meenamma,
you are on my watch now.
The TC is on our side.
See how he teaches them a lesson!
Enough!
This is too much.
You all have made me so angry that now
I have to sit.
You sing and dance.
We are going by Chennai Express.
You laugh and cry.
Meenamma?
Whatever happened with the TC,
you are the solo witness to it.
That is why you will come with us
to Komban village on Chennai Express.
On Chennai Express!
All my wishes were washed away
with the ashes.
I had come to Goa to immerse the ashes
but instead drowned the TC.
My friends tried
to get in touch with me.
But they could not track me down because
My 35,000 rupees cell phone
was lying somewhere on a railway track.
I want to sleep.
You sleep.
Periyanna, check on the next station.
I am hungry.
Okay.
Meenamma...
What is happening?
I cannot understand a thing.
You are scolding your kidnappers
And they are listening to you!
I will clear your confusion.
My father is a highly respected man
in the Komban area.
He is a... You know, Periyathalai?
Periyathalai? You mean teacher?
No.
Don.
These four are listening
to my pechi because...
Pechi?
- Chatter.
- Chatter! Oh, I get it.
So they were listening to me because
they're my father's goons.
Goons?
My father asked them to kidnap me
and bring me back to Komban.
That means your father
is Godfather of the South.
And he wants my Kalyanam to be done.
Kal...
With Tangaballi.
Yes, that is why I ran away!
I didn't understand.
Tangaballi is my father's friend's son.
If I marry him then my father will
own his friend's village.
That's why my father wants
to get me married.
Did you understand
the entire situation?
No.
It's your father, your goons,
your marriage! What's my fault?
The problem is yours, your kidnapping
that village is also yours
and it's my neck on the line?
That means, what is yours is mine?
No, Meenamma.
People fly kites in the air! Your goons
throw mobiles and TCs in the air!
I was happily going to Goa.
Goa is on! But no!
Take the Chennai Express!
I am ruined!
I thought of running away at night
When I opened my
eyes in the morning...
Will you have some Idli?
No.
I need to go.
- Will you eat?
- No, I'll go.
Why is he not eating Idli?
Inspector Sir...
Periya.
What, officer?
Did you hear the
sound of this chicken?
What did he say?
He said...
Have you ever heard chickens?
??
Check if there anything to eat?
Okay.
Meenamma.
That policeman instead of
helping me, he...
From here the entire region
belongs to my father.
Even the policemen here takes
my father's help.
What do you mean?
It means that no one can do anything
to these four.
That means from here
anything can happen to me?
Yes.
- Means I could even lose my life here?
- Yes
What are you agreeing on?
You should never tell
a dying person that he's about to die.
At least give me some sort
of false hope that I will be safe.
You can be saved.
Now my ashes will also be immersed
as that of grandpa's.
I don't know why did I give you my hand!
You gave me your hand?
In a bid to save myself I was running.
Why did you help them?
Had I known that
your brothers were goons
I would have kicked them instead
of helping them.
Anyway, you are the root cause
of this entire problem.
Ever since you've come into my life,
my life sucks!
Why have you come to me?
You came on my side!
Forget about sides, Meenamma.
Come to the point.
Is there any way for the two of us
to get out? Tell me, please!
- Please!
- Yes, there is.
What is it? Please tell me.
But you will have to do as I say.
As if everything was going
my way till now.
I'll do it.
Tell me what has to be done?
Once we reach Komban,
in front of my father...
whenever I look towards you,
just nod your head.
Nod what?
Head.
What?
Nod my head.
I will eat idli, dosa.
I will nod my head.
I will eat dosa...
Take the Chennai Express.
Hey, Chinna.
We reached. Come!
Let's go.
What are you doing, brother?
Meenamma, why did he pull the chain?
When we arrive at our village,
we pull the chain.
We decide where the train station is.
Come on!
Come?
Hey! Move on.
Who is this?
My father.
How many times will you try to escape?
Why are you doing this?
For what?
I don't want to marry Tangaballi...
Meena was making her
father understand, emotionally.
Her father was shocked
with what Meena was saying.
I am in love with somebody.
Who is he?
- And I was...
- Him.
And I was as clueless as you all are.
He loves me too.
Am I right?
The plan was to just nod my head.
That is why...
After such a reaction,
one thing was certain.
In the future, I wouldn't
be able to nod my head...
because it won't be there!
My dear...
Is Tamil your mother tongue?
What is your father asking me
about my mother?
He's asking you
if you know Tamil.
Father, he is settled in the North.
I will teach him Tamil
after our marriage.
Meena likes this boy. Bring him.
Meenamma, I thought
they were going to kill me.
But your father's goons
lifted me up on their shoulders.
What did you say to them?
I just told them three lies.
You lied?
At least tell me
what you said, Ms Subtitle.
My first lie was that we are very much
in love with each other.
My second lie was that we wanted
to get married to each other.
That's when you nodded your head.
Yes, I nodded. But that...
So, all of them have accepted this?
No.
The plan only worked when
I told them the third lie.
What was that?
That you lived in North
since you were a child,
which is why you
don't know Tamil.
He thought my story was genuine.
That's why they're taking us
to the village to decide our future.
Not to decide on the future but
to destroy my future.
Hey, brother!
Think about it Rahul,
I will get married.
Brother!
At first there were four
of them running after you.
Now the whole village will chase you.
I did this drama so we could
buy some time.
We will run away as soon
as we get an opportunity at night.
Run away...
I have a lot of experience
in running away.
Meena's family reminded me
of the population in China.
Meena began telling them the story
of Chennai Express.
As the story progressed, everyone seemed
to be impressed with me.
But I was depressed.
I was stressed.
Because the place where I had arrived
was a very dangerous one!
Everyone was treating me well.
But a goat is also well fed before
it is sacrificed!
I've asked Bobby to get a fancy number
at times but...
The numbers I was trying to call
Were all washed away from my brain.
The mobile technology definitely
connected us with our closed ones but...
It had also messed
with our heads.
At first when there were
no mobile phones
Then we would remember
all telephone numbers.
Now that we have a mobile phone
we don't remember any numbers!
Meena...
What's the plan to get out of here?
Meena, don't ignore me.
This drama has gone on for too long,
it's quite enough now.
- I'm losing patience.
- Rahul.
Hello, Sir.
- Get him a coffee.
- Get it.
The food is ready. Call everybody.
Madhi, come here.
Rahul.
Oh, no!
Hey, you are so smart.
What are you jabbering in Tamil?
Talk in Hindi.
Hey, you are very beautiful.
You learnt Tamil in a day?
Meena, I am not
this sort of a guy. Please!
- Meena.
- Rahul.
- Madhi.
- Puvi.
They came.
We just followed them.
Yes.
Let's go.
Go.
What's the hurry?
Hey! Come.
Meena I want to get out of here.
Please do something.
Do?
Are you doing fine?
Vanakkam.
Singh.
We need to take a decision
in some of these matters.
A Punjabi? Here?
So we should think and
take a decision.
You are right.
But tell Meenamma that...
This Punjabi man is speaking in Tamil!
With the boy she should not...
Give me a minute.
You're Rahul, right?
Yes. How did you know?
It's the work of policemen,
to identify a corpse.
A corpse? But I am still..
If it's not been done already,
it will be done.
I'm in charge of this area.
You have a lot of guts.
Fell in love with Meena, knowing that
you'll be in the bad books of Tangaballi.
No, not at all.
People here have misunderstood.
Actually, these guys want to frame me.
You will be framed up on this wall
And a garland will also be placed
on your photograph.
Garland! No, Sir.
This is against the law.
Here you go, you should have thought
about this before falling in love!
Hey! Tangaballi is here.
Tangaballi is here!
I have heard that this time
somebody has come with Meena.
Yes! What can we do?
What is he saying?
Tangaballi is asking about you.
What is the father saying?
The father is saying you
are the one because...
of whom Meena keeps running away
from home time and again.
Oh, no!
My marriage with
Meena was already fixed.
You are right, my dear.
What is he saying now?
The father is saying that his first choice
for Meena is Tangaballi.
But he's helpless because Meena's
first choice is you.
- No!
- Yes!
I am not here to decide what
is right and wrong.
It's about my prestige!
Sir, what is he saying now?
The father is asking to mutually
take a decision on this matter.
Not him, what is the giant saying?
He's saying that...
Now it's not about right or wrong.
It's a matter of his prestige.
If it's a matter of his prestige...
then why is he trying
to take away mine?
Sir, don't worry.
I can handle this.
Are you the one who wants
to marry Meena?
- At least hear him out.
- Relax! I'll handle it.
Do you think you're a hero?
- Listen to me...
- Its okay, he is joking with me.
If you are a real man,
fight with me!
We'll fight tonight.
If you win, Meena is yours.
If I win, Meena is mine.
What do you say?
What gibberish was he talking?
Please speak up.
Don't be scared.
He has challenged you.
- What?
- You both will have a fight tonight.
- Why?
- Yes.
Whoever wins, will get Meena.
My friend, you have just
accepted the challenge!
But I don't even understand Tamil,
I just nod my head as Meena told me to.
You came here alive.
You will not leave from here alive.
I will cut you into several pieces
and parcel it.
Tingu Sir, that's what I'm saying.
Peace, love, friendship, Gandhi...
Why didn't you tell me
what he was saying before?
You were tickling me instead!
- Let's see.
- What?
We will see.
Who is stronger!
Who is stronger?
What do you mean who is stronger, Sir?
I am not at all strong.
Make him understand.
I know there's a little problem.
A little problem?
The fight has been fixed for tonight
with that TV tower Tingu.
And even your father wants to find out
who amongst the two of us is stronger.
- Strong?
- Yes, strong.
Look, Meenamma.
If I get angry...
Then what will you do Rahul?
I will commit suicide.
I'll take poison, tie a noose around my
neck and be run over by Chennai Express.
- No, Rahul.
- The train is calling me.
Rahul... Rahul!
I will make a plan to run away tonight.
Till then you remain normal.
No, I cannot remain normal.
I will plan it.
You place a time bomb inside a person
and ask them to be normal!
You must have heard that name before.
- Meenamma!
- Yes.
So many people.
They are preparing
for your fight with Tangaballi.
I know. But how are we going
to get away with so many people around?
My escape plan is ready.
It's ready? What is it?
You just go out and behave normal.
- I am normal.
- Normal.
- I will come in a while and signal to you.
- Okay.
Then the two of us will run away.
Till then you don't make any mistakes.
No mistakes.
Dude, where are you going?
You are the one for me
Come and hug me
My body craves for you
Hey, he don't know Tamil.
Sing in Hindi once again.
My exotic beauty
I have veiled it
And brought it for you,
hiding it from the world
I am stuck between the devil
and the deep sea
Will someone tell me what to do?
I wonder who has cursed me
How have I landed here
Don't worry,
Be happy
Come and groove on the beat
One, two, three, four
Get on the dance floor
Booty shake, booty shake
Dappan goothu hard core
Let's dance hard core
Move your shoulders up and down
Move your body all around
Give me, give me
Some more
One, two, three, four
Get on the dance floor
Booty shake, booty shake
Dappan goothu hard core
Let's dance hard core
Move your shoulders up and down
Move your body all around
Give me, give me
Some more
It's amazing, it bombards the mind
My heart is fluttering, buddy
Marry me my small cuckoo
I'll provide you with slaves
You stabbed me here and there
And now she's coming
To set you on fire
Just sway to the beats
I can sense trouble
There seems to be bad luck written
In my future
My walk is the focus
Of everyone's attention
Don't hide your racing heart from me,
Don't act like a saint
The tinkling of your ear rings
Come as a warning bell to me
One, two, three, four
Get on the dance floor
Booty shake, booty shake
Dappan goothu hard core
Let's dance hard core
Move your shoulders up and down
Move your body all around
Give me, give me
Some more
One, two, three, four
Get on the dance floor
Booty shake, booty shake
Dappan goothu hard core
Let's dance hard core
Move your shoulders up and down
Move your body all around
Give me, give me
Some more
I don't care if your name is Pushpa
Or Champakali
I would rather run for my life
Than stick around with you
Where ever you go,
You will hear the one, two, three, four
One, two, three, four
Listen to it hardcore
All doors are closed my friend,
Talk less, dance more
One, two, three, four
Get on the dance floor
Booty shake, booty shake
Dappan goothu hard core
Let's dance hard core
Move your shoulders up and down
Move your body all around
Give me, give me
Some more
One, two, three, four
Get on the dance floor
Booty shake, booty shake
Dappan goothu hard core
Let's dance hard core
Move your shoulders up and down
Move your body all around
Give me, give me
Some more
Hey, Meena Lochini... Sundaram!
Meena Lochini... Sundaram!
What kind of name is this?
Addresses are shorter than this name!
I had gone on a holiday,
and you took me on a trip!
No, I won't nod my head now.
Hey, pot King!
Why are you sitting on that bike
and staring at me?
I had full plans of having fun.
Because of your ashes...
I've gotten into so much trouble.
Grandpa, I had full plans to immerse
your ashes in the waters of Goa but...
You changed my entire plan!
Hey, brother!
Hold this!
You were scaring me
by showing me your gun!
Now I will also show
you something. Look!
Did you see?
Can you do that?
No?
That's because your fat
comes in between.
Fatty.
Hey, don!
You were threatening me!
Wait.
Can you do this?
No, right? Then?
Mr. Durgeshwara... Sundaram.
Tamil is not my mother tongue!
How are you, my darling?
You have become a referee!
You fixed a match between
Tingu and me.
Where's Tingu?
Tingu!
Hey, you humongous monster!
Will you fight with me?
Why?
Okay, you can fight.
But before that show me
if you can do this?
Look, Tingu. Can you do this?
Catch him.
Tangaballi, can you do this?
- Hey, Sir!
- Rahul.
What happened?
You and me will have some buttermilk!
Yes, we'll have some buttermilk!
Come on, get up!
Get up!
You are completely drunk.
Careful!
Don't fall again!
Come, sit here.
Listen...
The station is on the opposite side.
Take the first train tomorrow at 5:30 a.m.
and leave. Understood?
Understood?
And don't tell anyone that
I helped you.
Yes and let it remain a secret.
Else, the entire village
will cut me into pieces.
The Almighty will take care of the rest.
Go to sleep.
Sir!
Hey! Look!
How did you come here?
From where have you come?
Where is this boat going?
Sri Lanka! Why?
To get diesel.
Have you gone mad? Why are you
going to Sri Lanka to get diesel?
We're going to Sri Lanka
with the smuggle diesel.
Everything is legal
when one has to survive.
If the Sri Lanka Marine police catch us,
we will be jailed.
If the Indian Marine police catch us,
we will be jailed here.
If police don't catch us,
all is well.
Oil is well!
Shut up and stop the boat.
Help me!
I've got on to the wrong boat.
- Bring out the gun.
- Help me.
Gun!
Enough.
Catch them and arrest them.
You're the first smuggler who is
so happy about being arrested.
No, Sir.
I'm not a smuggler.
I am not with them, Sir.
I am an Indian, Sir.
Is it? Show me your passport!
Passport? Why, Sir?
To verify whether you are
an Indian or Sri Lankan.
But Sir, I am not with them.
I speak Hindi, Sir!
We can also talk in Hindi.
Listen. Hindi!
What?
We all speak in Hindi!
Sir, he's my man.
And you are my wife!
What?
What are you looking at?
Arrest him.
What does that mean?
They say if you suffix word Ji,
to any other word
You gain respect.
Refu... Ji.
I did not gain anything!
Here my fate was being written by
my grandpa sitting in heavens
Whereas Meena's fate
was being written by her father.
He decided to get her
married to Tangaballi.
Meena was neither happy
with it nor was it her choice.
Who would have thought
That the tip of India
Would begin a new chapter
In Meena's and my life.
Brother, what are you looking at
with such fear?
- Is this yours?
- Yes.
I'm sure there is RDX in it.
Not "there is."
There was.
I mean, there was!
My grandpa is in it.
I mean my grandpa's ashes.
Allow me to show you.
I have been telling you that
I am not a smuggler!
You know, Sir. I came from Mumbai
to immerse my grandpa's ashes. That's all.
I told the police everything truthfully.
My history.
The geography of my travel.
And my chemistry
with the people of Komban.
After hearing all this, all
the Marine police officer said was...
So, the people of Komban know you, right?
Sir!
You!
Your fellow brothers are dropping
me to Mumbai.
Give me a hug!
You left me there, right?
Because of some smugglers
I went away to Sri Lanka.
You didn't go away. You came back...
- to Komban.
- No, I can't come.
How can that happen?
Look...
I'll be back.
Brother, me too.
Catch him.
What are you doing, man?
Sir, please leave me for heaven's sake!
Hello, Sir.
Hello.
Do you know him?
Do we know him?
We know him.
- Periya.
- Yes.
He is our family member, isn't it?
Yes, he is one of us.
Hey, where had you disappeared?
There's such tension
since you went missing.
Oh, family!
So you are an Indian after all.
I will release you here and leave.
Officer, you cannot leave me here and go.
I am Sri... Devi
"How are you, my darling?"
Refree, right?
No, Sir. I meant, Periyathalai Sir...
Hanger, right?
I meant strong, Sir.
You called me fat?
Chewing gum, right?
Do not step ahead.
I am warning you.
I will cut down all!
Hold this.
Nobody steps ahead.
If anybody comes forward, I will...
cut myself.
Okay, cut yourself.
Cut yourself.
I will cut Meenamma.
Stop.
Meenamma, open the door.
Nobody moves!
Move!
What do I do, Meenamma?
Catch him.
Come on, get out.
First you get drunk and run away
all by yourself.
Then you get into trouble
and use me to run away.
And now you're asking me
to get out of the car!
Yes, that's what I said.
Get out, please.
I won't get out.
This car belongs to my father.
If you don't get out,
I will take you back there.
Then you'll get married.
Before that, from Rahul you
will become Late Rahul.
I mean I think there's no parking here.
Let's go.
Rahul!
What happened? Has the
car broken down?
No! Who told you that?
What is with the smoke, then?
Smoke?
The car is smoking a cigarette.
And do you know why I came outside?
I thought to myself, that I could wait and
relax here and Tangaballi would come by.
And, when he comes, the three
of us can play together.
Can't you see?
Your father's car is even worse
than your Hindi.
You have wrecked the car!
Don't call this a car,
it'd be a sin to call this a car.
This car has saved your life.
It's not a car, it's a wreck!
My father's favorite car!
Catch it, Rahul!
I didn't mean it. Wait!
- No!
- Oh, no!
Take it!
Take it, Meenamma baby.
Your father's favorite car.
Actually the problem is not your father,
or his wrecked car.
The problem is you.
Wherever you go, you carry
a free trouble pack along with you.
Actually you are like a black cat.
Worse than a black cat!
If you cross the path of a black cat,
it will get cursed.
Then why are you with me?
Why am I with you?
Why are you with me?
Please, Meenamma.
Stop stalking me.
Alright.
But by the way, you stole the car and
drove in the wrong direction.
Now we have only one way out.
We'll have to cross Komban again!
Don't scare me with Komban.
If you are not with me,
I will manage on my own easily.
There's no word called impossible
in my dictionary.
Really? From where did you buy such
a rubbish dictionary?
Get lost.
I thought I would not meet
Meenamma ever again.
But fate had decreed
something else altogether.
Brother.
Hello, Sir.
I need to find the road.
Where is the highway?
What are you doing?
I want to see the road.
Where is the highway?
Relax, my child!
Don't take so much trouble.
I feel bad, then.
The two of us have the same problem.
At this age, we don't need
a new language.
Hey, brother!
Please, stop.
Hello, brother!
What do you want?
What is your work here?
I'm a boy, Rahul.
I need a lift!
You're from Mumbai, right?
How do you know so much about me?
The entire South knows you.
One fair boy has eloped with Durgeshwara
Azagsundaram's daughter in a car.
Oh my God!
Today you are in a car tomorrow
you will be the headline of a newspaper.
- No, listen to me.
- Go away.
You don't know, the village people
are chasing you with sticks!
Once you're caught they will kill you
and put that as a headline!
Let it be. Is it their kingdom?
The girl you have eloped with,
this is her father's kingdom!
Brother, please help me.
- Go away.
- Brother, please.
Brother, help me.
Brother!
I became numb after hearing this.
I could see the road ahead
But there was no way out.
Except one.
Meenamma...
What is it?
What?
You've come back to me after all!
You figured out how does it feel
to live alone, didn't you?
Look at your face.
It seems like you are getting
a fever because you are so frightened.
Come on.
I've come to take you.
We will go together. Come!
Again you've taken the wrong route.
This is the safer route.
That side you will find Tangaballi.
Come on!
Meenamma, I'll save you.
Vidamba village.
Come on.
A wedding ceremony is going on here.
If we make up a story
we can stay here for a few days.
Until then father and Tangaballi's tension
will get a bit diffused.
Then why are you standing here
and talking, Ms. Subtitle?
Go ahead and talk to them.
Such attitude!
Why don't you go and talk?
I can.
I know kunjam kunjam.
"Apadiya sapadiya Po."
Your grandpa can go take a hike!
You know how to speak Marathi?
If you can speak Tamil, why can't
I speak Marathi?
Oh, mother! Meenamma,
for now just go and talk in Tamil.
It seemed very pleasant but
there was something fishy.
There was something definitely fishy.
Once bitten, twice shy.
That's why, this time
I did not nod in agreement.
The second time when the villagers
looked at me, I...
What happened?
Hey! Don't come to me.
Open the window.
Let the fresh air come in.
Here is the towel and some clothes.
Rest well.
In the morning, after your bath,
we will arrange the prayers.
Rest well. Take care of him. Bye.
You know, a film should be made on me.
I laugh my way into a mess.
Whenever people gladly lift me up on
their shoulders, I know I am in a trouble.
And you, Meenamma...
What are the lies you have
spun around this time?
I told them we got married and ran away.
Have you copyrighted this story
of getting married and running away?
Then what did you say?
The second lie was that you're so good
that you will never leave me and go.
Then you agreed to me.
Yes.
Then I said you got so tired
with the journey
that you felt like fainting.
That's why...
You nodded.
Yeah, like this.
Nodded!
That's why I'm getting
this special treatment.
No.
The special treatment is because
I told them...
the reason why we eloped is because
my father has a huge problem
with you being poor and me being rich.
I am very rich.
And you are a confectioner.
How did you know
I was a confectioner?
You are a confectioner?
No.
Yes.
I am a confectioner.
What is so funny about that?
A confectioner is better than
being a don.
Quiet.
That means my third lie
is actually the truth.
You are making fun of me now?
Earlier, your father made
a fool out of me.
What a great father-daughter duo!
I wonder how your mother tolerates
the two of you.
Does she ever protest or
does she also...
I don't have a mother.
I had no idea.
I know what it feels like
to not have a mother.
Why?
Your parents?
They died in a car accident.
I was eight years old then.
Since then you've been all alone?
Actually I never really missed
my parents...
because my grandparents took their place.
Especially grandpa.
He was always happy when I was happy.
He couldn't live without me.
Rahul this, Rahul that... Rahul...
My grandpa.
Still Rahul...
To go through fifty years
of your life without parents...
Yes, Meenamma.
It is hard, but...
Fifty years?
Yes.
Do I look like I'm fifty years old?
Why? You're not?
Don't tell me you're more than that?
Meenamma, will you sleep on the floor?
This is not for me. It's for you.
Won't you be able to control yourself if
I sleep with you on the bed?
Shut up, okay!
I have a problem.
Yes, exactly.
You won't be able to control yourself.
Stop your nonsense.
What does that mean?
- Stop your nonsense.
- Do?
Naughty! Aunty!
Remember? Do...
I will sleep on the bed because
I am your spouse.
And as they say there is no business
like show-her business.
Come on, Meenamma.
Let us sleep, momma!
Fine, sleep if you want.
Don't tell me later that
I didn't warn you.
I can give no guarantee for
what will happen at night.
Rahul, consider that you
will be taken advantage of
tonight because your wife has no control.
Tangaballi... Don't come closer.
I will kick you.
I will not leave you.
I'm sorry but I don't know your language.
Do not come closer.
I will kick you.
Help me.
Meena has gone crazy.
Meena has turned into a witch!
Didn't I ask you to not sleep next to me?
I kick in my sleep.
Am I your father's scooter
that you will kick?
You're not the daughter of a don. You're
the daughter of a donkey!
I will never sleep with you.
You're a witch!
Get lost.
You get lost.
Now you do.
Are you dressed up
for your morning jog?
No.
It's the village ritual for newlyweds.
Ritual?
The husband carries his wife in his arms
and climbs up the steps to the temple.
They believe it strengthens
the marital bond.
Are you strong?
What is the need to be strong
to watch a ritual?
You don't have to watch,
you have to do it.
We are husband and wife for them.
No, I will not be forced
into doing anything.
No, the situation is like that.
What?
Helplessness!
What helplessness?
Do you want to stay here or not?
Yes, I want to stay.
Then you will have to carry me.
You won't drop me, right?
Meenamma, perhaps you are forgetting.
Confectioner?
We will reach the temple
after climbing three hundred steps.
Three hundred!
I will reach heaven
after climbing a hundred.
What happened?
Where has the power
of the common man gone?
I know you will drop me after fifty.
Rahul, you carried your wife
to the temple.
Meena, he will take care
of you all your life.
What is he saying?
He's saying that you've proved you'll
look after me for the rest of our lives.
Raaja, may you live for a
hundred years.
You both will live together
for seven generations.
Ms Subtitle. What?
They believe that the couples who are able
to complete this ritual...
God will keep them together
for the next seven lives.
Why haven't you put vermillion?
What is he saying?
Without the vermillion the ritual
is not complete.
What?
You should have mentioned it earlier.
Does that mean all of this is wasted?
My body is hurting so much!
Put this vermillion, my son.
No, Rahul.
What happened?
This ritual won't be complete
without the vermillion.
These people will take us out from here.
Come on and hurry up.
We have to descend 300 steps and
this time you will help me.
Like Lord Krishna, the one with
Dark cloud like complexion
With a butter eaten mouth
You stole my heart
Like Lord Krishna, the one with
Dark cloud like complexion
With a butter eaten mouth
You stole my heart
With nectar like sweetness
You ruled over all Gods
On seeing this sweetness
My eyes won't look at anything else
My heart, like a butterfly
Has taken flight far away
With sweet fragrances it has gone to stay
I have never felt this way
A ray of light
Kisses the darkness away
My heart, like a butterfly
Has taken flight far away
Should I say it in words
Or inscribe it on the sky
Praise be to you
My heart, like a butterfly
Has taken flight far away
With sweet fragrances
It has gone to stay
Your deep blue eyes
Tease me with a glance
Your soothing words can
Also put the birds in a trance
A little incomplete without you
Now I feel complete
Your simplicity has swept me off my feet
My heart, like a butterfly
Has taken flight far away
Should I say it in words
Or inscribe it on the sky
Praise be to you
Like Lord Krishna, the one with
Dark cloud like complexion
With a butter eaten mouth
You stole my heart
Like Lord Krishna, the one with
Dark cloud like complexion
With a butter eaten mouth
You stole my heart
With nectar like sweetness
You ruled over all Gods
On seeing this sweetness
My eyes won't look at anything else
What happened, Rahul?
What? I am packing.
Why?
Do you want to forever
live here in this Vidamba village?
Look, Meenamma. This is enough.
We will quietly slip away
without telling anyone.
Otherwise, these people
will keep making us do weird rituals.
You also get ready.
Let's go
No, Rahul.
If we run away from here then
what will the villagers think?
They will think that we've run away.
Get ready.
It's about the villager's feelings, Rahul.
What about when they find out that
we lied about being married?
Will they help anyone the next time?
Will these people be able
to trust anyone again?
- As it is...
- Meena..
Is it that you don't want
to leave this place?
I've noticed that ever since you've
started playing the role of being my wife
you have been having a lot of fun.
Look, don't get serious about the fact
that I've put vermillion on your head.
That was a stupid ritual.
Rahul!
Only you can think this way!
Did you ever think how would
the villagers feel?
Forget the village, have you ever thought
about your grandma's feelings?
You only said that your
grandpa had replaced your father, right?
And what did you do?
You changed the place where
he wanted his ashes immersed.
Yes! I changed the place.
Do you know why?
Because I don't have any feelings.
I am bad. Actually I am a very bad man!
Only you are very good.
These villagers are very good.
Grandma, grandpa is.
And a bad person has no right
to stay amongst good people.
So I'll just go. You know what?
You keep this with you.
You are good. He was good.
All of you make a company
of good people and live together.
I am not going to live
in this village alright.
Spare me, please!
Even though I was mad,
I had a sinking feeling
about leaving Meenamma all alone.
You've come?
Rahul! This...
This is too much!
Tangaballi, hold on a minute.
No personal enmity here, Sir.
Why do you want to take me
to Komban village and kill?
No point, Sir.
You've got your lady, Sir.
Leave me.
What?
From my heart, Sir.
I am speaking from my heart, Sir.
Throw away, Sir.
Do whatever you want
with your lady, Sir.
Get married!
Sir, she's your girl.
You can sing any song you want
to with her.
Now Meena is all yours, my friend.
Hey, you!
You're stupid, parasite
and an opportunist!
You are leaving me and running?
- Try and understand.
- Understand what?
- That...
- What that?
- That only...
- What that only?
I've played such a game
That I fool the opponent
And the game comes in my hands
To save you idiot
I've played a ruse
So, this was your strategy?
Since when did you become
brave enough to defend me?
Meena!
Washing powder, Meena!
No matter how wicked I am,
I am human after all
I thought to myself that
I must help you, Meena
Now do you understand what I'm saying
Meena!
Pick up the sickle that's
Beside Tangaballi
Take it
Yes! I will take it
I've understood my lady love
You two think I don't understand
And that you can make
a fool out of me
Tangaballi is singing in Hindi?
Yes!
Balli Balli I am Tangaballi
I know your plan
Means?
Now you're in trouble
You will not sing to him anymore
Now you will bid farewell to this world,
while doing disco
Okay, that's enough!
Hey, Tangu!
If you touch him, I will cut you.
You do not know...
who you are fighting with.
We're nice to good people
and a nightmare for bad ones.
Understood?
We live in South but we are in the center
of people's hearts.
Whoever ridicules our honor and culture,
we teach them such a lesson that...
they wet their pants.
Rahul!
Meena...
Nobody can understand women.
Even at a time like this she's
worried about her things!
Really, no one can
understand women.
Let's go.
Here, take your ticket to Mumbai.
And you?
I am going to immerse grandpa's ashes
in the waters of Rameshwaram.
You know Meenamma, I just realized...
No matter how wicked I am,
I am a human after all, Meena.
You thought it right.
You just said one thing wrong.
I will also come
with you to Rameshwaram.
What? Have you gone mad?
This is wrong.
- I'm doing the right thing.
- How is it right?
With such difficulty,
you've got the chance to run away.
I could have run away when you were drunk
in the village.
I didn't run away then.
So, why will I now?
I will also come with you.
Meenamma, try to understand.
I've taken a decision. Let me complete it
on my own accord, please.
And, you might be in danger there.
- What if Tangaballi reaches there?
- Exactly.
I will save you from Tangaballi.
That's why I should come with you!
Sometimes two roads travel side by side
They slowly converge
At the end of the ride
Sometimes when trouble
Become twice their size
They are halved when shared
With someone nice
Our love story is so strange
Sometimes we progress, sometimes we curb
Though I am the North pole
And you are the South
Yet our love has brought us together
Though I am the North pole
And you are the South
We are equal partners in every situation
Though we fight
Our partnership is alright
With you everything seems alright
We are two different people
With different attitudes
We wander the world in style
Sometimes we go apart and come back
We live our lives in the moment
Our moods change like the seasons
Though I am the North pole
And you are the South
The naughty north has given south a wink
Though I am the North pole
And you are the South
We will be together
Forget about the whole world
Sometimes two roads travel side by side
They slowly converge
At the end of the ride
Sometimes when troubles
Become twice their size
They are halved when shared
With someone nice
Our love story is so strange
Sometimes we progress, sometimes we curb
Though I am the North pole
And you are the South
Yet our love has brought us together
Though I am the North pole
And you are the South
We are equal partners in every situation
Tomorrow morning we
can complete the immersion ritual.
For tonight we will have
to stay in some lodge.
You know, Meena...
We are all so busy running around
in this fast paced life.
Our lives are no less than a marathon.
We're all running to gain
something in life.
Then someday we leave everything
and go away.
Just like I will leave you
and go tomorrow.
All your worries will come to an end.
But where will you go?
Pune.
My childhood friend lives there.
Chitra.
Meenamma, I was wondering if you
will be safe there or not.
I mean what if you father's goons
or your cousins reach there?
Meenamma, you come with me to Mumbai.
I have a house there.
My grandma will be there.
You can stay there peacefully.
Thereafter, you can decide for yourself.
You can start afresh.
And what if my father's goons
reach there?
That's not his kingdom.
That is not Komban village.
It's Mumbai.
Nobody can do such a thing there.
And if my father asks you,
what I am doing in your house...
What will you say then?
Then I will tell him that both of us...
You know?
You and me.
Pune is fine for me.
Anyway, I have troubled you a lot.
It's not your sympathy
But your love that I seek
I ask for your love
As I know you love me too
Because of the fear of the world
I promise I will never
Forfeit you, my dear
I will never let you go
If this isn't love
Then what is love?
Now that I have won your love
I don't care if I lose the world
I will never let you go
My life has lost its meaning
Since you are not there with me
Love is renowned
Since on this path I have walked down
I will not leave it mid way
From the path of your love
I will not stray
I will never let you go
Where have we come, Rahul?
You know...
We've come to the right place, Meenamma.
They will kill you.
- Without thinking...
- No, Meenamma.
I have come to this decision after
a lot of consideration.
But Rahul...
Rahul, you have gone mad.
We had run away from here.
But for how long will you run?
But for how long will we run?
Don't you have any dreams or
a life of your own?
Hello, Sir.
You must be wondering that
how I am back here by myself.
Father, he mean to say...
No, Meenamma.
Today your father and me don't need
any translation.
Because today I will talk by my heart
and you will have to listen.
Mr. Durgeshwara...
Sir!
The most important man
of Komban village.
Don!
You must be thinking why
I've come here.
Who is he?
Am I mad?
Or am I drunk?
Not drunk.
I just came to find out why you are being
so harsh towards Meena.
Why?
Don't you love your daughter?
You don't?
Because in a wedding you
give your daughter's hand in marriage.
But you tried to sacrifice her life.
Would a father do such a thing?
Like...
I am a confectioner.
But I will say something bitter.
You can be the father of this village,
the God father of this village...
But you cannot be your daughter's father.
Never, sir.
Your pull and power, full marks for that.
Very good, Sir.
But in one subject you have failed.
Zero!
Don't you have any value for
your daughter's emotions...
her wish, her happiness?
But alike Meena, no girl in this village
have rights to celebrate independence.
No right!
Even you people...
If you don't care for your daughter's
emotions, then this entire village...
this unity, Periyathalai!
This power is bullshit, Sir.
Now what do we do?
Do we fight? Come on!
Hit me.
I will not fight back because
I want to do the right thing.
It's straight and simple, boss!
I am a common man. I get angry.
What is it that you had said?
"You've come here alive but
that's not how you'll leave.
I will cut you into pieces and parcel it."
I'll now fight with you.
I will fight with each of your men.
Fight everyone!
Fight the entire village if I have to.
Only for Meena.
Rahul!
Father, please!
Father, please.
Father!
Rahul!
I will fight.
Enough.
My body...
My...
I certainly have a big body
but your courage is bigger!
Very big.
You are like us!
You win!
Go, Meena is yours.
Meena is yours.
Rahul and Meena will get married.
He's saying that you'll look after me
for the rest of our lives.
Those who complete the ritual
are kept together by God,
for seven lives.
You love me so much?
Then we should have eloped
from Rameshwaram.
Why did you risk coming to Komban?
Confectioner?
Confectioner.
Now will you nod your head for what
I am about to ask you?
Do you love me as much as I love you?
Meena Lochini...
Will you marry me?
Will you kick me at night, mistaking me
for your father's scooter?
1635 languages
are spoken in our country.
But today I realized, that
the most important language is love!
Indeed, love has no language.
The credit of making a common man,
the hero of Komban village
goes to my grandpa.
My grandpa!
He gave me a wake up call when
I was immersing his ashes
in the waters of Rameshwaram.
One wrong train,
Chennai Express, showed me the right way.
Today Rahul will surely
tell Meenamma that...
those who truly love,
get their love.