"O beloved...!!
!!Listen to the tune of love.!!
"I've chosen you...
you choose me too."
"O beloved..."
"Listen to the tune of love."
"No girl ever takes the first step."
"She never utters a word
unless her heart's helpless."
"My heart's crossed
all limits of happiness."
"I wish to spend rest
of my life with you."
"Come weave these
dreams of love with me."
"O beloved..."
"Listen to the tune of love."
"I've chosen you...
you choose me too."
"O beloved..."
Come inside, please.
When did you two get married?
Marriage?
Well...it was winter.
People were wearing warm clothes.
Why don't you tell them if you know?
25th October, doctor.
25th October!
How long have you two been married?
4 years!
- 4 years!
When did the problem begin?
l mean...tell me from the beginning.
Doctor, this is happened 4 years ago.
l was a small kid.
- Kid? Her?
Can I talk?
l was very young.
l loved a boy called Raja Awasthi.
This man tricked
me into marrying him..
What?
Can I talk?
Can I share my view..
You talk,
Doctor, l am going to sit there.
Let me know.
See...what did l say?
This is what happens.
It's okay.
- Dr. Goswami, l am a doctor too..
..and in my professional opinion..
..my wife is suffering
from a bipolar disorder.
She has anxiety issues,
acute hysteria.
Thyroid problems.
We got all the tests
done for thyroid..
..the results were negative.
You..
Go ahead and lie...go on.
Hormonal issues.
You know,
some days she's absolutely fine.
And then suddenly she's grieving.
Some days she gets furious
over trivial matters..
..and suddenly she's fine again.
You know, if she starts quarrelling,
she can't stop.
And if she's fine...
she's fine.
See the pattern, it's like a..
- Mr. Sharma.
According to this, all the
women in the world are bipolar.
And I think,
according to your description..
..she seems absolutely fine.
Mrs. Sharma, you tell us.
Doctor, I'll tell
you from the beginning.
My name is Tanuja Trivedi.
l am a resident of Kanpur,
Virana Road.
l loved a boy.
But this man fell in love with me.
He tricked me into marrying him..
..and brought me to London.
l thought he's a successful doctor..
..but, he barely makes ends meet.
Earlier, we lived at South Hall.
Where people hang their
underwear outside their home.
He finally changed home
after I kept insisting.
We lived outside London,
in the country.
Except for 5 pigeons..
..and 3 raccoons,
l don't see a single soul out there.
Calm down, dear.
Please take this.
So...was he always like this?
He wasn't always like this.
The first year was nice.
There was love,
excitement, relationship..
We would go out,
have candle-night dinner.
Drink beer in the pub.
But slowly he started
showing his true colors.
Everything just went 'poof'.
Went where?
What?
- l mean...it disappeared.
Vanished.
- Vanished.
What should l do for excitement?
I can dance..
- You think you can dance, Manu Sharma.
Have you seen your condition?
There's no meat left on your bones.
This man's growing like a ginger.
Sprouting from all directions.
l wasn't exactly Hrithik Roshan
before we got married.
l was always like this.
- You were like this.
No personality or sense of humor.
So...you could've
married Raju Srivastav.
Look, I can give her a stable life..
..l can't crack jokes.
He can never crack jokes,
he's the ultimate boring man.
Ask him about his weekend plans,
and he'll say..
..there's a 25% discount at Tesco..
..let's go shopping.
Let's go for a stroll around the lake.
lf I ask him for a party..
..then he calls four of his friends
from llT along with their wife.
There's not much
difference between them..
..and my aunty from Rampur.
l had such a happening life in lndia..
..but he's completely
messed up my life.
What?
Messed up
- What?
lt means...destroyed.
- Destroyed.
Destroyed.
l never...even made a
cup of tea for my father.
But l washed this man's clothes.
Cooked for him.
He said, start a children's créche..
..to keep yourself busy.
l did that too.
But he still doesn't respect me.
l thought he'll change.
lt'll juice up our life.
A girl has so many dreams
when she agrees
for a love-marriage.
But l think l love him,
but I stopped liking him.
l think l love him like a mammal.
Like a Homo-sapien.
Stop this.
lt's all a lie, absurd.
lt was never a love-marriage.
We had an arranged marriage.
And why did you think l will change?
Did we meet on some bridge,
with my arms open wide?
l was formally dressed,
when l came to see her..
..along with my parents.
- That was a nice pair of clothes.
So, l did come to your house.
- Please let him speak.
We got married with
the consent of her parents.
And I am no fruit to juice-up again.
Dr. Moris, how many different
ways can one say "l Love You".
No spark! No spark!
l am a man, not a lighter.
And let me tell you about her spark.
She hit my friend Mathur's wife
on the head with a coke bottle.
People stopped visiting us.
And the Créche...
Ask her how did that shut down?
She gave alcohol to the
children to shut them up.
There was a police case.
l was nearly arrested.
And this woman flirts around
in the pub...with foreigners.
Right in front of me!
- Who else should l do it with? You?
l tried that once.
But you're just a dead body.
Why shouldn't l flirt around?
There's a 5000 year old history
of atrocities against woman.
Have l been committing atrocities
against women for 5000 years!
Will you take revenge only on me?
Men are doing it.
All men are alike.
As long as you get relationship..
- What relationship?
lt happened back in 2013.
He remembers that.
He remembers that. - Yes.
That was the only thing
worth remembering. - Calm...
Calm down.
- Please!
Please calm down!
Sorry.
Doctor, l think he's a pervert.
The way he stares at girls..
What do you mean?
- lt's like he'll devour them.
He's a lecher.
l.. l never even gave
that look to my wife.
Why would l look at
other girls like that?
When he came to Kanpur, to see me..
..he kissed me when l was asleep.
Without my consent.
Without my awareness.
Ask him...ask him.
l was descent enough to tell you that.
You didn't know..
- You were drunk like a log. - No.
You were drunk..
- Calm down.
Calm down.
Calm down. Calm down.
Please calm down.
Did you kiss me or not?
- Yes, I did! l did!
l made a big mistake.
- Calm down!
Calm down please.
l won't spare you!
Crazy girl... witch.
Relax.
- Catch her!
You're making a big mistake,
Dr. Goswami by letting this woman out.
She has ruined my life.
Now she'll ruin other lives too.
This is illegal. Leave me.
Tanu, stop them.
Leave me.
Hello.
- Tanu! Good news!
You've become an aunty.
Boy or girl?
Girl... Little girl.
And the father's right here.
He's stuffing his face.
Hello, feed me too,
l gave birth to her.
Where are you?
How's your husband?
Where's Mr. Sharma?
He's in the mental asylum.
- What?
If he behaves madly
in front of a psychiatrist..
..then they're bound
to think he's crazy.
They kept him there.
What are you saying?
l don't understand.
Where are you now?
l am in London.
- l know you're in London.
But are you okay.
l don't know.
l am thinking about
going back to Kanpur.
Place the mask over
your nose and mouth..
..and tighten by pulling the straps.
Here...go.
Poor.
Yes, come on.
Be careful,
the children might spill it.
We'll distribute
it to everyone out here.
Come.
Hello.
- Where's the pickle?
Who is it?
Tanu speaking.
Sister-in-law!
Hello.
You forgot all about
us after shifting to London.
Hold on, sister-in-law.
The network's really bad in here.
You know,
it's an auspicious day today.
And look who called.
Pappi.
- Yes.
Manu is in the mental asylum.
So please get him out.
No, no..
- What happened?
Nothing.
St. Benedict Mental Asylum..
..for Mental Illness, in Trikanham.
What? What was that?
Come again.
l'll text you the details.
But please hurry up.
lt's been 2-3 days and he doesn't
have his phone or credit card.
Oh, God!
The only son of Sharma
Family is in a mental asylum.
Please get him out as soon as you can.
Was it your sister-in-law?
- Yes.
What's wrong with you?
Speak up.
Manu...
- Manu what?
Manu what?
He's in the mental asylum.
Passengers, your attention please.
The train arriving from Delhi..
Train no. 12717..
... is arrived at plate farm no 5.
Did you get married, Deepak?
- Yes.
l even have a 5 year old daughter.
l couldn't decide on
any one for a long time.
But then father passed away.
And my elder brother
refused to support me.
l left collage because of money.
l needed someone to
look after the family.
Do you miss me?
Yes.
Not often, only sometimes.
When?
Tanu aunty is back!
Mom, dad...
Sister-in-law, Tanu is back.
Aunty is back.
Tanu aunty is back!
Sister, l'll go get the veneration platter.
- Hurry up.
This is for your girl.
- Don't embarrass me.
Keep it.
- You think l'll charge you money.
l have such sweet memories about you.
Time and age ruined everything.
Yes, l'll you, let's go in..
Let's go inside.
lt was nice meeting you, Deepak.
Bye.
See you.
Uncle.
- Bless you, dear. how are you?
Hello, uncle.
- Fine.
Papa. - I'm going to buy
vegetables from the market.
Who was that, dear?
- He was a friend.
Friend?
She has a rickshaw driver friend.
How are you, dear?
That rickshaw-puller is your friend.
How can she have a rickshaw
puller as a friend?
Be quiet.
Dear, how did you
come so suddenly?
Is everything okay?
- Yes, everything alright.
How is Manu?
He's in the mental asylum.
What?
But.. - We learnt a
wonderful dance just for you.
lt's better than Katrina.
Later.
Who's that guy?
Chintu, from Rampur.
What's he doing?
After you got married..
..brother rented out your room to him.
He's been living here
for the past 6 months..
..without paying a single penny.
He's studying law at the university.
Every time we ask him to vacate..
..he threatens us with the law.
l suggested that we shut him out.
But that idiot,
uses a ladder to climb up.
He's a fool.
But you don't get into all this, dear.
Freshen up and let's have some tea.
Son...
3 days.
l want you to vacate
the room in 3 days.
Otherwise...or l'll pass
judgment on you on Virana Road.
lf Lucknow is romantic,
Kanpur is industrial
Listen carefully.
Don't forget to applaud.
lf Lucknow is romantic,
Kanpur is industrial
Bareli is naughty
Then Rampur is witty!
l won't leave easily.
You're free to give yourjudgment.
He's a big fool.
You don't get into this.
Neetu...check the lentil.
Sister-in-law,
you picked out all the cottage cheese.
There's no cottage-cheese
left in this dish.
They finished off the cottage-cheese.
Don't force me to tell them about you.
Be quiet.
Sister-in-law, make some tea for me.
Then go sleep.
You're neither watching
the video nor letting me watch it.
You're only making this worse.
Yeah. Yeah. - Look at that.
Have you been there?
Hold on.
- Look at that.
Wait.
Hello. - Pappi.
Have you reached London?
Did you get brother
out of the mental asylum?
Sister-in-law,
the ticket cost 60,000 rupees..
..so it didn't feel right to
head to the mental asylum directly.
So I thought...
l am on the Thames right now.
Are you crazy?
Do you know what a mental asylum is?
Be quiet.
Do you know what it means?
Yes, sister-in-law.
- So get him out.
And text me as soon as you do.
- Yes.
Look at that.
l heard a lot about you, until now.
We never got a chance to meet.
You know, Tanu you're the
Batman of this neighborhood.
We only hear stories about you.
l heard there were two
grooms in your marriage.
Shots were fired too.
Such sad eyes.
Where did you get those?
How about some tea, sister?
Are you just being formal,
or do you respect me as one.
l also have a bottle.
Sign here?
- Yes, sir.
You can take him now, sir.
Thank you.
- Welcome.
The beard suits you.
What kind of clothes are you wearing?
Didn't you get the
ones with the stripes?
His humor is running.
Are you okay?
Brother, l am in love.
Thank you. Thank you.
Remember that girl in
Jassi's marriage. Komal.
She's given the nod.
Look...two crazy
guys are playing chess.
Now you have to help me get married.
After all, l am 34 years old.
l have needs too. Try to understand.
This is what makes a
man turn criminal. Understand.
Taxi!
- Stop. Stop.
Astrid Kemp, please.
l told Komal's family..
..that l am very close
to the Sharma family.
And uncle's booked a
shop for me in Greater Noida.
And he'll leave 1 million for me.
Oh my...what a beautiful house.
ls it rented?
l think l'll have to elope with Komal.
What do you say?
lf her family doesn't agree..
..then that's my last resort.
Hear my plan.
The plan is like this..
The plane will land in Delhi, okay.
And from Delhi we'll
head straight to Punjab..
Speak softly.
- Okay.
From Delhi, we'll take a bus..
..and head straight to Punjab.
Okay.
Now yourjob is to talk
to Komal's parents in Punjabi.
How? Well...like you do normally?
Hi...hello.
This way they will feel comfortable.
All well if they say yes..
..if not, l'll elope with the girl.
And then...
Shut up!
Are you crazy?
Do you see my condition!
This is what happens
to a man post-marriage.
l was in a mental asylum for 5 days.
Do you want to go there too?
Do you?
Crazy fool wants to get married.
Tanu. How much longer will you take?
Hurry up, dear.
The boy and his family
will be here soon.
Tanu. The boy and his
family will be here soon.
You should see him too.
How is Ankita looking?
Neetu, have the sweetmeats arrived.
So you're out, beloved.
Give the kids some space to walk,
he might drop the glasses.
Try these.
He's such a fool. Whenever we
have guest, he's washing his clothes.
Do you have to do that now?
- l have to.
Mister, these days hair threading
is available in Kanpur too.
You have a big patch.
There's a clinic next to the lake.
They charge 10,000
and guarantee long hair.
May be.
Tanu?
Hello.
She's our daughter. Tanu.
She recently returned from London.
London
- Yes, London.
You see, out there everything is open.
Open...you see.
So who is the boy here?
Who is the boy!
What do you do for a living?
l..
- l!
l work for a lT Firm in Hyderabad.
lT...
ldiot they all work
for an IT firm, huh!
They all work in a computer shop.
Why do you want to get married?
Have you ever had a girlfriend?
Have you ever been to a club?
Ankita, my dear little Susie.
lt's nothing.
Your life has become boring.
And for that you don't need to..
..get this 70 kilos
of burden on top of you.
You just need to break the monotony.
Do something exciting.
Anything.
Run away from home with someone.
lf you can't find someone,
then run away alone.
But do something.
Let there be light, let there be life.
She's humiliated us, let's go.
Mister..
Listen...please..
At least have a glass of water.
You're back..
Now we all suffer.
- Listen to me, brother.
Will you stop laughing?
Papa...
l want a divorce.
Go ahead if you want to.
Someday l'll get furious and.
But why?
There's nothing left
between us to talk.
We fight over every trivial thing.
She doesn't understand, neither do I.
Uncle's been drinking.
And this mental asylum
incident was just too much.
How did you land in the mental asylum?
l can't make break
bread for him at midnight.
What more can I do? I'll
keep it aside, they'll eat it cold.
Mannu.
l'm was being tortured
for the past 4 years.
Don't forget to eat.
- We will.
We all are.
Your wife won't come feed you. I am
not destined to have a daughter-in-law.
Look at me...l've been
enduring it for 40 years.
And l am sure, so is your mother.
Who will clean all the
dirty plates in the sink?
So..
- So what?
Manage it.
And then...there's this.
Sometimes with water...or with soda.
And sometimes neat.
What do you think will
happen after divorce?
Either you will spend
the rest of your life alone.
All the lights in the
rooms are switched on.
All the lights are on.
You'll get bored...with living alone.
Or...you'll get married again.
And after the second marriage..
..do you think she
will make you happy?
How can we clean
it with the lights off?
You're too much.
Son...it's the rule of life.
A man and a woman are
supposed to fall in love.
Then getting married..
..and then,
getting bored of each other.
That's right.
That's why I say...
endure it for as long as you can.
And when you give up.
What happened?
Save electricity.
l say divorce her.
You're like a closed door
and sister-in-law is like the breeze.
You two can never get along.
I told you before this
marriage will never last.
You can't temper
lentil with ajinamoto.
Look, a criminal.
Mister. Where can l get a divorce?
l'll show you.
There's Faisal.
There he is.
Faisal.
Brother Faisal has
a record of 2500 divorces.
Once he got a couple divorced
on the following day of their wedding.
Come.
Greeting, brother.
- Get going.
Sit down.
Mister, I want to
send a divorce notice.
Of course. Just say the word.
Brother..
Think about it once.
l mean...think about it once.
So...which notice should I send her?
Divorce notice orjust notice?
What?
Well, the divorce notice means..
..everything's finalized...
marriage over!
But, with just a notice
you still have some chance left.
Take my advice,
and just send her a notice.
This is just the beginning.
You're the emotional type.
You can never say "Divorce!
Divorce! Divorce!"
And you see...marriage
is an expensive game.
And divorce.
Well, you can get one
for as cheap as 250- rupees.
Name?
Hold on.
Should l call him?
- Yes.
Say sorry?
Say "Call that stupid fool".
Call that stupid fool
Here.
Here, Tanu. Have some sweets.
l cleared my final year of law.
Chintu, you didn't call me sister.
Today is a good day.
Sister...there's a letter for you.
Son, have some.
Soon l'll have your room too.
There's a letter too.
Read it out...loudly.
My dear Tanu.
l never imagined that l'll
be sending this letter to you.
But things have gone too far now.
You've crossed all limits.
But there's still time.
lf you mend your ways and apologies..
..then l am ready to forgive you.
Waiting for your call.
Yours truly, Manu.
lt's from brother-in-law.
Son, do you only speak like that,
or do you write like that too.
No, l write clearly.
Then write him a letter in red.
l am done respecting you.
ldiot!
Go.
Chintu, you became a lawyer today..
..and you also got your first case.
Come on, get your bike.
l'll show you all of Batman's legends.
"O Beloved.."
"O Beloved...l'm bored of
singing all those painful songs."
"Now there's rock-n-roll
playing in my heart."
"Beloved Move on."
"Move on. Move on. Move on."
"Move on...on...on...on.."
"Why look for another stranger?"
"Why look for another story?"
"The heart's happy wandering around."
"So why look for a place to stay."
"Why look for a place to stay."
"Beloved Move on."
"Move on. Move on. Move on."
"Move on."
"Beloved Move on."
"Move on...on...on...on.."
"Whenever l start a new world."
"l'll also find a new God."
"lf I don't find someone capable."
"Then l'll be God myself."
"Beloved Move on."
"Move on. Move on. Move on."
"O Beloved...l'm bored of
singing all those painful songs."
"Now there's rock-n-roll
playing in my heart."
"Beloved Move on."
"Move on. Move on. Move on."
"Move on."
Let me introduce you
to the villain of my story.
Chintu, do l look okay?
What happened?
Don't just stand there, come on.
After this we'll
go get something to eat
Hello
The moustache looks nice on you,
Awasthi
You've turned quite spiritual.
- Yes
l took my mind of you and into God.
Good
You should keep yourself busy
How's the doctor?
How are husbands?
Don't know.
l'll tell you by next year
Really?
So you're taking the leap too
Yes.
Finally l found a girl I like
Oh dear!
So my ship sank close to the shore
Now that I am back,
you're leaving
Well...anyway
Chintu, let's go.
- Yes
See you brother
Hey boy..
- Yes, brother?
Who are you?
Me... Shoulder!
- Who?
Shoulder
You know...the breed of boys.
We come into the picture
when girls are very sad.
Fed up of all her relations.
When you shunned her,
that doctor gave her his shoulder.
Now when the doctor shunned her,
I gave her mine.
And when I do the same,
you can offer her yours.
I'll take your leave.
Madam has places to go.
Hey...
- Yes brother?
Stay within your limits, son.
Or you'll end up hurt
You think your wife will jump out of
the phone if you keep staring at it?
Look...shall l tell
you where you went wrong?
The day sister-in-law realizes..
..she will come running
and apologies to you.
And Listen..
Have some pity on poor guys like us.
Talk to Komal's family.
Please...
Do you want me to beg?
Please..
- Fine, I'll talk to them. Sit.
You don't care at all
Sorry Pappi.
l've made you all sad.
No seriously.
There's a lecture at Delhi
University day after tomorrow.
Okay.
We'll head for Chandigarh
right after that.
Really?
- Yes.
Wonderful.
And you can fulfill your dream
of getting married. - Of course.
That's more like it.
My marriage will be an
example for your marriage.
And just watch how it's done.
You will be uncle in a year.
For instance,
there are two types ofArithmia.
The bi-cardia and the tri-cardia.
Bi-cardia, where the heart
rate is less than 60 beats per minute.
And tri-cardia where
the heart rate is..
..more than 100 beats per minute.
Both cause symptomatic
problems like these.
lts...
Very rare that you see
a phenomena, like this.
l am sure it's also very dangerous.
So..
We're very lucky to have
Dr. Radheshyam Agarwal..
..who is an expert on this subject..
..and who has agreed
to speak on my behalf.
Dr. Radheshyam Agarwal!
Dr. Agarwal, please come.
l told you about the test,
remember. Now go.
Get your physical done.
Oh God!
Any question?
Sir, which is the
more common phenomena?
Bi-cardia or tri-cardia?
Good question.
You're a good question.
Next.
Doctor, why are there more
heart-related diseases in India..
..than in any other country?
What's your name?
- Anirudh.
3rd year student.
Anirudh, good question.
But your question hurt me.
lt's paining me.
Excuse me, doctor.
- Yes, doctor.
Can you check what's happening?
- Yeah, sure,
Here?
- Here?
Doctor.
Doctor, relax.
His question..
- Doctor, relax.
Lie down.
Doctor, relax.
Doctor.
Somebody call the ambulance, please.
She will apology...
...when she will realize.
You fool...
Are you crazy?
What were you doing
with your arms spread out?
This is no place to be Shahrukh Khan.
l thought..
- What did you think?
That l am Manisha Koirala?
Come on, Dhatto.
- Coming.
Shameless...good for nothing perverts.
We'll miss our bus.
What happened?
He was standing in
the middle of the pitch.
l am injured now.
- Are you hurt?
Old fool.
Hurry up. Come on.
Put the stretcher in the ambulance.
Pappi.
Come quickly.
Come on.
Sir, relax.
Sir..
Quick quick
Come on.
Do you know what happened?
Sir..
l've been noticing that..
..the Sharma family
enjoys embarrassing me.
Listen to me.
Tanu is right here.
l'll show you.
What? Who?
Tanu.
Oh, God!
lsn't that, Tanu?
- Which one?
That boy-cut.
That's not sister-in-law Tanu.
Aren't you wearing your glasses?
Pappi, that's Tannu.
- She isn't.
What if she is?
- And what if she isn't?
Sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law. Sister-in-law. - Quiet.
How can she be Sister-in-law?
Did she go back to college?
Lovers like you cause
half the pollution in Delhi.
How can you say she's
sister-in-law Tanu?
That's someone else.
She isn't?
And will you follow
anyone who looks like her?
Go on.
Come on, let's go to lSBT.
l see no hope, nor a face.
Death is inevitable.
But why can't sleep at nights.
Very impressive Chintu!
Who's it now?
My soul mate.
Hello.
- Payal.
Where are you?
- Kanpur.
Listen...today is the
function for the kid.
Everyone's so happy.
That's a good thing.
Do you know who l met today?
Awasthi.
Raja.
He's grown a moustache now.
He looks hot.
Listen Tanu.
Don't get yourself
in these hassles.
l am telling you because
l already am in one.
Believe me, it's no use.
You feel really guilty.
Guilty? Why?
lsn't this Jassi's kid?
Yes...it's not.
l'll tell you
in detail when we meet.
Tanu, come here soon.
Or else I'll die of guilt.
You've made this really exciting.
She's Mr. Trivedi's daughter,
isn't she?
Yes.
So why are you taking her around?
She's married.
- Are you her father-in-law?
Mind your own business.
Your moustache is beautiful.
You know, perverts love
a book called Lolita.
Have you read it?
You see...a middle-aged man
keeps staring at a little girl.
She wasn't even born when
you completed your graduation.
Look, I'll lodge a
complaint with the police.
There are 1500 students here.
lf they all slap you..
Oh, God.
- Get out before she gets here.
Don't look. Don't look.
Hey come come
This is a DTC bus.
Anyone can board it.
Come on.
- Pahad Ganj bus depot.
Keep your bag on your lap.
Shut up.
lf these people find out
we're following that girl..
They will beat us black and blue.
Whistle?
You don't know what's a whistle?
Remember those toy dolls we
used to play with when we were kids.
And if you pressed that doll,
it would..
Ticket?
Staff.
- What staff?
Delhi University,
don't you see?
This is the DTC bus...
No concession to any staff.
How much?
- 10.
And how much for your windscreen?
You fool, one brick..
..and you'll lose
10,000 instead of 10.
Ticket?
Brother...if this girl finds
out we're following her..
..then she will beat us to a pulp.
You do understand that don't you?
This one...our..
It's called something
more crude in Punjabi.
l..
Ticket.
Staff!
Brother,
you didn't eat your almonds
l'll need money today.
Walk straight. Straight..
Don't look.
What are you doing?
We can pay you only 200
Don't look at her.
Okay how about 250?
How much is that for?
Look at this one
Sit carefully.
Keep your knees to yourself.
Don't look at her.
- How's your stomach?
What?
l kicked you the other day,
remember.
Yes, it's fine.
Thank you.
Mister, why do l feel
like you're following me?
No, it's not that.
Just tell me who you're following.
Me or her?
We've a bet going.
No, it's not what you think.
Stop the rickshaw.
Stop. Stop.
Loveboy.
You say you're not following me.
Get down.
- Listen to me.
You're mistaken.
l am not following you.
You look like my wife.
Listen to me..
Just listen to me..
l am a doctor.
Will you listen to me?
My wife looks..
Look..
You look like my wife.
Wait..
Look. Take a look.
Your wife does look like me.
Normally we see this in films.
I never imagined I
could have a lookalike.
She does look a bit like her.
But is she dead?
No...
Did she run away?
- No..
She left me.
We're getting divorced.
- Oh..
That's sad.
But, mister, the reality is..
Your wife looks just like me..
..but I am not your wife.
My name is Kumari Kusum Sangwan..
..and this is my friend Pinky.
We study at Ramjas CoIlege,
Delhi University.
l got admission through sport's quota.
l am a national level athlete.
District Jhajjar, 12 45 07.
And l won't give my phone number.
No, l..
l thought...
Never mind, l am sorry.
Mister...
- l want to say sorry too.
l misunderstood you.
l can't make you
happy like your wife.
But if you ever want
to taste home-made food..
..you can come see me.
l bring lunch from home.
Keep the lights on.
l'm applying medicine.
My knee's cracked-up.
Listen, its creaking.
Switch it on.
You silly man!
This is the first time
l got beaten up by a girl.
My entire personality
is completely shattered.
Stop.
Stop. Stop.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Turn around
What? What? What? What?
What?
What are you thinking?
No. Not at all.
No.
This is called extra-marital affair.
lllicit relation.
lllegal affairs
This is where it all begins.
No, no, don't laugh.
You'll remember what
l said when you're in a jam.
No, don't to the dark path.
Understand?
Don't.
This is where it all begins.
Look.. You're head
over heels for that child.
She's dancing around
because she passed.
Who is it?
- Mr. Sharma.
Here she comes.
l passed.
l had no hope,
but l passed.
This calls for a party.
Party?
Wow, we're going boating.
Mister...you should pedal too.
How am l supposed to when
you have broken my legs?
What?
There's a handle.
l'll pedal using this.
lt's a wonderful ambiance, Mr. Sharma.
- Right.
Sing a song for me.
l can't sing.
- Everyone can sing.
l can't.
- Shall I?
Of course.
- l learnt it on BBC radio.
"l might be sentimental."
"But don't get so judgmental."
"So what l am an old-school girl?
Am l singing in accent?
- Haryanvi?
No, American.
- No, not at all.
"l might be sentimental."
"But don't get so judgmental."
"So what if l'm an old-school girl."
"I am an old-school girl."
"l might be sentimental."
"But don't get so judgmental."
"So what if l'm an old-school girl."
"I am an old-school girl."
"Darling though we're
from different time-zones."
"l still can call you
any time on your telephone."
"But I really long...
for your handwritten letters."
"You.. baby those days are gone."
"I love the smell of
your palm and your ink."
"One letter from you just
makes me love your everything."
"All sweet nothings you don't write..
"..between your lines."
"My heart can hear
them every single time."
"l might be sentimental."
"But don't get so judgmental."
"So what if l'm an old-school girl."
"I am an old-school girl."
"l'll fight with the
world if it comes to that."
"Be a big girl to prove I am right."
"But every time you say goodbye."
"I swear to God.."
"I cry! l cry! l cry!"
"I cry! l cry! Boy, I cry!"
"l cry! l cry!"
"Every time you say goodbye."
"I swear to God.."
"I cry!
"l might be sentimental."
"But don't get so judgmental."
"So what if l'm an old-school girl."
"l might be sentimental."
"But don't get so judgmental."
"So what if l'm an old-school girl."
"So what if l am an old-school girl."
"I am an old-school girl."
Mister, two glasses ofjuice.
Mr. Sharma..
- Orange?
Orange?
- Yes.
Yes, orange juice.
l am scared of dogs myself.
Mr. Sharma, until now boys have been..
..either my brothers or competition.
I never had any other
kind of relation with them.
l have lot of responsibility on me.
People will say..
Dhatto went to Delhi to be famous..
..but she fell in love instead.
You see...no other girl
will ever be allowed..
..to leave Jhajjar again.
My sister-in-law has
someone in mind for me.
You were someone's husband.
Let's end this right here.
When it has no future..
..there's no point in
going through all the trouble.
Like they say..
Precaution is better than cure.
You see, I don't know myself
what's happening and why.
But l..
- See you, Mr. Sharma.
Keep them safe.
l heard gold's getting expensive.
"Every time you say goodbye."
"I swear to God.."
"I cry! l cry! l cry!"
"I cry! l cry! Boy, I cry!"
"l cry!"
For you.
Here.
She sent a divorce letter.
Manu, l'll find someone better.
lt's not too late for
you to get married again.
Hello. ls that Manoj Sharma speaking?
Yes, speaking.
This is Tanuja's Lawyer,
advocate Arun Kumar Singh.
l am sure you received the notice.
Yes.
Well, l was thinking about
giving you another piece of news.
At your wedding, there was
another horse along with yours.
So that horse is back.
You must have heard
about Raja Awasthi.
Yes, so don't forget.
So, l'm hanging up.
Mr. Trivedi.
Hold on.
Now listen to him.
Pappi.
Let's go ask him.
Him?
He's stealing electricity.
Sir.
- Sir?
Sir, what's Om Prakash
Sangwan's address?
Pocket B, 411/2...that one..
Strange, he knows it by-heart.
Yes, l am Om Prakash Sangwan.
Oh God..
What do you want?
- Let's go. Come on.
Uncle.
Uncle, here's your 6 months' rent.
Uncle, last night l was in tears..
..while thinking about you.
l realized how l've wronged you.
ln the morning,
l went straight to the bank.
Took money from my FD..
..and came straight
to you with the money.
Keep the money.
Uncle, take my advice..
..and put some money away in a FD.
You don't have a son.
AIl you have is a daughter,
who is out of control.
lf you save some money..
..at least you won't
have to wander around.
What insolence is this?
- Exactly.
If you had been strict with
your daughter at the right time..
..then she wouldn't
have been in this mess.
Gunjan Talkies is screening
Aashiqui 2, matinee show.
AIong with Raja Awasthi.
Songs are being
sung...bangles are tinkling.
"Are you listening.."
"I am crying.."
Look, Manu.
l am not against love marriage at all.
l had a love marriage too.
- I see.
And on top of it, it was inter-caste.
l also have a small daughter.
Great.
But there is a problem.
But I can't understand
what the problem is.
Normally there are problems
in a love marriage.
But...Manu, l would still say that..
..you should talk to Kusum once.
You see...if my sister's willing..
..that doesn't mean
we don't have a problem.
There's still a problem.
But only then can I tell
you what the problem is.
Manu, please talk to Kusum.
l'll be right back.
Keep the door open.
This isn't the first time
l've fallen in love, Kusum.
l was in love with someone before.
l've worn my wedding attire before,
ridden the horse before..
..and taken the nuptial
rounds with someone before.
l've laughed with someone
cried behind someone's back.
l lost trying to build a home.
And l lost so badly..
..that l strongly detest
this husband-wife relation.
But after l met you..
..I felt like I had the courage
to repeat this mistake again.
lf someone who's scared of love..
..falls in love again,
then it must be something special.
AIl l would like to say is..
l will love you, and keep you happy.
Support you in joy and sorrows.
And every time you
win a competition, Tanu..
Kusum.
See...l told you this
has happened before.
l've said these things before.
But you happened to
me for the first time.
Brother, there's an outbreak
of cholera in Delhi.
l see.
So be careful with the fritters.
And I told you...
there will be a problem.
There's always a problem
in love marriages.
See, there's a problem.
What?
Well, my missus says
that he's a divorcee..
Which you already told me.
But I don't have an objection,
but my wife does.
And secondly...
She's already chosen Kusum..
..for one of her distant brother.
He belongs from your side.
UP.
Take a look.
You might have seen him before.
What's going on here?
Stop this.
Manu Sharma,
trying to be Shahrukh Khan, huh!
"This has happened before."
l'll tell you what happened before.
He tried to snatch your wife before.
And you left this poor boy hanging.
Last time he was busy
giving justification..
..but this time he'll
shoot first and talk later.
No. Why give any justification.
He'll shoot first and get going.
What justification?
Just shoot.
Why justification?
Pappi, what are you saying?
- Pappi?
He'll be taking your pappi (kiss) now.
She's supposed to be marrying him.
l am feeling uneasy.
Pappi, brother!
You see,
women are like blending machine..
..and men are the fruit.
And for the last two weeks..
..we were hovering
around this machine.
One wrong move, and..
And that Raja Awashti.
He would've rained bullets on us.
l saved you.
Your father came
to us with the proposal.
Manu had no dearth of marriage proposals.
- Who is she yelling at in the morning?
There are plenty of them out there.
What's wrong, aunty?
We had to get you two married..
..because he was in love with you.
lt's the machine! The machine.
You've made a mess of things.
Mr. Sharma..
- This is my new coat.
l had warned you that
she isn't the right girl.
But you let her father
cloud yourjudgment.
She couldn't even abide by
the marriage for 4 years. - Who?
And look at that haircut she's got.
Look at those fangs.
What are you blabbering?
- Where are you going?
Where's Chintu?
At the next shop.
Add some small pieces catechu.
Why did you tell
papa about me and Raja?
l even told your husband.
- Why?
Why?
Why did Ranjha die?
Why did Farhad die?
Why did Romeo stab himself?
And why do millions
of girls slit their veins?
Love.
Tanu, l was in love with you.
You're crazy.
I am married.
- That's just your marital status.
But you're a still
a bachelor at heart.
And...I already sent the
divorce letter to your husband.
What?
When? - I sent it yesterday,
by Blue Dart.
l'm sure he's already received it.
lt's only the seven
nuptial rounds, Tanu.
You won't mind taking them again.
l can give my life for you.
Hey...don't touch me.
This is the problem.
One smile...and you think
the girl's crazy about you.
Was I just a bike and
one liter of petrol for you?
Only good for taking
you to Raja Awasthi.
l warned you.
lt takes 2 hours to
get to Kanpur from Lucknow.
Raja..
- And you!
You husband-wife
have made my life bad.
Quietly get on the
bike and come with me.
And you..
You're just a shrimp, understand.
You..
Don't just insult me and leave,
Raja Awasthi.
Finish me.
- Let go.
Just finish me for good.
l am a serpent.
l'll make your life miserable.
Wait...
l will kill you.
- So kill me.
Stop.
He will shoot you.
l won't spare you.
Make another betel leaf.
Your courage has filled me with zest.
You aren't over your first wife yet..
..and already locking
horns with the bull.
Bull?
l have a brother.
Not Omi, another one.
When he was just 5,
he tried to wrestle a bull.
Got his bones broken.
After he got better,
he tried to wrestle it again.
And broke his bones again.
When he got better again..
..the fool tried to
lock horns with it again.
People say my brother is crazy.
But l like my brother.
And you too.
Mr. Sharma, l've decided..
..that I'm going to
take the bull by its horns.
We'll see what happens.
You do Iove me, don't you?
No, l'll believe it when
you say it convincingly.
'Say it convincingly,
or l'm getting out of here.'
Yes, l do.
Great, then let's go to Jhajjar.
Let's go deal with my family.
Don't be afraid if they beat you up.
lf you're doing a good deed,
then don't forget me.
Komal's getting married in 3 days.
Let's go to Chandigarh.
Pappi, if it's an emergency..
..then we'll deal
with your problem first.
What now?
Pack your bags.
Let's go to ISBT.
Catch the bus to Punjab.
Yes.
Are you crazy?
You think I'm going
to booze during daytime.
Don't you see I am with a lady?
Sorry!
What happened?
Why are you getting so furious?
You see, Tanu, your doctor husband..
..is just bad news.
And he's back in my life.
And this time...l won't
let him get the best of me.
l will shoot him.
Why are you abusing him?
Tell me what happened.
Four years..
lt took me four years
to find this girl.
l didn't talk or meet her,
just said yes to marrying her.
Why?
Because...
She looked like you.
l thought if not you,
then maybe someone like you.
But your husband can't
endure that either.
He wants the original
as well as the duplicate.
What are you saying?
l don't understand.
What do you mean?
I mean he's been getting
cozy with my fiancée, in Delhi.
Who?
Manu?
- Yes.
Who told you?
- My sister.
But you don't have a sister.
- She's a distant cousin. You don't know her.
Where does she live?
- Delhi.
Where in Delhi?
Uttam Vihar.
But Manu lives in Mayur Vihar.
Maybe they met someplace else,
I don't know.
He's in love with your sister.
Not my sister, her sister-in-law.
But you said he's been
going around with your sister.
Hey Tanuja Trivedi.
Are you a RAW agent?
Just try to understand
what l am saying.
Your husband's in love again.
He's betrayed you.
He's given you the finger,
and getting married again.
And all this is ruining my life.
He cannot show me the finger.
What could be better than..
..a man settling
down at the age of 40.
Shut up!
Don't you see we're talking here?
He cannot show me the finger.
He's a small potato.
I don't care if he's
a potato or apple.
Either you return my fiancée..
..or you come back in my life.
l am a simple contractor.
l don't have much brain.
But I do know one needs
cement to join bricks.
l don't care if its
JK cement orAmbuja cement.
But this should happen at all cost,
that's all.
Mister, will you take us to Sector 16?
Here.
Manu's gone, daughter-in-law.
What do you want now?
Didn't you feel ashamed..
..when you sent him
to the mental asylum?
l don't need him.
ln fact he needs my permission.
l am still his legal wife.
l can make all of you rot in jail.
That's all there's left for you to do.
You have done everything else.
So this is where Jassi lives now?
- Yes.
Stay back.
Why?
No need to hide, let's go inside.
We're not here on a holiday.
We're here to elope with the girl.
Komal is Jassi's cousin.
lf these Sardar's find out..
..they will abuse me to death.
You.. why you..
What rubbish.
Jassi's my friend.
l'll talk to him. - Don't...No.
Now it's too late.
You already missed the deadline.
Datto.
lf you're caught
eloping with the girl..
..they will beat you up terribly.
Strangely I have faith in you.
You can do this.
You must tell her once..
..that Pappi's here for you.
- Right.
WeIl then...do you have a
picture of her on your mobile?
l do.
You see, everyone knows us.
lf we go inside,
they will never leave us alone.
You go inside and tell her..
- l get it.
Komal...your Pappi's here.
No need to worry.
He'll jump over this wall
of wealth and take you away.
See... See that.
That's a city girl.
But they will recognize her too.
She's Tanu, right.
She's Datto.
Yes, but they will think she's Tanu.
She is Datto,
so everyone will think she's Datto.
Tanu..
Ohhh...they will think she's Tanu.
Datto...
Please wear the Turban.
Datto... walk carefully.
Sister, have you
seen this girl around?
Tanu!
Manu.
Jassi. - Mannu, my buddy.
What are you doing here?
How are you?
Everyone has changed in 4 years.
You guys were crazy back then,
and you still are.
Why are you doing this?
What...what are you doing?
Sister-in-law Tanu.
Aren't you ashamed?
Why would l be ashamed?
Pappi is going crazy for you.
And you want to know
why you should be ashamed.
Pappi's here too.
- He's here for you.
Pack your bags.
He's waiting outside by the rickshaw.
Hurry up.
For me?
Tanu.
Hello.
Hi.
This frock doesn't match
with your turban and beard.
lt's all okay.
Komal's would-be
husband is from Gujarat.
Get it.
That's why..
So you're going to do the 'Dandiya'.
- Of course.
We'll do the 'Dandiya'.
And not just me, you will too.
Not me. Come on.
- No, not me.
Oh, come on.
l don't want to.
- Oh, Come on. - Jassi, listen to me.
Hold on.
- Hello.
Hand me the mic.
Listen up everyone.
My best friend Manu..
..has returned from
London's mental asylum.
And l am really happy.
Very happy.
l've a humble request, please dance.
And l swear, those who don't dance..
..tomorrow morning
your mother will die.
Come on.
There's nothing I want to tell you.
l don't love you.
How long are you going
to lie to yourself?
That's the limit.
l am not lying to you.
You're just a good friend, Pappi.
You know..
Just like whatsapp friend.
Whatsapp friend?
Then what was all that LOLs for?
LOL at 3 am...
Those big LOLs for every small jokes.
What was all that?
Listen...l took that overcrowded..
..Punjab Roadway's bus to get here.
And you're refusing me.
You...
You've lost your mind.
Listen.
Tanu, l couIdn't conceive.
My family was bothering me.
Why aren't you getting pregnant?
When will you bear a child?
When? How?
They really got on my nerves.
We met all the doctors,
got all the tests done.
And then l found out..
..that Jassi was the one.
See...Jassi was infertile.
Be a man. Be a man.
- Listen to me.
Drink it.
- Come on.
It's important.
- Drink it. What are you doing?
That was neat.
Jassi...listen.
Jassi, l am getting married again.
You manned up in a single drink.
- Yes.
You cannot betray me.
- What betrayal?
Did I ever say that l love you?
Never!
That's only because you're shy.
- Shy my foot.
l don't love you.
And anyway,
the wedding's day after tomorrow..
..and I am really happy.
You'll have to get married
over my dead body, believe me!
Fine with me, just stop following me.
Such arrogance!
I wouldn't have given you
a second Iook if l was any younger.
Two really hip girls from
my neighborhood proposed to me..
..but I refused them only for you.
Understand.
Listen..
lf you don't love me yet,
then do it now.
Have you lost your mind?
Do you have any idea..
..how much property
my husband has in Surat?
Even I've booked
a shop in Greater Noida.
l have a receipt.
So Jassi ruined all
my plans of family planning.
Then I talked to Sukanya.
What's wrong?
What?
- l need to go to the bathroom.
Fine, we're talking after a long time.
Sit down.
Do you know where l met Sukanya?
She said if your husband
cannot give you a child..
..then try artificial insemination.
So that child is artificial.
Have you lost your
mind after going to London?
The child isn't artificial.
l mean...it's science.
lt's done with injection...
and costs millions.
lt's like...test tube baby.
And so costly..
How much does kid this size cost?
The child grows in your fetus,
not the thermos.
Have you lost your mind?
Am l drunk or are you?
This new haircut suits you.
Why are you buying the
same color Mercedes again?
Why don't you change color?
What do you mean?
This one's like Tanu too.
You could've tried something else.
Like Aishwarya...Deepika...Katrina.
There are many new
ones in the market now.
But you're doing great.
My life is ruined.
Pappi!
Come in.
Pappi.
- Jassi.
Pappi, how are you?
- Great.
Have a drink?
Where were you?
Some cripple was bothering me.
Manu, there is some
cripple in the party.
Where is he?
Who?
- Pappi.
Pappi was never here, Jassi.
He was just saying..
Jassi, l think you're drunk.
Pappi isn't here.
Listen to me.
Get some rest.
Here. Drink it.
Are you there, Manu?
- Come on. Drink it.
No one knows that
this child isn't Jassi's.
They never leave her alone. Right?
No one leaves her alone..
They're always carrying
her in their arms.
Tanu..
l have to go to the bathroom.
The bathroom's this way.
Tanu, l feel really guilty.
What do l do? Should l tell them?
But if I tell him,
it will hurt his manhood.
They're such ignorant people..
..they measure their manhood
with their sperm count.
Look there..
Oh...
How did you do that?
Did you hit her here? Karate.
What else could l do?
She wasn't letting me leave.
I see. - Did she finish
packing her bags? Shall we go?
She says she doesn't love me.
Doesn't love you?
So...were you mistaken..
..or is she going back on her words.
She's the one who's denying it.
She still does.
Then let's get out of here.
l think she'll say
yes if you talk to her.
What do l say to her?
If she isn't listening
to you why will she listen to me?
No, no, l think she'll
say yes if you talk to her.
l should try talking to her once.
- Yes.
This side.
You fools, Shahrukh Khan's outside.
Come on.
What are you doing?
That's what I want to ask you...
Listen, listen...
- Now, what are you doing?
Look, I'll scream.
Your family's already
making quite a racket.
Who's going to hear you?
Listen to me.
What's your problem
with this good man?
What's so special about
that boy from Surat?
Money.
Even Pappi can earn a square meal.
He loves you.
He came this far for you.
And you don't care.
Shut up!
Fools. Run away.
She isn't listening.
Shall l show her too?
Look..
What's wrong with her?
- She's drunk.
Drunk?
Payal.
There was no Shahrukh Khan.
She tricked us..
- She fooled us.
What happened?
Payal? Payal?
Payal?
That's him. Yes, him.
This guy was sitting there.
Catch him. Don't let him go!
Pappi..
She has put on a lot of weight.
You take so long.
Right, as if you were
missing your flight.
Mr. Sharma!
- Mr. Sharma!
Let's go. Let's go.
Run.
Come on, shift to second gear.
Second.
Stupid.
Thank you.
You know, Dhatto Manju
is getting married today.
Manju, you're getting married today.
Yes.
Brother, keep sister-in-law there.
Dhatto is back.
Greetings, grandma.
- Greetings.
Where's everyone?
They're all at Manju's place. Today
is the musical ceremony at her place.
Give that to me, Mr. Sharma?
Whose dead body is that?
- Which one?
This one.
Mr. Sharma, what will my brother..
..caIl your brother's wife?
What will he call her, Pappi?
-Aunty.
She's your aunty.
And who's this man?
Will you tell anyone?
- No, l won't.
No, you will tell everyone.
- l will not. Give me 100 rupees.
He's your brother-in-law.
l got 100 rupees.
Dhatto's brought brother-in-law home.
Come here.
Sir, we did the best we could.
Call the Commissioner first.
Why do you drink so
much if you can't digest it?
Tanu?
Weren't you ashamed?
- Look, mister..
Take him away! You brought
these idiots back home with you.
You went out to be famous.
Now l'll show you.
- Show me what.
l am not your wife.
l am a state level athlete.
I'll show you instead.
l'll have you arrested.
These idiots have
polluted your mind..
Leave my hand, Dhatto.
Don't humiliate your family.
l'm not even scared of my father.
Hey take her away! - "I'm in love."
"In love with you again."
"Tell me what to do."
"What to do?"
"l'm in love."
"In love with you again."
"Tell me what to do."
"What to do?"
They're trying to burn us?
- What?
Set us on fire.
Mister..
Listen, mister.
- PT Usha...now l'll show you.
Listen..
You cannot take the law in your hands.
What are you doing?
- Hand us over to the police.
Get lost.. go get the matches.
Matches...for what?
But he did come here, didn't he?
- Yes..
You were saying that..
Stop this nonsense.
And try to understand
what l am saying.
Let's get to Kusum's
village immediateIy..
..or else we'll reach
only after the wedding.
Village? You said she lived in Delhi.
Her brother lives in Delhi.
Her entire family lives
in the Jhajjar district.
Tanu, life has already
served me many blows..
..don't humiliate me anymore.
Sir...get the car.
Your friend has nipped you badly.
Get the Pajero!
Brother, give me your matches.
How are you?
- Give me the matches.
What will you do with them?
We need to burn two people.
Move aside.
Here. Burn them.
- Burn them.
Hey..
- Wait. Let him burn them.
Give it here.
Shut up! Shut up!
What's going on here?
Have you all lost your mind?
What?
Nothing.
You could've changed first.
For 18 years,
we've been fighting over this.
This is exactly why l left home.
l quit wrestling.
l will get a small job,
live in a small home..
..but stay away from
ignorant' like you.
And keep my sister away too.
The girls world-over
are making progress.
But you...keep your daughters
tied to your courtyards.
Don't let them make any progress.
Either you kill them
before they are born.
And if she grows up,
then strangle her to death.
Weren't you ashamed of assaulting..
..a girl that carved
a niche for herself.
Speak up.
Why don't you speak?
You think beating these
girls make you a man.
She could've eloped and got married.
But her mistake was..
..she came to get permission
from idiots like you.
Omi, we aren't against it.
But there's something as community.
Right.
You all belong to the royal
families of Rajasthan, don't you?
Which is why you're so
concerned about your community.
And uncle,
do you belong to the dinosaur family?
And if your daughter
married someone else..
..we'll all go extinct.
Look, he's absolutely right.
ln fact, l would say.. - Be quiet.
The can of kerosene
is still besides us.
He's doing good, let him.
Brother Omi, please send Dhatto.
l applied henna on one hand
now l need to get my other hand done.
Go, dear. She's upstairs.
Take her along.
Everyone listen carefully.
She's my sister.
She can marry anyone she wants.
Just try and stop her.
And l'll show you what brains are for.
"Like a hot-air balloon
she's rising up."
"No one can lay a hand on her."
"The girl's shining like thunder."
"Issued in the interest
of public interest."
"Now you handle this responsibility."
"She keeps chatting...waves
her hands around."
"Never takes a backseat."
"Sweetheart...your
swagger looks beautiful."
"Sweetheart...your swagger.."
"Sweetheart...your
swagger looks beautiful."
"Sweetheart...your swagger.."
"You're pure gold,
neither silver nor copper."
"Every subject she
touches...she's a topper."
"She flies away with
her own wings proper."
"Even bhangda feels proud
if you accept its offer."
"Never listens...always stubborn."
"And the sharp wit."
"She's a double-edged sword."
"Don't know if she's coming or going."
"She's running around in the lane."
"Better be prepared."
"She jumps around."
"She leaps and pounces."
"She never looks relaxing."
"Sweetheart...your
swagger looks beautiful."
"Sweetheart...your swagger.."
"..Beautiful."
"Sweetheart...your
swagger looks beautiful."
"Sweetheart...your swagger.."
Come.
Listen don't try to stop me today.
Yeah...yeah....we'll see.
Look there.
Hey got it!
You can't stab me again and marry her.
What happened, mister?
Hey...Hanuman.
Sister-in-law...you?
Trying to sneak away.
- No, no. I...was..
Where's your brother?
Who? Manu?
l haven't met him for years.
ls he here?
Where's Komal?
- Komal who?
Komal.
- Hold on.
l saw her at the ice-cream counter.
Komal.
What?
Forgive me, brother.
By the time l got there..
..they had already kidnapped her.
Sister-in-law, it's all ruined.
Hold on.
Komal, look who's here for you.
O Doctor!
Wow, Mr. Sharma.
l turned sordid..
..but you turned completely shameless.
Don't worry.
l only came here to see your bride.
Who is the one who did
what I couldn't do in four years?
Awasthi, you said she looks like me.
Settle for reebook
instead of Reebok, right?
Mr. Sharma,
you found her to replace me?
This joker. This ignorant.
You deserve better than this.
l deserve better than this.
You should've thought
about my honor at least.
Hey girl...come to your senses.
Talk respectfully.
You're laughing at me.
What about you?
You couldn't manage your own home.
Your father raised you first and then,
Mr. Sharma took care of you.
You never even bought an
underwear with your own money.
Laughing at me.
You can see the world,
booze and buy fashionable clothes..
..with his credit card.
How can you call me ignorant?
I got admission in Delhi
University through sports quota.
l am a state level athlete.
Calling me ignorant.
And listen...I am not
over smart like you.
But I can earn a penny for my family..
..and also take care of the kids.
You cannot even earn a penny..
..and kids are not your cup of tea.
What are you staring at me for?
Aren't you going
to say something to her?
No one's going to say anything.
One has to maintain
relations to keep them.
You shut up, you...
- Tanu!
Omi, fix a date for the marriage.
Can I garland her?
Go on. Go on.
Everyone look here.
Tanu
Speak in
Hello...just because
you're in Haryana..
..you cannot speak in
this new and new feudal terms.
Okay? She's chosen
to be a woman of leisure.
What can you say?
Tell your husband
how you had your kid.
Madam...
what do you mean by how?
This is as usual.
l'll tell you the truth.
Tell her.
Speak up.
ln the hospital, where else?
What will happen to you now, dear?
Your loving father even
refuses to see your face now.
Or your mother's face.
We're ruined.
You're ruined too, Tanu.
That long-fanged witch
devoured your marriage.
And she ruined my marriage too.
ldiot.
She broke my neck.
Broke our marriages.
Bad.
This is it, Tanu.
Love, affection,
inter-caste marriage...
Bindi, bangles, the nuptial rounds,
l love you..
Just one artificial insemination,
and everything's over.
"What kind of love is this?"
What was that song we used
to sing when we were in 1st year.
Have you lost your mind, Tanu?
You aren't listening
to what I am saying.
"What is this love...this affection."
You used to sing that, right?
"Go away...O Betrayer."
"What is this love...this affection."
"You're no one's beloved."
"All your promises are fake."
"Go away...O Betrayer."
"l've seen your loyalty."
"And the unanswered prayers."
"You didn't think about my heart."
"l've seen your loyalty."
"And the unanswered prayers."
"Go away...O Betrayer."
"Why shouldn't l sigh with sorrow?"
"I miss you, what to do."
"Just tell me oh ignorant."
"Should l live or
die thinking of you."
"Just tell me oh ignorant."
"Should l live or
die thinking of you."
"Go away...O Betrayer."
"What is this love...this affection."
"You're no one's beloved."
"All your promises are fake."
"Go away...O Betrayer."
What's all this?
That Kusum humiliated me..
..and you just stood there,
and said nothing.
l was always like that, crazy.
When did you change, Mr. Sharma?
Don't you miss me?
l don't.
Will you come along without
asking any questions?
lf it's not too urgent,
can l take a bath?
What is this?
Divorce papers.
Congratulations.
l am very embarrassed for
whatever happened yesterday.
But Mr. Sharma has
done a lot of favors on me.
He handled all the
arrangements in my marriage.
lf l can help out in his marriage..
..I may be able to
repay a part of my debt.
Please!
When is the marriage?
- On the 18th..
Great, you'll be
out of here in a week.
"The horizon's empty,
where do l look for you?"
"Where are you, I can't see
you...listen to my heart calling out."
"Don't go away...Don't go."
"I yearn for you,
makes me breathless."
"My heart's lonely."
"What bond is this?
l can see it in your eyes."
"It's getting crushed
between two hearts."
"Don't ignore your heart."
"Don't go away...Don't go."
"I yearn for you,
makes me breathless."
"My heart's lonely."
"My heart's full of love."
"It's a stubborn bird."
"Expectations have clipped my wings,
but hope keeps me alive."
"Don't ignore my humble request..
- More water. - Listen.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you doing this?
l don't know.
l love you, Mr. Sharma.
I know you can't
live without me either.
You think we'll all do as you want.
And no one will say anything.
You can say anything you
want but let's go home, please.
Don't you get it, Tanuja Trivedi.
Everything is over!
lt's over.
After a point of time one gives up.
So did mine.
l can't do anything more than this.
Please, go away.
l haven't given up yet, Manoj Sharma.
l will leave only
after l see you married.
Tanu!
"Don't go away...Don't go."
"I yearn for you,
makes me breathless."
"My heart's lonely."
l warned you before.
The cold is getting worse.
And l also said..
..that she should take care,
but she didn't listen.
Now he's caught a cold.
Kusum.
Can we talk for a minute, please?
Do you stitch shrouds too?
What are you saying?
If you don't,
then get me a readymade one.
One for you and one for him.
Shut up, Pappi.
Bless you, doctor.
Getting a suit stitched again.
l haven't had one chance
of getting married..
..and he's looking
to score once again.
Are you blind?
Don't you see your wife?
Look at her condition.
She's gone crazy?
ls this why you faced
me so bravely that day?
You should've let
me marry her instead.
l loved her,
and l would've handled her too.
And that girl...Datto.
She thinks there's nothing wrong..
..if her face matches with Tanu.
This is a sin.
lt's a sin. Big sin.
He's a sinner.
He thinks she's naive and innocent.
And it's the same face he
fell in love with the first time.
So pounce on it.
The old one's run her course.
That's not it.
- That's exactly it.
l didn't tell her to
send me the divorce letter.
That was a stupid
fool boy from Rampur..
..who made all this mess.
Oh!
Forgive these two.
Manu made a mistake.
And Tanu has never done
anything right in her life.
They both are big fools.
But you're the smart one.
Everyone can see their condition.
They are so sad. You didn't
notice because you're occupied.
Husband and wife often quarrel..
- Madam.
They were husband and wife.
But they aren't any more.
And what haven't l noticed?
Are you crazy?
Didn't you notice the
love between me and Mr. Sharma?
Raja, I am sorry you
got involved in this again.
Look, if I knew that Datto...
- Forget that, doctor.
TeIl me something new.
I am shocked that I've
been nipped in the bud again.
Let's be clear about what to do next.
You tell me what we can do.
AIl the arrangements are done.
Nothing can be done now.
Why not?
Say no to this marriage
and go back with Tanu.
And you...get lost.
Come on, get lost.
No one's getting a suit stitched.
Look...I don't have
all those qualities.
Just that I always stick to my word.
That day it was Tanu,
and now with Datto.
See..
If l can't do this, then
l'll be just 80 kilos of dead meat.
Nothing more.
What are you saying? What about
the fact that you married Tanu..
..the same way.
These days he's following in the..
..footsteps of Salman
Khan on commitments.
But everything is not that simple.
Consider the entire matter first.
Whatever it was,
but they were married for 4 years,
There are 2 families involved in this.
How can Manu just marry someone..
- Look, sister..
..l am getting married tomorrow.
l am really busy.
I know you're feeling
bad about your friend.
But there's nothing I
or Mr. Sharma can do.
Mr. Sharma wants..
- Look.
lf Mr. Sharma tells me that,
l won't marry him.
Now get out.
Where are you going?
Everyone's left this guy behind.
Left him behind.
Where's mama?
She left you.
lt was a mistake, Jassi.
l didn't tell you because
l didn't want to hurt you.
Forgive me.
Mr. Sharma.
l'll be right with you.
Mr. Sharma,
Payal came to see me..
Nothing will change, Datto.
AIl these things happening
the past few days..
Tanu coming here..
..l am really sorry for that.
You must have found me unsure, and..
AIl I want to say is don't worry.
l'll be a good husband.
Then get ready and come to the dais.
Yes, just hope things
don't get in a mess later.
Let that go, dear. It'll tear.
ls it real?
- Yes, absolutely real.
We'll make a similar
one for your groom.
Get up everyone.
The groom's here.
Why are you holding that?
Come on. Climb the horse.
Can't we walk or go in a car?
What are you saying?
lt might be your second..
..but it's my sister's first marriage.
Come on, come on.
Bring the boy.
lt's alright.
Don't be scared.
Climb up.
Pappi.
Listen to me..
Give me a quarter.
What have you been drinking?
Give it to me.
Daddy, how about a drink?
- Are you crazy?
Fine, l'll have a peg.
Give me 100 rupees.
l don't have money.
What do you mean you don't?
- l don't.
Old man...what about the
6 month of rent that l paid you.
That was a year ago.
Fine, you can deduct
it from the dowry.
What dowry?
That's not it.
- What are you saying?
Uncle, everything is
ruined and you're coming now.
Why you..
No need to be scared.
l'll break your head.
- So hit me. Hit me.
Throw away the stone.
We don't know whose side we're on.
We're on the right side.
We're on the right side..
..but which is the right side?
The right thing to
do is get out of here.
How can we just leave, Awasthi?
l want to feel humiliated some more.
Come in marriage party.
The smiles of their face,
joys of the heart..
..and shame, wonder what else
your lovers have sacrificed for you.
"O beloved.."
"I did what l didn't want to,
my world's come crashing down."
"A hale and hearty,
good looking girl has gone crazy."
"I've gone crazy."
"Every morning...
in the pitch darkness."
"I ran from home."
"I ran from home only for you."
"Without a reason,
in the middle of the night."
"I woke up in the middle
of the night for you."
"Don't listen to the world,
listen to what my heart's saying.
"I've gone crazy."
"Here and there,
and everywhere."
"I've come back...back to you."
"First the world and
now the Lord itself."
"I've fallen in your love."
"l hope you won't cry when l go away."
"I've gone crazy."
"You have gone crazy."
"Yes...you have...
you have gone crazy."
"You've gone crazy."
"I've gone crazy."
Tanu!
Dear.
Greetings.
To bad with your greetings.
Aren't you ashamed
of what you're doing here?
She is your daughter-in-law.
Dear, let's go from here.
Tanu, don't be scared.
l am here.
Hey you..
Awasthi..
Abuse me, but don't hit me.
- Stop. Stop.
Who is he?
Tanu, what do you want?
l want to see Manu get married.
Don't beat me again.
Move back! Move back!
I've left a letter at
Hazratganj police station..
..stating that if l
don't return in 3 days..
..then Raja Awasthi
is responsible for my death.
Should l drink this? Should I?
You'll be charged with
sections 302 and 307..
..and rot in jail.
Move. Move.
l am here for my bride.
Your time's up.
Now garland each other.
Now they'll pour the water.
Do you want to say something,
Mr. Sharma?
This is the last round.
After this our marriage
will be finalized.
l can't do it.
l am an athlete, Mr. Sharma.
l either win or come last.
Never settle for consolation prize.
But who were you putting
up this charade for. For me?
Have you heard those
announcements in airplanes?
"Please fasten your seatbelts
before helping others."
You look after yourself and your wife.
Don't worry about me!
l didn't want a wedding like this.
Look at everyone's faces.
No one's happy. Not even me.
Thank you.
l'll send you the bill.
Just pay that.
Thank you.
Datto, will you never get married.
Tell me. - Will you
never get married again?
Datto..
Manoj Sharma, how are you getting
this girl everytime?
Why did you give birth to him?
In my next life,
l'll be born as your son.
And l swear I'll sell your home..
..and make you two
rot in the old-age home..
..or my name isn't
Advocate Arun Kumar Singh.
Lord..
Tell me.
- Shut up!
I...Rampur Session Judge,
Rajesh Kumar Singh's son..
Today in this gathering..
Who is he?
- God knows who he is.
Their marriage won't
last for two days.
They will be ruined
..you will feed on each other's flesh.
Hey boy...stop this.
Yes, sister.
Look there.
"Sweetheart...your
swagger looks beautiful."
Cannot eat.
Had some 'Dahi-vada'.
Disgusting,
"Sweetheart...your swagger.."
lf you go looking for a 3rd one,
will she be like her too?
That's enough,
all my desires are fulfilled now.
l thought there will be a 3rd time.
The other day you said
you didn't miss me at aIl.
What do you think?
Isn't this the same tie l
gifted you on your 40th birthday?
Why did you wear it today?
lt was matching.
Matching..
That means you have no sentimental
attachments no value for it.
No, I do.
- Just a matching tie with your suit.
lt's just a blue tie.
No..
So.. - lt's a tie
you gave me for 40th..
"Like a hot-air balloon
she's rising up."
"No one can lay a hand on her."
"The girl's shining like thunder."
"Issued in the interest
of public interest."
"Now you handle this responsibility."
"She keeps chatting..."
"..waves her hands around."
"Never takes a backseat."
"Sweetheart...your
swagger looks beautiful."
"Sweetheart...your swagger ..."
"Sweetheart...your
swagger looks beautiful."
"Sweetheart...your swagger..."
"Sweetheart...your
swagger looks beautiful."
"Sweetheart...your swagger..."