Years pass, but there are some days in
our lives which we just can't forget.
That was one such day.
The last day of
the "Student of the Year" competition.
Just like any other competition,
there was one winner.
But all of us lost something that day.
But the biggest loss that day
was Dean Yoginder Vasisht's.
He started this competition 25 years ago.
That was Dean Yoginder Vasisht's
last year at St. Teresa's.
After that day, he left...
and made a separate world
for himself far from everyone.
Except for our Coach, Mr. Shah,
no one else had access to this world.
But I could never forget him.
I always wondered where he was,
how he must be.
One question kept
bothering me all the time.
Did all of this happen
because of me?
And ten years later,
I got a chance to find the answer.
Hi! How are you? Of course, I remember.
Tell me.
Tell everyone? Okay.
I will tell everyone.
No, I don't need their contact numbers.
I'll get them from Facebook.
Okay. I will be there.
Haven't spoken to anyone in ten years.
I will call all of them, but...
so much has happened.
I don't think everyone will come.
Who's this... Sudo?
I was wrong. All of them are coming.
Because like me, all of them
have been searching
for the answers to their questions.
Probably, this is the last
chance for all of us...
to learn the truth.
I will call you as soon as I reach, okay?
She still has a bit of a flu.
The doctor's number is written there.
Don't forget to give her the medicines.
Okay, Mom. Bye!
- Hey, Jeet! How are you?
- Good.
- Hi, brother.
- Hey, Dimpy! How are you?
I'm fine... and you?
I'm good.
Heard you have become a big coach.
Yes, in the girls' school.
You have also become a big lawyer.
Yes. A big lawyer.
Brother, I'll be back.
Ma'am! Extension line, please.
Awkward meeting... after ten years.
Today, they are all greeting
each other and air kissing.
Ten years ago,
they wanted to kill each other.
Yes, sir. Only four of them are here.
Yes. So, are you coming?
Okay, sir. See you, soon.
He was devastated after
the prize distribution of your batch.
He felt he was responsible for each
broken relationship of every batch.
Yours was the last batch,
so he remembered you often.
Especially Rohan and Abhi.
He felt as proud of their
every achievement...
as he felt regret
for what happened with them.
He kept withering with that regret and...
I never thought I would see
Dean Vasisht in this state.
I can't believe this is
the same happy face that
welcomed us every morning
with a "Hello, boys and girls!"
Those were the days.
I wish those days could come back.
I would change so many things...
that I said, that I did.
I wanted to be
the school's head cheerleader.
I became that. But yes, I have one regret.
I wish things would have
worked out with Rohan.
Rohan... I was his biggest minion.
I mistook it for friendship.
But Rohan has only one friend.
I mean, he had.
Younger scion of Delhi's business
tycoon, Ashok Nanda.
He had taken an admission in St. Teresa's,
but wasting time was his major.
He wanted to be
the world's biggest rock star!
My dad says...
I'll make it big one day
His son will...
Make him proud
But nobody...
Knows this
One thing was sure.
The only property he would inherit from
his father was going to be the guitar.
He wasn't your big fan either.
I don't know what my best friend was
doing with him for so many years.
The only daughter of her mother
and her stepdad's fifth.
The most beautiful girl of St. Teresa's.
When they saw my beautiful eyes
All of them went crazy
Control yourself, you poor boys
You might just fall for me
Everyone knows...
That I'm number one
The world follows me
I'm ahead of everyone as I'm number one
When they saw my beautiful eyes
All of them went crazy
Control yourself, you poor boys
You might just fall for me
Unfortunately,
no designer label was selling love.
Or, Shanaya would have
bought the whole counter.
- Where were you?
- In jail.
- Shanaya, talk to your sister properly.
- She is not my sister, Mom.
She is your husband's daughter.
- Did you see my boyfriend?
- Yes... there.
I'll be back.
You do know that wine
stains are permanent, right?
Thank you for the washing-machine tip!
You'll need it.
What are you doing?
Rohan, if you don't change
your antics this term...
I will leave you.
You look sexier when you threaten me.
Like its name, it was an English school.
Built 100 years ago by the Britishers...
and run by the Deans post-independence.
The top professionals of every field
in the world were St. T's students.
It wasn't a normal school.
It was a different world.
And the most unique
specimen of that world...
The most dynamic Dean of St. Teresa's.
He looked cute, but he was scary.
The only person who could
scare him was his mother.
I'll just say that it was a posh school.
Under the rule of Dean Vasisht,
it was divided into two parts.
Tata Students and Bata Students.
Tata students would spend
money to get an admission,
while Bata students used to
swot up for the scholarship.
And then, entered Abhimanyu.
He shook the Tata students to the core
and elevated the Bata students' status.
Nobody knows where he has come from
Everyone's heart skips a beat
He is cool and wonderful
On seeing him, the girls go crazy
He is better than the rest
On seeing him, the boys also go crazy
He is tall and handsome
He casts a spell on everyone
The boy is amazing
Of all the boys, he is the most amazing
His sexy antics woo girls,
He is the most amazing
The boy is amazing
Act cool, but remember
This is temporary
Your magic will fade soon
Start counting your days
You can plead, but you can't be one of us
I am the leader and they all follow me
The boy is amazing
His sexy antics woo girls,
He is the most amazing
The boy is amazing
Of all the boys, he is the most amazing
Hey!
Hey, you! Hero!
Move your Honda or get an LIC policy.
- This is Rohan Nanda's parking spot.
- So?
It's Rohan Nanda.
Ashok Nanda is his father. He is his son.
So, why are you overacting?
Aren't you your father's son?
Shut up, you TV serial!
Enough with your drama!
Look, there's the film.
What's this, Dimpy?
Don't you get enough
money to keep watch?
Move this junk from here!
Not you, Sudo!
I was talking about this junk.
It's called a bike.
Really?
- What did you say your name was?
- I didn't say.
Hey, quiz show!
Are you going to give four options now?
Tell us your name!
- Abhimanyu.
- Abhimanyu, listen carefully!
This is my parking spot.
It'd be better if you
take this tractor's
brother back to the fields.
My car has a standard.
You are right. Your car is top-class.
Hey, are you a human or Google?
Were you a mechanic back in your village?
No, valet at a nightclub!
Let me do you a favor.
Take this and park my car.
And here, 500 rupees!
Get your bike cleaned.
Listen! Keep the change.
Where do they come from!
Village bums.
Here is your 500. Get your car cleaned.
And, listen! Keep the change.
Fights and more fights!
Boys love to fight, right?
It gives them a chance
to display their machismo.
Fighting, arguing...
all this is against St. T's rules.
In this campus, if there is any
violence allowed... it's by me!
So, now, will you please tell me...
who started this fight?
- He took my parking spot.
- Does your father own that spot?
Yes, he does. Half the school
runs with my dad's trust fund.
- You must be paying my salary as well?
- No, sir.
Exactly! That's not the case, Rohan Nanda.
You love running fast, right?
You will find yourself running as
fast out of this campus...
if you repeat this cheap
hooliganism again. Get it?
Your father, the rich and royal
Ashok Nanda is visiting.
Am I pretty?
Why are you staring at me then?
- Is our Dean like that?
- Like what?
Like the ones who prefer a shortcut
rather than a highway.
He is a Dean, not a taxi.
Come on! He used to stare
at Coach all the time.
What are you saying?
Wow! Is that your name
or the canteen's menu?
Listen! All of us scholar students
give you a grand salute.
- You shook up the ABCs as you entered.
- ABCs?
Yes. Affluent Brats and their Companions.
Look, how they are staring at you!
I'm not scared of anyone.
Hey, where are you going?
That seat is empty.
So is your pocket!
Just sit with the nerdy gang.
Stay in your limits!
I'm going to make the first move.
Want to join?
No, thanks!
New term, new dreams
and a new challenge for all of you.
I started this competition 25 years ago.
There's only one out of you,
who will win the trophy.
The only one who'll go
for higher studies...
to an International Ivy League college.
He will be sponsored
by St. T's trust fund.
Your dad looks dashing.
I can do two things right now.
One, I can share some
bookish knowledge with you.
Or, I can get real with you about life.
Because no one has made money till date
by either reading or teaching textbooks.
If that was possible, your teaching
faculty would have been here
and I would have been there...
in their place.
Teachers teach rules...
but winners make them.
If you want to play, be attentive.
The whole school is talking
about your football skills.
- Don't you want to play for the team?
- I do, sir.
So, why didn't you ask?
Borrowed things have to be returned, sir.
I want to earn it.
It's football, not lottery.
Let's see if your dribbling skills
are as sharp as your tongue.
This Abhimanyu must be shown his place.
Why? Hasn't he settled in his room?
He was showing off on the field today.
But, boss... he's good at the game.
You are also good.
There's nothing great about that.
Some games must be played off the field.
Go and get the keys for the notice board.
Just go, dude.
- Pind level.
- What is Pind level?
Used to play with the boys in the village.
Really? That's why you play rough.
Don't know about rough,
but my game is strong.
Sometimes you tend to lose
form when you focus on style, right?
Listen, you village Beckham!
Arrogance must have its boundaries.
And here, I am the only
exception to that rule.
Why? Are you the PM's son?
You can say that.
Don't worry... I will vote for your dad!
So much anger... such arrogance...
It's not good for your health.
Acting like my mother, are you?
No, father!
Your father!
After the medical.
It's written on the notice board...
in English. Read it.
- Dimpy.
- Yes?
Give this to Coach.
What's in it?
This has... my...
Your?
That thing... on the notice board. My...
Why are you blushing like a bride?
Just give it.
I'm going to Coach's
house, I'll give it to him.
This time, it's free.
Pay the next time.
Leave!
God, I'm late. He must be asleep.
- Hey!
- Dimpy, listen! Just leave this.
Listen! Munni is notorious, but not young.
Sheila is young, but not notorious.
Why, Dimpy? Why?
How do I know? I'm a boy, not FM radio.
- Just take this.
- Watch some TV.
Silly rich kids and their minions!
If I ring the bell, he will be angry.
I'll just leave it here.
"Respected sir, thank you
from the bottom of my heart
for selecting me in
the football team.
I'm sending you some holy water."
That's nice!
"Hope it purifies your home
and your family just as it has mine.
Yours, Abhimanyu Singh."
He is a sweet boy!
He has sent holy water.
Holy water? Let me sprinkle
it through the entire house.
You're so silly! My home is you.
And how can we forget our son?
My son, live long!
Here... holy water. Keep it safe.
It stinks!
What happened?
It's urine.
Is this your prank
or someone else had a hand in this?
He must have done it.
Why does he need someone else's hand?
Tell me.
Sir, I did it.
If you stop, start all over again.
Hey, listen!
Hey! Stop running and listen.
- Say it.
- I have a dance booking with Sudo.
Give me 100 bucks and I'll
say you finished your rounds.
Give me 100 bucks and I will
say you watched me run.
You will grow up to be a politician.
Did I ask for the bribe?
Now, go! Scoundrel!
Rohan always acted tough.
But he was still compassionate.
Hey, listen! I'm talking to you.
Yes, Abhimanyu. Thanks for yesterday,
but you didn't have to save us.
- I know. I didn't have to.
- Then, why did you do it?
I was trying to act great.
Wanted to know how great people feel.
You know that you are a little
crazy, right?
I am a little crazy,
but you are totally crazy.
You have heard my dad.
It would rub off, wouldn't it?
Your dad is not insane.
He's just a little crooked...
and he should be.
To reach that position,
you must be crooked.
Wow! Gandhi in your hands
and such lofty thoughts?
You'd rather have notes
with Gandhi's picture on it.
God made a mistake.
- You should have been my father's son.
- Why do you care so much about your dad?
I don't. I don't care about anyone.
You do.
You want to earn his respect,
but he doesn't...
- want to loan it to you.
- Wow!
Now, you are an expert in
the parents' philosophy as well?
Yes, I have become one... after they left.
Left? On a holiday?
Don't get emotional.
Yours are alive. Come on!
- Scoundrel! You do know you are a big...
- Yes, I know.
A big asshole, right?
Let's go! Come with me to the canteen.
It's time.
- Time for what?
- Shanaya.
This year, the head cheerleader
for the football team is...
You must be feeling terrible.
Because this position is normally given to
the most popular girl in the school?
To hold pom-pom in hands and scream
for the boys is not my style.
If they scream for me... or whistle...
This beautiful face, these tresses...
These deep eyes hide a big secret
This beautiful face, these tresses
How do I praise your creator?
So much love? So much attention?
Is everything okay with you?
Yes, everything is fine.
Or you just want to show the whole world
that you are still Shanaya
Singhania's boyfriend?
You would have made such a good boy.
God fell asleep and you were born a girl.
I think you are asleep.
That's why you can't see your competition.
Oh, so you are the new
boy in the school.
As if you didn't notice before.
Just saw you. Notice?
Don't be delusional.
Come, let's sit.
Jeet... chair!
Not for you... for Shanaya.
Don't! She's my girlfriend.
She's not my type.
I have a different plan.
Whatever your plan is...
I'm just happy that I have
a worthy rival in school.
What?
Friction, friendship, love, jealousy...
this was St. T's daily routine.
But every second weekend all
of us used to get a reality check...
when we used to go home...
into our real world.
- Do you think we'll have mid-term polls?
- There are chances.
Our stocks have just stabilized.
- If there are mid-term polls...
- Dad, I think...
Hold on!
You think?
When did you develop this new hobby?
It's our job to think in this house.
You just strum the guitar.
Hey! It was a joke.
You are also important in this family.
You will decide which band
- will play at my wedding, right?
- Enough.
Stop now!
I think it will be a year
or two before we stabilize.
Ashok Nanda is an influential man
all over India.
Don't give up on your
friendship with Rohan.
He got you into the school.
He will be of use in
the future as well.
What's that supposed to mean?
I also have a unique personality.
Shut up, you idiot!
A man is either a minion or a leader.
And you are just like your father.
A minion! You don't have
it in you to be a leader.
Shut up!
"I believe the stocks of your
husband's company have fallen."
So what if the stocks fell?
We've still got the money.
I'm pregnant.
Shanaya's father is back in the headlines.
I hope you are taking good care of her.
I'm her friend, not her security guard!
- Everything alright in school, Abhi?
- Yes, Uncle.
I needed some money
for the science project.
Of course! Mr. Richie Rich...
withdraw some money from your
Swiss bank account and give it to him?
Stop it!
I will give you the money
tomorrow, my son.
There's no salt in the food today.
I guess... it's okay.
Is Shanaya still Rohan's girlfriend?
I've got you some
push-up bras from London.
Are you wearing them?
I will win
the "Student of the Year" trophy.
Very good... but who are you?
I'm Kaizad.
Why are you massaging like a girl?
Do it harder!
I can't do it harder than this.
They say if you press certain points
in your body, it helps with the pain.
I think your wife is
troubling you at home.
She loves me a lot.
I'm a bit concerned with the captaincy
of the football team.
Between Rohan and Abhimanyu.
Well... Rohan's dad is
a childhood friend of mine.
We grew up together.
But you aren't suggesting I make
Rohan the captain because of that, right?
I don't care who the captain is.
We must defeat St. Lawrence.
They have been winning
consistently for 25 years.
And their mean Dean, Harkisan Sanan...
he has been torturing me for years now.
Hello, what's up!
Last year, when you arrived,
I felt you are the one...
who will seek revenge for all
the things done to me.
You will, won't you?
After much thought, I have decided that...
the captain of
the St. T's football team...
is Jeet Khurana.
What was my mistake, sir?
You heard me, right?
You are the captain this year.
And we must win at any cost this year!
Is that why we chose Jeet?
I would have made
a better captain than you...
Hey! There can only be
one football on the field!
Then came the day,
when a lot of things began.
And a lot of things ended.
Get ready to lose!
We have been winning for 24 years.
This year will be the silver
jubilee of kicking your ass...
Not this year, Harkisan Sanan.
My boys are fully prepared this year.
St. T's losers... what will they do...
Coach, Mr. Shah, has trained them.
The gossip says that
you have been saying...
"Coach!" a lot these days.
What do I do, Coach?
I feel butterflies in my tummy
Half time! St. Lawrence, two
and we as usual zero. Nil.
Wonder why Coach was using
such complicated language!
He just should have said, "Be Punjabi!"
The boys would have got it!
Hey, you...
- Hope you won't kiss me now.
- I won't even hug you.
We had to win.
- I was the captain, after all.
- We didn't win because of you.
- We won because of Rohan and Abhi.
- Coach was a smart man.
He made you the captain, so there's no
ego tussle between the two of them.
What ego? It was Abhi's arrogance
that came between them.
The winning goal was Abhi's,
but he deliberately let Rohan score it.
This was all Abhi's plan.
- He wanted to replace me.
- Abhi didn't want to be a minion, Jeet.
He wanted to be Rohan's friend.
Small-town boys know
how to make contacts.
Not that big-city girls are any less.
You were also Shanaya's body part.
Hanging on to her for life!
Saw your best friendship!
I'm telling you this was all Abhi's plan.
Listen, we don't know if it
was his plan or not.
All we know is that the gates
of their friendship opened that day.
This is Abhi. Abhimanyu.
- Hello, Auntie!
- Welcome, son. Dad was looking for you.
For me? Why? Is he ill?
Come on, Rohan!
Sir, just do this much for me...
- Dad, he is...
- I'll send a big suitcase to thank you.
Yes.
- Will you have something?
- No.
- Dad, this is my friend...
- Abhimanyu, right?
We are celebrating today.
Thanks to Rohan, we won the match.
Thanks to Rohan?
Really? I can't believe it.
Dad never praises anyone... especially me.
If you want praises, then learn
to earn them. Do something big.
Win the "Student of the Year" trophy
and we will talk.
You won't be happy then either, Dad.
Tell me, Abhimanyu.
Don't you want to win the trophy?
It's already mine, sir.
Just has to reach home.
This is what I like.
I'm pleased to meet you.
Tell me.
What do you want to be in life?
I want to be you, sir.
Like you, I come from a small town.
Like you, I bagged
the admission through scholarship.
I want to work in your company, so that...
I can be a bigger
business tycoon than you.
Look at some, who want
to change the world with a guitar.
I hope, some of your spirit
rubs off on Rohan.
So, he can become someone.
I don't know what I will be in life...
but I sure will be
a better Dad than you... Dad!
Let's go, Abhi!
We are all jobless
Come, join us
In our cars, rocking music plays
Let's enjoy the moments
Let's spend the evening having fun
Elders complain that we play mischief
-We friends don't care for the world
-They call us jobless
-But it doesn't matter
-Our future is bright
-They call us jobless
-But it doesn't matter
When with friends, everything is all right
Everyone sees our friendship
They call us crazy
We roam proudly
This friendship is forever
Let's drink to the heart's content
Let's check out girls
-They call us jobless
-But it doesn't matter
Our future is bright
-They call us jobless
-But it doesn't matter
When with friends, everything is all right
We're the jobless guys
Do you miss your parents?
Yes.
I also miss mine.
We'll talk about Queen Radha's story.
She says...
Breasts.
- Buttocks.
- What?
You two gentlemen, stand up! Stand up!
We get excited as our hearts thump loudly
When girls meet their eyes with ours
They kiss us, they say they miss us
They give us their hearts,
They give us their lives
We drive fast before girls
We honk and wave them goodbye
-They call us jobless
-But it doesn't matter
Our future is bright
-They call us jobless
-But it doesn't matter
When with friends, everything is all right
We are all jobless
Come, join us
Do you love Shanaya?
I'm confused.
About Shanaya?
About love.
Are you gay?
Yes. Come on! Come.
Why are you asking questions
like a talk-show host?
"Do you love Shanaya?"
We are all jobless
Come, join us
We came late last night,
so Rohan asked me to stay over.
Come, sit.
Hello, Auntie!
The maestro is practicing.
The noise that Rohan Nanda calls music.
I was going to take suggestions
from Rohan for my wedding music.
Wedding reminds me.
Ajay is getting married in Thailand.
Your coach, Dean, Shanaya,
Tanya and their parents...
everyone is coming.
Rohan didn't mention anything about it.
He hasn't been invited yet.
Let's leave. We're getting late.
Please, come. Sit! It's your house.
I'm coming for your brother's wedding.
- Mr. Nanda just invited me.
- Congratulations.
He might give you a share
in his inheritance as well.
That's what I'm aiming for.
Don't forget, Dad will come with it.
For this kind of a bank balance, I can
take Dad, Granddad and ancestors as well.
Welcome to Thailand!
Yes, Mr. Nanda.
I have been on a diet for two weeks.
Oh, I'm on a diet as well.
Really? I can see that.
- Can I tell him to...
- Yes.
No, sir.
I was asking you to take our picture.
Your picture? The light's not good!
Where's the baggage?
Baggage? Your clothes must
have fit in this handbag, right?
The boy's amazing
- Thepla?
- Oh! Good morning, Thepla!
We have met before.
No. That's not my name.
I was offering it to you.
What's the plan?
Nothing.
She is massaging your back.
Should I massage your neck?
You are fond of massages, right?
Rohan is so stressed.
I am just releasing his tension.
Why don't you open a counter?
All the Bangkok boys can come to you...
to release their tension.
You are just being clingy, now!
Why do you need to be so insecure?
I'm just chilling with friends.
What am I doing wrong?
What is wrong?
Nothing, Rohan. Nothing.
He didn't come...
but sent his minion to wipe my tears.
I'm no one's minion.
I haven't come here to wipe your tears.
Your nose is running.
You are the classy type.
Doesn't suit you.
Now that I'm here, are you going
to tell me your tragic story...
or are you just going to waste time?
I'm fed up of Rohan.
I've known him for ten years.
I have been his girlfriend for four years.
And for the last one year,
I have just been feeling
that all of this is a big mistake.
So, why don't you leave him?
I don't like breaking relationships.
Then, do something.
Get him on the right track.
How?
By taking the crooked route?
Sorry?
Krishna roams around
With the village girls
He plays and dances with them
He doesn't stop
Now...
I don't like him
The beloved holds my hand
Krishna teases me
He may have won millions of hearts
But I think he's crazy, as he says...
O Radha, your scarf
O Radha, your ring
O Radha, your naughty glance
O Radha, your earring
O Radha, the shake of your waist
The whole town is after you
O Radha, your scarf
O Radha, your ring
O Radha, your naughty glance
O Radha, your earring
O Radha, the shake of your waist
The whole town is after you
He wears a peacock crown, he steals butter
He plays the flute, he steals the hearts
If I look around, I'll find someone else
I'll give him my heart
Radha is naive
This youth won't last long
Please, someone tell Radha
She won't get a beloved
- O Radha, your scarf! O Radha, your ring!
-O Radha, your naughty glance
-O Radha, your earring
-O Radha, the shake of your waist
-The whole town is after you
O Radha, why so arrogant?
Don't throw tantrums
Do you think only you're famous here?
There are many crazy for me
The world is mine
Every story starts with me
Let it be crazy, you'll stop teasing
If I strike like lightning
Hey, there! Play the tambourine
I beckon you
Let me dance merrily
O Radha, your scarf
O Radha, your ring
O Radha, your naughty glance
O Radha, your earring
O Radha, the shake of your waist
-The whole town is after you
- What are you doing, Shanaya?
- What am I doing?
What do you mean?
You are all over me!
- I was taking your advice.
- My advice?
You said to take the crooked
route to set things straight.
Who else better to carry
out that plan than you?
Shut up! Rohan is my friend.
That's why you won't
take advantage of me.
And my work will get done.
You are being a true friend...
by saving your friend's relationship.
And who knows?
We may become friends along the way.
You are not as stupid as I thought.
What's the plan?
May I sit here?
You are so stressed.
Can I release your tension?
Feels good, right?
Yes, of course!
What are you doing?
Rohan! Come on, make noises.
To hell with the noises!
I think he has left.
You act so well! Come, let's go!
I am fair and young
I sit in the shade
Hey, why are you staring at her like that?
I have been watching you for two days.
- You said Shanaya is not your type?
- Now, she is.
- Stay away from her!
- Why?
She's my girlfriend.
Really? Since when?
You are serious?
That's the problem with you.
You are not serious.
- Do you have time to get serious?
- What do you mean?
When did you last
hold Shanaya's hand?
Hugged her?
Looked into her eyes and spoke?
Who looks into the eyes and speaks?
Listen, just drop this
cool-dude attitude of yours!
You were jealous seeing
me with Shanaya, right?
Yes.
- You died of envy, right?
- I did.
This was our plan to get
you on the right track.
- This was all a plan?
- Yes... a plan.
You won't get another girl like Shanaya.
Look at how she laughs...
she is so dramatic.
Says a fashion designer's
name after every breath.
She is arrogant... has a temper.
But she is justified.
She feels the lack of love.
So, she needs it badly.
She's not that clever...
maybe, that's why she loves you so much.
You are sweet.
To explain all this to me, you
have studied her so well.
- You are right. I'm just a big...
- Yes. A very big one.
Now, if you leave her hand,
I will hold it.
I will kill you!
But before that, I will give you a hug.
You're sure you don't like
Shanaya, right?
No... I like you...
I am fair and young
They say you should hide your
boyfriend's name in the henna design.
If he finds it,
then it's a relationship of a lifetime.
- So, should I look for it?
- Yes. Look for it.
I've stepped into your heart
I pray to God
Shanaya wasn't in Abhi's plan.
He was used to winning,
but here he had lost.
It was all because of Shanaya.
She was playing with the emotions
of both the boys.
Everyone's not like you, Tanya.
Shanaya didn't know
about Abhi's feelings.
To hell with these feelings!
It's Abhi's feelings that
ruined it all for everyone.
Everything went awry!
Everything went awry
because of the competition.
Did the competition ruin
everything? Or did we?
Just a second, I'll get a chair.
How are you, Jeet?
I'm good.
Come here.
- You look like a girl.
- Effect of motherhood.
You have also become something in life.
Effect of leaving my dad.
Really? What did the doctor say?
Come...
- How are you, brother?
- Great, how are you?
I am also great. Are you married yet?
I hated Rohan because of Shanaya.
And Rohan wasn't a serious boyfriend.
I was looking for someone else
for Shanaya.
And that day, I got the chance.
Look, Shanaya. Your boyfriend is here.
Look... I don't know what
happened over the weekend.
But I was observing Abhi.
It's because of him that
Rohan and I have come closer.
He was staring at you from afar, Shanaya.
And only a one-sided
lover stares like that.
You were also staring at him...
I mean, observing him.
Don't try to act smart.
It doesn't suit you.
I just told you what I saw.
I just wanted to thank you again...
Everything is okay, right?
Like... between us.
Everything is not okay.
Abhi... I love Rohan.
I have heard that, Shanaya.
Are you telling me
or convincing yourself?
Look, I came here to make my future.
To win the "Student of the Year" trophy.
I got distracted for a while,
but now I see my goal clearly.
No one can get in my way now.
This competition is
divided into three parts.
First... the treasure hunt.
Then, the dance competition
and finally the Triathlon.
These three segments will test
your three A's... Academics,
Arts and Athletics.
After every segment, four
contestants will be eliminated.
But before all of this
is the elimination round
which is the IQ test.
Are you studying for the test?
You?
Me?
The mind is boggled
Come on, mug it up
Bang your head to get the knowledge
Drink your coffee and beat the temperature
Whet your skills
Come on, mug it up
Climb the mountain of books
Mug up 100 times
Faster!
Let your brain run faster
Come on, mug it up
Faster!
Don't be scared
Just mug it up
Come on, mug it up
Everyone is studying.
But I am just going to do one thing. Pray!
Help me, Goddess!
I'll just be back.
It's affectionate love
You're under pressure to perform
It's an ocean which you've to cross
Only the strongest will survive
Everyone gets a chance here
Everyone has only one goal
Don't lose the opportunity
It won't knock on your door again
Come on, mug it up
Please, show me the answers.
Hail Goddess! A!
Hail Goddess! B!
Gut wrenching day!
The announcement of the Top 16.
Who's first?
Stop... you! What are you doing?
You bulldozer!
Enough, enough! He will die.
Okay, I'll spare you.
You, fatso!
Sit. Sit here and tell me...
My bum!
How did you score the first rank?
How did you?
I told you!
I just recited the Goddess's
name and ticked the answers.
All of them turned out right.
Say, Hail Goddess! Say it aloud!
- Hail Goddess!
Is your Goddess exclusive?
Sudo, you are a minority.
Very few of you are left.
Tell me, will Goddess listen to
the majority, or you?
- Now, this new system also among the Gods?
- Yes.
No, dude.
You drama queen, why are you crying?
We are all in the Top 16.
What does it matter who
wins and who loses?
Of course, it matters.
Our ambitions are big.
Your father is.
He can get you into any big university.
Here we go again.
He is after my father.
Hear me out.
Take my father and in exchange,
give me your ambitions.
If you want my ambitions, I will
give them to you happily.
The whole campus knows that
you're generous, Tanya.
But we are digressing from the topic.
We are talking about
the competition and
I think there shouldn't be any
competition among friends.
Is that why you were studying stealthily?
If we all are vying for
the same place, then
there is bound to be competition.
Does that mean to win,
you will prey on your best friend?
Yes... maybe.
Next step... the treasure hunt.
The Top 16 will be
divided into four teams.
Every team will get four different
clues one after another.
The last, winning clue will be
the same for all the teams.
The team that reaches
the last clue first...
will win this segment.
The combination for Teams
A and B was weird.
Rohan and Abhi in different teams.
Rohan and Shanaya in different teams.
Rohan and I were also in separate teams.
- Shanaya and I were in different teams.
- I was in Rohan's team.
Here are the first clues
for the four teams.
It says, "Blue sky above
and blue sky below.
To find the answer,
delve deep, gentlemen."
"Ancient smile is Ajit's beloved.
She follows you with her glance,
this mysterious lady."
What kind of a clue is this?
Who's Ajit?
Is he from the faculty?
I know only one Ajit.
The one who says, "Mona, darling!
- Where's the gold?"
- "Where's the gold?"
Ajit, Mona, smile, ancient...
It's the first clue and our
hopes have been washed away.
Washed away... water.
Will someone tell me what's happening?
"Blue sky above and blue sky below.
- To find the answer, delve deep...
- Gentlemen."
"Angels sing the song of life.
Their beloved will come from the skies."
"They will unite at 9:30.
The answer lies in a ray of sunlight."
Angels!
Angels... where will we get them?
In the canteen!
In the church!
It's just five minutes to 9,30.
"I'm a tree and yet I'm not.
If you chat, I hear you.
So beautiful am I that your
teacher loves me."
It said tree, so we are in the woods.
But I can't see any teacher here.
What are we looking for?
Teacher or tree?
We are looking for the clue.
If you have a better idea,
tell us, Shanaya.
- Just leave sister-in-law alone.
- She must be your sister-in-law, not mine!
Think... who is the teacher?
The Lord!
There is no temple in the campus.
- I think we should have one.
- Suggest it to Yogi, okay?
Okay, I will.
Yogi... he is our teacher.
"Beautiful tree, teacher loves it."
He talks to his bonsai every day.
Wait a second!
Is his mother's name Bonsai?
Shut up! Let's go!
"The answer lies in the
ray of sunlight."
Ray of sunlight...
RAY OF SUNLIGHT + ANGELS' SONGS
= HYMN BOOK
Open it!
"Last step... last mystery.
How strong is your chemistry?"
LAST STEP, LAST MYSTERY.
HOW STRONG IS YOUR CHEMISTRY?
- This is not a tree. It's a shrub!
- Give it to me!
"The first voice of Independent India.
The answer lies in a silent room."
The silent room is the library.
- Go fast, Sudo!
- That's it.
Sudo... this is blank!
I apologize on behalf
of the treasure hunt.
Guys, think about the clue!
"How strong is our chemistry?"
Hurry up, Jeetu.
I don't want to play this game anymore!
Who's going to answer
in a silent room? Books?
Shut up! What's the first
voice of Independent India?
- "Long Live motherland!"
- It said voice... not a slogan!
I think it must be Mahatma Gandhi.
I think she's right.
He went on a diet for our country.
- Fast!
- I can't say it any faster than this.
Shut up! Not Mahatma Gandhi,
it's Jawaharlal Nehru.
India's first speech was
given by Jawaharlal Nehru.
Oh, right! That's the first voice.
THE FIRST VOICE OF INDEPENDENT INDIA
+ PANDIT NEHRU = TRYST WITH DESTINY
It's written with the invisible ink.
It's visible after using ammonia.
It's visible now.
Just a second. Let me open it.
- Can you see it?
- Hang on a second!
"You must be happy that
this is the last step."
"The morning bell will help
you surmount this climb."
"Read carefully before
giving your suggestion."
"Because the above words will
decide who the victor is."
I have got a flu with this clue, man.
One moment! Morning bell...
Morning bell... our period bell.
It says bell.
There's the bell!
There's the period bell!
They are already on top.
They will get there before us!
What is he doing?
Sudo! Let's go, man!
God, please bless me.
I'll give up nonvegetarian food.
I love you, Mom.
Hey, you! It's the wrong bell!
Oh, no!
Again the wrong bell!
Rohan... again the wrong bell!
Think, think!
You are the smart one, right?
"You must be happy that
this is the last step."
"Last step... last step."
"You must be happy."
Second step... second step...
You must be happy today.
- A big asshole, right?
- A big asshole, right? Run!
After the treasure hunt,
four students have been eliminated.
And now, you guys have reached the Top 12.
The next step is the dance competition.
Please, remember!
It is important to get a date.
Meaning a partner.
Or else, you will be eliminated.
- Come, let's celebrate.
- What? Your defeat?
No. Your victory.
I'm coming to your house.
Why?
- For home-cooked food!
- They don't cook at your house?
Of course, they do.
But I'm tired of room service at home.
Okay, let's go!
The food is fab, Grandma. Fab!
Come more often, dear.
Today, I came without an invitation.
You do know that your
grandson is abnormal, right?
Did he fall somewhere when he was young?
Eat your food, will you?
Abhi! Is that how you speak to guests?
Rohan, my son! I can call you that, right?
Just wanted to say that your photographs
in the newspaper don't do justice.
You are far more charming
and handsome in real life.
Keep some butter aside
for the bread, Geeta.
Butter is expensive, Mom.
We have to make do
with the words in this house.
Rohan, we are shareholders
in your Dad's company.
I'm sorry about that, sir.
No, no! We have earned quite well.
Yes!
Abhi! Do get some tips on
the stocks and let me know.
We should also benefit
from your friendship, right?
Don't worry, Uncle.
I will benefit so much from him that...
I will leave him far behind.
Yes, of course!
Buy the Taj Mahal as well.
You don't need money to dream, do you?
Stupid people like you
and I dream, Auntie.
Abhi is a blue-chip investment.
He will not rest until
you are all millionaires.
Mark my words!
Pass me the pickle!
Felt good when you stood
up for me before Auntie.
Felt like someone my own was talking.
I never knew Mr. Nanda's
son had this talent.
A slap and a compliment both together?
Is that how they say "Thank
you" in your village?
Okay... here it is.
Why do you hide your emotions so much?
Are you a girl?
What kind of questions are these?
Matters of the heart.
No one listens at home, so I
thought I would try it on you.
Here, it's the same situation.
The ones who listened,
left me and Grandma has a hearing aid.
So, both of us are in the same situation.
So, we can talk to each other.
You... won't kiss me now, right?
I won't even hug you.
- What happened?
- Call the ambulance, fast! Grandma is...
Just call the darn ambulance!
Her pulse is low.
- Stop! Where are you going?
- Grandma...
We will take care of your grandma!
You will just bring bad
luck wherever you go!
Leave me!
This is wrong.
Are you okay?
Or do you want one more hug?
I know you are angry with me.
You just never look at me.
I don't know what I have done, but...
Can I please listen
to your sad tale later?
Grandma is not well.
That's why I came to meet.
Yes... why?
What kind of clothes have you
worn, Shanaya?
What do I do?
I don't have hospital-type clothes.
But don't worry.
I'm going shopping today.
Because I want to come here every day.
The love like a ruby,
The love like a burning sensation
The love like purity
It's more than a love
It's affectionate love
I'm in love with you
I don't know how it happened
It's affectionate love
She is also in love, but I love her more
I seemed to come out of my slumber
I've seen the sunshine
You've brought light in my life
I want to meet Grandma.
No.
Why? I'm looking right, am I not?
Yes... to go to a temple.
With all the grace,
The moon is hiding nearby me
It's affectionate love
I'm in love with you
I don't know how it happened
It's affectionate love
She is also in love, but I love her more
Just imagine this...
You are with me
And we get lost
Together
It happens and...
My heart is at peace
When I see a shooting star
I just ask for your heart
The heart yearns for more
It's affectionate love
This heart acts more naive today
The fear of losing you is more
It's affectionate love
I'm in love with you
The love like a ruby,
The love like a burning sensation
The love like purity
It's affectionate love
It's more than a love
The love like a ruby,
The love like a burning sensation
The love like purity
It's more than a love
It's affectionate love
Doctors are saying it's serious.
If something happens to you,
I will never speak to you.
Never speak with your back to a person.
Bad manners, right?
There's something... urgent.
Tell me.
After I go...
please, put my nice picture
in the drawing room.
A smiling one.
Please, don't go.
Abhi was broken after Grandma's death.
He became quiet.
He wasn't saying anything to anyone.
Rohan's room is ahead.
I've come to meet you.
To condole me?
Rohan was saying you don't
want to meet anyone.
You can't be alone...
I must get used to being alone.
Everyone who was close has left.
You should stay away as well.
Or you will die!
- You need a friend...
- We can't be friends, Shanaya!
Do you want to be my friend?
What are you doing?
Shanaya, Just go.
I don't want to meet anyone.
Go! I said, go!
But, Abhi... this won't suit you.
What are you doing...
Shut your mouth!
You showed your true class.
Came down to your true cheap self!
I should have never entertained
small people like you!
I was your best friend...
and what did you do?
You can never be close to anyone.
Never! That's why there's no one for you.
Everyone's dead.
Mom... Dad... Grandma... everyone!
If you say one more word about my mom
or dad, I will break your face!
Forget me, you couldn't be
close to your mom or dad.
You talk about class...
status. What about you?
You just waste your
father's money and time.
Father's money... father's money...
You were always after
my father's success.
That's why you became
friends with me, right?
You wanted to live my life.
That's why you wanted
to snatch my girlfriend...
Stop this nonsense
of girlfriend-boyfriend!
Shanaya has never loved you and you?
You pounce on every second girl.
You have no right to call
her your girlfriend.
Don't teach me my rights!
Shanaya is mine and only mine!
Ask her whom she belongs to.
Shanaya loves me.
What do you two know about me?
About my feelings?
Nothing!
Neither of you wants to know.
You just want to own me.
I'm not a part of the competition that...
you guys will fight and win.
- What happened, Rohan...
- Nothing.
- You are bleeding. You say it's nothing?
- It's nothing, Mom!
Nothing happened, Mom!
Dad, it's nothing.
Look at yourself!
You look like a street ruffian.
Whom did you fight with?
Answer me!
I told you I don't want to answer...
You must answer! It's my house.
I have had it with your insolence.
You don't speak properly at home.
At least, keep my prestige intact outside.
You haven't earned prestige, Dad.
You've only earned money.
The same money that supports
your lifestyle, get it?
You only know how to waste
that money and embarrass me!
What are you ashamed of, Dad?
That I'm not like you?
That I'm not your photocopy
like your elder son?
That I don't want to be
an industrialist but a musician?
Yes, I'm ashamed!
I'm ashamed that my son has
such middle-class dreams.
Dreams don't have a class, Dad.
But only a father would understand
this, not a corrupt man!
I don't want to live in your house.
And I don't want to be your son.
You have lost that right.
I was never your son, right?
No, Mom.
Not today! You've kept
quiet for so many years.
Don't say anything today as well!
I thought it was a family fight
that would be solved.
But the spoiled rich brat had reformed.
And he had decided never to look back.
I made the mistake
of being your good friend.
Now, I won't lose the chance
of being your worst enemy.
I will win
the "Student of the Year" trophy.
I will snatch your fate from you.
Watch it!
The war had begun.
Now, it wasn't enough to win.
It was important to defeat others.
Friendships, relationships...
all of it was immaterial.
We all had our eyes on one goal.
Come on, mug it up
Aren't you planning to move ahead?
Today upper body...
just upper body!
Come on, mug it up
Whom are you going to the prom with?
Abhi or Rohan?
The whole school is gossiping about me.
Forget the school.
Talk about your feelings...
I hate them both.
You love Abhimanyu.
- Rohan and I have been...
- What about Rohan and you?
It's nothing, Shanaya.
Your pair was not destined.
It was an arrangement.
You are confused.
Take some time.
Your heart will give you the right answer.
This competition in
the middle of all this...
Give it up.
Is this competition more
important than your feelings?
No, right?
No.
I'm not going to be
a part of this dance competition.
That means, I will be disqualified...
What do you think?
If I was in your place,
I would do the same.
I was thinking about you.
You are dumb,
but you have a good heart.
That's why I have decided
that this year...
on the prom night, I'm your date.
You are not a date. You are late.
Shanaya has already asked me.
And she is going to enter with me.
Yes. She is hot and you are not.
You are going to the prom with Jeet?
Yes... I suddenly thought...
why should I let Rohan
and Abhi control my life?
And why did you think that
suddenly, Shanaya?
You should be happy.
I don't understand this reaction.
You wanted me to back
out of this competition.
You wanted me to be disqualified.
So that the chances
of your winning go up.
Come on! Let's face it.
You dancing is like me being poor.
If I was in your place,
I would do the same!
No. I have just fought with Shanaya.
I'm fed up.
Why? What happened?
She says she's confused
between Rohan and you.
But she's going to prom with Jeet,
so that Rohan gets jealous.
Then, what's the confusion?
I don't want to get
caught up in all this.
Yes?
Whom are you going to prom with?
Jeet, no one's going to the prom with me.
Help me, please.
Look, Sudo.
But I can't go to the prom with you.
Not you...
but set me up with someone.
You think I run an agency?
Just go. Let me sleep.
Ge up, Sudo!
- Just get up! Up!
- What is it?
You will go with Shanaya to the prom?
- Who the hell do you think you are?
- Jeet.
I know your name, idiot!
Have you been bitten by a crazy dog?
Yes, when I was a kid.
But what has that got to do with anything?
Just go and tell Shanaya you
can't go to the prom with her.
- Come on, go...
- Hey!
I'm not your slave, okay?
And I don't need your
permission to lead my life.
You, wastrel! You have been living
on my credit card for the last two years.
And now you're trying to act smart?
So, I have given full services
for the credit card.
"Jeet, get a drink.
Jeet, park the car.
Take Shanaya here.
Take Shanaya there."
Now, I'm taking Shanaya to the prom.
Showed me your true class.
Just go.
What class are you talking about?
You have left your dad now.
The credit card is of no use to anyone.
- Get away!
- I'm not scared of you!
I'm now on my own.
I'm not your bodyguard!
You'll see...
how I win
the "Student of the Year" trophy!
You will win the trophy?
I'd like to see that!
If you want...
I will go to the prom with you.
No one wanted to go to the prom with me.
And finally my hand was held...
I'll forget the entire world
I'll dance with you
Come and talk to me
Let's create a saga
We're crazy about disco
The night is intoxicating
Give me your hand
Let's sing and dance
We're crazy about disco
I have my eyes on you
Let our eyes do the talking
Come and embrace me
That's how the nights begin
These talks happen in moments like these
And that's how you get
To meet the entire world
We're crazy about disco
The night is intoxicating
Give me your hand
Let's sing and dance
We're crazy about disco
This is a game of night
Play it for a while
Dance while embracing me
With just my gaze,
I'll make you understand
The night still remains
Make me lose my senses
Dance like there's no tomorrow
Move like you are intoxicated
Party like crazy
Say what you want
It's easy to make excuses
We're crazy about disco
The night is intoxicating
Give me your hand
Let's sing and dance
It's affectionate love
The love like a ruby,
The love like a burning sensation
The love like purity
It's affectionate love
It's more than a love
After the dance competition,
four students out of the 12
have been eliminated.
Now, these eight finalists
will fight in the triathlon.
Hi, Abhi. How are you?
Abhi and Rohan both
are in the top eight.
The competition is tough.
You will say that.
Rohan is your son, after all.
That's why...
I say the victory is Abhi's.
Get 100% ready
Go and win it
You can do this
There's only one solution
To your problem
Come on, push
Harder!
Oh, no!
Come on, push
We are on the last leg of the competition.
This is a unique combination
of swimming, cycling and running.
The last eight finalists
will participate in it.
Every student of St. T's dreams of winning
the "Student of the Year" trophy.
There have been many exemplary students...
who have won this in 25 years.
I don't mean to insult anyone,
but I can't accept this trophy.
I have my own reasons.
When you should clap,
why aren't you guys clapping?
This kind of unruly behavior...
won't be tolerated in this school.
Get him out of here!
This "Student of the Year"
is your idea, right?
Then, you should get the award.
Take the award...
for the most stupid idea.
Why? Because you didn't win?
Just look at yourself!
Yes... I lost. But why did I lose?
Because of you.
Because of your dumb rules.
Make the girls and the boys race together.
Get a partner to the prom.
Dance and win a trophy.
But who cares about us who can't dance!
Who cares that people like us
don't get partners, Dean?
Just let me speak!
This charade has been
going on for 25 years.
And why? Because Dean Yoginder Vasisht
has no entertainment in his life.
He is alone and so, he wants
to break our friendships.
Your final episode is a hit!
The friendships that were built over two
years have been finished in two weeks!
We hate each other!
I thought you would call
me, when you had a baby.
So much ego?
Not ego... shame.
What was the use of all that?
Forget all that and show
me the baby's picture.
What's her name?
I can't afford that name.
You haven't changed, have you?
Listen...
how's Tanya doing?
She's hunting for a new husband.
Keep Abhi away from her.
I have to keep Abhi
away from someone else.
Right!
It's a hospital.
Can't have them trashing it.
I'll just be back.
You didn't invite me for the wedding.
I would have come...
from the bride's side. It's my right.
Why this intense look?
There must always be pain
on a musician's face.
Or else CDs don't sell.
I have listened to your songs.
Abhi lets you do that?
I listen to them stealthily.
Okay, come and meet Abhi.
You married him and still
exercising your right on me?
It has been ten years.
Can't you just say a hello?
He sings loudly on stage.
He can also say hello!
You are an investment banker,
not a nine-year-old.
And you are my wife...
not your ex boyfriend's lawyer.
I saw you hugging him.
Feeling the love for him, are you?
What else did you expect?
His bank account may
have crores, but class...
is still not affordable for him.
What did you achieve with your high class?
You just strum strings on stage.
But I hug nicely.
Bastard, mind your tongue!
She is my wife.
When you kissed her that
day, she was my girlfriend.
Stop them!
Wait a minute! These are
the pent-up feelings of ten years.
Don't stop them.
Why such rage? Why so much anger?
Can't be because of Shanaya.
You never loved her.
Then, why this anger? Why?
You lost on purpose that day.
On purpose!
This question has been
bugging me for ten years.
Why did you do it? Tell me, why?
Because your father was a rogue!
He looked happy, when he saw you losing.
I wanted to be like him,
but I'm not that bad.
In that moment, I realized I could defeat
India's most influential man
by making you win.
So, I did it.
My dad had died, Rohan...
but yours wasn't alive either.
I destroyed my father when I left home.
I didn't need your greatness.
Greatness? And what about
your greatness on stage?
You made a great sacrifice
and you left, right?
If you knew all this,
why didn't you say it that day?
Because you wanted to show
your father that you won.
Whom did you call a loser?
My last five albums have
been platinum hits.
So? My company's turnover is 500 crores!
Top international music
labels run after me!
Top multinationals beg me for mergers.
When I perform, the whole
of Wembley trembles.
stock market shakes.
- I have done 100 girls...
- And I have...
100?
Almost 100.
Almost?
I guess.
You haven't changed.
You're still a big...
A big asshole, right?
I remember.
You won't kiss me, right?
I won't even hug you.
- Drama queen!
- I am.
Look how popular I am!
I was a dean for 25 years and...
today about seven students
have come to meet me.
I suppose, it's my fault.
I couldn't handle my relationships.
So, got busy breaking others'.
Everyone has friends...
but school and college
friends are different.
They understand us like our parents do.
They know us.
Friction, envy, competition...
no matter what it goes through,
it never clouds the heart!
We have a chance after ten years.
Now, this friendship will not break.
Just one business was unfinished.
- A big asshole, right?
Run!