You need to be a little careful.
The law will be
enforced any day now...
l am not selling my property,
Majumdar
Then form a Trust.
Even that takes time.
All the other landlords are doing it.
Pakhi...
Where were you lost?
How long have you been up?
l have been up for ten minutes,
but you were staring into space,
moving the fan like a statue.
How are you feeling now?
l am feeling fine, thank you.
Did it hurt?
Did l ever tell you
the Bheel Raja story?
No
A long time ago, there lived the...
mighty Raja of the Bheel tribe.
Very powerful.
No one could ever harm him.
Everyone was afraid of him.
The English made many
attempts on his life.
They cut him with swords,
they slit him with a thousand arrows,
but he just wouldn't die.
Then they heard that the Raja...
confined his 'life' in a parrot.
But there were a thousand
parrots in the forest.
Which one would it be?
Then they sent a spy.
A beautiful one.
The Raja fell in love with her.
Married her.
One fine day she found 'the' parrot.
She got hold of it and...
Then?
Then he died.
Pakhi, you are my that parrot.
lf anything happens to you...
You know,
finally Manikpur has electricity.
l see. And how long
is it going to stay?
What?
Stick to the left side.
Slowly.
We don't want to have an accident.
lf we get into an accident
then you were driving.
lf not then l was driving.
Watch out!
Watch out.
Pakhi.
You will get me fired.
Watch out
That motor...
What are you doing?
Shh...
Doctor Uncle
Pakhi, you can go home.
He's alright. He'll be okay.
Ok
Move.
Why?
You almost killed
the poor motorcyclist.
You don't know how to drive.
Me?
Then who? Me?
Come.
''The springs came and went.''
''But l didn't experience
a single one.''
''My heart was drenched this time.''
''l wonder what you did?''
What's wrong?
The filament got damaged.
Filament?
The thing that lights up.
lsn't that electricity?
The electricity lights the filament,
the filament lights up the bulb.
Oh, yes. l knew that.
So whatever it is,
lnstall it everywhere.
And give the bills to Majumdar.
You aren't being serious.
lf the Zamindari
Abolishment Act is passed..
..you will be left with nothing.
The Act won't be passed, Majumdar.
lt will.
There aren't any landlords
in government who will support you.
Why do our fathers keep arguing?
My father feels that Zamindar
uncle doesn't understand him
and Zamindar uncle feels
that my father keeps yakking.
l see. Yakking?
Yes?
My name is Varun Srivastava
Where have you come from?
You stay here.
Babu, someone has come from Delhi.
From where?
Some 'English' place.
He is an archeologist.
Wants to excavate our temple site
He thinks there is an ancient
civilization buried underneath.
So?
He's coming home for dinner tonight
Ask him yourself.
Varun Shrivastava.
Yes?
Don't look back
The driver who drove into you,
his name is Babu Singh.
Ok.
And what is your name?
Don't try to be smart,
because you are not.
Ok.
Which one are you?
Mr. Srivastava
Yes?
You are very punctual
This is my daughter, Pakhi
And Pakhi, he is that
gentleman l told you about.
Hello.
She wants to be a writer
She's not bad.
She has written her
name on all my books.
Baba, l am good.
l am sure
So, Archaeologists.
l always thought they were old men.
Busy amidst the cobwebs
of archaic buildings.
l guess that's why the
name starts with 'Archaic'
Of course.
Where are you staying?
At the Circuit House.
Nearby the temple.
What happened to your head?
My motorcycle had
an accident with a car.
ln Manekpur?
Yes.
Who was driving?
l was driving.
lf you drive both of
them at the same time...
l was driving the motorcycle.
Of course.
Coffee?
Yes
And some bad amateur
was driving the car.
Couldn't spot a motorcycle
on such a wide road
l don't think these amateurs
should be allowed...
Sorry. l'll get some cold water.
Sorry about that
Even the villagers here are
quite used to her driving lessons.
But...
For days together,
the kitchen remained silent
the blind dog slept hungry
For days together the
lizards crawled on the walls.
For days together, even
the rats were brought to the brink
Food came home, after days together
Smoke filled the courtyard
after days together
Rooms sparkled again,
The crow spread his wings,
after days together
Baba Nagarjuna.
Real name Vaidyanath Mishra
Lives in Darbhanga,
my native village.
Where did you say, you are staying?
l'm impressed, Varun Babu.
This mansion instead
of that guest house.
Are you understanding anything,
Debdas Mukherjee?
l can understand everything.
My parents talk exactly like this.
Learn Bengali
You'll have to learn one day
Have you seen Baazi?
No
You should watch it.
Now that's what you call a movie.
Dev Anand plays a gambler.
And a moment comes
when he has to choose.
a hell lot of money
or his sister's life.
Or he has to quit everything,
for his love.
He's an amazing actor.
And an even better fighter.
You want to see how he fights?
Like this, while swaying...
No matter how many goons attack him
they will not spoil his hairstyle.
''Why are you scared of the world?''
This temple's 500 years old.
Nobody is allowed to build
or demolish anything here.
This famous Radha-Krishna..
..idol is the legacy
of my Roy Chouhdry ancestry.
lt's at least three
hundred years old.
This...
This is where we start excavating.
And we can put up the camp here.
We would need some labourers.
Definitely
So this is where we dig
Do what?
Digging
Good
Now, do you guys know how to dig?
Sir.
What have we got all this for?
Very good
But why are we going to dig?
Well...because this is land and...
''Try your luck.''
Pull more.
Go further back
''So what if the oars
of your boat are broken.''
''Use your arms as the oars.''
''lf you trust yourself,
try your luck.''
''Try your luck.''
''Take a chance and mend your fate.''
''lf you trust yourself,
try your luck.''
''Try your luck.''
News from the capital.
ln a historic decision
today the government of lndia..
..announced the
Zamindari Abolition Act.
One of the prominent
lawyers from the High Court..
..Mr. Rao added that
according to this Act...
the Landlords will be allowed no more
than fifteen acres for themselves.
Many landlords from
Uttar Pradesh and Bengal..
Will they seize the orchard?
Yes.
what will they do with it?
Divide it amongst the villagers...
Free fruits for all.
My stomach is growling.
No one eats before
the first fish is caught.
Tradition, you see.
Of course. - Of course.
Varun Babu.
You are looking in the
wrong direction, Varun babu.
Are you mad?
l was just looking.
l saw how you were 'looking'
How was l looking?
lt's that 'look'
Things happen.
Nothing happens
your hunger has gone to the brain.
Why are you getting upset?
l am just adding to the stuff
you are already cooking up...
l am not cooking up anything.
You are not cut out
for this painting stuff?
Neither are you Raja, nor Ravi Varma.
You carry that blank
canvas everywhere.
But you never put any paint on it.
My dear friend, Debdas
One day l will paint my masterpiece.
And the world will watch.
l want to learn painting.
Why the sudden interest?
lts not sudden.
l've always been interested.
You keep talking about.
l've always told you,
l wanted to learn
You never told me.
l did You never listen to me.
Fine. Ask Majumdar Babu,
he'll get someone
Ask Devyani also
Devyani only wants to cook.
And there's no need
to look for anyone.
Varun Babu is a great painter
Finish your tea.
How do l look?
Very beautiful. Now go.
Now what?
Just go
Have you tried to paint before?
l mean, when you used
to study in Shantiniketan.
You know that l used
to study in Shantiniketan?
No. As in since you
are the Zamindar's daughter.
l learnt a little.
So what do you want
to learn from me?
You tell me.
Lets begin with landscapes.
They are easy to grasp.
Then once you get a hang of it...
No. After mangoes and apples,
the first thing they
taught us was Landscapes.
Can't we learn portraits?
You don't think l know
how to paint a landscape?
Shall l show you?
You know how to paint.
l don't know how to paint leaves.
Leaves!
They are really easy
Show me.
Sure
Take some green
Take some black
What is this?
Leaves
This?
lts Modern Art.
You don't know how to paint, do you?
So you are a teacher to him?
For the class to run,
someone has to be a teacher
Someone is too smart
for his own good.
l always wanted to learn painting.
And this is a good opportunity. No?
Of course.
''The breeze is against the ambiance.''
''Because the bees stole
the nectar from the buds.''
''Life feels different today.''
''So, why don't l
take this chance and..''
''Mend the condition of my heart.''
''The breeze is against the ambiance.''
''Because the bees stole
the nectar from the buds.''
''Life feels different today.''
''So, why don't l
take this chance and..''
''Mend the condition of my heart.''
''The courtyard's filled
with a new ray of light.''
''Who's knocking on my heart?''
''How can l say..''
''..who's been doing
mischief secretly?''
''Mend the condition of my heart.''
''The breeze is against the ambiance.''
''Because the bees stole
the nectar from the buds.''
''Life feels different today.''
''So, why don't l
take this chance and..''
My father calls me Pakhi Express
Because l'm always in a hurry
What do you want to do?
l want to write.
Lots and lots of books.
Sometimes, l feel like running away
to our house in Dalhousie.
And just keep writing there.
While the snow keeps falling outside,
lnside l keep writing...
- Writing and more writing..
The Raja there has a big palace.
Jandhrighat palace.
That Raja is very rich.
Much more than my father.
And he also has an ancient
unique Ganesha idol
ls it?
Made of pure gold.
At least five hundred years old.
Do you like what you do?
This is all l know.
l've never known
anything other than this.
lf you get a chance
to do something else,
What would you do?
Tell me...
l want to see Chandratal
before l die.
Where is that?
Beyond Manali.
Deep in the Himalayas
Clear blue waters,
And not a sound.
None at all?
No
And?
l want to paint a masterpiece
that the world will remember.
Really?
Yes. Don't tell anyone.
And if l tell?
lt's a flat tyre.
Will take sometime.
What happened?
Pakhi?
Why didn't you tell me?
''Flying away on paper wings''
''lt's heading where it shouldn't.''
''lt can't understand
the delicate heart.''
''Because it's under an illusion.''
''Doesn't see,
think, or know...restrictions.''
''Lost its way,
what a fool the heart is.''
''Flying away on paper wings''
''lt's heading where it shouldn't.''
Pakhi is a good girl.
''Because it's under an illusion.''
And you will have to break her heart
''Doesn't see,
think, or know...restrictions.''
''Lost its way,
what a fool the heart is.''
She will be shattered when you leave.
''Lost its way,
what a fool the heart is.''
And if l say that l love her?
You aren't allowed to love,
Mr. Srivastava
lf you want to love,
you need permission.
And that stone-hearted
uncle won't give it to you.
''lt can conquer all forts,
break through walls.''
''Love's a beautiful thing.''
''lt tosses the heart
around now and then.''
''The heart feels more like a ball.''
''lt accepts every
grief with a smile.''
''Because it's under an illusion.''
''Doesn't see,
think, or know...restrictions.''
''Lost its way,
what a fool the heart is.''
Start digging in the
opposite direction first.
Start here first
Madam
Let's go.
Varun Babu
No class today?
Yes. Our work is about to finish.
There isn't enough time.
We can learn here also.
No. Not here.
No problem.
Tomorrow?
No.
The day after tomorrow?
The day after that?
Next week?
l leave next week.
There's a lot of pending work here.
Everyone's waiting for me.
So am l
lt would be better if you leave.
lt would be best, if you die
They can dig two
feet more by morning.
That's not great,
when will the other work happen?
Why are you doing this to me?
Come on get back to work.
What's the matter with you today?
With me? What's the matter with you?
Why are you doing this to me?
lt's like you don't want to see me.
Like l'm nothing to you.
Do l mean anything to you?
l leave next Tuesday.
And, the time that
we spent together?
You wanted to learn painting
And you didn't know how to!
Why did you agree?
You could have said No then.
l was stupid.
Do you love me, Varun Babu?
Please say yes.
Don't think so much.
you did the right thing.
No need to be my guardian angel.
Eat your food
Uncle sent a telegram asking
why is it taking so much time?
Hello.
Biswajeet Roy, Treasury Department.
What department is this?
There is an official
seal on the letter.
This is ..
The East lndia Company
gifted that to my grandfather.
lt's at least two hundred years old.
Even more
Pal Babu - Yes.
Put all of these into our van
What are you doing?
All of this is lndia's heritage
lt will go to the National Treasury
and then maybe to the Museum.
This is my family heritage.
You can't take it.
Whatever the East lndia
Company gave you was not theirs.
lt was all stolen.
lf you wont co-operate,
then we will have to arrest you.
Arrest me?
ln Manekpur? ln my own village?
Pardon me
l'm a government servant not yours.
Goodbye.
The world has changed Varun Babu
lt's improved for you.
and ended for us.
l was so used to this way of life.
that even after you
and Majumdar warned me
l didn't think l
would lose everything
The country got free
from British yoke...
but that freedom cost us dearly.
You still own a lot of
assets that are very valuable.
There are a lot of buyers out there
l can help you?
The government wants to destroy us.
They think we were
friends with the English
But our hands were tied
We gave money to
the lndian National Army
Was it our fault if the Government
didn't accept their fight to freedom?
Varun Babu...
Call them.
Sell everything.
Get up.
Put that away
Did you hit me?
The Zamindar is ready to sell
lnform uncle
Once the labourers leave tomorrow,
we will start digging
in this direction
All this mud can
be removed and put here
We have to finish
this in three nights
lts the first car
l owned Very dear to me
Hope you take good care of her
l will.
Thank you.
Moves certainly. - lt's a lovely car.
Meet my friend, Varun Srivastava
Mr. Mukherjee
Hi. - Pleasure.
He's bought my car.
Can Deb go with him?
To Calcutta?
Yes today itself
Ask him, l have no problem
Zamindar Babu,
l'll also be leaving
in a couple of days
The month is up? So soon?
Our work is done
we didn't find anything
All the best
Thank you
Don't go.
Zamindar Babu, l really love Pakhi
l want to marry your daughter
What does your father do?
My parents are dead
l don't even remember them
l have an uncle
He raised me.
Taught me everything l know
Call him here
What happened?
He wont come
Why not?
He won't allow it
Won't allow what?
Zamindar Babu, we will get
married and go some place else.
l really love your daughter
l'll make sure she stays happy always
l would give my life for her
Please write... - Yes.
'Zamindar Soumitra Ray Chaudhry
cordially invites you to the...
Pakhi Ray Chaudhry
with Varun Srivastava.
engagement of his beloved daughter...
Done?
Yes
- Mr. Roy Choudhry? - Mr. Bajpai.
How was the journey?
Good. Thank you
Some kind of celebration going on?
My daughter is getting engaged
Congratulations
You're getting married to Pakhi?
Yes.
And what will you tell Bajpai Uncle?
l don't know
So why are you doing all this?
Do you want to completely ruin her?
What are you hiding from me?
Nothing
There is something
Where is the engagement?
At the temple
When?
Tomorrow
Tomorrow?
And our work?
lts your work now. Get it done.
No, its our work
Bajpai Uncle
Congratulations Varun
Heard
Bye.
Don't bite the hand that feeds you
Uncle, l have to get married sometime
l never got married
How would l have taken
care of you boys, if l had?
l know What you did for us
Taught us everything
l did everything you asked me to
l never asked you anything.
Does she know what
you do for a living?
Why you're here?
Suraj was killed
He was trying to escape
He had two daughters And a son
You know that
This is the life we live
ls this what you want to give her?
l want you in Calcutta tomorrow
We cant afford the luxury
of relationships in our work
You still tried
Don't think l cant tell your
father-in-law what you really are
Good morning gentlemen
Happy?
Congratulations, lets go
Fake, they're all fake
Not a single original note
Dinner is ready
Should l go home?
Yes
Do you need anything else?
No
Ms Pakhi
You know Varun better than anyone
lf you won't help then it is
difficult to nab their whole gang.
What happened in Manikpur,
has happened many times before
This gang has robbed millions
from Zamindars and Rajas
Many families have been ruined
Your father wasn't the
only one who died because of them
My father didn't die
because he was robbed
He was heartbroken
Deceived him.
He trusted Varun.
lf he were alive?
He would want Varun to pay, isn't it?
l don't want revenge, Mr. Singh
l just want to forget him
Ok
lf you need anything or...
if you feel like sharing something,
You can contact me on this number.
''My heart's thinking about you,
where are you?''
What are you writing?
''l'm right here..''
Some story?
Yes
What story?
lt's just a story
ls there a boy in the story?
And a girl?
Yes
Do they love each other?
No
Are they going to fall in love?
l don't know
The boy wants to know something
The girl isn't talking to him
ls she angry?
Yes
Because he's leaving?
Because he's asking
too many questions
So what is she saying?
Don't ask so many questions
So?
Has he stopped asking questions?
He's a fool
Doesn't even understand a thing
Has the boy told the
girl how beautiful she is?
That there's nobody more beautiful
than her in the whole world.
No
Has the girl told the boy
that she loves him the most?
No
So when is she going to tell him?
When?
Dalhousie police station
Can l talk to lnspector K N Singh?
Who's speaking?
Pakhi Ray Chowdhury
Hold please.
KN Singh speaking
He had once told me
that the Raja of Jandhrighat
owns a valuable idol of Ganesha.
Made of pure gold
Maybe their next target
will be in Dalhousie.
Thank you
Ok
Guesthouse available on rent
lt's tuberculosis
lt's life threatening
You should move to a warm place
You will live longer
Everyone dies some day
What should l live for?
You could write another book
My life is being taken
by what l am writing
Did l ever tell you
the Bheel Raja story?
No
A long time ago, there lived the...
mighty Raja of the Bheel tribe.
No one could ever harm him.
The English made many
attempts on his life.
They cut him with swords,
they slit him with a thousand arrows,
but he just wouldn't die.
Then they heard that the Raja...
confined his life in a parrot.
But there were a thousand
parrots in the forest.
Which one would it be?
One fine day the
spy found the parrot
where the Raja's life was confined
There's two men at the gate
For the guesthouse
What should l do?
Show it to them
Who stays out there?
The Lady of the house.
She is not keeping well.
Please come.
Hello - Ms Pakhi,
this is lnspector K N Singh
Yes
l called to inform you that
the gang leader has been arrested
He's confessed that Varun and Debdas
should be reaching
Dalhousie any day now.
We have booked all the
places where they can stay
They will eventually
reach your cottage
As soon as they do...
Excuse me, Mr. Vijay?
What happened?
How do you plan to ship
the idol to the Museum?
By truck
lt's on its way from Delhi
And security?
Six of our people
will accompany the truck
And if you wish,
you can send some people too
So how can l help?
We need to take measurements
of the idol for the shipping crate
So if you don't mind,
could we start work tomorrow?
That's it?
We can stay here if you'd like
Come tomorrow
l'll inform everyone here
that you'll be coming from tomorrow.
K N Singh speaking
This is Devender Singh - Yes.
lt's them
Thank you
How many men do you have?
Twelve. - Do they all have weapons?
We have 303.
l want them all, immediately. - Okay.
Bajrangi, get them ready
He's not answering the phone
Must be asleep
Listen...
Give me a cigarette
We're being followed
You go left, l'll go right
Ok
See you here in fifteen minutes
Follow him
Come with me
Get up! Follow him
Stop or else l'll shoot you Varun
Shoot
Have you given him any medicine yet?
Not yet Doctor
How far is it from here?
Five minutes
ls he breathing okay?
Mr. Singh?
He's been shot
Won't be able to get very far
He's in town and he's wounded
Spread the word
Put up his sketch everywhere
Yes, sir!
l want this man
Keep looking till you find him
Dead or Alive?
You told the police!!
My friend died because of you
l won't let you die so easy
l didn't think you
had any emotion in you
You still don't know a lot, Pakhi.
Please leave, Varun
l need a place to hide
You wont get it here
Leave or l'll call the police
You won't
Close the door, Shyama
Are you mad, Varun?
Did the police stop you?
Did they ask you any questions?
About me? - No
Don't try to fool me, Shyama
Your sketch is up everywhere
They're looking for you
You've been accused of
killing a police constable
And they say that
you killed your friend
You killed Deb?
There are shoot-at-sight
orders for you.
Who are you?
He is an avatar of
Lord Vishnu, Shyama?
With ten names and faces.
l didn't kill Deb on purpose
He was my friend, like my brother
And the police constable?
They were firing at me,
So l fired back. lt was a mistake.
l don't believe you
lt's the truth
You should have said the truth then,
a lot would have been saved
l couldn't betray
Deb and Bajpai Uncle
He raised us,
when we were this little.
l couldn'tjust abandon them
But you could abandon me
You could betray my trust
You wouldn't understand
You've seen nothing
You've lived in luxury all your life.
You wouldn't understand anything.
Keep it
Use it in the kitchen
Should l call the police?
No.
Why are you trying to save him?
Hello.
Hello. - Chaubey...?
lt's Nandu
l will leave tomorrow morning
l'll have to spend the night here
You can call the police, if you want
Zamindar Babu...?
ls dead.
How?
You killed him
Like you killed Deb
lt wasn't your fault
l am going home
l won't tell the police anything
l came here to run away from my past
To forget everything
Why did you come back to my life?
Why did l allow you to?
Why don't l just kill you,
when you are asleep?
lt must give you so
much joy to see me like this
You see that tree?
l stare at it, day and night.
As if its that Bheel Raja's parrot...
...with my life inside it.
l stare at its leaves that fall.
The day the last leaf falls...
...is the day l will breathe my last.
This is where you have brought me to
l hope you are ashamed
of living like this.
But l know you don't care
As always, all you will do is hide
''The complaints are fading away.''
''The dawn's untainted.''
''lt's melting the snow.''
''There's a fire burning somewhere.''
''l didn't want to fly this time.''
''Even the birds agreed.''
''With the darkness
tucked in the arms.''
''The light's here to stay.''
''lt has returned that
thing stolen from me.''
''The complaints are fading away.''
''You're my victory.
While l am the defeat.''
''l am the bond that connects us.''
''You're my victory.
While l am the defeat.''
''Tell me my mistakes.''
''The stars can decide my fate.''
''Turn the looters into protectors.''
''lt's all about fate.''
''lt's a story of earth.''
''This is austerity.''
''The complaints are fading away.''
''l didn't want to fly this time.''
''Even the birds agreed.''
''With the darkness
tucked in the arms.''
''The light's here to stay.''
''lt has returned that
thing stolen from me.''
Nandu!
''The complaints are fading away.''
''The dawn's untainted.''
lts still unsafe outside
l will have to stay
here for a few more days
Tea
l don't want
What are you trying to prove?
Nothing
When you should have done...
- l went away, l know.
You were surrounded by people.
l know what you want.
ls it?
What?
Once wasn't enough for you.
Of course, since you're
looking beautiful these days
l am not joking
l don't know how to make jokes
Why don't you eat something,
then we can...
Just leave
Pakhi
Don't say my name!
Don't shout,
you'll get another attack
See, l told you
Why are you... - Shut up
Sometimes l feel like murdering you.
l hate you so much.
But l don't have the strength anymore
l just want to release Varun
from you,
from myself,
from this life
''The springs came and went.''
''But l didn't experience
a single one.''
''My heart was drenched this time.''
''l wonder what you did?''
''The heart's...feeling
intimate again..''
''O tormentor.''
''My stubbornness..''
''Persuaded my innocent heart..''
''O tormentor.''
''Tosses the heart...around
like a coin.''
''O tormentor.''
''My stubbornness..
persuaded my innocent heart.''
''O tormentor.''
''Mannerless, but unique.''
''l lost my conscious.''
''But, still in my
senses.'' ''O tormentor.''
''My stubbornness..
persuaded my innocent heart.''
''O tormentor.''
May l come in?
l tried calling, quite a few times
No one answered
ls everything ok?
Just a little cough
Did you see him or meet him?
Who?
Varun
Why would l meet him?
You said he might come
The guesthouse is still empty
The 'For Rent' board is still there
Yes
Can l look inside?
Do you have a warrant?
Sorry?
l don't have one right now,
but l can get one tomorrow
Then please come tomorrow
Why are you trying to protect him?
l am not protecting anyone
He's responsible
for your father's death,
and he shot one of my men
He will spend the
rest of his life in jail
He might even hang
l'll be back tomorrow
with the warrant
l'll have ten policemen
with me who l am leaving outside
lf he tries to escape at night,
they will shoot him
lf not, then tomorrow
l will shoot him
l already shot him once,
He's badly injured but he got away
Not this time
Do you know my real name?
What?
Atmanand Tripathi
You look beautiful when you smile
K N Singh is going to kill you
You know what Deb
would have said to that?
What?
There isn't a KN Singh or Rahman
alive who can ruin Dev Anand's hair
You are not a hero
He won't be able to touch me
l have escaped from much worse
He'll bring the warrant tomorrow
l'll leave tonight
Don't look away Pakhi
Look at me
Listen
l know you don't
believe a word l say,
But today l'm not lying
l cannot forgive myself
for what l did to you
Only you have the right to do that
But l hate myself
and l will keep hating
myself as long as l live
Did you ever love me Varun?
l did
l still do
You were my only chance
to lead a better life
And l threw it away
Everyone in my life used me
Only you loved me
And l couldn't love you back
This isn't the life
you should be living
Depending on that
last leaf isn't right
lt isn't your parrot
And if it falls?
lt won't
That's my promise.
''Let me be.''
''l am alive, that's all l need.''
''l asked the winds for my share.''
''And in return l got my breath.''
''When l struck a conversation
with my loneliness.''
''My heart called out to me.''
''The story l started.''
''l've to complete it.''
''l want life to stand
proud at my grave.''
''That's how l want to die.''
''l've nothing left to wish for.''
''l got what l need.''
''l am alive, that's all l need.''
''Let me go.''
''Let me be.''
l don't know how to paint leaves.
l always draw it wrong.
Leaves!
They are really easy
Show me.
This is how it's done in Modern Art.
l want to paint a masterpiece
that the world will remember.
''Does the light ever..''
''Bring darkness with it.''
''The dried up ink.''
''Stands witness.''
''Of an age old story.''
''That remained untold.''
''Does the light ever..''
''Bring darkness with it.''
''The dried up ink.''
''Stands witness.''
''Of an age old story.''
''That remained untold.''
''Does the spring ever announce..''
''The coming of the fall?''
''The rains express their anger..''
''Of the sky.''
''The leaves that
fall from the branch.''
''Don't do so without a reason.''
''All of them.''
''A riddle of dreams.''
''Was it true or false?''
''Patted my forehead.''
''And stole my slumber.''
''Of an age old story.''
''That remained untold.''