And now, friends.
It's an honor to
introduce to all of you..
...the nation's heart-throb.
The one and only.
Singer, music-composer,
and song-writer.. Rahul Jayekar.
We're bringing you live
updates about this concert.
As you can see, the ambiance
is ready, the stage is set.
And the fans have
been waiting for..
...Rahul Jayekar for
the past two hours.
Mr. Deepak. He won't make it.
I am Aryan. I'm a singer too.
Ohh! Get lost!
- Let me go on the stage.
Sir. Listen to me.
Sir, I've been struggling
for five years..
...all thanks to people like these.
Sir, I am ready.
Take me in, please.
Struggle for 10 more years.
Turn authentic.
And if I'm still alive,
you can come meet me.
Okay. Get lost now.
Hello. Where's Vivek..
Vivek! Vivek!
Tell me honestly..
...am I going to have a show or not?
Please. Get this show
done for the last time.
That announcer's
tired of announcing..
...sir's arrival on stage.
"He's coming now!"
"He's on his way!"
Please. Don't ruin my show.
Rahul.
Time to go on stage.
What's the problem, Vivek?
They paid me for this.
I'm here to sing.
And I won't leave without singing.
In fact, those who expect nothing..
...are the more responsible ones.
Let's go.
After countless album songs,
and live concerts..
If anyone tries to create a scene,
just ignore him.
If anything goes wrong..
...the security here will handle it.
Listen.
Just control yourself.
RJLRJL R!
Ask the boys to be ready.
We're going to give them a show.
- Your wait's over.
And we're going to call on stage..
...your favorite, RJ.
That is, Rahul Jayekar.
"Bless me with your grace."
"Give me thoughts."
"Give me oaths and promises."
"Give directions to my prayers."
"Give my heart refuge.”
"Give me new reasons."
"Give my dreams wings to fly."
"Bless me with your grace."
"Take a look at me as well."
"Are you listening?"
"I am crying."
"Why I am crying."
He's drunk! RJ!
"Destiny's are lost."
"“The path's forlorn."
"'Come and take me away."
“That's all I pray for."
"It's your safekeeping.”
"You belong to me."
"Bless me with your grace."
"Take a look at me as well."
"Are you listening?"
"I am crying."
RJ!
Come, come.
What are you waiting for?
Get the camera.
Hurry up.
Take the shot!
Get up. - Rahul, leave.
You have ruined me.
1 won't spare you, RJ.
Rahul, let be.
Get out.
I don't want security.
I don't want it.
Wait.
Let's go - Yes sir.
I know, these things
happen in cheap shows.
Anyway.
We'll discuss this
back at the hotel.
I want to stay alone!
Go somewhere far away.
But, do you have a
problem if I come with you?
No, there's no problem.
I just want to go away
from this commotion. - What?
There's not much
of commotion left now.
It's almost over, Rahul.
After doing shows at London,
New York, Australia..
...now you don't have work.
No one wants to work with you.
Music directors. Film industry,
stage shows, pop albums.
You've nothing.
No one's going to support
a drunk artist for too long.
No one's going to tolerate that.
And now, it's come to this..
...that we've to perform
in small cities.
And pardon me,
this is what happens in such shows.
There's a lot that
happens in my heart too.
So what? - Nothing.
Just stop drinking.
We haven't lost anything yet.
You were a star yesterday.
And you still are.
- Are you finished?
Can I go?
Yeah, go on.
But, this isn't Mumbai.
Sir your car.
Where will you go?
In this strange city?
If you meet with an accident
in this state, you'll end up dead.
You know me well, Vivek.
I don't drink to die.
But, I would die for a drink.
So see you, Vivek. - Rahul.
"The time's standing still."
"How did this happen.”
I want you to come in my life."
"Like a wish comes true."
"You're the satisfaction
of my soul.”
"You're my faith."
And this award
goes to Rahul Jaykar!
"Bless me with your grace."
"Take a look at me as well."
Rahul Jaykar has been honored
with the best male singer award.
RJ the most popular Indian singer.
RJ's new song is super hit.
RJ! RJ! RJ!
"Are you listening?"
"I am crying."
"You are listening, aren't you?"
Oh no!
Sorry!
Are you okay?
What okay?
It's a sunny day, right?
So, you're driving
with your goggles.
You made me drop
all the vegetables.
I just lost 86 rupees. - 86 rupees.
It's a lot of money.
- What are you looking at?
Pick up the remaining tomatoes.
Come on.
Yes.
Three were crushed under the car.
I'll send you the money.
Give me your address.
No. You should be taught a lesson.
Bend down.
Bend down!
And pick them all up.
Sorry.
They are spoilt now.
Forget it.
I am sorry Ms..
That was two days ration.
You ruined it.
Make me a large.
- The bar's closed.
Make me a drink. - The bar's..
Mr. RJ sir, you!
Sir, I'm a big fan.
Make me a drink.
Sir. - I'm okay.
I am sorry, sir.
But the bar's closed.
The owner's father
passed away, so..
Father's dead.
So, where can I get a drink?
Sir, I can give you
drink mixed with coke.
No one will know.
Forget it.
Someone's father is dead.
Why cheat.
Then, can you tell
me if there's a bar around.
I'll be grateful.
Bar?
Oh yes, there's a beer
bar just a few paces ahead.
It stays open until 2 o'clock.
But, that place
isn't your standards.
I'm not up to my standards, either.
What?
Nothing.
Thank you.
"Destiny's are lost."
"“The path's forlorn."
"'Come and take me away."
“That's all I pray for."
"It's your safekeeping.”
"You belong to me."
"Give me thoughts."
"Give me oaths and promises."
"Give directions to my prayers."
"Give my heart refuge.”
"Give me new reasons."
"Give my dreams wings to fly."
"Bless me with your grace."
"Take a look at me as well."
"Are you listening?"
"I am crying."
"Why I am crying."
Keep this inside.
What are you doing?
- He's here.
Who? - Don't know.
He was drunk and driving.
I barely managed to escape.
He's no-good.
Just enjoying for free.
Don't look at him.
Forget it. The manager's watching.
Go on.
"The time's standing still."
"How did this happen.”
"I want you came in my life."
"Like a wish comes true."
"You're the satisfaction
of my soul.”
"You're my faith."
"Bless me with your grace."
"Take a look at me as well."
"Are you listening?"
"I am crying."
"Why I am crying."
Salim, he's right here.
I'm going to yell at him.
He's coming, isn't here?
He's here, right?
Look, I..
Hello. - Hello, sir..
RJ. - Yes.
Rahul... Jayekar! - Yes.
This song.. - You, at our hotel?
And, I was singing your song. - No.
Salil. I said such rubbish.
I want to talk to you.
- Sir, sorry..
Sit. - And,
I made you do such stupid things.
Pick up vegetables..
- Be quiet for a minute.
What's your name?
Aarohi Keshav Shirke.
Aarohi.
You've a great voice.
- No, I was just..
Just listen.
Yes.
You sung my song better than me.
I just realized my flaws.
The mistakes I made in my songs.
I never felt any
of my song like this.
You're joking.
No.
I never joke when concerns singing.
Rahul! Rahul!
Are you mad?
I found your car crashed,
in the middle of the road.
Whether you're dead or alive,
you could've have..
What are you doing here?
Let's go.
Let's go from here.
Rahul, let's go.
- Don't go, Aarohi.
Let's go.
Let's leave.
He's a drunkard.
He was just trying
to convince her..
Yes, let's go.
Is 1 am. And,
the police can raid any moment.
But, he's such a big artist.
If we leave..
He won't know. Let's go.
Deepak's looking all over for you.
We've four more shows to do.
If this continues..
...we'll have to
return all the money.
We will return the money, Vivek.
What are you saying Rahul?
Listen. I've to go
back to Mumbai tomorrow.
This singer, Aarohi.. - Who?
Where's everyone?
Forget it, let's go.
Rahul, let's go. - Wait.
Where's everyone? - They all left.
I want that girl's address.
Where does she stay? - Kolhapanaji!
I'm going. - What?
Give me the car keys.
What are you doing? - Give it.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
- Pay for the whiskey.
Rahul!
Rahul! How will I go home?
"You've a great voice.'
'You sung my song better than me."
'l just realized my flaws."
'The mistakes I made in my songs.'
I never felt any
of my song like this.'
Aarohi!
Hi. - Oh, God!
I want to talk to you, come down.
Come down.
I can't come. - Fine, I'm coming.
No. no. no. - What?
I'm coming. - Come down.
What are you doing?
What happened?
Come on.
Come here.
What are you doing?
I'm not allowed
to meet anyone here.
If the bar's management sees me..
...he'll deduct a day's salary.
- Sorry.
I had to come.
We couldn't complete
our conversation at the bar..
What?
So...
You want to be a singer?
- Who said that?
You did.
You were looking at Lata's picture.
Just like a child
looks at the moon.
Wants to touch it.
That look told me everything.
Everyone looks at the moon.
What good is that? - The beginning.
Of every successful journey.
You know,
the best artists in the world..
...are the ones who
have their own style.
A style,
that doesn't come from imitation.
A style, that's born with them.
And, you've got that.
That special thing.
I wonder what's that thing..
...that you heard,
but the others can't.
I tried really hard.
But, no one gave me a chance.
That's why I am here.
Because,
1 want to make you successful.
I want to make you the greatest
singer of this millennium.
Look I... not the
kind of girl you think.
I don't say these
things to those girls.
But, what to do?
Il think ll am in love.
I've gone crazy.
Now, whether it's the art
or the artist, that's yet to say.
We'll know.
But, only after you're sober.
Listen. - What?
You won't work in that bar.
You'll leave that job.
Because I say so.
Do you believe me?
Listen.
What?
Nothing.
Just like that.
Aarohi, are you okay?
Yes. I am fine.
25,000!
That's what I spent
to bring you here.
I suggest,
you pay up and you can leave.
What?
Don't have it.
Go.
Shankar sir.
It's the question of my life.
Please let me go.
I'll return your money
once I get to Mumbai.
No one's going to pay
even 200 for this face.
What do you think?
This is no orphanage.
Pay up and leave.
You take up 50 percent.
And, what are we left with?
We've to buy food
with our own money.
It'll take me months
to arrange that kind of money.
Yeah! Exactly.
That's why you steal
money from the money-bag.
What else do you expect me to do?
You cut 100 rupees
for minor mistakes.
200 for coming late.
And my salary.. - Babu!
What's wrong with her?
She's constantly
saying "'l want to go".
She was fine until yesterday.
That singer RJ that
came to bar yesterday..
...is the one that provoked her.
That he'll make her a singer.
Give her a chance to sing in films.
Since then.. - I see.
RJ. That singer.
Just a minute.
Look.
His picture's in the papers.
He had a fight
with a man yesterday.
He left before the show started.
The organizer of the
show was crying on camera.
There are many other
stories about him.
But, no news about his work.
He'll get you work.
A man that's living off
his hit songs of yesteryear..
...can only pass time with you.
Do you know why?
Because you're worth it.
Hello, sir... you..
I am here for this girl..
...because she's going
to a great singer.
But, I can see her future, not you.
One more thing.
You run a bar.
You live off singers.
Learn to respect singers.
Ones that sing at your bar.
And the ones,
whose songs help you run your bar.
Get that.
Vivek, throw the money on his face.
He isn't worthy of any respect.
Let's go, Aarohi.
Okay. Goodbye.
What's all this, Rahul?
This is it.
I pray to Allah that
you're never heart-broken.
If that happens, don't hesitate.
I'll get you work,
and won't taunt you either.
No, no, it's fine.
I'll drop you.
No.
The place I stay,
isn't your standards.
I've noted my number, address..
...and my manager's
number in your diary.
So, call me when you get a new sim.
Okay.
Don't forget.
Thank you. - For what?
For giving me new hope.
Bye. - Bye.
Listen.
What?
Nothing.
Just like that.
Father!
Aarohi.
You're back. - Yes.
I was thinking about you. - Really?
I even called you in my dreams.
Your mother yelled at me. - Why?
She called me crazy. - Father.
But, you left for three months,
didn't you?
And in one month..
- I'll tell you everything.
But where's mother?
At the station.
Today's Thursday.
She's gone to buy the
Maharashtra Rajya Lottery.
She's been buying lottery
tickets for the past two years.
But she's never won anything
more than 100 rupees.
Enough!
The daughter's back and
the father can't stop yapping.
Mother.
Why didn't you say you're coming?
I would've prepared
something for you.
We live off on fritters.
But now that you're here,
we'll make something nice.
Give me 100 rupees..
...I'll get something
from the market.
We'll make something good today.
Mother, I..
...didn't get paid. - Why?
I met someone.
He said he'll give me a
chance to be a singer, in films.
So I.. - You believed him.
And quit your job.
Mom.
Everything will be okay.
Trust..
It's just a matter of few days.
Once I start working.. - $0?
I only have 300 rupees.
300 rupees..
Your father doesn't earn a penny.
He.. keeps repairing everyone's
radio and TV's for free.
What are you saying?
- Let me speak.
Is this why I sent
you to the best teachers?
Taught you to speak good Hindi.
So that you can become a great..
I stitched clothes
to pay for your fees.
Finally you found a job,
but you quit that as well.
And..
I don't win.. the jackpot either.
I thought if you get some money..
.1 will manage a few months.
Now, I'll have to
borrow from someone.
No, mom.
Let's see whether anyone
will lend me money or not. -Mom.
Mom. Mom. Listen to me. - Aarohi.
Let her go.
Actually, it's not her fault.
She's always seen poverty.
And I never gave
her anything either.
But look.
All our hopes are with you.
We want good things for you.
Father.
First time someone's
believed in me.
First time I believed in someone.
He came all the way from Goa,
only for me.
And he's gone to talk
to someone for me, father.
Uncle, I'm not joking.
- Deadlines, boys.
There's a girl
Thank God!
Get married, straighten up!
No, no, no, it's not that.
No. - No.
This girl's a very,
very, very, very good singer.
I would've believed you
if you had said "very" once.
Please cancel my
appointment for tomorrow.
She was singing in a bar.
Bar.. you mean where
you were obviously..
Yes..
But, what a voice.
I had an entire bottle,
but I couldn't get drunk.
Can you imagine?
- 15 minutes.
Basically, I want you to
give her a chance to sing in films.
Or, make an album.
She's superb, uncle.
I can write that in blood.
Do you have any blood left?
Where is she?
She stays here in Mumbai.
She's from a poor family..
...and performs out of
the city to make a living.
In these small bars.
But I am not going
to let that happen again.
I really want to help her, uncle.
She's a superstar.
Superstar? - Yeah!
A star, is someone whose songs,
and voice..
...makes you want to..
Whistle.
Just like people used
to whistle at your performance.
You were the star. You.
She's better than me.
She's amazing.
I'm telling you, she's amazing.
Call her.
I'll first hear
her and then decide.
You're serious? - Yes.
Yes.
Thank you, uncle.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Out. Get out.
Thank you.
Listen to him. He's a good man.
Excuse me, give me a simcard.
- Take this.
You are leaving Deepak's show?
You will forget to sing.
Be careful.
Careful, please.
Careful.
Don't you dare tell
anyone about this!
If any journalist or media-person asks you about him..
...then say,
he's gone to London for a show.
In the meanwhile, nobody comes in,
nobody talks to him.
You get that.
Hello. - Hello.
Can I talk to Mr.
Rahul? My name's Aarohi.
He asked me to call me.
I'm a singer, we met in Goa
and he said.. - Rahul isn't here.
He's gone to London, for his shows.
And he'll return after 20-25 days.
- 20-25 days?
Yes, but just listen to me..
Hello! Hello!
"It's your fault, my heart!"
"Why did you trust him?"
"All the promises were fake."
"The one you followed here."
"Beloved's nowhere."
"Now, stop seeing those dreams."
'Now, shatter those
dreams yourself."
"Beloved's nowhere."
We don't have evidence..
...whether Deepak's involved or not.
But I swear Rahul.
I will find out whoever he is and..
Did Aarohi call?
Not yet.
Is your phone on?
2417,
Tell this girl that
it's a wrong number.
Hello. - Hello.
Hello, is Rahul back.
I am sorry, this is a wrong number.
What?
Hello. Hello.
"There's punishment
for every mistake."
"If you're destined for sadness."
"“There's always a reason."
"All my pain has
conjured in my tears."
"My tears don't
stop trickling down."
"Beloved's nowhere."
Okay. Give the money.
See you. Goodbye.
This fracture showed
me the importance of my legs.
Take care.
Great.
Good news.
It's time to celebrate.
I'll have a drink with you as well.
Where to? - To look for Aarohi.
Come on.
Excuse me, is this Rahul's house?
Yes, this is his home.
But, sir's out of town.
I don't know when he's coming back.
Vivek sir said he'll be
coming back after 20-25 days.
It's been two months now.
He hasn't returned.
What can I do if he hasn't?
I'll let you know
once he comes back.
Please leave.
Please give this top
Rahul sir when he returns.
Tell him Aarohi was here.
I tried calling him many times.
I'll give it to
him once he returns.
Please go now.
Coming!
What happend?
Sister-in-law, Salim.
Aarohi. What's wrong?
Salim.
What's wrong? Who is it?
What's wrong, Aarohi?
I want a job.
Any place. Good, bad or cheap.
Just get me work.
I need money, Salim.
Come in.
Sir. A girl gave this.
When did she come?
Yesterday evening.
She said she called
you two-three times.
Maybe she spoke to Vivek sir.
She looked decent, so I told you.
Thank you. - Welcome sir.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Don't ask why I did that?
You know.
I told that girl never
to sing in a bar again.
I told her she'll
be a successful singer.
I told her she will be a star.
I went to her hotel, Vivek.
She didn't come to me.
And what did you do?
You humiliated her.
You hid her calls from me.
You lied to her.
You treated her like an enemy.
- Yes, because I'm your friend.
I've been with you for years.
You could've shown
some respect for me.
And for any darn girl..
- She's no ordinary girl!
This is why I did it.
So that you stay away from her.
I didn't want this to happen, man!
First alcohol, then drugs.
And now.. - Whatever I do
with my life is my problem, Vivek.
No!
This isn't your personal problem.
I've been with you for 10 years.
I looked after you, your career.
I saw your success, your downfall.
But, I can't see you
handing over your success..
...which you need the most now,
to some girl.
I can't see you doing
this for someone else instead.
I feel sad. It hurts me.
To know that you've stopped
recognizing your talent.
You've forgotten your own voice.
One that's unmatched.
Why?
Why don't you see yourself?
Why don't you hear yourself?
You call me your enemy.
Just.. look at yourself.
You're right.
But the truth is,
ll don't want anything.
Fame, fortune,
success, money, respect.
It should all go to
the one that deserves it.
Give the bread to the
one that's hungry for it.
And I've seen that in that girl.
And I no longer have that.
And I've admitted this truth.
You should too.
Your friend can't pay
you your salary anymore.
RJ. - You're a free man, Vivek.
You can go anywhere you want.
Hello.
Can I talk to Aarohi, please?
She's performing? - Where?
Hotel Nightingale.
"What seemed like reality,
turned out to be an illusion."
'A saga, that was bound
for a twist, has ended."
"I forgot, so did she.”
“How do I tell
everyone about this?"
"I've slowly compromised myself."
"I've slowly controlled myself."
"Beloved's nowhere."
"It's your fault, my heart!"
"Why did you trust him?"
Aarohi! Aarohi!
Please let me explain.
Look. I work here.
Don't create a scene.
I got this job with
great difficulty.
Damn the job,
1 want to speak to you.
Why should 1?
I've been waiting for two months.
First time I hurt my
parents and trusted someone.
I started dreaming.
Everything seemed true.
What now?
Go ahead.
You can vent all your anger.
I am your culprit.
But, I am not.
I waited for you.
Get in.
Come on. - What are you doing?
Get in. - What are you doing?
What are you doing? - Come on.
I want to tell you a story.
I don't want to hear your story.
Let's go.
If all that happened with you..
...then, why didn't
they show it on TV?
Aarohi, the TV..
Please forget it.
I want to keep my promise.
In fact I brought
Sehgal uncle along.
He's called you at his office.
But, I cannot quit this job.
I cannot take a risk again.
Then don't..
You can keep the job
until you're satisfied.
But, you've believed me so far,
then why not another day.
Be ready at 11 am tomorrow.
Please.
Please!
You sing well, dear.
You're talented.
And you understand tunes.
But, for playback
singing and albums..
...you'll need some grooming.
Just a little.
Because singing in recording
studios with new songs..
...can get a little overwhelming.
- Okay.
Fine.. we'll start your
vocal training from next week.
Yes, I'll do that.
I'll train her. - Fantastic!
What else do you want?
So many awards, records.
They're all yours.
They're mine, or not. I don't know.
What?
Nothing.
Don't worry.
Someday you'll
come with your award.
You'll have more awards than me.
I promise.
What?
Nothing.
Just like that.
I can't do it.
Okay, listen. I will show you.
It's in B flat.
“Just tell me,
whether I want it or not."
“Show me the way to your heart,
You sing so well.
It's your training not me.
Let's start singing.
“Just tell me,
whether I want it or not."
“Show me the way to your heart,
"Let me tell you, that
I don't have faith in my love."
"still, the heart thought.."
"..now that we're here,
why not ask.”
“Just tell me,
whether I want it or not."
“Show me the way to your heart,
"I never had such desires before."
"I never tried this
hard to meet anyone.™
“Solve my confusion,
whether I want it or not."
“Express it through your eyes,
Aarohi! Aarohi! Aarohi!
Ladies and Gentlemen.
The time has come,
for me to introduce you all..
...to the nightingale of India,
and our country's..
...latest singing sensation.
The beautiful,
the talented, the wonderful!
Aarohi Keshav Shirke!
Yes, dad.
Rahul. How are you, son?
Everything fine?
- Everything fine, dad.
In fact, I'm really happy.
After along time.
You're in love, huh!
"Just tell me..
How did you know?
I'm your father.
Come.
When the son's in love,
the father knows.
“Show me the way to your heart,
whether I want it or not."
What happened?
Sir, she needs five more minutes.
It's been half an hour, Rahul.
Is there a problem?
- No, sir. There's no problem.
Aarohi.
Come out.
Let's go.
I cannot sing.
Aarohi, we all get nervous.
I was too.
I ran away from the studio.
It's okay.
No.
The bar was a different story.
Making mistakes were okay.
But, here..
amongst these big people..
You're not alone.
I am with you.
Please, come out.
I cannot sing.
Aarohi, I love you.
ll love you.
I've waited too long for this day.
More than you.
Come out for me.
Please.
“I've small dreams."
"Dreams have songs."
"Songs have life."
"Love and affection."
"I don't dream any longer."
“That's without you."
“I'm finally saying,
what I didn't so far."
“The heart trusts you,
more than me."
"1 weave dreams about us,
in my empty moments."
"You're in love with me."
“I'll never ask you,
whether I want to or not."
"I want to live in your dreams,
because I want to." - Fantastic.
Really nice.
Ladies and Gentlemen.
Welcome to the Indian Music Awards.
Finally!
Uncle. Where's Rahul?
- We're waiting for you.
When you can't
find Rahul anywhere..
...you must always check the bar.
But, it's such a big day
of my life, he should be with me.
I've been nominated.
I understand..
Mom and dad are here.
I'll just..
Come. Please come.
Come on, he'll be here. Come on.
Please.
Aarohi! Aarohi!
Come here.
Looking for me?
You scared me.
Where were you? - Forget that.
How do you feel?
It's useless.
Wonder where you
keep disappearing to?
I was at the bar.
If you drink so much, how
will you recognize me in the crowd?
1 will.
Amongst,
thousands, million, billions.
I can forget myself, but not you.
When did you fall so
deeply in love with me?
Hi, ma'am!
I'm from CNTV Live.
Do you mind if I
take a small interwiew?
Please. Just for five minutes.
No, right now I.. - Just a second.
Never do that.
Okay. Never do that.
Go. Time to touch the moon.
Go get them.
Ladies and Gentlemen.
Moving on the next award.
Nidhi Chaudhary for "Aa jara"
Listen. - Yes, sir.
Did you get the bottle from home?
- No, sir.
Then, why are you being a miser?
Pour some more.
Sorry, sir.
And award goes to..
Aarohi Keshav Shirke.
She won!
Thank you.
The girl sings well.
She's very good.
I heard she was offered
to sing in films too.
But she refused.
She'll say yes.
Everyone wants to be a star.
Of course, she will be.
But, not a star, a maid.
What's that singer's name?
That star.
Rahul.
She'll be his maid.
And later, his nurse.
Come on. He loves her.
He's made her.
She made it this
far because of him.
That's what I am
trying to tell you.
The higher she climbs
the ladder of success..
...the lower she'll
fall because of Rahul.
She belongs to a poor family,
after all.
That's why RJ's taken her in.
So that he can make her serve him.
Keep her awake all night,
for his entertainment.
To vent out the
anger of his failure.
And as days will go by,
he will start hitting her.
He'll beat her every day,
humiliate her.
And once he falls sick..
...she'll be cleaning his pukes.
Remember this.
Often, those who light the lamp..
...are the ones that douse it later.
There have been many
such stories in the industry.
Another glass of whiskey.
Rahul!
Rahul. What are you doing?
Get down.
Finally, you touched the moon.
You were looking very beautiful
on the big screen with the award.
Does this bottle
look nice in my hands?
It doesn't.
But what to do.
I just can't let go.
Rahul. - No, no, wait.
After I got my first
break without any struggle..
.-1 got fame, fortune, status.
The world was at my feet.
But, I didn't know what to do.
I couldn't handle the fame..
...OF my senses.
That was the condition yesterday..
...it's still the same today.
And it'll always stay that way.
Rahul. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
We'll have to end
this relation here.
Now.
Nothing's lost yet.
We aren't so close.
We can live without each other.
You're successful now, Aarohi.
You've everything.
Go, live your life.
My habits have scared me.
I don't know my future.
What I might turn into.
How I may treat you.
It doesn't take long for
one to turn into the devil.
So, why should I hold you back?
I can't do this.
Then.. then..
Leave this habit.
Leave it.
It's no good.
I'll help you.
I'll help you leave it.
Just give me a chance..
- I can never leave it.
It's like a wife,
that won't ever leave me alone.
So, listen to me.
You'll be happier without me.
That means, you can live
with this habit, but not me.
Rahul.
Love is not a joke.
- But my life is.
But, you always had this habit.
If you were so scared,
why did you come so close?
You should've stayed away.
- Exactly.
Until now, I was my own enemy!
And before I become a
threat to you, just go away!
Fine.
I am going.
Away, from you and this success.
Don't misjudge your success.
Only a few fortune people get it.
I know.
And also that,
you were with me in my bad times.
But if you're not with
me in my good times..
.Then I don't want it.
Aarohi!
Aarohi! Aarohi!
Aarohi, listen!
I can't live without you."
"I don't exist without you."
'If I separate from you,
I'll lose myself."
"Because it's you.. it's you."
"You're my life."
"My relief, my pain."
"You're my love."
"We can't stay away a moment."
"Il live only for you."
"All my time is devoted to you."
"I can't live a
moment without you."
"Each breath's just for you."
"Because it's you.. it's you."
"You're my life."
"My relief, my pain."
"You're my love."
Uncle one second wait uncle.
Yes uncle don't worry.
Aarohi! - Yes, mom.
Dear, you're getting in
a live-in relation with him.
Without marriage?
What's the world going to say?
This is my world..
...that's it.
"I lived only for you."
"I've surrendered myself."
"Your loyalty supported me."
"It cured all my pain."
"My destiny's tied with you."
"You made me complete.”
"Because it's you.. it's you."
"You're my life."
"My relief, my pain."
"You're my love."
"Because it's you.. it's you."
"You're my life."
"My relief, my pain."
"You're my love."
Sir.
Sir, Vivek's here to see you.
He has won our heart.
And today for his new song..
..."YARA' he is going to be
honored with the national award.
Now Aarohi's name will
be written in history.
Hi.
I came to apologize.
What I did..
ll shouldn't have done..
- Forget it.
Forget it.
I thought you would still
be angry.. - Forget it.
What will you drink?
Enough. Stop. What are you doing?
Is there any work?
What?
I want to work.
I am not alone.
There is.
There's a small-time producer.
They want to record a song.
Will you sing for them? - So what?
Music can't be compared with money.
This is just good.
Let's do this.
Let's just do this.
You know what, you're back.
You're back my friend.
You're back.
"It's not easy to be in love."
"To shed tears."
'Lovers are always
struck with grief."
"Not everyone's blessed with this
boon." - Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Sir, the pitch is going flat.
Please up it a little.
One more. - Yes.
Come on.
"It's not easy to be in love."
"To shed tears." - Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Sir, again pitch problem, sir.
One more. - Okay.
Yeah. One more.
“It's not easy.." - Stop.
Do you want me to down it a little?
- No, no need.
Let's try again. - Yeah.
My voice.. One more.
Come on.
What's wrong?
Think it's funny?
Can you sing this song?
Can you?
Then sing it. - Sir..
Sing it..
- Sorry, sir. It.. Wasn't for you..
The tune's so strange, and you..
I need a break.
Sorry.
Rahul, I won't spare them.
I swear they won't
know what came their way.
Who do they think they are?
Let's go inside.
Come on, I'll show them.
Come on.
I've lost my voice.
I couldn't sing.
My vocal chords are fried.
That's not true.
It's okay.
It happens.
Let's try again. - I am finished.
"You.. leave me.."
“That can never happen..
...beloved."
He's back again.
These stars look
so ugly after they flop.
"I always mention about you."
“I'm always concerned about you."
I am what you are."
"You're the one that
gave me my style.”
"Because it's you.. it's you."
"You're my life."
"My relief, my pain."
"You're my love."
“It's you.. it's you."
"You're my pain, you're my cure."
"My relief, my pain."
"You're my love."
Sorry.
I tried,
but I couldn't come earlier.
How was the recording?
Nothing happened?
So, what did you do today?
- Nothing.
I was listening to my songs.
Trying to sing.
You don't get them these days.
You will.
I will pray for you.
You can do that later.
But first, did you eat or..
...were you singing
on an empty stomach?
I am very hungry.
Let's go out.
Let's stay here. I've ordered food.
It'll be here soon.
Aarohi,
there were few calls for you.
Sehgal uncle called.
He spoke to someone for you.
There was a call
from a talent show.
For a judging job, or something..
And from a magazine as well.
For an interwiew.
I asked him to call tomorrow.
Rahul. - Yes.
Look at me.
Has anything changed?
Nothing's changed?
Come here.
Food.
How much? - How much? - 1560.
I got it. I got it.
How much? - 1560.
1560.
Keep the change. Thank you.
Can I get an autograph? - Yes.
Not yours, madam's.
I'll call her.
Aarohi, he wants your autograph.
Now. I'll give it later.
These moments are priceless.
They don't come back.
Go.
I'll do it, go.
I'm a big fan, madam.
I listen to all your songs, madam.
All of them.
Name? - Anil.
Anil.
I had a great desire to meet you.
I'm really happy.
Thank you, madam. Thank you.
Due to your tax problems,
your accounts have been sealed.
You've only few millions left.
But, you can't withdraw them.
I've struck a deal
for your house as well.
It's a penthouse,
so it'll sell easily.
It'll take some time.
Sorry, sir.
But your card is not working.
Just like that.. - No problem.
Thank you sir.
We're not that bad.
“It's you."
It's all over.
Rahul.
What's all this?
Nothing to drink.
It's all over.
- What are you doing?
It's all over. - Rahul.
It's all over.
Rahul. - It's all over.
- What are you doing?
It's all over. - Rahul.
Rahul. - It's all over.
What are you doing?
Nothing's over yet.
- It's all over.
Everything's okay.
I'll get water.
Rahul, water.
Sir bill.
Hi, dad.
How are you?
What happened to your voice?
It's everything okay?
Why are you sounding so low.
What happened?
Hey rahul!
I really love her, dad.
I really love her.
Rahul, tell me what's wrong?
I'm worried dear tell me.
What happened?
I don't know.
I'm just a little lost.
Rahul you not alone.
Did you hear me?
We'll come back tomorrow.
You're not alone.
I am not alone, dad.
I am not alone.
Good evening sir how are you?
Ladies and gentlemen it's pleasure
to have all of you here on stage.
It's the most important
day of my life.
25 great years of long struggle,
pain, success, failures.
Your love and good wishes.
Now without wasting any more time.
And now, I call upon the stage.
Ms. Aarohi Shirke.
Please get back. Please move back.
Back, back please.
She is the singer of
our recent super hit films.
And also are fourth coming film.
Please stay back. - I am with her.
Do you have a invitation card?
What? Don't touch me.
Please move back. - Go out!
Please behave. - Please, sir..
I said she's with me.
Leave me.
What do you think?
- Don't create a scene here.
You get out of here.
"Go here, go there.
Don't sit here."
Rahul come on.
Earned a lot for him.
I sung one hit song after another.
Relax - What relax?
And, now they bloody
treat me like this.
I've been to many
such parties in my life.
I am Rahul Jayekar.
I am a bloody! star.
I am still sing
better than everyone.
I was, I am and always will be.
- Rahul.
Aarohi.
Get up.
Rahul. - No.
Rahul, stop.
No, let him go.
- Let him go.
“It's just you."
Sorry, sorry.
Don't do this.
Stop it.
You're always hovering around me.
What am I doing? Why am I doing it?
Am I asleep? Am I awake?
- Rahu), what are you doing?
I'm fed up of this.
I was better-off before. - Rahul.
I was happier alone.
- Listen to me.
I feel suffocated
since you came here.
What are you doing, Rahul?
- Get lost.
Go!
- Rahul, listen to me.
Just go away!
Rahul, open the door.
Please.
We all fall weak, Rahul.
We're scared.
I was too.
I thought that was my life.
Then, you came in my life.
And changed everything.
You cannot leave me alone
after giving me all this.
I love you!
This is what you've
been waiting for.
It's here.
I am what you wanted to make me.
At least,
open the door for my sake.
Please.
At least, open the door..
"“Empty.. your eyes.”
"1 wish you.. could fill my eyes."
Help me.
"I wish you.. could fill
my eyes." - Please help me.
How can they disappear?
- I don't know.
We've recordings lined up,
shows have been organized.
Who is going to do it?
Find out where they are. - Yes sir.
"My beloved,
if you give me your pain."
"I swear I'll get better."
"My beloved,
if you give me your pain."
"I swear I'll get better."
"If you give me this gift.."
“I'll forsake all happiness.™
“I'll die."
"My beloved,
if you give me your pain."
"I swear I'll get better."
"I want to spend the rest of
my life, leaning on your shoulder."
“If my dream comes true,
I'll be so fortunate."
“It'll be your tears, and my eyes."
"If you give me your grief."
“I'll be filled with happiness.”
“I'll die."
"My beloved,
if you give me your pain."
"I swear I'll get better."
And now,
I'd like to invite on stage..
...the one that's
captivated our hearts.
I would like to call upon,
our favorite RJ.
That is Rahul Jayekar.
Clap!
RJ! RJ! RJ! RJ!
"Whether in happiness, or grief."
"“The heart always
called out to you."
"You made me, you shaped me up."
"The world looks up to God,
but you're my support.”
“All I need is you."
"No matter what it is."
“I'll do it for you.
“I'll die."
"My beloved,
if you give me your pain."
"I swear I'll get better."
"My beloved,
if you give me your pain."
"I swear I'll get better."
The recording studio
called yesterday.
You didn't go for your recording.
Rahul needs me, and..
I want to look after him.
If I stay busy,
who will look after him?
He's going nowhere.
You'll be at loss, because
you don't know what you have here.
You can lose all this in a moment.
I tried explaining it to him.
I beg you.
Don't test me.
I'm tying you down, right?
Don't do this, Aarohi.
Don't miss your schedules.
I'll stay here, with you.
Otherwise you will be alone.
You will do whatever you wish.
I cannot take this risk.
I won't break your trust this time.
- But, Rahul..
And you won't waste
your life for me.
But, Rahul I..
- Aarohi, your failure..
...will be the biggest
defeat of my life.
I cannot see you
go down the same lane.
You'll never be Rahul Jayekar.
Not even for me.
Promise me.
Best of luck. Do well.
I am right here.
It's here just for you.
Ma'am we raedy for you.
Lovely Aarohi Shirke.
Okay.
Who's he?
Yes I will come.
See you.
Rahul Jayekar.
What's up, buddy? - Nothing much.
How are you?
Rocking.
What are you doing here?
Watching the show.
Good to see you.
You're doing well. - Yeah.
Rahul!
Sorry. Beer?
No, thanks. - Sure?
Yeah. Quit!
Pass me a diet coke.
Diet coke, huh!
Cheers.
Mr. Rahul.
Kunal Basu, I'm a journalist.
Okay.
I want an interwiew.
Exclusive interview.
About your personal life,
etcetera, etcetera.
Sorry, but I'm no
longer famous enough..
...for people to read about my life.
They know it all.
Not about your love-life.
I mean, the thing between
you and Ms. Aarohi.
Few people know about it.
I don't want to talk
about me and Aarohi.
You don't understand.
Aarohi's fans want to know
when she's getting married.
I told you this is
my personal matter..
...and I don't want
to talk about it.
Your personal life's
public property as well.
No, it's not.
Thank you.
Mr. Rahul.
You don't know what
people say about you two.
That's nothing new.
People also say that,
Aarohi used to sing in beer bars.
And you supported her
just to have some fun.
You used her.
You made her your
concubine and left her.
Who do you think you are?
- What are you doing?
You dare hit a journalist.
Who do you think you are?
You ruined a girl's life.
You sleep with that girl.
You stay with her,
but you can't admit it.
I'll have you arrested. Wait.
You rascal.
9870541084.
Yes, that's my number.
Save it. Okay.
We're here for him.
Him.
Not possible.
What a man.
He was drunk.
He created quite a scene.
He beat-up a journalist.
Then, he beat-up a taxi-driver.
He smashed someone's car.
That's not done.
And what's the time now.
You won't get bail now.
I'll call Kamte.
The court will open
at 11 am tomorrow.
He'll be present
in the court first..
...only then he can get bail.
He has to stay here tonight.
Brother.
Can I have a minute? - Sit.
I.. - 1 know..
You're Aarohi Shirke, right.
Yes.
Who's he?
...
We're friends.
We had a fight.
I threatened to leave him.
That got him worried and..
Love story.
Right?
Please, you can keep this..
What's this?
- And let him go. - No.
And let him go. - What's this? No.
It won't happen again.
I promise you, and..
“It's you."
We'll go far away.
Where no one knows us.
I'll finish the contracts
that I signed, and leave.
Without Rahul,
ll don't want anything.
I wanted to be successful..
...but not at this price.
Not by losing him.
You don't fall sick
along with the patient.
Dear.
If your love was his cure..
...then why didn't it work yet?
He's dependent on his habits.
His flaws.
He doesn't want to get anywhere.
So, where will you take him?
Not me.
He'll take me, in his world.
The place where he
stays day and night.
And he's happy.
His habits will be mine.
His flaws will be mine.
He cannot leave them, but..
I can take them up.
If this poison is his first love,
then I'll accept it too.
I'll stagger along with him.
Then, I might find
him at some point.
He might get fed up of his habits.
He might come back and say “Aarohi,
I am tired...
Then I'll say "Come..
...let's go home."
And, he'll come back.
We'll come back, uncle.
You've gone crazy.
You don't know what you're saying.
When did you get up?
You kept crying all night.
My love's made you sad.
I was crying,
because I was missing you.
I am right here.
Just like that.
Come closer.
I came here to tell you.
You can cry all you want.
Your days of crying are over.
I'll leave everything, Aarohi.
I'll turn over a new leaf for you.
Everything will be fine.
You and me.
You'll help me, won't you?
Have I ever said no? - No.
The day I saw you first,
I realized..
...why you came in my life.
You've loved me a lot.
Given me a lot of things.
I gave you what was easy for me.
You endured my difficulties,
my betrayal.
Divided love.
And I couldn't give
you your right place.
But all that's going to change now.
Right now. From this moment.
Because Aarohi,
1 am going to join a gym.
That's going to
be my daily program.
Gym in the morning,
jogging in the evening.
Proper diet. Aarohi.
Really?
Will you really.. - Yes.
This time I am serious, Aarohi.
Like I never was.
I am going.
Keep the food ready,
and wait for me.
Miss me.
Rahul.
I love you.
Come on.
I'll change all this.
Aarohi.
What?
Nothing.
Just like that.
"Forget me.
This is my final goodbye."
"You've to live on.. without me.
"“This is your journey, your path."
I pray you attain fame."
'l pray you're blessed
with all the grace.”
"You've to live on.. without me.
"Forget me.
This is my final goodbye."
"You've to live on.. without me.
"You're my shore, my support.”
"You're the tune in my heart,
my saga."
"Be your own God."
"I am like evening that's fading."
"You're the new dawn."
"You've to live on.. without me.
Sir, one body found in water.
And Ambulance will
come for take the body.
Aarohi dear listen. - Aarohi.
Aarohi where are you going?
Aarohi don't ...
Aarohi - where are you going.
Coward!
Coward! Coward! Coward!
“It's you."
Where are you going?
Anywhere?
What do you mean?
I mean far away.
I'm leaving everything.
But, that's not what Rahul wanted?
Rahul who?
I don't know any
person by that name.
Aarohi, decisions taken in a rage,
always hurt in the end.
For the first time,
my decision hasn't hurt me.
Good.
Very good.
Please go.
He should fade away.
Die inside you.
He was worth that.
I tried stopping him.
But he didn't stop.
He said..
"This is it".
He sold your art,
like your secretary.
The little life that he had,
was just for you.
But my friend died,
the day he hurt you.
The day he raised his hand on you.
The day he saw you
at the police station.
He knew.
Drinking was his weakness.
He had become your weakness.
The biggest obstruction
in your path.
And so, he gave his life.
So that you can live.
So that,
you don't become another Jayekar.
But you know what, he failed.
My friend lost.
You turned out to
be another Rahul Jayekar.
"The place where
buds will blossom."
“That's where you'll find me."
"“The place that'll
remind you of my loyalty."
“That's where you'll find me."
“I'll come see you, I promise you."
"I'll always be with you,
I promise you."
"You've to live on.. without me.
Aarohi ma'am, I'm a big fan.
Can I have your autograph, please?
Thank you.
Thank you, ma'am.
- Thank you so much.
Wow! but Aarohi rahul Jayekar.
Yeah rahul Jayekar that singer.
"Because it's you.. it's you."
"You're my life."
"My relief, my pain."
"You're my love."
"You and I share a strange bond."
"We can't stay away a moment."
"Il live only for you."
"All my time is devoted to you."
"I can't live a
moment without you."
"Each breath's just for you."
"Because it's you.. it's you."
"You're my life."
"My relief, my pain."
"You're my love."
“It's you."
"I lived only for you."
"I've surrendered myself."
"Your loyalty supported me."
"It cured all my pain."
"My destiny's tied with you."
"You made me complete.”
"Because it's you.. it's you."
"You're my life."
"My relief, my pain."
"You're my love."