When a person is faced with a question
as to what the consequences would be..
..he hesitates.
Such a person..
..has no right to be in the force.
The Force is nobody's personal fiefdom.
(Background Music)
The Force has..
..its own dignity.
It's our responsibility
to uphold the dignity.
(Background Music)
You might think that it is wrong.
Because what you perceive
is your reality.
What I perceive is my reality.
There is no reality as such.
There are only perceptions.
We respected Gandhiji..
..for as long as we could.
I did what I felt was right.
It was not perception.
Not my perception, but clarity.
(Background Music)
Mr. Anna, I have a solution
in mind for this problem.
But your ideals..
..and your principles would
prevent me from doing it.
I don't undertake a task..
..which I cannot accomplish.
We know it's a serious problem.
I am accountable to the people
more than the party.
I know gangsters mistake my
Gandhian values to be my weakness.
Those values cannot deal with them.
We have to give them a fitting reply.
Everyone including me concur with it.
You find a solution to this problem.
All of you have firsthand knowledge..
..and understanding about
this city and its crimes.
Especially you, Mr. Pradhan.
When you were the police commissioner,
crime was under control.
So you can use your experience
and explain to us..
..what kind of problem we are facing.
Mr. Jagirdar..
..we always forget that
the people in the Force..
..are more important
than the Force itself.
And our system..
..ignores people who are made
for this job..
..and gives responsibility to people
who don't know what it means.
In order to handle this situation,
we need a capable, intelligent..
..confident and non-corrupt person.
- Who do you have in mind?
- Sadhu Agashe.
He has the capability,
but look what he's doing currently.
He is idling at his native place..
..due to the legal cases
filed by the system.
If you ask me, there's no better person..
..than Sadhu to handle this situation.
Sir, you forget..
..that Sadhu was in jail for
1.5 years before getting bail.
Case are pending against him.
Bhandare, there are cases
against you too.
If Mr. Pradhan says Sadhu is the right
person to handle this situation..
..then he definitely is.
We'll get him back.
- Keshav!
- Yes, sir.
Call Sadhu immediately.
- Go and meet him.
- Yes, sir.
(Background Music)
Where does Sadhu Agashe live?
(Car Door Closing)
Mr. Sadhu! Mr. Sadhu!
Mr. Sadhu!
(Background Music)
(Birds Chirping)
Sir, Keshav here.
Yes. Over to Sadhu.
Home Minister Janardhan Jagirdar.
(Birds Chirping)
- Hello, sir.
- Hello, Sadhu. This is Jagirdar.
I have good news for you.
I will take care of
all the cases against you.
You have to do me a favor.
I want to revive the
defunct encounter squad.
I want you to lead the squad.
Let the cases against me continue.
If I have made a mistake,
I should be punished.
If I am right, I'll be acquitted.
You don't have to do me this favor.
Who told you I would come back?
- Listen, Sadhu..
- Thank you, sir.
How can you talk to
Mr. Jagirdar like that?
- Don't you know who he is?
- Do you?
Of course. He's the Home Minister.
So why do you ask me?
(Background Music)
(Birds Chirping)
(Car Engine Starting)
(Background Music)
(Birds Chirping)
Who was that, dad?
They lost their way.
They asked for an address.
Do you serve coconut water
to those who have lost their way?
(Chair Moving)
I have created a new tune.
(Piano Playing)
How is it?
Nice.
What are the lyrics.
Haven't thought about that.
The tune before the lyrics?
Lyrics always comes first.
Dad, tell me the poem mom had written.
'Just six of us in the house.
Four walls, roof, and I.'
"Dark night is a friend.
Bright day is an associate."
'Just six of us in the house.'
'Four walls, roof, and I.'
She wrote it to instigate me.
I would be at work all the time.
She would be alone in the house.
She spent loneliness really wonderfully.
Like your mom, you too are a good writer.
But lyrics come first, then the tune.
Dad, recite the poem again.
'Just six of us in the house.
Four walls, roof, and I.'
"Dark night is a friend.
Bright day is an associate."
'Just six of us in the house.'
'Alone, I follow my
shadow wherever it goes.'
'I feel like a bird
on this blue canvas called sky.'
'Like a dew drop on
a rainbow branch.'
(Gunshots)
'Just six of us in the house.'
- Wonderful!
'Four walls, roof, and I.'
Sadhu is bound to react that way
after what our system has done to him.
I don't know why we need Sadhu so badly.
We have to beg him to come back.
We have a fearless and aggressive
officer like Suryakant Thorat.
We will never need Sadhu.
I know Thorat very well.
He is too aggressive.
He shoots first and contemplates later.
Suryakant doesn't have
the intelligence, confidence..
..and experience that Sadhu does.
Sadhu is not a relative.
I am not promoting him.
There is no alternative to Sadhu.
Are you trying to say the police
department can't do without Sadhu?
Bhandare, things are happening in Mumbai
Despite of you being the commissioner.
You are unable to handle the situation.
That's why we need Sadhu.
Don't get into ego problems.
(Background Music)
We have Mr. Pradhan's
experience to guide us.
Don't ask him stupid questions.
Mr. Pradhan, you are right.
The way I approached Sadhu was wrong.
Sir, let me speak to Sadhu personally.
He won't refuse me.
Okay.
Great!
(Birds Chirping)
Throw it back.
Again.
(Vehicle Stopping)
Sadhu, you are playing marbles?
Uncle Pradhan?
Uncle.
How are you?
You seem to have forgotten me.
Uncle, don't fool around.
Come along.
Sure. Let me first meet your dad.
What are you doing here
while Mumbai is burning?
- What brings you here?
- I missed you.
We'll play later.
- Those are mine.
- Mine.
What are you doing?
Hurry up! Come on!
(Background Music)
These are fresh.
I just caught them.
Who taught you to cook?
His mom and circumstances.
Viswon.
It's called 'Surmai' in Mumbai.
- It's delicious.
- Really? Have some more.
I'll have to visit you often, Sadhu.
Don't go back.
(Background Music)
(Indistinct)
(Sigh)
It's so windy.
Your back should be
towards the wind direction.
- Else it falls on you.
- Quiet.
- Good.
- Quiet! Give me some water.
(Laughing)
You are still childish.
(Sighs)
- Cheers.
(Forest Ambience)
Watching it?
Yes watching. It's good.
His big brother has come.
Circumstances have changed, Sadhu.
Be careful.
New people have joined the system.
(Background Music)
The system itself is changing gradually.
For better and for..
Mr. Anna and Jagirdar.
(Birds Chirping)
They honestly want to
do something about it.
You may know about it.
Some people were unjust to you.
It might not be right to vent
your anger on these people.
Listen, Sadhu.
Every person has a purpose in life.
He should pursue it. You are a cop.
You only say that once
a cop, always a cop.
I respect you a lot.
You said some things to convince me.
You are right.
But I won't join the Force again.
You tried to convince me,
but I'm convinced by myself.
Now it's just me and my life.
I don't want to think about Force.
No. Not at all.
Me, my son..
..and these people. That's all.
I don't want to know
what's happening around us.
Don't ask why. I'm sorry.
You took so much trouble to come see me.
Genuinely, I'm sorry.
(Background Music)
(Water Splashing Sound)
(Crows Cawing)
(Car Engine Starting)
- Give it another thought.
- I already have.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Bye.
Dad, why did you refuse Uncle Pradhan?
(Background Music)
You hold yourself responsible
for mom's death.
You haven't overcome that guilt.
You fear..
..that something
might happen to me too.
That's why you left the city
to live in this village.
(Crow Cawing)
It's been years.
I have noticed many times..
..you become silent
after reading the newspaper.
You don't speak to me for days.
You endure the pain..
..upon reading those tragic news.
I can see that you are in pain.
But I can't do anything about it.
I feel guilty.
Two people feel guilty
in the house, not one.
(Water Splashing)
You peel coconuts.
You play marbles with kids.
Sometimes you clean the settlement.
You sit in a boat mid-river for hours.
For fishing.
It doesn't look nice
watching from the shore.
Dad, I don't want to be the reason
why you refused that job.
My dad is a cop.
(Birds Chirping)
Not a fisherman.
(Water Splashing)
(Background Music)
You have grown up.
(Background Music Continues)
You mistook me the other day.
I'm sorry. I respect Mr. Anna
and he respects you.
I see no difference
between the two of you.
I will try my best to control
the situation in the city.
- I trust you, Sadhu.
- I'm honored, sir.
Welcome back.
(Background Music)
Sir, Abdul Kazi.
Come.
(Background Music Continues)
Hail India, sir.
- Hail India.
- I am Jagdale.
How long have you been in crime branch?
Seven years, sir.
Reduce the fat.
I am trying, sir.
I'll surely do it.
Sir, Ghorpade.
Hi.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
- Answer it. Who is it?
- Sir, my wife.
Your wife? Answer it.
You never know when
you'll be able to talk to her again.
Hello, sir.
Suryakant Thorat.
- Sir!
- Have heard a lot about you.
I hope it is positive.
Positive as well.
- Ghorpade, order tea for everyone.
- Yes, sir.
- Where's the washroom?
- Sir, the last door to the right.
- Show it to me.
- Come on, sir.
Had heard a lot about Mr. Sadhu.
I'm glad we will get a chance
to work with him.
Not with him,
But we have to work under him.
(Telephone Ringing)
(Background Music)
Why this oldie is sitting on my head now?
If he wouldn't be there,
then I would have sat inside.
What's this? Is this some
family room in an Irani hotel?
- Put a latch here.
- Sir!
I should be able to see
what's going on outside.
Suryakant, come in.
(Door Creaking)
Sir!
The job we've been given
is nobody's father's business.
It's a government job.
Both of us have agreed
to work together. (Siren Wailing)
We should trust each other.
If we set out to bump off someone..
..we should cover each other.
Else we won't be able to
bump him off. Got that?
Sir.
(Vehicles Hinking)
Come around.
Come on.
Sit down.
Sit down. Come on.
(Background Music)
Now get up. Sit over there.
You must be thinking the department
has made an oldie your boss.
But for me, you would be in this post.
I made you sit in my chair
and rotated it.
Why?
(Telephone Ringing)
Because I am a fool.
No, sir.
- I can't think of it.
- You can't think of it.
How can you say it then?
'This oldie is the boss now.'
'But for him, I would be boss.'
Sorry, sir.
But it's true, sir.
If you weren't here then..
..I would have sat in your chair.
But I am here.
They called me back. Accept it.
We'll have to work together
to solve the problem.
You want this post.
You want the chair.
I have taken the chair.
Will you sit in my lap?
Henceforth, speak to me directly.
Don't use other people's ears
as commode. Got that?
- To err is human.
- Sir.
Go on.
Go find where the tea is.
(Background Music)
Take this.
- Will you do it?
- Yes, sir.
How can I forget you?
- How is your son?
- He has been abroad for years.
How are things here?
God has been kind.
- Here you are.
- What do I do with this?
Okay. See you.
Things are different now.
All the shooters have become businessmen.
A gang has four to six
permanent shooters.
The others work on daily basis.
Outsourcing in the underworld?
Where do they get shooters from?
There are several in the market.
Like fast food?
You just have to hire them.
They would think twice before
attacking a cop. Now things are different.
Gangsters switch gangs every day.
There's no professionalism
in this business.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
Set the table.
Want more omelet?
- No.
- What?
No.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
- Hello, who is this?
- Sadhu, do you recognize me?
Rawale. You have forgotten.
Your ***still ***paining or what?
Thanks to you.
The only consolation is..
..that I can deal with people
sitting right here in Mumbai.
You know that.
And I know that the home minister
has brought you back.
To clean up.
When will you thank me?
You should thank me.
Had I not bumped off Zameer
and your brother..
..then a computer engineer like you..
- Good morning.
- Would never have become a don.
- Apply some butter.
- How much butter will you have?
That was not for you.
Why did you call?
I want to reconcile with you.
I want to forget the past.
Come to the airport.
No.
Take it easy.
I was told you have hired
a person for advice.
Jyoti, eat.
Yes, Jyoti.
Cell no. 8 at Arthur Road jail.
You are a computer engineer and..
Hold on. I need you
to do something for me.
I have an important document
on my computer which I can't open.
I see some junk characters.
How do I open it?
First, close the file.
The touch pad isn't working.
How do I close it?
- Press Alt + F4.
- Dad, do you want more bread?
- No. You have it. This will take a minute.
- Right click on the file.
How do I right click with
a non-working touch pad?
(Birds Chirping)
Press Shift + F10 on the file.
I hope that won't delete the file.
Don't you trust me.
Select 'Open With..'
The file will open in Word.
It's done. It's done. Thank you.
- Sadhu.
- Yes.
- Congratulations on your new innings.
- I was wondering..
..who should I start
my new innings with. Rauf or you?
You have my file.
Read it and then decide.
Hang up. I have to go.
(Background Music)
Sorry. Esther..
..bring me another fork.
- Congratulations, sir.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations, Ghorpade.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Ghorpade, congratulate your wife Vaishali.
- Definitely.
What's the good news?
Sir, wedding anniversary.
Good. Congratulations.
- How many years?
- Sir, seven years.
(Telephone Ringing)
Why are you laughing?
He is celebrating 7th anniversary
with his only wife.
Shouldn't make fun about these things.
- Want a day off?
- Sir.
Go home.
Enjoy the day with your wife.
Cut a cake.
We'll make a list of guests.
Kazi, note down.
Rawale's shooter Samuel Krishna.
Head of fake currency racket
Ejaz Abbas Qureshi.
Badru. Rawale's right hand Manya.
Rauf's right hand Mushtaq.
His shooters Buraz, Shana Shakeel,
Mohsin, Afzal Pathan.
- Did you note it?
- Yes.
- I hope you haven't missed anyone.
- No, sir.
Who will be first, sir?
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Hello.
(Background Music)
- Ghorpade!
- Sir?
Make a new entry in the station diary.
We are going to carry out
an investigation.
I got a tip about Samuel Krishna.
Get the weapons! Hurry up!
- Take this. Give them to others.
- Cut the cake tomorrow. Hurry up!
Go! Go! Go!
Suryakant, you take the lead.
Go on.
Don't bump him off.
Bring him alive.
(Door Closing)
(Child Yelling)
- Hello, strong man. Wait up.
- Smarty, come on.
Come on.
Come on. Get lost.
- You didn't bring me any customer.
- Don't waste my time.
Why don't you come?
Hey!
How are you?
- I am fine.
- Is this your car?
Yes.
Let's go.
No.
Hey.
Come on.
Get lost.
- You shouldn't trouble a kid.
- Kid?
I am too small for this.
(People Chattering Indistinctly)
Come on, Sadhu.
- Want a 'vada'?
- Yes.
Hey you.
(Background Music)
Krishna.
- Mr. Suryakant?
- Krishna.
Not here. Over there.
Come on. Get dressed quickly!
Hurry up!
Come on! Come on!
- From there!
- Okay, sir.
(People Chattering Indistinctly)
Are the 'vadas' hot?
(Shouts)
- Move!
- What are you doing?
(Shouts)
(Groans)
(People Chattering Indistinctly)
(Shouts)
(Groans)
(People Chattering Indistinctly)
Stop!
Ghorpade, go straight.
Move!
(Background Music)
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Hello. Tell me.
Now? I don't know..
..how long it will take.
(Car Engine Starting)
Eat up.
(Car Leaving)
Sir, are you going to bump me off?
It's his wedding anniversary.
We brought you here to cut the cake.
We'll get some information
out of you and let you go.
Who were involved in the
contract killing of Kailash Prasad?
Ejaz for sure.
Manya and who else?
Who gives the order?
Taimur? Who gives the order?
Rawale.
- Who gives the orders?
- I said Rawale.
How is he?
- What do you mean?
- He's your boss.
How is he?
Does he pay you on time?
Yes.
Why did you leave him?
He is selfish. He doesn't trust me.
(Vehicle Screeching Noise)
He suspects me. So I left him.
I started my own business.
Alone or in partnership?
Alone, sir.
Will you take me in your gang?
What is wrong with this place?
Shopping?
Are you crazy?
We can shop for the festival later.
(Gunshots)
(Vehicle Screeching Noise)
(Bicycle Bell Ringing)
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Bye.
- Stop. Where are you going?
- I want to meet the department head.
You can't go inside
without an appointment.
I have an appointment.
I have to meet Sadhu Agashe.
I want to talk to him.
- No, no, not at all.
- Hey! What's wrong?
What kind of men have you
appointed here? He has no manners.
- I have an appointment.
- Come up. Come up.
- Let her come.
- Fine. Go in.
- Sir, I am Shalu Dixit, crime reporter.
- So?
Is there a press conference here?
Sir, I am not here
for the press conference.
May I know why the Home Minister..
..called you back although
he has a plethora of officers?
You are asking the wrong
question to the wrong man.
You should ask this question
to the Home Minister.
If he gives you an answer
then come and tell me as well.
So you don't want to tell me.
Sir, I know a lot about you.
Those you killed, those you didn't.
Even why you killed them and why not.
Why do such R&amp;D about me?
Not me, Anant Dixit did this R&amp;D.
I am his daughter.
It's a small world.
You are Anant's daughter.
Father was writing
a book on Encounter Cops.
- When..
- Aslam shot him.
And then you shot Aslam.
I want to complete that book.
He genuinely understood the department.
He never wrote anything
wrong about the department.
I need your help in completing his book.
Only you can supply
me with such information.
The police department never gives..
..any information until you
don't grease their palm.
Normally pigeons and
crows shit in this place.
We are lucky today.
(Vehicles Honking)
- Would you like something to eat?
- No, sir. Thank you.
What can I offer?
Indian burger. Our staple food.
Sir, you weren't here for a long time.
Where were you? What were you doing?
- I was fishing in Goa.
- What?
You want to know everything in one day.
Forget about me,
tell me something about yourself.
A series of professions and yet..
..you became a crime reporter. Why?
(Vehicles Honking)
I didn't choose this profession,
it chose me.
Father was on crime beat.
All day he would talk
about the same thing at home.
We would already know..
..what people would
read in papers the next day.
I would be surprised at how he knew it.
Maybe that's when I decided..
(Vehicles Honking)
..that I want to be a crime reporter.
And then when that incident
occurred with him..
..I started hating this profession.
But there was a subconscious attraction.
And in this dilemma..
..I don't know when
I took up this profession.
And now, I love my job.
Anant. Absolutely Anant.
Like father like daughter.
Am I boring you?
Anant always asked the same question..
..and I would always say, "Yes."
(Cell Phone Ringing)
- Hello.
- (Honking)
Yes.
Okay. Okay.
- Sorry. I have to go. I have a meeting.
- Okay.
- We will meet again?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Okay. Finish your tea. Bye.
(Car Engine Starting)
You asked me to lead.
I did.
See... you are in focus
and we are out of focus.
I asked the photographer
to keep all of you out of focus.
What do you think?
Staying in focus will make you a hero?
You have to pay a price
for staying in focus.
I am not afraid of paying the price, sir.
If you stay in focus..
..many people will
be ready to kill you.
Stay out of focus and
you live a little longer.
Everyone has to die, sir.
So why not do it staying in focus?
At least my son should
know who he is idolizing.
Next time I will ask
him to keep you in focus..
..for the sake of your son.
He will never change.
Killing you is easier
than explaining to you.
(Background Music)
In '98 we had similar information.
There was a new recruit, Bingar Dhiwe.
Zestful like you.
In the chaos I shot him.
(Birds Chirping)
He was shot on his right shoulder.
It was an accident.
He got well later.
Anything can happen.
Suryakant, you lead today.
Me?
- Yes.
- No, sir.
- I don't want to, sir.
- Why?
- You lead the team.
- You will be in focus. (Eagle Screaming)
What focus, sir?
I was just joking, sir.
I am not joking, honestly.
What do you think, Kazi?
- Yes.
- Yes what?
What?
Sir is senior.
Sir, you lead the way.
We are there, sir.
We are behind you, sir.
I never shot anyone.
I was just joking.
Come on.
- No, sir. Not for that, sir.
- What?
Not for that, sir. You do it.
We are there.
(Birds Chirping)
(Background Music)
Forget him.
You stay here.
Ghorpade, come here.
You go, Kazi. Go there.
(Background Music Continues)
'Zestful like you.'
'In the chaos I shot him.'
(Footsteps)
- Sadhu sir?
- He is on the other side of the boat.
'It was an accident.
It can happen anything at anytime'.
Sadhu sir?
'Suryakant.'
Go that way.
'Killing you is easier
than explaining to you.'
(Background Music)
'In the chaos I shot him'.
Toba, I am going to take a nap.
Take a nap once you finish working.
- Come on.
- Fine.
(Groans)
(Gunshots)
(Eagles Screaming)
We managed to achieve
a lot in such a short time.
What makes me most proud is that
an officer like Sadhu is with us.
And seems like our goal is not far.
- Sir.
- Here comes Sadhu.
- Come, Sadhu. (Telephone Ringing)
We were talking about you.
I feel proud that we have officers
like you in our system.
Sir. Compared to you
we are doing nothing.
- You are being modest.
- No, sir.
Your deeds, your ideals..
..no one in Maharashtra
can match up to them.
(Telephone Ringing)
Yes.
Hold on. Hold on.
- Sadhu.
- Sir.
What I regret is that as long
as Gandhi was pinned up on walls..
..we idolized him.
Once we started printing
him on currencies..
..we forgot about him.
Their responsibility ends
after felicitating their ideals.
This is what the new
generation thinks. What to do?
Sadhu, the way you
are leading your squad..
..in annihilating these
anti-social elements..
..one needs a set of ideals
and unlimited courage to do that.
- Well done.
- Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
So this is what I was talking about?
Jagirdar and Anna sir are good people.
It's hard to find such
people in politics these days.
Okay, father.
Then I will join politics.
Become a leader.
And anyway, you don't want me
to take up music as a profession.
I never said that.
I only said that you should take up
something else along with music.
If you want to enter politics,
then go ahead.
But remember, politics is not a business.
It's a profession.
If you want to do something for
the people then go ahead. (Doorbell)
Sit, sit, sit. I will open the door.
- Come.
- Hi, sir.
Welcome. Welcome.
Aman.
She is my friend's daughter, Shalu.
- Hi.
Her father was writing
a book on encounter cops.
It was left incomplete.
She is completing that.
My son Aman.
Does he play the piano?
He writes too.
Oh!
You two writers can chat while
I get something for you to eat.
- Father, please don't make eggs.
- No eggs today.
Today I will make your mother's
special 'Sambhar' (Lentil).
Remember what your mother
would call 'Hing' (asafetida)?
- She called it 'Hing'. What else?
- Hey, Mozart.
Rest of the world call it 'Hing'..
..your mother would call it 'Kayam'.
- Nice house, sir.
- It's nice.
Given to me by the government.
Feels like my native place. Nice. Sit.
(Piano Playing)
- Aman.
- Yes.
I need your help too for that book.
Me?
(Cell Phone Ringing)
- Hello.
- Hello, Sadhu sir.
- We have a tip on Eijaz.
- Okay.
- He is coming tonight.
- When is he leaving?
- I am sorry to bring this up.
- No. It's okay.
You were there when your mother was shot?
Yes.
What was your father's mental condition?
I can't remember clearly,
but it was chaotic.
I was quite scared.
Father... wasn't calm,
but he was amazingly composed.
I never understood him all these years.
Even though I am his son,
I never understood him.
Confirm the flight number and inform me.
(Doorbell)
Sir, shall I open it?
- Who is that?
- Postman.
(Background Music)
What is it?
- Registered mail.
- What name?
Sadhu Agashe.
(Gunshots)
(Groans)
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Sadhu.
Father.
I got your letter.
Your postman is lying here.
My postman? I didn't understand.
I have called to thank you.
You did my work by killing
Krishna and Qureshi.
They were betraying me.
Thanks.
You have kept yourself
physically fit even at this age.
That's why you overpowered
people half your age.
Sir, when you are facing death,
everything becomes easy.
A cop should stay fit not
just when he is in the force..
..but also when he is retired.
Bullets don't give consideration to age.
Who knows when one might need it?
I have reached the retiring age,
Sadhu, not you.
Come.
But I feel..
Thank you.
I feel... when a man reaches this age..
..his ability to rationalize
and exploit people gets better.
That's why the politicians of our
country don't want to retire.
Maybe.
(Birds Chirping)
- But one thing, Sadhu.
- Sir.
Whenever a man reaches
the peak of his career..
..with the experience
he has garnered..
..he wants to do something
for the society and the country.
And that's when our system retires him.
Irony.
Everyone is busy increasing their
vote bank and Swiss Bank figures.
No one has time or intention to think
for the interest of the people.
If we have a few more
politicians like Jagirdar sir..
..then something is
possible in the future.
People say that his past..
I am thinking of the future
and you are stuck in the past.
(Honking)
There are always allegations
against politicians.
But take it from me.
He is a very genuine guy.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Yes, Rawle. What is it?
Sadhu, I found out about your postman.
- You were amazing.
- Let's meet and I will do better.
(Laughs)
You never met again.
I am driving at the moment.
Here, talk to Shalu.
She is a crime reporter.
She will print your
interview on the first page.
Here. Talk to her.
What will I say to Rawle?
You are a journalist, ask him anything.
- But still.
- What?
- Ask him about his girlfriend.
- Girlfriend?
Are you mocking me?
You got emotional when
asked about your girlfriend.
Did it remind you of an old wound?
He hung up?
Tell Manya I want news about
Sadhu's every movement.
Yes, boss.
Boss, Prasad is here.
Why you called him here at this hour?
Boss, he wants to apologize.
He says he was mistaken.
And what is the guarantee
he won't make a mistake again?
I guarantee that, boss.
I know him well.
Call him.
Send him in.
Rawle..
There is just one way
to clear misconceptions.
Forget about yourself,
never vouch for others.
People change with time.
I need a trustworthy boy
in Mumbai in place of Krishna.
Your brother's son.
- What's his name?
- Babu.
Appoint him on the job.
But I will give someone
more trustworthy and capable.
No. I want Babu.
I don't want any guarantee for him.
You are there.
We have received news
from IB Delhi that..
..the underworld is trying to carry out
a big terrorist activity in Mumbai.
I thought Rawle is behind it.
But the IB says it's not Rawle.
Rauf is going to do this job.
We have to eliminate both.
But for the time being
you concentrate on Rauf.
- Sir.
- Yes. Tell me.
Manya is coming to meet Jadhav
this evening at his cow-shed.
(Indistinct)
- Is the news confirmed?
- Yes, Mushtaq.
Last night he was
with Shabnam and Ruksana.
Remember, if the news is wrong,
I will shoot you.
Why would I lie to you, son?
- But my reward?
- You will get it.
- Boss.
- What is it?
Boss, we have a tip on Manya.
Here are 500,000 rupees
and a plane ticket.
Stay in your village for four months.
(Background Music)
Mushtaq, stay close.
(Cow Mooing)
(Background Music Continues)
(Cows Mooing)
- Hello.
Was the old hag lying?
Oh Lord!
(Dogs Barking)
(Gunshots)
Why did you open fire?
I thought they saw Ghorpade, sir.
(Cow Mooing)
(Cows Mooing)
- Mushtaq.
- Yes.
You handle this side.
I will handle things there.
(Panting)
(Groans)
(Background Music)
You spilled Mustaq's blood on milk.
Now watch.
I will spill yours and
Jagirdar's blood on cow-dung.
Look, Rauf.
(Birds Chirping)
Lord has made nine holes in a human body.
Two ears, two nostrils, two eyes.
One mouth.
And you know the other two.
If you dream about hurting Jagirdar..
..I will make the 10th hole.
For the society, we cops..
..are wrong if we do something wrong..
..and even if we do something right.
Thankless job.
- Sadhu.
- Sir.
Come.
My son Aman.
- I see.
- Hello, sir.
Come, son. Come.
Sit here. Come.
Your father is a hero.
Come. Sit.
I don't get the time,
but I do have a few hobbies..
..like photography, music..
Sir, music is... not my hobby,
it's my passion.
Good.
He is crazy about music
since his school days.
His harmonium is still lying in my home.
I feel really happy
when I see kids like him.
- Jagirdar.
- Yes.
If you hadn't sworn to celibacy..
..even you would have
got a son like Aman.
Aman is like my son.
Aman, you are right.
A person has many hobbies,
but only one passion.
That's okay.
What about profession?
Bread-butter.
Sir, I... want to turn my
passion into my profession.
But, sir, what's wrong with music?
Nothing.
But there is a difference
between profession and passion.
There should be.
(People Chattering Indistinctly)
But what could be better..
..if your passion
becomes your profession?
It seems nice in movies,
not in real life.
Sir, I think Aman has a point.
We have a point too.
I am his father. I worry for him.
That's why I say it.
Once you have kids,
you will know what I mean.
What's the point of regretting
after your entire life..
..slips through your
hands chasing your passion?
So you are one of those
stereotyped parents..
..who want to make their son lawyer,
engineer or doctor.
I am a middle-class father.
I think the same way.
I am not different.
But anyway, right now he
will do as he pleases.
It's his life. I am with
him as long as I am there.
Very humble chap.
I will be with him.
(Gunshots)
Run! Run!
(People Chattering Indistinctly)
- Run! Run!
- Run quickly.
Get the bike!
Let's go. Let's go.
(Background Music)
(Birds Chirping)
Pradhan sir has come.
Coming.
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Sadhu, this shouldn't have happened.
You lost your only son.
I am sorry.
No one knows who is going
to serve the last blow.
Involving the family isn't right.
Rauf committed a sin.
And he should be punished for it.
If you need my help, let me know.
I will always be there for you.
(Background Music)
I don't want your sympathy.
Thanks for coming.
(Background Music)
'You play marbles with kids.'
'Sometimes you clean the settlement.'
'You sit in a boat
mid-river for hours.'
'For fishing.'
'It doesn't look nice
watching from the shore.'
'Dad, I don't want to be the reason
why you refused that job.'
'My dad is a cop.'
'Not a fisherman.'
(Background Music Continues)
Sadhu.
Everyone is destined for some bad luck.
What happened was very wrong.
But sometimes you have to
forget the wrongs for the right.
Mission is more important than emotion.
And this is not our personal mission.
A reputed police officer getting
attacked in broad-daylight..
..is humiliating for the system.
From here on whatever you do..
..there should be no place
for personal emotions.
The system wants to eradicate them.
Whether I do it for
the society or for myself.
It doesn't make a
difference to the system.
Sir, Sadhu sir is clear..
..that it was Rauf's shooter Bhura.
Impossible.
He wasn't in Mumbai that day.
Ghorpade,
what's the news on Bhura?
Sir..
..as far as I know..
..Bhura isn't responsible
for your son's death.
- He wasn't in Mumbai..
- Just do what I say.
Only I will give orders
and rack my brains here.
Your brains will work if
you were in your senses, right?
Sir!
(Background Music)
Sir, you being senior
doesn't entitle you to hit me...
Speak to me at my face. Not behind me.
(Background Music Continues)
(Vehicle Passing Sound)
- Where is Altaf Bhai's home?
- There.
Yes?
I want to speak to Altaf Bhai.
Who is it?
- She has come to meet you.
- Please come.
Do you know this person?
The police are also looking for him.
I will inform you as soon
as I have any information.
(Person Shouting Indistinctly)
It is imperative that I find him.
Hey! Bhura Bhai!
Do you know him?
Bhura is going to Hyderabad
tonight by train.
(Train Sound)
(Train Announcement)
(Background Music)
(Sighs)
(Shouting)
Sir.
(Groan)
Who has sent?
Rauf had sent, sir.
Where is Rauf?
I G Hospital.
(People Chattering Indistinctly)
(Background Music)
Son, have him admitted
to a good hospital.
Mother, we cannot take him anywhere else.
Tell me, if you have any problem here.
I will go to the washroom.
Father, I am Rauf. Rauf.
Have you got these medicines?
I am asking you.
The doctor is asking you
if you have got these medicines.
Yes, go to sleep.
I think she is dumb.
If any of your other relatives come
ask them to get the medicines.
They are important.
(Background Music)
Rauf, if you move I will shoot you.
- Where are you going?
- Bathroom.
- Will you be able to manage?
- Yes.
All right. Go.
Look Sadhu, I want to kill you for sure.
If I get a chance
I can kill you even now.
But I am not emotional.
I have not killed your son.
Bura betrayed me and joined Rawle's gang.
He attacked you and your son was killed.
(Groan)
I made a mistake.
I accept that I am lying.
(Groan)
Sadhu, I have got information.
If I tell you that, you
will have to let me go.
Rawle's henchman has told me..
..that he has accepted the contract
of killing Anna Saheb.
Anna Saheb.
Rawle told his minion.
And he told you. Are you related?
Sadhu, believe me.
I lied to you at first to save my life.
You were correct in not believing me.
But this time,
I am telling you the truth.
But you do not believe me.
You will be sorry. Don't be emotional.
Do you know who has ordered
Rawle to kill Anna Saheb?
You will be shocked to hear his name.
(Gunshots)
It was an order from the top brass.
To kill Rauf and to follow you.
You killed. I killed. It was an order.
Bhandare.
(Background Music)
Rauf was lying even before he died.
What did he say?
He said that Rawle has accepted
a contract to kill Anna Saheb.
Who will want to kill Anna Saheb?
Before he could say
anything Suryakant shot him.
But Rauf was blabbering.
He was trying to distract
me so that he could escape.
This is what criminals usually do.
He also said that..
..not him but Rawle had killed Aman.
I have heard that Rawle
is returning to India.
Is he planning to die?
(Cell Phone Ringing)
Hello? What? Sir.
What happened?
'Today's breaking news
is that chief minister..'
'..Anna Saheb has been murdered.'
'We are not able to
trace the murderer yet.'
'Anna Saheb was attacked
on his way to Pune.'
'You can see a huge crowd collected
here.' (Cell Phone Ringing)
(TV News)
Rauf was right.
- Hello, sir.
- Sadhu.
Come and meet me at
City Hospital immediately.
I have to discuss Anna Saheb's
assassination. Come here fast.
Sir!
(Background Music)
(Mob Shouting)
(People Chattering Indistinctly)
Sir!
How are you connected to Rawle?
- Call Pawar.
- Yes.
I am impressed.
I knew that you would
come to know of it one day.
But so soon...
- I am impressed.
- Sir.
- Yes.
- Mr. Pawar is here.
Tell him to arrange a long trailer.
A long one.
Yes.
Everyone in politics wishes to lead.
And I couldn't lead till
Anna Saheb was there.
- Sawant.
- Yes, sir.
The cutout should be huge.
I need flowers. White, orange, green.
I need flags. It should
look like the tri colored flag.
Politicians need both
the underworld and police..
..to control the system.
Things which police can't
do can be done by the rogues.
Like this accident.
It is important that a
city shouldn't have two gangs.
Otherwise a third might
use the second gang.
What is your name?
Please go outside. Out.
(Mob Shouting)
I used the underworld
to get rid of the people..
..who were against me in politics.
And I used loyal police
officers like you to get..
..rid of people who were
against me in the underworld.
Rawle and Rauf's enmity
was useful in ruining..
..the crime situation of Mumbai.
Anna Saheb was pressurized.
And he was forced to
appoint me as home minister.
(Background Music)
- Rauf...
- Mr. Jagirdar.
You dealt with Rauf.
So now Rawle will also stay quite now.
This is politics.
You should have the skill
to use things at the right time.
You should know how
to mess up good things..
..and how to straighten up bad things.
You didn't understand. Okay.
You are a very ordinary
part of the system.
A very small part.
But I am system.
The work for which you
had been brought here is over.
Now you are no longer required here.
I am also disbanding the squad.
If you tell anyone about it,
no one will trust you.
Because after Anna Saheb
the people love me.
You are shocked to hear this, right?
If you stay with me, then I
will take care of you for life.
But if you are still
entrapped in the web of..
..god-bad, just-unjust then
take a picture of Anna Saheb.
Venerate it.
(Background Music)
If you want to stay with me then okay.
If you don't then that's okay too.
Think about it before you decide.
Yes.
(Background Music)
(Piano Playing)
'Papa.'
(Background Music)
I gave my life to the force.
What did I get?
I lost as a husband and a father.
I even lost as a policeman.
And now I know that we are
paid by the underworld.
No matter what,
we have to expose Jagirdar.
Jagirdar is far more cunning than us.
Sir, I have a got a lead regarding
Jagirdar and Rawle's connection.
Nothing is possible.
Forget everything.
- How can you let go so easily?
- It is not easy for me to say so.
I have committed a lot of mistakes.
I don't have anything else to lose.
You must have collected a lot
of material for your book.
(Crickets Chirping)
Don't come here again.
Complete your father's incomplete book.
Take the constable along.
All the best, baby. Take care.
(Background Music)
(Machine Sound)
Have you returned to
India for any special reason?
I cannot stay away from my motherland.
I couldn't have survived
here till Rauf was alive.
Now since Rauf is dead I have returned
to my people. (Camera Clicks)
And it's such a great feeling.
In spite of knowing that you have
many cases registered against you..
..aren't you scared of punishment?
Of course not. I am innocent.
I trust the system and I am
sure that I will get justice.
And with regards to legal aspects
you can refer to my lawyer.
We have heard that you
are planning to join politics.
I haven't planned anything yet.
If my fellow countrymen
allow me to serve the country..
..then I will try my best
to return what I have got from it.
We have heard that you are
connected to the chief minister.
Thank you.
Sir, I think Rawle thinks that..
..there are no proofs against him.
But he should know
that the encounter squad..
..doesn't require proof.
Bhandare, do you think that we
still require the encounter squad?
I don't think so.
Rawle, is a gangster
but unless he is being..
..convicted of the
crimes he is accused of..
..you will be responsible
for his protection.
But sir...
Follow the orders.
Sir.
(Camera Clicks)
Who will take over Anna
Saheb's responsibilities?
No one can replace Anna Saheb. No one.
Well known criminal
Rawle is joining politics.
Is there any political connection to it?
Maybe you have forgotten
that in democracy it is..
..not right to call someone
a criminal till he is convicted.
But you all start the
media trial before the court.
This is wrong.
If Rawle doesn't have
political connection..
..then on whose support and
protection he is returning to India.
Who is supporting him to announce
openly that he is joining politics?
Madam, I am telling you again
that today we have gathered..
..for minister Anna Saheb...
Mr. Minister,
you are changing the subject.
Answer our question.
I am not changing the subject.
Sit down.
Where has she come from?
What kind of journalist...
Don't you understand?
There is some ethics.
Please sit down.
Sir, Anna Saheb
didn't die of natural causes.
It was an assassination.
It is being investigated
and it will be completed.
When will it get investigated?
When will you tell us about it?
Today is your chance to tell
us what steps are being taken..
..to complete the investigation
of his assassination...
Let me speak. Sit down.
- It was an assassination.
- Yes, I know.
Teach her. Where do
these kids come from?
What is the name of your university?
What is your name?
Shalu Dixit.
(Background Music)
Don't underestimate that girl.
She is very intelligent.
Very intelligent.
I know sir.
She is also connected to Sadhu.
Very intelligent.
Okay, sir.
Sir, I have got proof of
connection of Rawle and Jagirdar.
I am in Bandra right now.
I am heading to Sachivalaya.
Behind the Gandhiji Park. Let's go.
(Tyre Screeching Sound)
Take this.
(Background Music)
Yes, I am here. Where are you?
(Honking)
Hello? Jyoti.
I will tell you the reason later.
A few weeks back Jagirdar's PA Keshav..
..had gone to London to meet Rawle.
To give him the contract
to kill Anna Saheb.
Rawle made me record this meeting.
So that if ever Jagirdar
plots against Rawle..
..then even Rawle will be
able to use this CD against Jagirdar.
I made a copy of that
CD without informing Rawle.
We no longer have
an amiable relationship.
Now I will avenge whatever
he had done to me by killing him.
(Tyre Screeching Sound)
The CD...
(Groan)
(Gunshots)
(Vehicle Sound)
(Vehicle Passing By)
Shalu.
Look.
- Sir. What is the matter, sir?
- Sir?
Shalu is in the ICU. Stay outside.
- Take care of her.
- Yes, sir.
- Stay here.
- But sir you...
(Background Music)
Whatever I say anything
about Anna Sir is less.
He was more attached since college
days into social movement.
He was a part of it.
Society was only his family.
He dedicated his whole life
into the society.
And he even said that
the root of the sadness,
Is because of economic inequality.
We have to get rid of this problem.
I had promised Anna Saheb
that I will fulfill his dream.
But I...
(Background Music)
I am just a medium.
I want...
Your support.
Anna Saheb worked till his last breath..
..to change our weak system.
So we will have to
change this system forever.
Anna Saheb had dreamt
of a self-sufficient..
..self-reliant and
an advanced Maharashtra.
And we fulfilling his
dream will be the best way..
..to portray our regards for him.
Hail India. Hail Maharashtra.
(Background Music)
You have taken the right decision.
- Welcome to the system.
- Thank you, sir.
May I say a few words about Anna Saheb?
Yes.
- Thank you.
- Go.
I pay homage to Anna Saheb.
I have not touched
anyone's feet till date.
That includes my parents,
teacher and God.
But I touched his because
he has changed my life.
(Background Music)
You might know me.
I am Sadhu Agashe. Encounter Cop.
I clean up garbage.
If garbage gets collected
in your area for 7-8 days..
..the place becomes full of stench.
The garbage van comes, cleans off
area and the stench disappears.
In the same way when crime
rate increases in the society..
..great people like Jagirdar call
people like us to clean up.
Usually there are no
witnesses for encounters.
We do this dirty work in private.
So that there is no proof.
But I want to do one encounter
in front of everyone.
(Background Music)
So that people ask
me why I have done this.
(Groan)
Stop him.
(Gasps)
(Shouts)
Hey!
Take care. Take care of him.
Go and get the ambulance.
(Shouts)
(Siren Wailing)
(Camera Clicks)
(Shouts)
When I left the force I
had done 56 encounters.
This one encounter is equal to 56.
The matter didn't end here.
This was just the beginning.
This will happen. This should happen.
Many such people like Jagirdar are..
..powerful personas in politics.
They have different names
but they are same.
It is the responsibility
of the new generation..
..to finish off this dirt altogether.
Such politicians are the biggest mafia.
We cannot do anything
against them lawfully.
They should be encountered like this.
In front of everyone. In public.
We need a force for that.
I am sure they will
do it for their future.
They will have to do it.
I have run so far. Now they will run.
I don't know what you think about me.
But I am proud to be a cop..
..and always will be a cop.
(Background Music)
I must say thanks to my child Aman.
He insisted.
Because of him I came back to force.
Thank you.
You might feel that
I did this for myself.
Do you think it is personal?
I don't think so.
(Background Music)
(Footsteps)
Take care of Aman.
(Background Music)
I will.
(Background Music Continues)