'Inter-state bus terminus'
'Fine builders'
Come on, move!
- "Glory to Lord Rama!"
"Glory to Lord Krishna!"
"Glory to Lord Rama!"
Is that him?
- Please let me go.
I don't know, sir.
Please let me go.
Buy oranges!
"Lord Ram."
Let me go, sir.
I don't know.
I think it's him.
"Lord Ram. Lord Krishna."
"Lord Ram."
Government hospital?
Good morning, professor Govind.
- Yes.
I said, good morning,
Professor Govind.
You're mistaken.
My name is Dharamprakash.
Govind, Dharamprakash,
Wilson, Srivastav, Deshpande...
Choose any name,
it makes no difference to me.
Adil Khan, Senior S.P. Bhopal.
I know.
I've been waiting for four years
to meet you.
Shall we?
There are many charges on him
from here to Nandighat.
'Govind Ram Suryavanshi.'
'He was born in a rich
business family in Mumbai.'
'After passing out of the renowned
Doon School of our country,'
'he studied at the
London School of Economics.'
'After completing his doctorate
from Oxford University'
'he returned to India.'
'Touched by the exploitation
of the poor,'
'he gave up everything
and joined the Maoist movement.'
Mr Govind has been underground
for past 30 years.
He's known as important ideologue
of the Naxal Movement.
'Naxalism,'
'which the Prime Minister
Manmohan Singh'
'thinks the biggest threat
to internal security.'
'More than 200 districts in the
country is affected by it.'
'It all started 45 years ago'
'in Naxalbari,
a village in Bengal,'
'when poor farmers killed a
landlord'
'to swan their right
over their land.'
'Naxalism started from there.'
'Naxalism has spread to
East Karnataka, Andhra Pradesh,'
'Maharashtra, Bengal, Bihar,'
'Odisha, Jharkhand,
and many other states.'
'Thousands of tribals
have taken up arms.'
'They are fighting against
the system of the country.'
'It is believed that the tribals'
'are given'
'arms and training from terrorist
organisations in India and abroad.'
'The reason for the increase
of Naxalism in these areas is that'
'there's been no development here
for the last 65 years.'
'Today you speak of development'
'only because under that pretext,
you want to seize their land'
'which is rich in iron,
manganese, coal,'
'bauxite and many other minerals.'
Look,
it is simple,
unless we utilise these
natural resources in the land,
how can there be development?
That is why we are signing
this 15 billion agreement with
the huge Mahanta Group!
And the rehabilitation plan
for the tribals is ready.
As Chairman of the Mahanta Group,
I want to assure you all that
the needs of Nandighat
people will be fulfilled.
Concrete houses for the tribals,
hospitals, an international school,
and a world class university.
Along with business,
the Mahanta Group takes its social
responsibility very seriously.
Mr Mahanta,
will there be seats for
tribal children in your
world class university?
Look...
- Sir,
it's obvious that the tribals
do not want to move.
Will they be moved by force?
Look,
when the media succumbs
to Maoist propaganda,
how will the public know the truth?
The tribals are our brothers.
No one can force them.
Force will be used
only against the Naxals.
Their menace will be wiped out
from Nandighat.
This is the government's promise.
We are all ready.
What I don't understand is
while you advocate democracy,
you're unwilling to speak with the
government of the
world's biggest democracy.
I don't believe in a democracy
which doesn't respect the poor.
We shall talk about your
extremist violence
and police counter-violence
some other day, Professor.
For now, I just want to ask
some basic questions.
Before you waste your time
on meaningless questions,
let me clarify,
I only do three things now,
reading, writing,
and teaching.
You can ask me any question
related to this, I will answer.
Other than that,
I won't say a word.
And that's my right, too.
Professor, if you choose to
stay quiet, fine.
In my records,
you're responsible for the death
of 91 policemen
and 150 innocent civilians.
KK,
how are things in Nandighat?
Fantastic!
You've shaken the entire Movement
by arresting Govind Suryavanshi.
Did he give any information
about Nandighat?
Not yet, but Rhea won't spare him.
Give my regards to Rhea.
By the way,
isn't your college reunion today?
Yes, it will be a boring party.
But we will have a blast tonight.
Lots of fireworks.
- Why?
Are you planning something?
Is it an encounter? Tell me.
I'll make an encounter to remember.
I'll kill one such leader that
you'll be celebrating all year.
Who? Rajan?
Be patient, my friend.
Read it in tomorrow's newspaper.
I can't bloody wait.
Get that rascal!
- 'I will.'
Who is it?
- Somebody named Kabir.
Kabir?
Hello, Kabir?
Is that really you?
'The one and only!'
Oh God, I don't believe this.
Where have you been, man!
'I'm good. I'm here, Rhea.'
Wow! Are you coming to the party?
'Yes, but where is my friend?'
Right here.
It's Kabir!
Even he is attending
the college party.
You've been angry for 7 years.
It'll give you an ulcer.
Can't you forgive him?
You are acting like a kid.
'How can I say
what Kabir meant for me?'
'He was more than a friend to me.'
'He had no one else in this world,
but for me.'
'What are you doing?'
'I was day dreaming.'
'I'm going back to the
government college now.'
'As it is, the course was tough'
'and now they have
raised the fees too.'
'Your fees have been paid.'
'I don't want your dad's money.'
'I used dad's money
to pay my fees.'
'With my scholarship,
I paid yours.'
'What's this?
- Our future.'
'Look boss,'
'until now we did
everything together,'
'but now our paths are different.'
'Stop delivering dialogues
and just sign the form.'
'But, I don't want to do this.'
'No ifs and buts.'
'I'll make you a cop,
come on, sign it.'
'Freezing cold, torrential rains,
or scorching heat,'
'in thunderstorms or floods,
night or day,'
'once you're on duty,
nothing else matters.'
'You have to stand,'
'come what may.'
'Sir, what do we do
if we want to pee?'
'Reform yourself, Kabir.
You joke all the time.'
'Stop this nonsense.'
'You are speaking nonsense.'
'Your seats are reserved...
- No, Kabir!'
'One moment.
- What are you doing, Mahesh?'
'Let him go.'
'This is not the way to talk to a
weak person. - Who are you?'
'I had asked Kabir
not to get involved in any fights.'
'Let it be, Kabir.'
'And not ruin his life
over petty fights. - Stop it!'
'I said stop it!
- But Kabir...'
'Leave him.
- I say leave him!'
'He could never control himself.'
'I cannot apologise.'
'This is how I am,'
'and this is how I will be!'
'If you knew this already,
why did you bring me here?'
'I made a mistake! A big mistake!'
'Dad was right.'
'You can never achieve something.'
'Don't ever show me
your face again!'
'After all these years...'
'I don't know where was he,
what was he up to.'
'Now, he shows up himself.'
'Does he think
I'll give him a hug?'
Kabir!
This guy...
Forgive me, my lord and master!
I will never disobey you!
You're my master.
If you don't forgive me today,
I'll kill myself.
I'll do everything you say.
Stop being melodramatic.
Nothing much...
I did some boring jobs for a while
then joined an electronics company.
And then, I started making
my own mobile phones.
What, mobile phones?
- Yes.
Your own brand?
Have you ever tried this handset?
RAK?
What is RAK mobile?
You'll never reform.
R.A.K.
Rhea, Adil, Kabir!
- Yes!
No wonder it flopped.
Flopped?
The first consignment sold out
in MP and Chhattisgarh in a jiffy.
But after two months...
there were complaints
and the dealers stopped paying.
The bank guys came home.
I had a fight with them.
I ended up hitting a cop.
They arrested me.
You hit a cop?
Well done.
So, for how long
were you locked up?
Let it be.
At least he's back.
Good evening, sir.
12 km from here, a village fair
is being held at Tulasi mountain.
We got information that the Naxals
are holding a zonal meet there.
Central Committee members, Shivram
and Chakravarthy are expected.
The Zonal Commander,
Rajan, will also be present.
Rajan?
How true is your information?
We've cross checked it, sir.
Intelligence has confirmed it too.
They're planning to retaliate
against Govind's arrest.
Alright.
Keep me informed.
I will be in the Control Room
in an hour's time.
Right, sir.
Sir, please leave from there.
Comrades have gathered
behind the temple.
Their meeting is about to begin.
'Sir, Kamal Kishor here.'
Hello KK, Rathod here.
'Good evening, sir.'
We have the confirmation.
Rajan is here.
He's 400 yards away
from the target.
Good, very good, KK.
Don't let Rajan get away, SP!
Kill him in an encounter.
Just finish him!
That was the
Home Minister speaking, KK.
Sir.
Be very careful, KK.
- Sir.
KK, can you hear me?
Try the second line.
Hurry up!
KK!
"Always be prepared
for the worst..."
KK, can you hear me?
KK...
- Oh God!
Sir...
- KK, can you hear us?
Sir, it's a trap.
We are surrounded.
Hello, KK?
'No entry'
Lal Salam! (Red Salute)
- Lal Salam!
Lal Salam!
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, can you tell us
about the massacre...
Sir, can you please tell us
which group has done this?
Sir...
- We're investigating the matter.
We'll talk with you later.
- Sir...
Sir, can you please tell us how long
it will take for the investigation?
'The massacre of 84 policemen,'
'paramilitary personnel
at Nandighat is confirmed.'
'Their funeral with state honours'
'will take place
at 4 o'clock today.'
'Meanwhile, Naxalite leader Rajan'
'spoke to the media
at an unidentified location.'
'We wish to declare
before the world,'
'though the stooges
of the government'
'falsely label us
murderers and terrorists,'
'every attack of ours
is in defence of poor tribals'
'who have been crushed
by the police and the state.'
'We will not allow the government to
take even one inch of tribal land.'
'Lal Salam.'
'After the massacre of the
Nandighat, the Naxal zonal...'
You have to take the responsibility
of this massacre.
But sir,
the Home Minister himself
allowed the attack.
He was in the Control room...
When did I give you permission?
Did I say
the information is accurate
and send them charging?
In fact,
you conned me into it, DGP.
Please, don't blame me
for your failure.
'This incident raises questions
about the Mahanta deal.'
'Prashant Mahanta, the Chairman
of the Mahanta Group'
'has called a press conference.'
'We take you to his headquarters.'
'Where even the police
and CRPF aren't safe,'
'how can we risk setting up
a plant there?'
'Until the government guarantees
the life of every worker,'
'we will not begin any work.'
'After Mahanta's statement...'
Tell us, DGP,
are you capable of dealing
with this problem
or do I ask Mr Mahanta
to sign the agreement
with Rajan instead?
Show some action, DGP.
Action.
Sir.
Instant retaliation will have
its own complications.
The enemy is not waiting at the
border whom we can attack.
This massacre has emotionally
disturbed our men.
Driven by vengeance,
they may commit excesses,
and innocents will die.
That will provoke
the tribals further,
which is what the Naxals want.
I know, Adil,
but these politicians
have their own compulsions.
To fulfil their selfish motives,
they keep pressurising us.
Do they even care
how many men we have lost?
We lost such a brave officer
like KK.
They will hand out
a little compensation
for publicity, that's all.
In such a terrible situation,
who'd want to go to Nandighat?
What? How can you do this?
You took such a big decision
without even discussing it with me?
I can't understand.
Even I can't understand, Rhea.
How can 84 policemen be
killed in one night?
And how Nandighat
is ruled by terrorists
instead of the state?
Why nobody wants to be
posted there as the SP?
Look Rhea,
someone's got to do this.
Right.
And you're the only one who
can move this mountain, right?
There is no other man in the
entire police department, right?
Talk to her.
She is overreacting.
Obviously, she will.
What you're doing is foolishness.
It was so tough to get
a posting in the same city.
We had just spoken
about starting a family
and he took a
transfer to Nandighat!
Don't do this, Adil.
I don't see anything good in this.
'Nandighat'
Which route are you taking?
- Main highway, sir.
It is safer.
No, we will go via Lakhimpur.
But the forest there...
- So?
'This is our territory.'
'Policemen,
enter at your own risk'.
'They are responsible
for their death'.
How far is Lakhimpur from here?
- About 4-5 km, sir.
Drive down the slope,
it'll pass through.
But, sir...
Take it down, Rajaram.
Give me the keys.
Get back in.
Come, sir.
'Police station'
Why is the gate locked?
- I'll check, sir.
Open!
- Sir.
The keys are with the Inspector.
Hurry up.
Tell Tewari the SP is here.
Sir.
Sorry, sir.
Is this a police station
or a den of thieves?
Sir. - How much area does
Lakhimpur police station cover?
2 km, sir.
- What?
2 km?
- Yes, sir.
But the next police station
is 23 km from here.
There are roadblocks in each
direction 2 km from here.
The staff fears to go there.
Every new post we build,
the Naxals blow it up
with dynamite.
Then how do you get information
about the Naxals?
Do you have informers in villages?
How do you control crime here?
Even if a murder is committed
nobody reports it.
All matters are settled in the
people's courts of the Naxals.
It's very peaceful here, sir.
Don't fire!
Manager,
came on your own?
I thought you'd bring
the cops with you.
Why do I need the cops,
when you're here, Mr Naga?
When you're here...
- Manager,
stop delivering dialogues.
I'll put an end to your drama.
Go ahead and plant the dynamite.
Why are you getting angry, Mr Naga?
We aren't outsiders. We'll listen
to... - Shut up, idiot!
Your company buys this land for
pennies and mints billions, and we?
We just ask for a donation of
2 million and you grumble.
Give me a minute,
I'll arrange for it.
That's all the time you have.
- Okay.
Or in 60 seconds you'll be history.
Hello...
"Ravishing youth..."
"I'm impressed with your beauty."
"I can't do without you..."
5...
10...
And...
15. Total.
Lal Salam!
- Lal Salam!
Hey!
What are you doing?
I was taking my wages, Comrade.
Is that so?
- Yes.
That is what I like about you.
You're very sharp with accounts.
That I am.
It is with your money that they
buy arms and ammunition.
This amounts to a criminal
conspiracy against the state
for which I can arrest you
under section 120-B and 121.
Sir, I'm Ravinder Nath. Project
Manager of Cosmos Global Steel.
Our pipeline work was stalled
since the past 4 years.
Sorry, but the police does not even
reply to our request for protection.
We were losing millions every year.
You tell us,
what option do we have?
If we settle with the Naxals
and work, you kill us.
If we don't,
the losses prove fatal.
You tell us...
- We're helpless.
Not only do we bear losses,
but there is a threat
to our life as well.
When there's a call from the
jungle, there's no cop in sight.
You'll get it.
You will get both,
police help and protection.
But you too will have to help us.
I want to cut the Naxals' supplies.
They can't buy arms merely
with tribal donations.
Remember,
we have to fight this war together.
Our men don't understand politics.
They can't understand
why we're fighting against our
own countrymen and dying.
They feel our politicians
don't want a solution.
We're being used as scapegoats!
The condition of
the camps is so bad
Sir! - that even if they
escape Naxal bullets,
malaria will kill them.
- Sir!
A posting in the interiors
means no electricity... - Sir!
No network,
- Sir!
They can't talk to their
families for months. - Sir!
What about our intelligence?
- That's our biggest problem.
If that was foolproof
KK and Sarabjeet
wouldn't have been trapped.
The scariest part is,
the villagers support
the Naxals totally.
We declared a reward
of 1.2 million,
but nobody dares step forward.
Since the Maoists
belong to the villages,
they mix easily with them.
Their network is so strong,
they're aware of all our movements.
It's only because of this
that Rajan
and his two area commanders
Naga and Juhi
have spread terror in Nandighat.
We have to destroy
their control, at any cost.
The police are here.
Run!
The villagers have never seen
a government official.
They think the police
is the government.
They don't fear death as much as
they fear the police uniform.
Come, let's go.
Let's go.
- Wait a minute.
Listen.
Run!
Forgive me, sir.
I don't know anything.
- Get the cot.
Come.
- Forgive me sir...
Sit down.
Sir...
How did you get hurt?
Please sit.
Sit.
You need not fear.
I am Adil,
your friend.
I admit we've made mistakes.
The government did not pay
attention to your needs
and there has been injustice.
Even today,
you fear the police.
I'm here to rid you of that fear.
With your cooperation,
we can correct our mistakes.
The government and the country
want you to be a part
of our progress.
Your children should have
a bright future
and not live under the shadow
of terror and guns.
Think for yourself.
What good have the
Maoists done by giving you guns?
Roads, electricity,
school, hospitals,
for which you took up arms
did they give you all of that?
Can they give them to you?
The Naxals don't believe
in democracy.
They want to capture power
through the barrel of the gun.
And whoever gains power
through a gun,
on what basis will they rule?
You should think about that.
This war has to stop now.
It does no good to anyone.
Stop living in fear
and cooperate with us. Together we
can work towards a better society
where no one can threaten you.
No one.
Here...
If you have any problem
or if anybody threatens you,
be it the Naxals or the police,
this is my phone number.
Call me. I promise I will take
immediate action.
Trust me.
Everyone here is a member
of the party
and you all have equal rights.
What to do,
whom to listen to
is your choice.
All I can say is,
what SP said here was a lie.
They have been cheating you
for the past 60 years
with sweet talk and false promises.
By feeding you a piece of candy,
they will
suck the blood out of you.
Don't forget, Comrades,
these cops serve an
corrupt government.
Mahanta,
the owner of the Steel Project,
where do you think he lives?
He lives in London.
His mansion is worth 15 billion.
40 bedrooms,
and a room each for eating,
bathing, dancing, and defecating.
Swimming pool, golf course,
God knows what else is there.
Where does he get this kind
of money from?
Tell me, from where?
From the minerals lying
beneath this very land.
Mahanta has struck a 15 billion
deal with this government.
How much?
- 15 billion!
15 billion!
Am I right, Balu?
- Yes, Comrade.
Have you ever seen so much money?
- Yes Comrade,
in my dreams.
Three bills of a billion each!
What does Mahanta promise?
He will open a first class
International University
where our tribal children
will learn to read
and talk in English.
Shut up, you bloody fool.
- Shut up!
This is a ploy to take our land
and displace us.
Will we be displaced?
- No!
We will never be displaced.
'Hello.'
Mobile.
- 'Hello.'
'SP sir.'
'SP sir? Hello?'
Go.
- Yes.
Hello? SP sir?
SP sir.
- Hello.
'Hello.'
SP sir.
You bastard!
Come on!
- Come on!
You bastard!
Give it.
'Adil Khan'
Hello?
SP Adil Khan?
Who is this?
I'm Rajan.
Rajan who?
Listen to this
and you will know.
Listen.
Rajan!
Rajan, you bastard! Let him go.
Why are you torturing a poor man?
If you're a man, come and face me.
Shut up!
Don't mislead
our innocent villagers
with your false promises.
Don't dare to sneak into our
village again!
If you want to live,
stay in Nandighat town!
Stay put there.
Shut up!
The law of the
people's court is clear
on the punishment for betrayal.
There's only one punishment
for giving information to police.
Run!
Sir.
They killed my son, sir.
Nobody will reveal anything, sir.
Even if somebody puts
a thumb-print on the report,
they will change their
statement in the court.
It's impossible to win this
war by legal means.
Rajaram, I want Rajan,
at any cost.
The same information here, too.
Rajan had camped at
Latehar last night.
He left this morning
at 10:00 via Kolhar.
He's expected to cross
the border around 3:00 p.m.
via Takroli lake.
How many people are with him?
Around 40-50 people, sir.
Rajaram,
is the information foolproof?
Sir, that...
I've put my life in danger
to reach you.
If Rajan comes to know,
he will crucify me.
Trust us.
You go that way.
Rajaram, you go there.
- Okay, sir.
No!
Sir!
Let's go, sir!
Stay put in Nandighat, SP
or I won't spare you!
Lal Salam!
- Lal Salam!
- No.
Lal Salam, Comrade.
- Yes.
Well done.
Kabir?
Are you crazy?
I could've shot you.
My friend, this life is yours,
take it anytime.
Get me a drink first.
Didn't the security stop you?
Your security is so tight,
I wouldn't have a chance
to come in.
So, I came my own way.
How'd the poor guys know
we're trained guerrilla fighters?
You seem to be under great tension.
Forget that, tell me
what brings you here?
- What brings me here?
I missed you,
so came over to see you.
Rhea told me about you.
Heard you killed 8-10 Naxals.
I didn't.
It was a trap.
It was a bloody trap, Kabir.
That bastard Rajan has created
a death-like terror here.
He butchered poor Dagdu
and acts like a big hero.
He got away today,
but I'll hunt him down.
I will hang his corpse from the
Home Minister's window.
I'll clean up Nandighat.
What do those guys think?
I am the police here.
I decide what is right and wrong.
If he has the guts,
let him face me.
I challenge him man-to-man,
without any weapons.
One-to-one!
I'll smash the scoundrel!
Okay, go to sleep now.
Come on.
All I need is one reliable lead.
I'll finish Rajan off.
Go to sleep.
I am glad you came.
Everyone is scared.
Adil.
Haven't you slept yet?
I need to talk to you.
Get up.
Are you crazy?
No,
I have thought seriously about it.
We can do it.
If they have a doubt,
they'll kill you in a second.
How will they suspect?
Nobody here knows me.
Nobody has seen me here before.
Neither locals nor Naxals,
not even your police.
Once I get set with them,
I'll send you all the information.
Their plans, movements,
hideouts.
You just keep attacking
and wipe them out. End of story.
Kabir,
your idea is totally stupid
and very dangerous.
Danger from whom?
I will be one of them,
their Comrade.
There's no question
of any suspicion.
Adil,
we have always worked
together as a team.
No one could ever touch us.
Trust me, man, we can do this.
Kabir, you don't understand.
Look,
your conventional police
methods aren't working.
You will have to do
something different.
You want Rajan, right?
I will give you Rajan.
Trust me, we will win.
You just figure out
a way for me to get in.
Moti,
have you switched sides?
My shop is for the public.
Can I refuse anyone?
It's been 7 days since
I put up the poster.
You've not given any information.
It's not easy to get any
information about the Naxalites.
You have seen yourself that
they take money
and give wrong information.
Old woman,
give me the money.
Sir, I haven't sold anything yet.
Shut up! Every week you give
the same excuse.
I need to buy medicines, sir.
My daughter is in the hospital.
Let it go!
You are a public servant.
This doesn't suit you.
- Hey!
How dare you touch a cop?
Thrash him!
Catch him!
Come to the police station.
I will teach you a lesson.
Take him along.
Move!
'Police station'
53!
419!
420!
468!
You scoundrel!
Which Naxal unit do you belong to?
How many times must I say
I am not a Naxal?
I came to collect
my outstanding dues.
Give that story to someone else.
I'll write your story.
You scoundrel,
I'll charge you on so many counts
that you'll forget counting.
Madhav!
I'll deal with this.
You take care of your nose.
I think it's broken.
You!
- Come on!
Settle your score tomorrow.
He isn't going anywhere.
Go.
Leave him.
Do you want to hit me too, SP?
Come on, hit me.
But remember,
I won't spare anybody.
Solitary lock-up for him.
He speaks a lot.
Let him rot!
The rascal escaped!
- Catch him.
'After escaping from the lock-up
run straight into the jungle.'
'Don't be afraid.'
'The cops won't follow you
into the jungle at night.'
'The jungle is Naxal area.'
'They will find you.'
'Remember,'
'they suspect every stranger
of being a police informer.'
Hey!
Get up!
You can leave.
He's in our custody now.
Who are you people?
Get him up.
Catch him!
- What are you doing?
Tie him!
Where are you taking me?
- Get up.
Come on!
Sit here.
Sit.
What's your name?
Kabir.
Full name! Kabir what?
What's it to you?
Are you a cop?
You are the cop.
What do you think?
Just because we live in the jungle,
we are fools?
What?
Hey,
we know you're SP Adil Khan's man.
You're right.
I know you're Madhuri Dixit.
Hey!
We are not playing games.
In a second this bullet
will rip through your skull.
Why are you asking such questions?
You brought me blind-folded here
and then insult me
by calling me a cop.
You're not from here.
What are you doing in Nandighat?
I had a business in Nagpur,
manufacturing mobiles.
It didn't work out,
and people here owed me money.
I came here to collect my dues.
I heard his shop had shut.
Which one?
Shri Computers.
He sells second hand mobile phones
at Hanuman Chowk.
What?
Is it prohibited to
collect your dues?
Will you shoot me for that?
Stand him up.
"That dawn."
"That dawn will surely
come one day."
"That dawn"
"will surely come one day."
"That dawn,"
"wait for it."
- He's so melodramatic.
I cross checked
with Shri Computers.
What he said is true.
And the police?
- They're hunting for him.
They've charged him with 7-8 cases.
Untie him.
I get it now.
You are not humans,
but you are Naxals.
Please forgive me.
I came to the wrong place.
It's okay if I don't recover
my money.
Radio, TV,
I'll make something else.
You can go if you want,
but the police will frame you.
They'll give you the
title of a Naxalite too.
I heard you broke
Madhav Rao's nose.
They had caught me
if not, I would have...
Let's go.
Hey?
Where are you going
leaving me here?
What do you expect us to do?
We can't keep you with us.
Why did you capture me?
You just said
if the cops find me they'll
kill me, labelling me a Naxal.
You've left me with no option.
What he says is true.
Comrade,
we don't know his politics.
He could also be a criminal.
What politics, Comrade?
An enemy's enemy
is always a friend.
He seems a useful man.
He sings well.
He was singing all night.
Alright, put him with the
theatre group.
He'll be useful for the campaign.
"We've had enough of
your autocratic rule."
"It is our turn now."
"The inflation has doused
our kitchen fires."
"They set out to remove poverty.
Instead, got rid of the poor."
"Like sipping sweet lemonade..."
"Like sipping sweet lemonade they
swallow the country in a gulp."
"The common man's pocket
is cleaned out bare."
"Like sipping sweet lemonade they
swallow the country in a gulp."
"The common man's pocket
is cleaned out bare."
"We've had enough of your
autocratic rule."
"It is our turn now."
"We've had enough of your
autocratic rule."
"It is our turn now."
"Be it Birla or Tata,
Ambani or Bata."
"For their selfish motives,
they've carved up the country."
"Be it Birla or Tata,
Ambani or Bata."
"For their selfish motives,
they've carved up the country."
"It is our blood"
"that drives their engines,
fast and furious."
"The common man's pocket
is cleaned out bare."
"We won't bear it anymore."
"It is our turn now."
Madhav, go through the
entire district and enquire.
I will check personally.
- Sir!
'101.'
Sir!
He's the same Naxalite.
I told you.
I won't spare him today.
- Arrest him.
Give me the wireless.
Come in, patrol party...
Sir, phone call from
the headquarters.
Here, sir.
Yes, sir.
Get him. He's a Naxal.
- Yes, sir.
They are from the Theatre Group.
Arrest the man
playing the harmonium!
I will check, sir.
I'll check, sir.
Come on.
Sir.
Yes, sir.
"Come on, brother, play the drums!"
- Move aside.
'To gain their trust,'
'you will have to feed them
information about us.'
'Monday morning,
I'll patrol Jhingna and Ratonwadi.'
'And the wireless frequency on
Monday mornings will be 132.5.'
Where are you running like insane?
Five police contingents
are heading to Jhingna.
We have to move at once.
How do you know?
Through the radio. Stop questioning
so we can leave?
Stop this nonsense!
Do the cops announce their
plans on the radio now?
Didi!
Didi, there's a message
from Ratonwadi.
The enemy is reaching Jhingna!
And, when I told you?
You get ready to hit me
for every little thing.
Run from here.
Inform Comrade Rajan immediately.
We'll wait for him at Motireta.
Lal Salam!
- Lal Salam!
Who is he?
This is Kabir, Comrade.
Kabir?
Is it him?
The one who broke
Madhav Rao's nose.
He intercepted the police
talk on the radio!
The radio?
Just a minute.
'We are patrolling in Jhingna,
sir.'
'We haven't found
any truck here. Over.'
'We are heading
in your direction. Over.'
'We will need more men, sir.'
'Over.'
'Continue your paroling.'
Well done, Comrade.
- 'Over.'
Where did you learn all this?
'Give updates. Over.'
I'm a B.Tech engineer, Comrade.
Moreover, I'm interested
in such things.
"March carefully, or you will die."
Keshav,
keep him with you.
Are they new recruits?
Those are the new recruits,
their training has just begun.
- Okay.
16!
- 17!
18!
- 19!
20!
- 21!
Number 21!
Start from 1 again.
- Why?
Why 1 after 20?
Because our tribals
can't count beyond 20.
Amazing.
They can't count beyond 20,
but they know everything
about politics, revolution,
Mao, Lenin.
Very good. One!
'No obstruction in putting up the
Mahanta steel plant', says the PM.
See,
don't take this Adil Khan lightly.
They've posted a senior officer
like him here
because they intend to use all
their force for this project.
Wherever Mahanta
set up such plants,
Indonesia, Brazil, Libya,
he has funded private armies
to displace the locals.
The politicians are making
a lot of noise here too.
Tell the Central Committee
to prepare for direct action.
We'll hold a training camp
and train the militia
and comrades in weapons.
Done.
- But we need funds to buy arms.
We don't have enough.
Why are you looking at me?
Your accounts are bad, Comrade.
What are you saying?
Comrade Naga,
in the past three months,
you've collected 25
from Road Contractors,
22 from the Bamboo guys
and 20 from Cosmos...
- What is this 25, 22 and 20?
I do the collections
and you are keeping an account?
Comrade Rajan,
you're being misled.
Whatever I collect,
I deposit every single penny.
You have to prove the account.
You can't talk to me like this.
I am an area commander.
I've given my blood for the party...
- Sit down, Naga!
Sit.
Control yourself.
We're talking about accounts.
My accounts are clear.
SP Adil Khan has made
things very tough
and yet if the party needs
more funds, I can still do it.
Stop putting
false allegations on me.
Leave money matters to me.
I'll organise the funds.
Inform the supplier
that the arms must be
delivered on time.
Soon.
Lal Salam, Comrade.
- Lal Salam.
Be careful, Comrade.
110 automatic,
500 kgs of explosives,
gun powder and 25 AK 47.
They are in 4 boxes.
Come on.
Hurry up.
I'll do it.
Why are we leaving them here?
Here the forest is not dense
and the police patrolling
has increased.
It is dangerous to carry it back.
Very soon Comrade Shivram
will organise a training camp here.
We'll take it then.
Go with Kabir
and buy some vegetables
and spices.
I'll meet you at the bus stop.
We'll buy it from here.
Please come.
- How much for tomatoes?
Rs 12.
We just need this much.
"The flower has blossomed
in the garden."
"My bangles are jingling."
"Like in the river..."
I'm telling you, not now.
I'll call you later.
"Like the boat flows on water."
Rs 5!
Come on, just Rs 5!
Hello? Yes.
The bus is running late,
will be there in 10-15 minutes.
I will be there soon.
Is Juhi your real name?
Everyone here has many names.
I don't know if your
name is Juhi or not.
That's not my real name.
It's the name given by the party.
I don't even remember
my real name anymore.
It's been 9 years
since I left home.
What happened?
I am from Jharkhand.
My father wanted to educate me,
but destiny had different plans.
My dad had borrowed
some money on interest.
Those people
first took my two sisters away
and then seized our land.
When I went to the police station
to file a complaint,
the cop said,
'Come home at night'.
'I'll file your complaint then'.
Then I decided.
I don't care now.
My mission is to establish
the people's government.
If I live for another 10 years,
I will kill at least a 100 more.
Kabir...
It's time for your shift.
'Hello?'
- It's me, Kabir. Can you hear me?
Kabir?
How are you?
Where are you calling from?
From the camp.
I've joined them, Comrade.
I thought you'd just
continue with the singing.
I had to do it.
Now listen, a big consignment
of arms has arrived.
I'll send the location.
A training camp
is also going to be held.
'Will send the details as soon as
I know.' - When?
When I get to know.
Break the mobile phone
once you send the location. Get it?
'And take care.'
- Yes, okay. Bye.
What are you doing?
Who are you messaging?
Give it to me.
More than 500 Comrades
have registered this time.
We don't have enough weapons.
- Yes.
So, train them well.
Sir!
One, two, one!
There was a police raid
this morning.
One, two, one!
- Come here.
Everyone got trapped.
Everything is over.
- What are you saying?
Enemies seized the weapons.
One, two, one!
Nothing is left.
Where is Keshav?
I didn't see him on my shift.
One, two, one!
- Even I didn't see him.
He ruined everything!
110 automatic,
500 kgs of explosives,
gun powder, and 25 AK 47.
Their plan was to distribute
these arms to the villagers.
The Maoists are getting desperate.
But our intelligence
is watching their every move
and we'll never let them
succeed in their plans.
We have complete information about
their supplier and the source.
Adil Khan can try his best,
death cannot move us.
These incidents won't bother us.
Our movement is for the people.
For their rights, we will fight
until our last breath.
Until we don't uproot them
from every inch of our land,
we will not rest in peace.
The people's training camps
will continue until then.
Lal Salam!
- Lal Salam!
"We will snatch our right."
We will snatch our right.
"There's no doubt about it."
"This forest is our father."
"The river is our mother."
"If anyone snatch these,"
"we'll rip them apart."
Juhi!
"We will not listen to anyone.
We will not bear it anymore."
"We've heard enough.
We've suffered enough."
"How long should we keep mum?"
"One day, we shall speak!"
"He demands..."
"This new man demands
the right to live."
"When he didn't get it,"
"he took weapons in his hands."
"When he didn't get it,
he took weapons in his hands."
"You're a cloud
with rage filled in it."
"I'm a mountain,
standing in your path."
"If you mess with me,"
"there will be a shower of sweat."
"It becomes rain."
"It became a strange night."
"Once you break free..."
- The police have attacked!
Fire!
'Red revolution'
Leave!
Come Juhi, let's go.
Juhi, let's leave. Hurry up!
Attack!
Stop!
We smashed their biggest training
and operation camp in one night.
And the entire credit
goes to Adil Khan.
Sir, I am Mansi Dubey
from Dainik Bhaskar.
Are you certain,
there were no innocent
among 64 dead tribals?
- Look,
the police doesn't
target innocent civilians.
When police violate human rights,
why isn't there any enquiry?
There should be.
Let's get one thing straight.
There is a war going on
in Nandighat
which is started by the Maoists
against the sovereignty
of our country.
A war whose rules we can't decide
because the Naxalites
doesn't follow any rules.
If you are concerned
about the human rights,
why don't we talk about
their violence first?
2000 policemen lost their lives
because they were
protecting our country.
I suggest you start an inquiry
about their death first
and then I'll reply
to your allegations.
You were hurt, weren't you?
How are you?
Why didn't you give a warning?
Why you started firing directly?
We did warn, Kabir!
The music was so loud,
nobody heard it.
Their guards began firing,
what could we do?
Would we put down our arms?
This wasn't right, Adil.
Children, old people, women,
most people there were innocent.
Innocent people don't come
for arms training, Kabir.
They feel the government
has done nothing for them
and now wants to even
grab their land and homes.
They think the government
and police support Mahanta.
Listen Kabir,
I trust you completely.
Otherwise, I would have
never let you go in.
But, if you are getting confused
by their pointless propaganda
and want to leave the mission,
then it's fine with me.
Nothing is more important
to me than you.
Did I say I want to leave?
I took up this mission to help you.
I thought you'd understand
that their fight is for
their rights.
Their means are wrong.
I know that you're pained
by seeing their terrible condition.
What can be more shameful
for this country?
But, still, if there is no
development here,
this place will truly become hell.
You see, what both of us
are doing here
will eventually benefit
the local people.
Okay? Good.
Listen,
as soon as we get Rajan,
you get out.
I'll make arrangements for you,
okay?
Congratulations, Mr Mahanta.
- Most welcome, sir.
Please come, Chief Minister.
- Yes.
Congratulations, SP.
I have double good news for you.
You've done such good work for us,
we feel it's our duty
to do something for you.
I agree we can't end your
exile in Nandighat,
but thought I'd send
Goddess Sita herself to you.
The cabinet has
cleared the proposal
for a Special Intelligence Cell
in Nandighat.
And, we're posting Rhea Menon
here as its director.
Thank you, sir.
Nobody can stop you from winning
the President's Gold Medal.
Get yourself a new suit
for the felicitation ceremony.
Our progress will be incomplete
as long as the poor, backward,
and tribal society
does not progress.
And for that it is important
that there is education,
health, and employment here.
The government needs to bring
all amenities to your homes
and we will do that.
The steel factory being set up
by the Mahanta group
is especially for you!
Only if there's progress in your
homes, the nation will progress.
Nothing is going right, Comrade.
I know the training camp
was your responsibility.
But, you are not responsible
for what happened.
63 people martyred.
Comrade Shivram,
Chakravarthy...
What do we do now?
The Mahanta project
ruined everything.
How will we fight them now?
You're ever ready and courageous,
but you're looking
so helpless today.
It proves that you too are a human.
What should I do?
You tell me, what should I do?
This kind of war is always
a game of confidence.
The self-confidence
of the two leaders.
Adil Khan knows this very well.
I have studied his record closely.
Now, you now have to think
how can break his self-confidence.
Comrade, you need to do
something big.
Milord, there are
17 different cases registered
against Govind Suryavanshi
in Nandighat.
Your Honour, even I am saying
the same thing.
Instead of holding trials
in different places
why don't you transfer all the
cases in one place?
Transfer remand granted.
I read in the newspaper,
you are also going to Nandighat.
Right, Professor.
And that's why I didn't want to
leave you behind.
We must fulfill this mission
at any cost, Comrades.
We will enter the enemy's home
and kill him
and crush his arrogance.
Change your uniforms
and split into smaller teams
with your team leader and enter the
city from different directions.
Lal Salam!
- Lal Salam!
Change your uniforms!
You two will stand on the road
outside the gates
of the police headquarters.
As soon as the
police vehicles leave,
inform me over the walkie-talkie.
Yes.
- Move.
Comrade, no mistakes.
- No.
Lal Salam.
- Lal Salam.
'Police station, Nandighat'
The police have left
with Comrade Govind.
You all leave from there.
Move to the side.
- Hey!
Stop!
- Where are you going?
Move to the side.
They're VIP cars coming.
Move aside.
'District court'
Let's go!
Cover me.
Sir.
'Advocate, Kapil R. Tiwari'
Hey!
No!
Come Juhi, let's go!
Dad!
Come on, let's go!
- Juhi!
Kill everyone.
Well done, Adil.
Well done.
I don't understand
why he is being kept alive.
Sir is here.
- Sir...
Sir, one question, please.
- Sir.
This is a fantastic victory for us.
Adil Khan has broken their morale.
Our men fought with courage
and achieved a tremendous victory.
How can you call this your victory
when, in broad daylight,
the Naxals attack your city
and escape with their
leader Govind Suryavanshi?
Even the Gods
can't please you journalists.
You always talk negative.
What will the old sick teacher
going to do anyway?
Let them take him.
We have their commander-in-chief,
Rajan. The man responsible
for terrorising Nandighat.
We have won the battle there.
Thanks.
Don't look so disappointed.
Believe me,
you've won.
And I'm really proud of you.
But, I lost Govind.
So what, Adil?
I have asked permission
for satellite surveillance
over entire Nandighat.
I'll fix cameras everywhere.
He can't escape.
- He won't escape, anyway.
I will get information
about him soon.
Tell me something, Adil,
how did you setup such a reliable
information network so soon?
I mean, you have turned the biggest
weakness of Nandighat police
into your biggest strength. How?
Well, intelligence leads
to intelligence.
Necessity is the mother
of all invention.
Helplessness is the other
name for Mahatma Gandhi.
This is rich.
Gandhi with a gun.
- Something like that.
You have done wonders, Mr Adil.
My son is a huge fan
of your courage.
It is only because of you
that this project will take off.
Please, sir.
I am just doing my duty
and I will try my best to see the
Naxals don't bother you. - Okay.
Why don't you do one more thing?
This is the list of
230 tribal villages
residing on our project
and mining areas.
Get them evacuated.
Don't worry about the cost.
Mr Mahanta,
to evacuate the villages,
you will need to contact the
Collector and Revenue Department.
Yes SP, we will do that.
You know
these villagers won't leave
unless you use your stick.
Forgive me, Mr Mahanta,
but my stick is used to
maintain law and order.
And, when needed for that,
I will use it to good effect.
Thank you, Mr Khan.
Thank you for coming.
I've talked to the
Central Committee.
They'll supply arms
on an emergency basis.
We'll go to the villages
who have been asked to leave
and ask them to protest.
What you wished for,
will happen now, Rajan.
We will fight.
What happened?
You called Kabir as Rajan.
Oh.
He is just like Rajan.
Nobody can take
Comrade Rajan's place.
That's true.
I really miss him,
but we have to carry on his work.
I want you to take
on his responsibility
for training and fight back.
Hereafter, your revolutionary
name is, Azad!
Lal Salam.
- Lal Salam!
Jobs, commission, and progress,
you will get all the benefits.
But until we get the land,
how will the project begin?
These 230 villages
have to be evacuated soon.
You have done this before too.
Look Mr Mahanta,
after the Supreme Court orders,
Salwa Judum has ended.
- Really?
But you people have your own
private armies, don't you?
We appreciate such straight talk.
You make a contract
and you will get results every day.
Right? - Yes.
One more thing,
the more money you put
in our hands,
we will increase the pressure
and get the work done faster.
- No tension.
I value time more than
anything else.
As for the government,
leave it to me.
We stopped worrying
about them, long ago.
Move ahead!
Come on, move!
This is an appeal
to all the villagers.
Evacuate the place immediately
with your utensils and provisions.
Evacuate the village!
Do not worry.
No!
Get going!
This is the government's order,
only for your benefit.
Get going!
The government will
guarantee a bright future
and will take care of you.
You support the government.
The government is with you!
A bright future awaits,
move to the camp.
Get going!
Don't worry!
Evacuate the village!
Don't worry.
Empty the village!
Please help us.
Demolish it!
Get going!
You!
I will thrash you!
Come on.
Hey, come here.
- The police don't help.
And when the villagers
evacuate on their own,
you arrest them!
I mean, is this a joke or what?
Sir, it's the Nandighat SP on line.
SP, the cabinet has approved
the voluntary evacuation
by the villagers,
do not interfere.
Sir, it wasn't voluntary,
force was being used.
SP!
Petty fights happen even
during festival times.
Does that mean
you will arrest all of them?
Let them go.
You focus on the Naxals,
they will manage the villages.
Please try to understand, sir.
The situation is very tense.
The tribals are already
angry with the government.
By doing this, whatever little
goodwill we have made,
will also be...
- To hell with goodwill!
We just need the land, that's all!
- I am sorry, sir.
But if anyone breaks the law
in my jurisdiction,
I will take action on him!
It won't take me even one second
to get him transferred!
How dare he teach me the law?
Talk to him!
Adil, I am sending a special unit
to supervise land acquisition.
They will report directly to me.
Release them.
Sir, this is not right.
It's no longer your jurisdiction,
Adil Khan.
Leave it to me.
Thank you.
'No longer my jurisdiction'.
They destroyed our training camp.
They killed dozens of our comrades.
This was a well thought plan
by Adil Khan
to weaken us.
But, we must get arms again
and retaliate strongly.
Not now.
First of all,
we must use whatever we have
to reinitiate
and feed these helpless people.
It will be too late by then.
This is the truth of our country.
Nobody cares about the poor.
The big projects and businesses,
only care about profits.
The state, police,
and the system,
everything is for them.
Nothing for the common man.
That is why we fight.
And we will continue
with all our power.
But right now
we need to heal their wounds.
Juhi, my dear,
whatever funds the
Area Commander has,
call for it.
Dad, we don't have much left.
Naga's collections were huge,
but he denies it bluntly.
"Don't put a price on love,
beloved."
"Weigh it with your eyes."
"O Kabir, open the pot."
"Open."
"Open the pot."
"Since I've become the spirit
of the neighbourhood."
"My heart is wounded
and my eyes are faithless."
"My senses are lost
and my faith is shaken."
"Since I've become the spirit
of the neighbourhood."
"The noise within can no longer
be suppressed."
"Beloved, tell me
your hearts desires."
"O Kabir, open the pot."
"O darling, open the pot."
"My kohled eyes will kill you."
"Your eyes are amazing."
"A gentleman has become a lover."
"Love has blossomed."
"The night has passed
and it is dawn."
"Don't delay anymore."
"O Kabir, open the pot."
No, Kabir!
The decision will be made
in the people's court.
Lal Salam!
- Lal Salam!
Lies! All lies!
You have no proof, Comrade.
My accounts are clear.
I have never forced myself
on any woman comrade.
All false allegations!
I'm telling you.
Come on!
- Let me go.
Get up!
Come on!
Speak up!
Why are you silent now? Scoundrel.
The rules of the
people's court are clear.
The money which the area
commanders collect,
belongs only to the Movement.
Naga has broken this rule
and misused his position
for his personal pleasure.
The only punishment for this is,
death!
Let me go!
Let me go. I don't want to be
a part of the Movement.
Let me go!
The verdict of the people's
court does not apply to me.
Let me go!
Lal Salam!
- Lal Salam.
'Red revolution is immortal'
I see some movement there.
Enlarge it. Quick.
- Yes, ma'am.
Trace the location through GSM.
Quick. - Yes, ma'am.
Hello.
- Adil, I need you here quickly.
I've spotted movement
on the satellite.
I'll be there.
GPS, North 23.
15.59507, East 77.
Ma'am, it's the Barakhedi village.
Barakhedi village?
I know where Barakhedi is.
Rajaram.
- Yes, sir.
Find out who is patrolling
near Barakhedi. - Yes, sir.
Sir, there's a call
from the headquarters.
Hello.
- 'Madhav Rao.'
Sir?
We've tracked movement
in Barakhedi. Check it out.
Sir, we are quite close by.
- Good.
Enlarge this.
- Stop!
Stop!
- Go back.
Are you okay?
Comrade Azad?
- Yes.
What is wrong with you?
Nothing.
You guys carry on,
I'll get something and come.
Hello?
- Lal Salam.
Lal Salam.
What's the use of this tower
if there is no network?
- Lal Salam.
Lal Salam.
- No not this.
- Lal Salam.
Danger'
'Danger'
Hello.
- Hello.
It's me, Kabir.
How are you, partner?
- I want to meet you.
When can you meet me?
It's important.
It's a bit tight now.
Can we meet in 3-4 days?
- It's urgent, Adil.
Meet me tomorrow at the same place.
What's the matter, Kabir?
Are you alright?
I'll tell you when we meet.
Okay, tomorrow at 6:00
at same place.
Whose number is this?
Where are you calling from?
Barakhedi village.
- Barakhedi?
Get out of there, right now!
Why? What happened?
I've sent Madhav Rao
to raid the place.
'Get out immediately!
Okay? Fast.'
The police are here!
Where have they gone?
Where are they hiding?
Catch them!
I think Balu and others are hiding.
They're waiting
for your orders, Comrade.
Catch them!
We must be careful.
The lives of women
and children are in danger.
Come out!
- You scoundrel!
Let the children go.
Juhi?
Get them out or I'll...
If I walk out now,
only I will be arrested.
Drag all of them out here.
Come out!
- Otherwise these scoundrels
won't spare even the women
and children.
Bring them all out!
Come out!
Inform the others not to fire.
Wonderful!
Comrade Juhi herself.
You sully woman!
Pankaj,
Juhi said not to fire.
Come on.
Come on!
Sir, should I inform head office?
'Section Four,
reveal your position.'
Disconnect it.
Let me investigate her first.
'Section Four,
reveal your position. Over.'
Take the car to the
forest police post first.
Looking at you
it's hard to believe that
you have killed 49 cops.
Untie my hands for a minute,
I will make it 50 now.
No! Let me go!
Leave her.
You guys go out.
We will take our right.
We will take...
Inform sir
Barakhedi operation was a success.
I have arrested
Area Commander Juhi. - Okay, sir.
Let's go.
If you breathe,
you will die twice!
Do you get it?
Don't let him move.
We'll catch them
by tomorrow morning.
We will take our right.
Our...
Our right.
We'll take...
How are you?
What happened suddenly?
Can you stop the Mahanta Project?
What?
The project will
destroy this area, Adil.
See Kabir,
based on whose understanding
you're saying this,
they don't want...
- Can you stop it or not?
No.
Then you leave Nandighat.
Go back to Bhopal.
Go to Bhopal? Why?
I don't want anything
to happen to you.
To me?
What will happen to me?
You don't understand, Adil.
These people are very upset
with your actions.
They're bound to be
because Rajan is in our custody.
But, don't you worry about me.
We will end this mission together.
The goal for which you
took on this mission
is going to be achieved soon.
Look at this chip.
We will be able to track
your location.
Since they trust you fully,
they will not even check.
You just be near Govind
and Juhi tomorrow.
Only those two are left, Kabir.
Once they're finished,
the game is over.
Another thing.
Yesterday some Naxals attacked
the police post and freed Juhi
and abducted Madhav.
Find out where they have him.
Do you know what Madhav Rao did?
He arrested Juhi. What else?
He shot two children and a woman.
And threatened to burn down
the whole village.
To save innocent lives,
Juhi surrendered.
And then he took her
to the police station,
tortured her,
and raped her.
How can you be so sure of it?
Because I was there.
- You?
How could you have been there?
You'd left by then!
Did you do all that?
Did you attack the
police post, Kabir? - Yes.
And, it was I who freed Juhi.
It was I who killed 5 of your men.
I blew up the police post.
Madhav Rao is in my custody.
What the hell are you
talking about, Kabir!
Do you know the
consequences of this?
Why did you do this?
Have you lost your mind?
Release Madhav Rao immediately!
If he has committed a crime,
the law will punish him.
He will be tried in
our people's court.
Your people's court?
Wow, Kabir.
You too speak the language
of the gun's terrorism?
The terrorism of the gun
is nothing.
To keep the poor in poverty,
to loot their land,
to take away all their rights,
that is the real terrorism.
It is your government
who is doing this.
But now, anger is rising in
the blood of every poor tribal.
That anger will now emerge
from the barrel of the gun!
Stop this nonsense, Kabir!
No solution ever emerges
from the barrel of a gun.
And, the people whose cause
you're advocating
their methods are wrong
and even you know that very well.
The Maoists are using
the poor and helpless
tribals to gain power.
They're blackmailing our country.
Weren't you the one who said,
'If the system doesn't work
one should repair it'?
'No one gains anything
by destroying it'.
Kabir,
I am telling you for the
last time as a friend.
Release Madhav Rao.
This is beyond
our friendship now, Adil.
Alright then,
I'm ending this mission.
Leave now. Your work is done.
- No.
My mission has just begun.
I am completely with them.
Henceforth, if anybody,
touches a poor tribal,
I'll do to him exactly what I have
done with Madhav Rao.
No matter who it is.
So, finally you've revealed
your true colours.
When I was feeding a snake,
I didn't realise
that one day it would turn
around and bite me.
But remember one thing,
you are not only betraying me,
you're committing treason
against your country.
And you know the
punishment for treason.
From today, our friendship is over.
It is you who is showing
your true colours.
After all, you are a cop.
Kabir...
Don't do this, Kabir.
This will end
in a terrible tragedy.
Very true.
The next time we meet,
only one of us will
walk away alive.
Move back.
SP Adil Khan...
Why don't you say anything?
Who is Azad? Why is he
taking the responsibility?
You have to answer,
this is a shocking incident.
Is the crime getting
out of police's control? - Sir.
Who is this new menace? - Sir,
is it an insult for the police?
Azad?
Sir, please tell us.
'Police dog'
This? - These are files
of all the suspects.
You must have videos of arrests
and interrogation. - Yes, ma'am.
Get them.
Fast forward it.
- Yes, ma'am.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
- This is the wrong disc, ma'am.
'Sir, we are in the Ratobadi area.'
'We have run out of petrol.'
Play it.
- Yes.
'This is...'
This is the People's Theatre Group.
Ma'am, he is a Naxal too.
Escaped from the police lock-up.
'It might be a bit
dangerous, sir. Over.'
What were you thinking?
Rhea, please calm down.
- Kabir?
I mean, we both love him
so much, but,
he is like a wild horse!
Who knows it better than you?
Yet you made him your informer
and sent him amongst Naxals?
What were you thinking, Adil?
- I don't know, Rhea.
I don't know what I was thinking.
It was his idea.
I know, I should've said no,
but I never expected
Kabir to turn against me.
I mean, he is my best friend.
- He was your best friend, Adil!
Today he is your biggest enemy.
This is your double tragedy.
Jesus Christ!
You've created a monster.
God knows what he'll do next.
Stop!
Let them go.
Go... Go...
Rajan!
We are all equally concerned
about this, Mr Mahanta.
Believe me,
the government is with you.
We will leave no stone unturned.
You...
- I want Aditya, Chief Minister.
If anything happens to my son...
Nothing will happen to him.
We'll use everything in our power.
Nobody can stop your project.
- To hell with the project!
I won't setup my project.
Remember,
if my son doesn't come back,
no investor will ever invest
in this country again.
Don't say that, sir...
'Azad, the man-in-charge
after Rajan's arrest'
'talks to the media
for the first time.'
'We're taking you live
to the location.'
'Nothing will happen
to Aditya Mahanta'
' as long as our demands are met.'
'We have a single-point demand.'
'Release our Comrade Rajan'
'and we'll return the boy
safe and sound.'
'What if the government
refuses your demands?'
'Then the government will be
responsible for the consequences.'
'But will the police agree
to release Rajan?'
'Then you might demand
other things.'
'These are pressure tactics.
- This is pure blackmail.'
'Do you have...
- Just a minute!'
'This is not a press conference.'
'No questions please.'
'We have no personal enmity
with the police.'
'Just stop preaching
development to us.'
Hello.
- 'Sir, it's the DGP.'
'Getting Suryavanshi released,
Aditya Mahanta...'
Hello?
- Adil,
the government has decided
to release Rajan.
No, sir.
This will be a huge mistake, sir.
Please don't do this.
Sir, whatever we have
achieved till date
will be laid waste.
- Adil, try to...
Enough is enough, Khan.
It's the government's decision.
'We cannot take any more risk.'
Secure the release of
Aditya Mahanta.
There should be no mistakes.
'Do you get it?'
'The one who responded quickly'
'was area commander Azad.'
I have him deeply sedated.
- Okay.
This is your responsibility, ma'am.
This chip can cause
infection and be fatal.
"My heart is sad.
My friend abandoned."
"It cries,
my friend is upset."
"My heart is sad.
My friend abandoned."
"It cries,
my friend is upset."
"Be generous, oh Allah."
"Have mercy, oh Allah."
"Our abode is left behind."
"Our own have robbed us."
"Oh Allah."
"Be generous, oh Allah."
"Have mercy, oh Allah."
Do you really want me
to publish this?
Yes,
but remember,
you got this from an
anonymous source, not me.
Understand?
- I understand very well.
This is front page news.
If I could get a photo of the two
of you, it'd make super hit news.
Thank you, sir.
The fever has reduced.
You!
What are you doing?
- Shut up, you scoundrel!
What's happening, Juhi?
'New Maoist leader Azad
is SP Adil Khan's friend'
So, this is your real face?
Bloody traitor!
'Dainik Bhaskar'
Is this true?
Sir... - Is it true that Adil Khan
is your friend?
That he sent you here?
You mean to say, this man,
this monster,
who killed Madhav Rao
and 5 other cops,
who kidnapped Aditya Mahanta,
is your man?
- Yes, sir.
You have hammered
the last nail in the coffin
of whatever little respect was
left for the police in Nandighat.
You have turned our anti-Naxal
operation into a joke!
There is only one reason
for revealing the truth.
Naxals never spare traitors.
Kabir is my best friend.
I know when he decides something,
nobody can stop him.
This is the only way to finish him.
That's why I leaked this news.
After that, I'm ready for
any action you want to take.
Sir...
As a result of your conspiracy,
Comrade Shivram,
Comrade Chakravarthy,
16 other revolutionaries and
many innocents lost their lives.
I didn't know that
the police would open fire
at the training camp.
What did you think?
On receiving your tip the police
would come to us with garlands?
We gave you shelter,
trusted you completely,
loved you as one of us, and you...
And you kept stabbing us
in the back!
It is true that
I came in as his man.
But, when I realised
what your fight is about,
when I got to know you,
I had a change of heart.
I abandoned Adil's mission.
That is precisely why he
leaked this news to the press
to break our unity.
How do we know that
this is not another trick?
What trick, Balu?
I kidnapped Mahanta's son
to free Rajan.
Adil is punishing me for that.
He knows there will be
a public trial
and in the presence
of all comrades...
The police are here!
Everybody leave.
Police!
Run... Run...
- No!
No!
Somebody please untie him!
Help him!
- I will hold them.
All of you, move out of this place!
Start firing!
Come on!
Ma'am, the target is moving.
Where's the helicopter headed?
How do they know?
Adil, the dot is moving,
they are trying to shift Rajan.
They are headed in the
south-west direction.
Okay.
This way.
Stop!
What is it?
What are you doing?
Just a minute.
They can't see you,
but still they know
which way you're headed.
This chip was revealing
your location to Adil.
I will lead the police
in the other direction.
You escape from here.
How'll you stop them all alone?
- Sir, don't worry about me.
It is important for Rajan
and you to survive.
The two of you can create
thousands of other comrades.
Azad, no matter how you began,
your end will be that
of a revolutionary.
Comrade...
Lal Salam.
- Lal Salam.
"This is our land."
- Kabir...
The chip is moving in the
opposite direction.
Let's go down.
He is running fast with Rajan.
'They changed their direction.'
'Adil,
he is moving south east now.'
Kabir!
Stop!
Sir!
Hey!
Kabir!
Juhi!
Come on!
Get up.
Okay, sir!
Juhi...
Juhi?
Juhi!
Juhi...
God damn it, Kabir!
Why?
Why did you do all this?
What did you get out of it?
It was my fault that
I let you go in.
But you?
You supported these people?
Come on now.
No.
No, Kabir.
No! Kabir!
No!
Kabir, don't do this.
Kabir...
Why?
Why did you do this?
What happened?
I...
Whatever I did,
I have no regrets.
I'm only sorry about one thing
that I hurt you.
No, it was all my fault.
I should've never sent you.
Never.
You'll be alright.
Sorry, Kabir.
Kabir?
'Kabir and Juhi's martyrdom
gave fuel to Govind and Rajan's
struggle even more.'
'The rapidly growing Naxal movement
is deeply entrenched in more than
200 districts of India.'
'Thousands of armed
Maoist guerilla troops'
'are engaged in a bloody war'
'with Indian Military forces.'
'Not a day goes past
when Indian soil'
'is not soaked by the blood
of its own children.'
'Why can't we find a way out
of this quagmire?'
'In 65 years of our independence,'
'we achieved progress
at a fast pace,'
'but, at the same pace,
majority of the population'
'was left far behind.'
'The truth about
brighter India is that'
'one-fourth of India's wealth'
'is hoarded by
a mere 100 families.'
'Whereas, 75% of the population is'
'forced to survive on less than
Rs 20 a day.'
'The mistrust arising out this gap,
is increasing.'
'And perhaps, time is slipping away
from our hands.'
"This is our land."
"We were born here."
"We will live here."
"We will die here."
"There is no value of anyone."