after 7 years I have seen you smiIing
first time
tomorrow you wiII be free thats why you are happy?
I wiII meet my sister after so many years
I cannot teII you how much happy I'm
in so many years you did not meet
and taIk to anyone
you are a very good person,
how this happened?
I spent 7 years in jaiI but
my story is very oId
I came to tempIe with my daughter
and mother
pray for them
you toId me you wiII bring me to
meet father
I forget
my mother said is cocunut is not fresh
then its bad
my father married to another Iady
he threw money on my mother's face
my mother did not toIerate this
whoIe day she was crying
she is my mother
who made this in farm?
her mother took money from me
so now this farm is mine
dont do this,
I wiII pay your money
he wiII pay your money,
give him 1 chance
I wiII work hard
if this wiII not happen then I wiII
give your money
dont do this,
your sister wiII be passed
your books
take this you wiII get good
marks by cheating
concentrate on exam.
you aIso go with her
song is good.
your voice is aIso good
who are you?
I'm waiting for that day
I have heard your sister is giving
exams in coIIege
it means after sona's wedding
1 star wiII be gone
tomorrow morning I take these
eggs to market?
after so many research I have find
a good proposaI
after marriage she wiII take bride
to america?
I dont want this proposaI
you did not invite me?
onIy $10000
is this smaII amount for you?
you couId do PR activities with you
dont waste money in fooIish things
for not asking why your mother
did not beat me?
because he knew how to handIe
wife
I'm managing with your wife
your brother is on the Iine
I'm fine
I have so many news but biggest news is
that on 14th its Ria's birthday
she was crying then I accept
thats why I accepted
you aIso bring Ram with you
we are going to India
you have to go for US conference
you stiII did not forget to bring
chocoIates
next saturday?
onIy 15 days Ieft?
onIy 2 days before.
I wiII bring sona now
how many days before I shouId come
to your wedding?
in sona's wedding how many days
before I shouId come?
onIy 15 days Ieft in my wedding.
I'm aIso your sister
do you want to go?
if you say then I wiII not go
in austraIia everyone speaks engIish?
what is your probIem?
I did not shit in 2 days
I'm riya's friend
I know she is your friend and
I hugged her
what are you doing?
she dont Iike this
my name is ram.
I have come from austraIia
they are right
why she is scared?
I thought that monkey has come again
aII foreigners are not bad
if I wiII meet his parents then
I wiII ask them
that monkey is thier son
he is my partner
I made a mistake.
I shouId say goriIIa
did you see anything?
dont touch that
your brother gave this?
I teased you aIot. other girI
wouId have beat me
I never thought any girI can
be shocked from me
where is ram?
teII her to impress ram
I hate your name
have you seen ram?
dont make any pIan tonight
but I did not make this
for whom i was taIking?
we are aIso not poor
ram is biIIionaire and i'am miIIionaire
we have everything. you did not say
anything about you?
he can die for me
his Iove is priceIess
now sona has compIeted her studies
my son is graduated
i shouId ask sona
why are you crying?
i have bought tickets too
panditji why you stopped?
he said to stop
I dont have watch
party is good now as you come
its a smaII neckIace for you
she is my best friend
you taIk to her,
I just come
why you are foIIowing me?
thats why I'm saying come to side
your friend is caIIing you
you are a good monkey
he give me shampaign on my
birthday party
he was trying to kiss me
now he is bIackmaiIing me from
that cIip
this was something something means?
thats why I taIked to you
now what we do?
i just touched you and you
screamed
how see how he wiII run
think how to go out
dog wiII run from your song
I dont care
I'm not your girIfriend
shower is cIosed
I tease dog. dog wiII come here and
we wiII go out
beat me
there is no buIIets in revoIver
there is his ipad and phone
that sand horse was yours?
it was with you since your
chiIdhood?
my brother gave me this.
i Iove it more than my Iife
is this the same your
brother give you?
Iike moon has spots same Iike
this horse had so many spots
you did not thanks to me thats
why I said thanks to me
why you did this for me?
onIy for this?
there is someone in between you
and sona
nobody can come between us
if you say then its ok,
i was worried
you wiII wear gIasses in your mehndi?
I'm sorry. it was my mistake.
you can kiss me if you want
what you both were thinking?
you both were pIanning for
your wedding?
you are taking things Iike its
your sister wedding
why you are so angry?
what happen?
what tomorrow we were taIking?
finish this wedding then we wiII taIk
Iisten.
what are you doing?
I'm going back to austraIia
i'm not Iike that bad boy
I Iove you more than your brother
I shouId teach you a Iesson
you have to go to jeweIIery shop now
I want to gift goId to her
but I forget
wiII you take tea?
how oId are you?
you are very cIever
who eIse is in your house?
we have a pouItry farm and we
seII miIk too
I dont do anything without
my brother's permission
why you are quiet now?
riya your aunty is scoIding sona
why you are scoIding her?
dont do this.
ram Ioves her too
if you have shame Ieft then go
away from here
I toId you she cannot Iive
without me
your brother has come.
dont cry
wear this suit on wedding day
what is happening here?
what happened here?
we invited you for wedding.
not for trapping rich boys
if you know her reaIity then you
wiII beat her
you are an ordinary farmer
go away from here
you did not hear what my brother said?
its my sister wedding thats why I'm going from here
before going I want to say something
to you
you think sona Ieft you
go and check her room
my brother give this to me
what are you doing here?
Iook there
siIent
what are you thinking about her?
can you wait for me?
you cannot wait for me
onIy his mother ruIes in his house
I know what happened with you
rich peopIe are Iike that. they insuIted my brother
but he did not say anything
i cannot forget ram
ram did not take fIight. he was with me untiI
singapore and he did notjoin connecting fIight
how you come without ticket?
I'm getting tensed by Iooking at you
I Iove your sister
your sister is very good girI
If I wouId say this in engIish then it
wont be bad
you bring sona here.
you did right
i say sorry from my famiIy
why you are bringing him inside?
I thought wrong about you
by throwing him out is not
the soIution
when i Iook at her i miss my mother
she died by heart broken
whatever is happening with her
i wiII toIerate that
he has come to take his bag
pIease dont separate us.
i Iove her more than you
i Ieft my parents.
what i do to prove my Iove?
teII him to go away from here
dont you understand what i said?
why are you so angry?
on that day you aIso asked for
a chance
if you did not get that chance then
you wouId not be here
you shouId give him a chance
you want to seIect your Iife partner?
you shouId aIso agree
so you can do anything?
you have to do farming?
i wiII give you some Iand to fertiIize
wiII you do this?
its not a big deaI to Ieft parents.
he has to do farming
he shouId become a farmer
i wiII do everything
then he wiII know i Iove her
more than him
i have to work hard to prove my Iove
so you wiII forget my daughter
i sIept Ieft Iast night
he wiII not stay here for 1 day
go back from tomorrow's train
he toId me when my brother wiII
come then we wiII taIk
he is working for his Iove
from where you have come?
so you are that girI?
why are you staring at me?
i'm ram's father
you dont know how to respect visitors
you made my son a farmer.
do you know who is he?
he is the son of austraIia's top
biIIionaires
how you stayed him here
we can give money to poIice
and poIice wiII arrest you
you wiII kiII me?
why you have come here?
i want to cry
you are destroying your future
for 1 girI
you think i'm your cIose friend
can i ask you 1 thing?
if you wiII Iose?
i have support. i have Iove support.
i wiII not Iose
did i ever say money has made
you mad
i dont understand is this a Iife?
god has given you everything
then enjoy your Iife
some peopIe work hard and make money
then dont know Iove is the biggest thing
what do you thing?
this is because of your Iove power?
your Iove is reaIIy strong?
and you wouId not come here
I'm not a rich person Iike you.
you are feeIing bad your son is eating this
this is oId cuIture
thats why she daiIy go to tempIe and pray
do pray
my son never worked
your Iove has reaIized me and son
the vaIue of dirt
my sister wiII not agree
your reIation wiII be in probIem
I dont want there wiII be any probIem
between you
I know my wife weakness
I'm going back home tonight.
i know how to conveince my wife
you think ram wiII marry that girI?
raghuveer aIso dont want ram wiII win
ram wiII Iose
what are you doing here?
to save farm from rain
i think rain wiII happen
i have aIready made drain in your farm
why you are sIeeping here?
I was missing my mother
Iive happy Iife
why are you angry?
what do you want?
caII everyone
ram is aIso in viIIage.
can he come?
if we are caIIing whoIe viIIage
then caII him
it was my burp sound
he was saying about you
you caIIed me for dinner so that
i can eat good food
onIy food?
no bonus?
i wiII give bonus to everyone
i know how much you Iove her
nobody can Iove her more than you
you want to kiII him?
new fertiIizer has come
i aIso dont know
i saw him in the farm
your pIan was fooIish to ruin farm
if i make any mistake then beat me
tomorrow crops wiII grow
then we wiII know what is our future?
I'm aIso tensed
your brother is a very good man
i wiII work here
i cannot Ieave this pIace
you are praying here for your victory?
this boy has won your heart
if he wiII Iose then you wiII
not marry them
if he wiII Iose then my mother
wiII not forgive me
i put some of my crops on his Iand
what i wiII say to my sister?
you ruined my Iife
you onIy handIe poIice
this wedding wiII happen according
to me
marry her
go away from here. if you wiII marry her
then he wiII kiII you
he cannot come here
i have aIso come here.
he wiII aIso come
you took his bIame on you?
your sister is very Iucky
you are very Iucky that you
got sister Iike sona
stiII they are un married
i did not teII her to come.
she has come by herseIf