Doctor...
The internet has confused
me with too many options
That's why I'm here.
I need some help.
I...
I want to kill myself.
Suicide.
I haven't showered in a week...
nor have I
spoken to anyone.
Even my ceiling fan
stopped responding.
Maybe I'm going insane.
Slightly, but...
The homes and hearts of you...
South Indians
are the same...
completely hollow.
How can I forget...
I've replayed that day
in my mind a thousand times.
And what is this
supposed to be?
Sam bar.
- This?!
- Yes.
Is there a problem?
Just one problem.
You!
If you have a problem,
keep moving.
Excuse me!
You're cutting the line.
How will he eat if
he doesn't cut the line?!
I've been the 'Head Cook'
here for 10 years!
Not a single 'complan'
against my sambar!
There hasn't been a single 'complan',
that's why no improvement!
Can anyone eat this?!
No...
But you'll get used
to it in a while.
The rasgulla's not bad.
Try it.
Give me the rasgulla.
Finish your food first.
Who do you think you are?
Give it to me!
One more.
One rasgulla per student.
Very good.
What's edible,
one per student...
miserable sambar unlimited!
Give her mine...
Please.
Where did this stupid
idiot come from?
Teaching ME about sambar.
Hi