What time will
the Train come?
lt's time for it to come...
lt's expected
any time now...
Ask him exactly
when it will come?
He says he can tell you that
only when the train arrives.
Call him and ask him where
the Train is at this point...
Hello...
l am Virat's sister...
Yes!Tell me...
Our Train has stopped here because engine
ls he there?
Yes he is playing?
Virat...Virat
Your kind attention please...
Special Train from Jammu
to Mumbai Central,
Train Number; 1 2472,
Jammu  Express is arriving
on Platform Number 5...
Brother is there...
-Where is he?
Hi, Brother!
- Hey,Preeti! How are you?
How are you dad?
What's with the tiny beard?
Let us get out from here
Virat were are you going?
DaD were are we going?
Come fast
Come sit
Keep the bag in the Trunk.
Get in.
Change to the third gear...
Where are we going
in such a hurry...?
Don't you know?
If i knew why would i ask!
We are going to see
a girl for you to marry.
The inauspicious month
starts with tomorrow...
And the inauspicious time
starts in 25 minutes...
We have to see
the girl before that;
else you will remain
a Bachelor even this year...
Mom, will i go with a uniform
Let me have a bath,
change clothes,
let me eat and
then go out for this.
You're getting old!
l am going to be the same
age all of today, Mom.
Change to the fourth gear.
Greetings!
Welcome.
Hasn't the Groom come?
This is the Groom!
He looks like he is coming
straight from the Battlefield!
Please come.
Please come in...
We have to see the girl before
the auspicious time gets over...
That's why l brought him
directly from the Station.
Please ask the girl to come...
Saiba
Is this saiba?
Saiba can sing a  good song...
One can only sing the
National Anthem...
Aren't you happy, my Boy!
Dad, can you give me
their number?
Don't make noise...
The Groom is on line.
Please tell me...
Sir, your daughter
looks beautiful...
But, our tastes
seem different...
l don't know if we
will be a good match...
But, you will surely find a
better Groom for your daughter...
Hey!!What is this!!!
He is not going to get
married in this lifetime!!
Give me one reason for
not liking this girl!
l have three reasons!
That girl has hair that is
a meter and a half long!
take ages to set
their hair before going out for party
Did l ask for this? Did l?
Did l ask you to
get me married now?
On top of that,
she is shy.
Look at her,
slapping her own Father...
Well!
You should have disciplined
her while she was young.
You were the one who played
with her...
...asking her to ''Hit Daddy''
l thought she would be
a stylish girl,
Why do you need
so much money?
l've given 6 people coffee
This is my tip
Postmotem report say's this lady
commit suicide
This is murder
Someone had murdered her
Your case is solve
Just fine the killer
When i knew you are coming
I was suppose to go away
My luck could not get of duty
Virat every time you come here for holiday
You will interfere
in everything l do.
Just when l am about to get
promoted from...
...being a Sub lnspector (Sl)
to an lnspector,
...you will drag me back to
being an Sl.
Ok fine next time i wont
What is going on here
Championship
Are you not on duty
Will you play with the dog
Rocky is retiring tommorrow
Rocky's last dayon duty
What happen on his foot
Department don't need him
Can i keep rocky
I am on duty so keep calm
How did it go yesterday
you went to see a girl
Don't ask me
She is a shy girl
I don't like this girl?
You need a girl like her
That is just not possible!!!!
He has gone mad!
He said he didn't like her,
but now he says he likes her.
He's got hold of a lame
Police dog from somewhere..
...and is trying to please me
saying it's my birthday gift!
ls she a Girl or a dish
that you can re-order?
lf we listen to him,
we'll turn crazy!
Hey!Tell them!
We can't talk to them again!
Forget it!
What is it?
ls he kidding?
He said he didn't like me then.
But, now he likes me!
After the wedding, he might
not like me again. ls that ok?
l don't need to do all that.
Virat don't get married
She is the boxer
Should we try saying ''Hi''.?
He is the guy l said ''No'' to.
Hey! Get down!!
Come on, get down!
What are you going to do?
He'll be dead today!!
Why did you kiss me now?
Me.?
Ya. l only kissed the Mirror.
This is my Mirror.
l will do whatever
l like with it.
The Mirror is yours, but
the reflection in it was mine.
That belongs
to the Government.
l will kiss my Mirror,
cajole it, break it.
That is up to me.
Why should you break it?
l'll break it myself!
No violence, please.
This is a public Road.
What cheek you have
to kiss on the Road?
What kind of
a Policeman are you?
You are sitting there like
a sack of Potatoes!
lf l complaint of
eve teasing,
they'll put you behind
bars and beat you up
She is worse than
my Mother-ln-law!
You can enquire about
''Boxer Saiba
She has my bike key's
Had you said you liked her
at the first instant,
my bike mirror
would have been saved.
lsn't this super?
She flicked the Bike keys
as she was talking to us!
She wasn't talking,
she was chiding!
What did my Department Bike
have to do with your fight?
Thief!
l had 5000 Rupees
in my purse!!
Don't panic.
l am a Policeman.
The two of us are Policemen.
We'll check everyone.
We'll find out.
Driver! Stop the Bus.
No one will get down.
We'll check everybody!
Balaji, check people here.
l'll check people
on the other side.
Get down, one by one!
Sir, that's my purse!
Hey there! ls this yours?
- No, Sir.
You go in and check,
check under the seats.
Check the Bags as well.
Please open the bag.
My purse!!
Why are you running?
Why?
Don't panic untill im here
Virat let's go give an interview
come
lnstead of enquiring
him first,
...they are treating him
at the Hospital.
Look at him making speeches
with bated breath,
...as though he caught him.
l should have been there.
You dragged me
away from there!
Had l appeared on Television,
my Mother-ln-Law would be shaken.
Things would have been
different at home.
l would have become
an lnspector!
The motive ofTerrorists could
not have been to plant...
...a bomb in the
State Transport Bus,
but could have gone off unexpectedly,
while in transit to another place.
The Minister of Home Affairs
has expressed...
...concern over the number of
terrorist like,
Ajmal Lateef and their motives
l've been waiting for you.
-Why?
Go in, l'll tell you.
What is it?
At this time
They work with me.
They're off duty now.
They will stay on guard here,
just for tonight.
Leave  with
your family tomorrow morning.
Why are you
doing all this?
He has escaped
from the Hospital.
What?
He has killed a Doctor
and two Police Officers.
How?
l don't know.
Fine, you go ahead.
lt was you who caught him;
l suspect he might
come looking for you.
They are here anyway.
Both of you go
to the rear side.
l'll get going.
So many policemen today
What did those innocent kids
in the Bus do to you?
Do you know why l
chopped off your finger...
...without asking you anything?
l am going to ask you
a question now.
lf you don't answer it, you should
know what could happen to you.
One question.
Just one second to give me
an answer,
else, the other finger
will go as well.
That's all. So simple!
Who is it?
- lt's me!
What are you doing here
at this time?
Who is it?
- l am coming.
l am asking you.
What are you doing here?
l need to talk to you.
Can you come up
to the Terrace?
What do you want
at this hour?
We can talk in the morning.
The guy you helped escape is
now at my house as my guest.
Sorry, l didn't tell you
who l am.
One of the specialists at
the Defense lntelligence Agency.
A Secret Agent in the Army.
People who work with me.
My friends.
Even my family
doesn't know this.
Are you wondering why
l am telling you this?
Because, you are not going
to be alive any more.
While we are at the Camp,
the other Country firing at us
and us firing in return
happens often.
One day, at our Camp,
a boy called ashraf,
a chap ,
went missing.
We looked for him for 7 days
but didn't find him.
We found him
on the eighth day.
Poor thing, guess he got
caught in their Camp.
They dug out his eyes,
shoved a Beer bottle
through his body
...and broke it inside him.
We were the ones
who went home and
delivered his dead body.
His Mom was howling,
his Dad was beating
his chest in grief,
his sisters were weeping.
And on the fourteenth day,
his younger brother
joined the Military.
We die there every day, so that
you guys here can live happily.
This is a locally made Gun.
This is my Gun.
lf l shoot you,
l will have to explain
why l did so.
Even when you are dead,
your family will slander you.
Your children will have
to beg on the streets.
Your wife will have to beckon
men on the roads at night.
But, if you shoot yourself,
it would be called a suicide
while on duty and someone from
your family will be given a job.
They'll get your
Provident Fund money,
the monthly Pension.
You take a call.
But if that Gun turns
towards me, l'll shoot you.
You are playing with Danger.
l know the two of you are not
aware of everything.
When?
Try to understand i am getting married
I want to ask you a question?
Is this maths class
Come to the side
You looking beautiful
And now. how did you get
married to a guy like this?
Look here, you need
to think practically.
Praise him and
get married to him
Why are you sitting
here like this?
l am thinking about something.
lt's not falling in place.
Tell me what it is.
Let's see if l can
think of something.
l being a Policeman
can't do it
and here you are
thinking you can!
Do you know the difference between
a Policeman and a Military man?
You Military men don't
have to use your brain.
You just have to put have your
feet together for''Attention''
and split them for
''Stand at ease''.
And if you are told to shoot,
you just have to rapidly.
But, we Policemen
have to use our brains.
When we are going to
nab a Pick Pocket,
we have to think like him.
When we are going
to catch a murderer,
we have to think
like a murderer.
And when we are going to
catch a Terrorist,
...we have to turn
in to a Terrorist.
l am a Policeman and yet,
struggling.
You go ahead and play.
Tell me what your problem is,
l'll see if l can help.
l'll tell you,
try and get the drift.
The night that
the Terrorist escaped,
a Police officer shot himself
and committed suicide.
He was on duty when
the Terrorist escaped.
My doubt right now is if these two
incidents could have any connection.
Firstly, that is not a suicide.
lt's a murder.
How do you say that?
l was the one who killed him.
Why did you kill him?
Why did he let
the Terrorist escape?
He let the Terrorist escape?
How do you know that?
The Terrorist told me that.
The Terrorist escaped from the Hospital.
Where did you see him?
Well! The Hospital.
The Hospital.?
l am asking you
where you saw him.
Tell me what it is!
Can l marry you?
When did you get this idea?
This morning. at 8.40am
-What happened at 8.40am?
lt was my friend's reception.
She's the most beautiful
girl in my college.
The guy she is marrying
doesn't look one bit good.
l asked her about it and
she gave me some advice.
And then,
friends encouraged me.
But, we didn't make a good
match right from the start.
l said ''No'' at first
and then you did,
and now you are saying
you want this.
l am only saying l want it.
Yes, but our tastes
should match.
Do you smoke?
- Huh?
A Cigarette.
- No way! How can girls smoke?
That is not allowed in Boxing.
See that!
l only like girls who smoke.
Well. l can't say
l've never smoked.
l have smoked at Girls parties,
New Year and occasions like that.
What about Drinks?
Liquor, my dear.
Yes. Red wine.
That's good for
the heart and skin.
l've even tried Vodka once.
See that, l can't stand
girls who drink Liquor.
No!! You are saying different
things on purpose.
You are in love with me.
You are purposely doing this
- Saiba, wait..
l came here straight from
the wedding,just for you.
l didn't even eat there.
lf you want, l can get married
to you right away.
l was just kidding.
There is a small hitch.
Again? What is it?
Because l was angry with you,
l agreed to marry another guy
my parents found for me.
You said ''yes'' to him?
That is not a problem.
Saying ''Yes'' at first and
rejecting him after that
...is hardly a problem for me.
What l said to you is different
from what l told him.
He is from the Military too.
lf l convince him,
all problems will be sorted.
He has asked me to come to
the Coffee shop at 1 2.
Ok! l'll come along too!
l'll take care of it.
Shall we leave then?
-Yes.
lt's here.
Just wait a moment.
He's a Military guy,
he's here on time.
l'll go first.
You can come later.
Hey! l'll talk to him first
and then will call
Hey, Virat,
what are you doing here?
How are you?
When l heard the loud voice,
l imagined we were
in the Parade ground.
Ok, come on.
Well!
The girl l am going to marry has
said she would meet me here today.
All this is to meet her...
l am nervous because
this is the first time.
Please sit down.
Your Mom called to say that
you like me a lot as well.
Sorry, Saiba. Meet Mr..
But, he is much junior to me.
He makes mistakes and
gets punished very often.
He is a little more scared
of me because of that.
Saiba, what will you eat?
- No. Nothing!
What about you, Jagdish?
Saiba, l have a get together
at the Hotel this evening.
Virat, you must come too.
- Yes, Sir!
Now! lt's 1 2.30.
We said we would meet at 1 2.
So, we'll meet in the evening.
ls he mad?
l'll see you in the evening.
ls this how you planned
to talk to him?
That's not it, Madam.
Whatever it is,
you are his fiance.
Hey! even after he left,
you are calling me ''Madam''
Aren't we in love already.
We can break up with each other.
We've not been in love even
for an hour;
and a break up before that?
Look here, Madam.
He is better than me
in every way.
lt takes me 52 seconds
to run 400 meters,
but he can do that
in 48 seconds.
ln a High jump,
l can get across a height of
6 feet and 1 inch,
but he can cover 6 feet
and 4 inches?
ln the Long jump,
l can leap across only 7 meters,
but he is 7.4 meters.
ln Weight lifting...
ls someone recruiting people
for the Military here?
l don't like him.
But, you didn't like me
at first either,
but you like me now.
You don't like him now,
but you could like him tomorrow.
They are two
different things.
Not just that.
l can find a match easily.
But who will marry him
at this age.
What do l do for that, why me?
Your phone is ringing.
lt's your phone.
Hey!Where did you see the Terrorist
who escaped from the Hospital?
Will tell you later,
The two of us have an
important job to do tomorrow.
Hey!Why are you
sitting here?
Like you don't know
why l've come!
lt's not that.
Don't come in to
my room all of a sudden.
Where did you see
that Terrorist?
How did you catch the guy
who escaped from the Hospital?
After you left that day,
l stayed back at the Hospital.
We shouldn't keep him here,
we must hand him
over to the Police.
For him to escape again?
Only then will we know how
many more of them are around.
Why are you taking
the lnjection?
Don't untie him.
Where are you going?
How many questions
will you ask?
l've injected him
with Ketamine.
He will remain
unconscious for two hours.
Let's go.
Where do we go?
To the Wedding.
My Batch mate is
getting married today.
Let's go.
This is a bit too much.
You want to keep him at home
and go out to attend a wedding?
You've even untied him.
We'll come back.
Who is this?
He wants to play,
be it the Camp or...
...where the Train stops
now even at the Wedding.
Guys, this is a serious game.
We'll all in one team
ln two minutes from now,
a man will come out of
the back door of my house.
We will follow him.
When he meets a man
after that,
our group will split
into two.
One group of 6 will
follow one man.
the next 6 will
follow the other.
As they keep meeting
more people after that,
we will divide further
and follow them.
Keep your cell phones on.
Don't attend any
other call but mine.
We will stay connected
through a conference call.
He is coming.
- ls he the guy?
lt's a risk only if
we don't do anything.
Start the vehicle and
slowly follow him.
Who is the other guy?
What if they don't split
as 1 2 but stay at one place?
No, they have work at 1 2 places.
Stop the vehicle.
You follow him.
Boys! We are 1 2 of us
for 1 2 of them.
The game is going to end now.
Look at the Case in your bag.
There is a gun inside
There is a gun
Let no one panic.
l was the one who kept it.
The guys in front of you
are no ordinary thieves.
techniques of serial bomb blasts
and simultaneous blasts.
without a seconds' difference.
Who are these sleeper cells?
Sleeper cells are
present at places
Where terrorism is a challenge
We can't identify them, because..
Even these 1 2 men have led
a normal life with the public
They are people who have druid
against the country and the government
They are cultivated for years.
And their grudge is misused
for terrorist activities
After 9/1 1 the U S is free
from terrorism because..
...only in that country
sleeper cell
have been identified and
destroyed completely.
..and their further growth
was arrested
Mom, Dad
Who did all this?
lt is still unknown
Even the policemen are clueless
Did you get any clue?
The police has seized the equipments
of all the 1 2 sleeper cells
But the non tracker phone
that belonged to one of them...
..has been taken by the person
who killed him.
Whose phone is it?
Adzar Ali, the one was
killed
No' idea who you are?
You kill my 12 people
One was my brother
I am coming
Where ever you are i'll finish you
I'm waiting
What is the height for this wall
They are good jumper's
What was the speed of the bus
They also no swimming
They kill my 12 men on the forehead
Train shooter's
They are not policemen
Any common with this 12 people
They all was wearing suit's
You think you are smart
I want a list of all the wedding
Yes, they are Sleeper Cells.
One or may be two of their
Heads will make the plan.
The Sleeper Cells merely execute
...and will even be willing
to lose their lives for it.
Even if one of them
does get caught,
there is nothing we can
get to know through him.
Does that mean Sleeper Cells
carry on lives...
...as normal people
until they get orders?
Yes, they will wait for years.
ls there no way
we can kill them all?
We can't kill them, but we can
stop them from functioning.
lf we kill the main head
who gives the orders,
these guys will keep waiting
for orders all their lives.
That's fine.
But, how will you search for
the leader? who gives out orders.
l don't have to go in
search of him.
l've made him come in
search of me.
lf we killed the 1 2 of them,
he would retaliate by attacking us.
That was my assessment.
l was right.
He's out to get me.
Oh, my God!
But, how will he find you
in a big city like Mumbai?
While killing the 1 2,
we would have surely left
behind some kind of a clue.
He will work
towards finding that.
lf we find out what that is,
we can catch him
before he attacks us.
Your senior officer has asked the
both of us to come over to his house.
l am coming.
Virat, this is wrong.
Look at what are you doing
amidst our important work
Don't run behind a girl,
sit here and think of something.
Why don't the two of you
get married?
Don't get me wrong.
We were in love,
but never once did l touch her.
Ask her.We haven't.
l know you will find it
difficult to forget me.
Can l be faulted
for being handsome?
lt's our first date.
As per rules of dating,
l can't refuse anything a
boyfriend asks of me.
Hey! Come on! You've already
spent a lot of money for.
What if you ask me
for a kiss?
How can l refuse that?
Virat, this is Amar Singh.
Someone kidnapped
my brother's daughter.
Yes, she went jogging
with her friend this morning.
Someone forcefully dragged her
in to a vehicle.
The fifth girl
has gone missing too! Yes!!
Are you human?
You are a sadist!!
Are you even feeling bad that
the girls have gone missing?
You want to kill
the Head of the Sleeper Cell.
Mumbai city will not have
terrorist acts for the many years.
Did you even think of what
their families will go through?
My sister is one the girls
they've kidnapped.
He will keep all the
kidnapped girls in one place.
We have to save them
and get him as well.
l sent my sister Sanjana
Where are you?
Why should l bring her Bike?
Do what l ask you to.
Fine! There is a 40 percent Off
Sale at Levis.
Will you buy me a
pair of three fourths?
Fine, you hurry.
This is Preeti's Dupatta.
Buy me a Maroon colored Top, it
should have embroidery on the sides.
l will look around for
anything suspicious. Let's see.
Untie them
Project the photo one by one
Who knows him?
He is my brother.
Go that side.
That's my Uncle.
Who is this?
ls he your Brother?
Yours?
No.
Show the other photograph.
This is my Brother.
ls your Brother one among
these 5 people?
No.
Show the group photos one by one.
ls your Brother in this group?
That one?
Who asked you to get
the Bike of the girl...
...who was going
to be kidnapped?
My Brother asked me to.
Tell me
The operation in over
We have found the team
One of them has replaced
and sent his sister on purpose
We removed all their sim cards
There is no way he can find us
lf he has sent his sister,
he has a route yo reach you.
He will get to you.
-What are you saying?
Before he comes Kill that girl
and get out of that place.
Get ready, all of you.
Tie up the 4 girls.
Tie this girl up and
bring her here. Hurry up!!
He has come
He is trying
to kill everyone.
He held a huge Knife against me!
Right here.
He might have pulled it out.
Only because we risked lives
could we catch him.
You should have risked
your life for that.
What did l do?
Do only Policemen and Military men
have to die during troubles like this?
Will all of you do nothing
but swap news channels...
...and exchange ideas on what
should have been done?
What would have happened if a bullet
had hit me during your crossfire?
You would have been dead once.
Those guys who want to kill
thousands of people...
...aren't scared of
giving up their lives.
We think of saving lives,
we shouldn't worry about
our lives either.
The main man has been
caught alive now.
He is not the main guy.
Someone called him
and gave him orders.
They brought out their
knives only after that.
Why did you come here?
You left me half way.
That is why l came here.
You should not come here all of
a sudden and try to scare me.
Why?
You can't be sure that l will be
the only person in this room.
Sand Bag. Dumb Bells.
Do you work out?
Did you know?
l read this in a message.
40 calories get burnt
in one deep kiss.
lf you want to be kissed,
ask me directly;
don't hint at it by saying you
read this in a message...
... or this is as per some rule
You lead us on and
then claim Men are mean.
You might as well
stand in a queue...
...and buy kerosene instead of
asking him for a kiss.
You are here anyway,
why the fuss?
Why burn 40 calories,
let's burn 80 calories!
Not here. Let's go there.
You are the one
laying down rules now.
Close your eyes.
lf l close my eyes,
you will run away.
l told you.
My mom has come.
Oh! God!
What do we do now?
Open the door first.
Where are you going?
l am going to hide
in the Cupboard.
That Cupboard engaged.
You get in to this.
What is it Mom.
lt's you.!
Did you watch TV.?
ls this on TV already?
ls there a camera in the room?
l am coming from there.
l saw what you did.
1 6 people have died.
All of them belong to the Sleeper Cells.
They lead normal lives.
Their families are weeping
for them.
None of them believe this
to be true.
This is what we expected.
Did you find a clue about
the Head of the Sleeper Cell?
l expected this
He is not the main guy.
We missed the one giving the orders.
Why is he coughing
in a woman's voice?
Don't you have the habit of keeping
clothes or books in your Cupboard?
Are you going to marry?
You want only the Petromax light,
don't you?
Yes.
Then your life will be coma
Hey,Virat, how are you?
Kapil, where are you?
l have come out with my family.
-Yes, where?
There is a bomb in that building.
Come out now.
What are you saying?
There are so many of them here.
Listen to me, alert everyone and
get them out of there.
Come on menthol out!
lt is only in the Army and Police that
we are awarded with retirement
l have already spoken
to each of you on the phone.
This is the time
l have been waiting for.
We are going to execute
an assignment together.
l am going to meet the guy who controls
the Sleeper Cells tommorrow.
No one can follow me
when l go to meet him.
Hence, even before l go to meet him,
l will insert
a tracking chip inside me.
You should track the chip from
the Control Room
and keep him informed about
its movements.
l have secretly procured explosives
that we use in the Army.
That should reach
all of you this evening.
You should make the C4 Plastic explosive
using that and hand it over to him.
After you get to know about
my whereabouts
Bring it there
l think they will surely
take me to an isolated place
You must leave the vehicle carrying
these explosives in thats place
l still don't know
why they want me alive.
But in the fifteenth minute of me
meeting the Sleeper Cells Head,
...the bomb must explode.
Along with me, the guy who gives orders
for the Sleeper Head will be gone.
After that, all Sleeper Cells
will become Coma Cells.
They will not get
any orders all their life.
Are you kidding?
You are talking about a Suicide Attack
and they are applauding!
He is a very dangerous guy.
But, why are you saying you will die?
Did you think about your family?
Who doesn't have a family?
When the Taj was attacked,
the Men told their children
that they would see them soon.
Hemant Karkare and Vijay Salaskar
died in 20 minutes,
...only their dead bodies returned.
Didn't they have families?
What about these people.
They've lost their limbs
in the same war, yet are happy.
Don't they have families?
An Army man has no better
opportunity than this.
Even the guys who want to kill
...thousands of people are ready
to sacrifice their lives.
Even those of us who want to save lives
should be ready to sacrifice our lives.
l have made a clear decision.
lf you think you want to do
something for me.
People at home are innocent.
And l have two sisters.
lf you are free,
check on them every now and then.
We have just four days left
for the Engagement.
Why are you calling
it off all of a sudden?
Let's not have it for now.
We'll consider this when
l am here the next time.
The wedding is only next year;
it's just the Engagement now.
Yes. Let's not have it now.
You first said you didn't like me,
later, you said you did.
Do you not like me again?
Won't you understand?
But, l don't know if
l'd be able to forget you.
lt'll take me long.
You don't know why you
haven't been killed,
or our plan for you, right?
These are vehicles you have parked.
See what they have in them.
We are not going to let it explode.
We will inform the Police.
Ouestions will be asked about
who put them there.
And then...
...when the Police come
in search of you,
...we would have killed you and
all your team mates.
Do you know who would have killed
you and...
...diffused these bombs at
the right time?
Look at the monitor.
Joint Secretary in Defense.
We will say that
it is his team that...
...killed the 1 2 people during
the shoot out, earlier.
They will come to a conclusion that
you are a double agent.
He will get promoted as
the next Defense Secretary.
So far, it is only the lndian Army
that didn't have Sleeper Cells.
Through him, we'll get a lot of recruits
for the Sleeper Cells in the Army;
...we'll do whatever
we want after that.
l shouldn't die.
Sleeper Cells in the Army is akin to
the Nation suffering from Cancer.
Release the lock now and hit me.
What?
Listen
Your Boss beat me up
when my hands were tied.
l am asking him to unlock me
and he's hesitating.
You broke my hand; you have
Your men around yet you fear me
You better fear me
You broke my hand;
you have so many men with you...
Yet you fear to release
the lock and hit me.
l like that fear.
What are you doing, shoot him.
Listen to me,just shoot him.
You can't beat him.
These two will beat
each other to death.
l can shoot him if you let me.
No way!!
What do l do?
l am telling you!
Kill them both.
You are not smart enough.
Even if you kill me,
...details that control
the Sleeper Cell are in that Ship.
They will continue.
You don't understand, do you?
You can die with that suspense.
Had he said he liked this girl
at the first instance,
we could have got him married
The same with her.
What do we do?
He's not serious about anything.
They are a super pair, Sir.
if they are together today,
l am responsible for it.
You are?
- Yes!
On the very day we arrived,
his Dad rushed him to see this girl.
At first he said he didn't like her,
and then she said she didn't like him.
some ldiot came in between them
and confused everything.
Things have been solved only now.
But, how are you saying that
you brought them together.
You spoke about an ldiot
that came between them,
l am the ldiot.
Hey!What is it?
The Army is truly great.
For another 1 1 months,
you are going to be in
a Desert or a Snow clad mountain...
You will have to live your life
in some dimly lit tent,
and thinking of these 40 days..
Keep on seeing family photos
over and over again
And live with it right.