Mom, I don't want to meet dad.
I want to sleep with you.
''We will be successful.''
''We will be successful someday.'' Yeah.
Where are you?
Yes, I am coming.
''We have this faith.''
''Complete faith.''
''We will be
successful someday.''
''We will walk hand in hand.''
''Someday.''
''We are not afraid.''
''We will walk hand in hand.''
''Someday.''
''Today. We are not
afraid.'' Kartik.
''Not afraid.''
''Someday.''
Good morning, friends.
Thought for the day.
If I am not allowed to..
Ravi. Yes.
See Gupta madamís face.
Doesn’t she seem tense?
Seems like Mr. Gupta didn't
return home last night.
If she looks here,
she will come here.
Are you okay?
What happened?
Nothing.
Kartik, please.This is school.
Exactly. The safest place.
Very funny.
Shall we go to the class? The
assembly is about to end.
Principals lecture has just begun.
She bores for half an hour.
That’s why I was saying..
Can’t we talk about
something else?
We have been talking
since so many days.
What else do we talk about?
Discipline.
Discipline is the only thing..
We know how important
discipline is.
Look. See Gupta ma'am.
in discipline will
not be tolerated.
Who is this guy?
New admission.
Siddhant Rajeshwar.
He was in Doon school earlier.
You are responsible for
your acts, right or wrong.
You didn't come for the assembly.
Where were you?
Not well. I was
here, in the class.
With whom? Kartik
was also not well.
He also had chums?
Okay, tell me. What
were you guys up to?
Nothing, dear.
So what’s the use of
leaving you alone?
Anu didn’t come?
Even today she must have
gone on a date with someone.
Shall we call her up?
Hello.
What the ****!
I am with Sandy.
Shut up, you moron!
You know that I must not
have done the homework.
I am depending on you.
Just put my name on
your own notebook..
..and give it to ma'am.
Okay. Fine. See you
in the dance class.
I won't be late today.
Okay. Bye.
Tell me something.
What if your parents find out
that you have bunked school..
..and you are with me?
So?
What do I know? They
are your parents.
First, they will kick your ass.
And then, they will kick my ass.
I will have to endure
their lectures.
And after a few days,
everything will be normal.
Back to school.
So you have thought of
everything beforehand.
Dude, it’s called intelligence.
And I am intelligent enough
to know what’s good for me.
You wanted to tell me
something important, right?
I want to get my portfolio done.
You told me you have a
photographer friend.
I want to be here.
What’s the hurry? You
are still too young.
And you have time.
Okay.Tell me one thing.
What if you don't get there?
I will.
Come what may.
I know I have it in me.
Of course, you have it in you.
I will also say that you
used to go out with me.
Don't forget me.
Come on.You are my baby.
I love you.
How can I forget you?
We will reach the top together.
Oh, no!
What were you doing in the car?
Well..
That too early in the morning.
Don’t you have any
other work to do?
We were just going.
Lying down on the seat?
Why don’t you speak?
What are you doing?
What is this?
Bribe?
I don’t take bribe.
Keep it with you.
Keep it, uncle. Shouldn't say
no to the first customer.
You are a Jat? Yes, uncle.
From where? Rohtak.
My uncle’s in law’s
house was in Rohtak.
We used to go there in
childhood to eat mangoes.
Okay. Tell me. Who is she?
Girlfriend? Yes, uncle.
Okay. Do one thing. Park the
car a little ahead. Fine?
And do whatever you want to do.
A VIP car is going to
pass from this way. Okay?
Go. Come on. Take the car ahead.
Come on.
Scoundrel.
Let’s move from here.
Dad said he will buy
me D&G if I score 90%.
Let me tell you.. Ashwin,
I need eco notes.
There is a test on Monday.
And I have no clue.
My notes are not complete.
Take it from somebody else.
Give it, man.
Get lost.
Buddha said believe nothing.
Just because the so called
wise person said it.
Believe nothing.
Just because it is
said in ancient books.
Believe nothing.
Just because it is said
to be of divine origin.
Believe nothing.
Just because someone
else believes it.
Believe only what you yourself
test and judge to be true.
Thank you.
Every religion claims to be
the ultimate path to God.
But every religion has
a different concept..
..of who or what God is.
God exists.
If God didn’t exist, so many
people wouldn’t be worshiping Him.
So many people can’t be dumb.
He is so dumb. Do you know?
You were there for
the debate, right?
With great difficulty I
controlled my laughter.
He just looked cute.
Tanisha, nobody is perfect.
Yes. He is just dumb.
What to do with brains?
But you have dumped so
many guys before too.
Some guys score less marks.
Some don’t ready any books
besides school books.
Some don’t have a
sense of humor.
And the best is Kunal.
He is such a 16yearold.
Come on, dear. You
are exaggerating.
I mean, I am not
asking for much.
Just a normal boy.
With good looks,
good sense of humor.
He should be a little matured.
And very intelligent.
I am not interested
in these dumb boys.
Great!
Come on. Perfect
guys also exist.
Ashwin is perfect. Ashwin.
Yuck! Not him. Okay?
He is in love with you.
No ways. Okay?
He is my best guy
friend.That's it.
You are so innocent, aren’t you?
Lt can be seen on his face.
in bold, capital.
Come on, dear. Please. Don't
spread such rumors about him.
I have reached my bus stop.
I will leave. Okay.
Bye. Bye.
See you. See you.
Here, Mr. Kapoor.
This is your future home.
I don't lie. Shall I
tell you something?
This house that I am showing
you is not a house..
..but a sweet home.
A lady lives here. And her
niece lives with her.
That's it.They are
very nice people.
You must have heard
about the riots.
Their relatives
died in that fire.
Since then they are giving
their house on rent.
Here she comes.
Sister, hello.
Hello. Hello.
Hello. We got late
because of the traffic.
lt's okay.
I told you. I will get a
very decent paying guest.
He is a writer.A writer.
And who can be more decent
than a writer? Right?
He has come from London,
to write a book.
He is a nice man. He
is my acquaintance.
Even if you slap him, he
won't say anything.Yes.
No.You are also decent.
Why will you slap him?
Tea? Sister, bring tea.
Yes. Sure. Excuse me.
I would like to see the
place first please.
Yeah, of course. lt'son
the first floor.
Yes, Chotu.Tell me.
I have the key of
flat number 12.
Do one thing.Tell the party to wait.
I will come. Fine?
Mr. Kapoor,you look around.
I have seen it.
I will come in 10 minutes.
Sister, I have discussed the
monetary matter with him. Okay?
Will you live alone?
I mean,your family?
No. I am single. Oh.
ls that a problem?
No. Not a problem.
A kid stays with you?
Yeah.Tanu. My niece.
But don't worry. She
won't disturb you.
She is not that small.
Writers need peace. I know.
How many writers do you know?
If I wanted peace, I would
have lived in the hills.
I wouldn't have come here.
I want to see Delhi closely.
I want to be surrounded by
the vitality of the city.
I want to experience it.
When did you come from London?
10 days.
You know, I think I am
getting a little late.
That's my niece,Tanisha.
Hi. Hi.
So, how do you like the place?
Nice.
Sir has major hots for you.
Why do you do that?
lt's fine. Old man was lustful.
I am so sexy, right?
You are so cheap.
He is so old. What will he do?
Just imagine. Sex while
doing'Kathak' (lndian dance).
That would be cool, right?
What is there?
There is a boy in the house.
God! You desperate girls.
Haven't you ever seen a guy?
Please. He is awesome.
I guess he is Kamat madam's son.
Where is ma'am? I don't know.
Mom had called up. She will
be here in 10 minutes.
Meanwhile, revise your chapter.
Excuse me.
Actually, we couldn't
understand an equation.
So can you please help us out?
Sorry. I study film making.
Didn't you pass your 11th?
Haven't you seen those boards?
Failed 7th, 8th, 9th standard.
And pass 12th directly.
So you will make serials, right?
Those slaughterings and
motherin law types.
Haven't you seen anything
beyond Bollywood?
He is hot. But he has
a lot of attitude.
Did he kiss you?
I she a good kisser?
I don't know.
I will know when I will
kiss someone else.
I mean, I have no
point of comparison.
If you want, I can
get you someone.
For what? For comparison.
That would be fun.
Okay.Tell me.
When do you plan to
do the real thing?
Not now. I am not ready yet.
You will die a virgin.
No. that's not true.
lt's just that I will do it. But at
the right time, at the right place.
I will do it.
Come on. Just cut this crap. You
can do it anytime, anywhere.
Like we have done it in the car.
Gross. How did your legs
fit in the backseat?
You'll learn.You'll learn.
Okay, Ms.Virgin.
Want to go to disco?
Now?
Dumb, at night.
ls that a joke? No.
Kartik.
Same thing.
Desperate. Call him too.
But my mom won't
allow me at night.
Why do you always harp
on mom like a kid?
Grow up.
You should not always
tell your mom the truth.
lt's not good for your health.
Tomorrow is Saturday. No school.
What?
What happened?
Rishi.
He is coming.
I want to talk to you.
Rishi, stop bugging me.
Listen.
Why are you doing this?
Just get lost.
Anu, don’t be a witch.
Shutup,you dog.
He is still after you?
What is he saying?
Why did you dump me?
Why did you dump him?
I don't remember. 2 months.
How many did you dump after him?
Shut up. I am not so bad.
Let's go. Otherwise this
scoundrel will come back.
What are you doing here?
You guys sit. I will just come.
Here.Your eco notes.
Thank you so much for your
kindness, Your Majesty.
Keep it with you.
Nidhi gave it to me.
Come on, Tanisha.
I have especially come
to give it to you.
At that time I was
a little upset.
Why were you upset?
Just like that.
Hello.
Yes,tell me,Anu.Tonight?
ls Nidhi coming?
What time?
Okay. Done. Listen,
Ashwin is also coming.
Don't be mean. Okay?
Bye. Okay. Bye.
I am going. Fine? Bye.
Wait.
Come here. Sit.
Man,what's your problem?
I mean, first you show attitude.
And then you say you were upset.
And then you don’t even tell me
the reason why you were upset.
I am so confused.
What do you want in life?
I want you,Tanisha.
I love you.
Liar.
I don't deserve you.
Hello?
I am talking to you.
Oh God! You can be
so irritating, man.
Forget it. What's the use
of being angry with you?
Want to come to the disco?
I don't have money.
I also don't have it.
What are Anu and
her boyfriends or?
But will your dad allow?
To hell with him.
He says only one thing.
You have to do IAS.
You have to do lAS.
I am fed up.
Tell him it's enough that
you clear your 11th.
I know. I will be happy to
join a call center. But dad..
ls there long term scope
in a call center?
Tanisha, long term is too long.
Mom, Anu is coming
to pick me up.
I will stay in her
house for the night.
Will you study or have fun?
Both.
Fine. But return early
in the morning. Okay.
Where are you going?
I am going to the disco with Anu.
Don't tell mama. Okay?
We are going.
You know we are going
to have so much of fun.
Who is he?
Hi. Hi.
He is our PG.
Come on. Hurry up. Or
else we will be late.
Yes. Come on.
Not at all means not at all. No.
I won't allow it.
Everyday you get to see
something on the TV.
There are so many cases.
But you are not at all worried.
She is our daughter,
not our neighbor's.
Yes,Anu. I am not coming.
Nidhi. One moment.
Yes, dad? Go and get ready.
Okay. I am getting ready.
Come soon.
You just remain good
in front of the kids.
And make me look bad.
Looking hot, sis.
Rahul! Thanks.
See today's brothers..
Yes,Anu. Okay. I am coming.
Anu has come downstairs. I am going.
Return before 12.
But, mom.. You won't stay
at her place for the night.
She is the one who
is spoiling you.
Bye, dad. Bye, Rahul.
Nidhi, one moment. I will
drop you downstairs.
Dear,there is no need
to tell you everything.
I know you will
never let me down.
You can trust me, papa.
Here. Thank you, papa.
And yes, return home before 12.
Or else both of us
will be beaten.
I will come, papa. Now you also
don't act like mama. Please.
Okay. Bye. Okay. Bye. Take care.
Try it, babes.You
live only once.
No. Come on. Just one sip.
Taste it and see.
Yuck. lt's so bitter. How
do you guys drink it?
Drink it as a tonic. Shut up.
I don't like it and all.
Hey, Anu. Hey.
This is Akash.
Akash, this is Anu.
Hi. Hi. Nice to meet you.
Anu wants to get her
portfolio done.
Sure.Take my number from
Sandy and call me tomorrow.
Okay. Cool.
Let's go inside. Come on.
''There lies a thin line
between you and me.''
''On this side is friendship.''
''On that side love.''
''I have to cross this line.''
''I need to take that step.''
''But it's going to me all
the day frustrating.''
''And just been waiting.''
''For me on the style.''
''For me to make
the first move.''
''Maybe baby you
are only a love.''
''But true love.''
''The way your body moves.''
''It shows that it does.''
''Maybe baby you
don't realize.''
''That true love.''
''The way your body moves.''
''It shows that it does.''
''Maybe baby, baby, baby.''
''lt's only love.''
Kartik, do you think mothers
have a sixth sense?
You are not listening
to what I am saying.
Kartik.
I am listening.
Do you know? Since the
time she has seen us..
..at the parents
teacher meeting..
..she is like, ''Stay
away from boys.''
''Concentrate on your studies.''
I think she has even told dad.
Kartik, you are not interested
in what I am saying, right?
Go on. I am listening.
Kartik, no.
Kartik.
Stop it, Kartik.
What the hell! I didn't
do it purposely.
You witch! Kartik.
Listen, Kartik.
''I need to take that step.''
When he had to puke, why
did he drink so much?
Wasted it.
You know how much
that beer cost?
Freaking 300 bucks per bottle.
Are you okay?
Chill, babes. He is a desperate guy.
He won't go anywhere.
He is desperate. That's
why he will go away.
He can sleep with
any girl he wants.
Come on. He is not that hot.
He is. Even you are not
responding to his heat.
Shut up,Anu.
Come.
Where are you coming from?
Group studies.
I was studying at
Tanisha's house.
Come here.
You were studying?
Or drinking?
Come on.
Go to hell.
Apply it a bit. Just a bit.
Why do you do this?
You know, don't you?
He doesn't like this.
He doesn't like anything.
Apply a bit. Enough. lt's done.
Go to sleep.
Will you eat something?
I already had a lot.
Finance minister sure
of 9% growth in GDP.
Another farmer suicide
in Maharashtra.
lndian batting failed again.
Goa, Kerala best states in
which to be born in lndia.
Newspaper reading...
...is a must.
lt will not only
increase your GK..
..but also improve
your language.
And you will understand
life in a better way.
But dad, even on the TV..
Not on TV. Not on TV.
Reading. Reading.
To become IAS..
Show me.
Drinking at night and
dancing in the disco.
All this isn't for you.
There are billionaires' and
politicians' sons for that.
Even if they commit
murder, nothing happens.
You don't have to be a
spoil brat like them.
You have to become IAS.
Hey!
Here.
Eat.
What did you drink last night?
36yearold handsome
and rich bachelor.
Looking for a soul mate.
Sounds nice.
Show me.
Yes. By now he must be
married and having kids.
lt's two years old newspaper.
Shall I bring this Sunday's newspaper?
Shall I hit you?
Will he do?
Shutup.
Thank you.
Are you comfortable here?
Absolutely. This place
is just perfect.
So Tanisha, do you like reading?
One minute please.
Hello. Hi.
I love reading. And I would
love to read your book.
After me and my editor,you will
be the first person to read it.
'To Kill A Mockingbird'.
No. I didn't read it.
Okay, Vikram.Tell me.
How did you become a writer?
I had nothing else to do.
You always knew?
I always knew that I was too
lazy to do anything else.
You are kidding?
No, I am not.
I mean, you also
have to toil a lot.
Yes. But I didn’t know that
before I became a writer.
Hey! What happened?
Nothing. I slipped
in the bathroom.
So..
Who beat you?
He slipped. Oh!
He didn't slip. Uncle beat him.
He didn't let the
entire sector sleep.
Uncle thrashed him very badly.
Kartik.
And who is that witch?
We are not talking.
Because of day before
yesterday night?
Poor guy. You wasted his
efforts of so many days.
Poor guy is bound to be angry.
Shut up.You are
my friend or his?
Come on. Grow up, babes.
Boys are like that.
That's how boys are.
They only want one thing.
Girls also want that one thing.
Then why don't you
want that one thing?
Come on. Not like that.
lt's not a sin. You
are not Mother Mary.
Dear, it's not that. lt's just
that first time should be special.
Forget it, babes. There's
nothing special about it.
lt's just hormones.
Sex is the most overrated
thing in this world.
Come on. Please don't spoil for me.
Really.
What do you say? Shall I go? Go.
Kartik.
Wait.
I know you are angry.
I sent you an SMS.
And l wrote on your wall too.
l told you l am sorry.
l think l need a break.
Why are you being so stubborn?
ls that the onlything
between us?
There is nothing between us.
Kartik, listen.
lt's over.
''Tears roll down fair cheeks.''
''There is no control
over my breaths.''
''lt's paining although
l am not hurt.''
''On my mind and heart.''
''Quarrels.''
Have Kartik and Nidhi broken up?
l haven't seen them
together since a long time.
Witch. She must have dumped him.
Kartik has dumped her. She
wasn't doing it with him.
''Bad habits play new ruses.''
''All efforts were in vain.''
''Heart is envious needlessly.''
''On my mind and heart.''
''Quarrels.''
ln a process. And one
leads to another.
Tanisha.
Did you read the book
that l gave you?
Yup. But l didn't finish it.
l think you should. lt's a
great piece of literature.
They are talking
about relations.
But all black characters
are stereotypical.
l think it'sa melodramatic,
overhyped book.
But thanks, anyway.
What can we say?
''Life seems very short.''
''All dreams l
have to fulfill.''
''Life seems very short.''
''All dreams l
have to fulfill.''
''Time is passing without
doing anything.''
''On my mind and heart.''
There are so many people.
''Quarrels.''
''Quarrels.'' Nidhi,
pass me the ties.
Nidhi, pass me the ties.
''Quarrels.''
Sister, papa's ties.
Rahul, get my mobile from outside.
Okay, dad.
Nidhi, are you okay? Yes, papa.
You can tell me. What happened?
Any problem in school?
lt's okay if you fail. Don't
take too much pressure.
No, dad.
Boyfriend troubles?
Please, dad.
lt's okay?
Don't trouble your mama at all.
Okay?
Okay, dad. Don't
do any mischief.
Bye, dad. What happened?
lf there is any problem, call me up.
Fine?
lt will remain a
secret between us.
Bye. Bye.
l think he is a virgin.
Maybe he was waiting
for me all this while.
He can talk about
anything in this world.
He is so intelligent.You know?
He is what l call a man.
What is this? Okay.
l will leave now.
Neelu ma'am had called.
Are you coming? No.You go.
Okay. Bye.
Hi.
Nowadays Kartik is not
to be seen with you.
Any problem?
Go wax your *** legs,witch.
Chill, babe. l am asking
just as a friend.
Look, we all knew he
is too good for you.
You..
Leave! Yeah!
Hi, Kartik. Hi.
Listen, l don'twant
to talk about her.
Dude, you were never
interested in talking.
You were just
interested in screwing.
Don't say that to me.
l am not Nidhi.
Nidhi is accepting her mistake.
She has sent you?
No.
What's the hurry?
Understand her
point of view too.
You do not understand
her at all.
l need sex and l am willing
to give up on love for it.
Typical guys attitude.
Do you know how
sensitive she is?
Do you really love her?
''Love. Love. Love.''
What do you think?
''We are afraid and yet
we want to love.''
''Love. Love. Love.''
''We are afraid and yet
we want to love.''
''We don't care about
the outcome.''
''Now there is no fear.''
''Savor it. Savor it.
Savor it.''
''Love. Love. Love.''
''Savor it. Savor it.
Savor it.''
''Love. Love. Love.''
''Savor it. Savor it.
Savor it now.''
''lt's time to love.''
''What is right and
what is wrong?''
''Why to worry about that?''
''Love. Love. Love.''
''Plunge.''
''Plunge and see.''
''Learn to swim.''
''lt's time to fly.''
''What is right and
what is wrong?''
''Why to worry about that?''
Yes, let's go day
after tomorrow.
Yeah. lt will be fun.
Hi, dad. Hi, sweetheart.
No, no. l have never been there.
Yes, Anu is here. Here.
Talk to her.
Hi, uncle.
No. Next time. Okay?
Sure. Soon.
Take care. Bye.
Akhil is saying let's go
to Mathura on Sunday.
Yes, let's go.
Anu. No, dad. l have
my test on Tuesday.
Pray on my behalf too.
Okay. Tell me. What will
you have for dinner?
Poor Ramesh is
waiting for so long.
Potato and cottage cheese.
No, dad. Cottage cheese
is so fattening.
Your cholesterol will rise.
Corn peas. Not a bad idea.
Alright.
We did it. At his
friend's farmhouse.
Yeah. Hold on. Wait a minute.
Wow! How was it?
Good. But he messed
up really soon.
Oh my God! Anyway, l am
really happy for you.
l know it was you.
Kartik told me.
l didn't want to.
But as long as you
lost your virginity.
Anything for a good cause.
Okay. Now hang up. Today
mom and dad are at home.
l need to spend some time with them.
Take care.
Happy anniversary of virginity.
Okay. Bye. Bye.
13 marks?
That's why l have enrolled you
in such an expensive school?
You came first in 8th standard.
You got a cup.
And you won the battle of life.
ls this how you
will do your lES?
lf you don't want to study, l
will send you to a mechanic shop.
Mr. Sinha's son is
an all lndia topper.
Competition has become so tough.
With these marks you won't get
admission even in a lousy college.
What is it?
Leave.
Say something.
Serve dinner.
Look, Tanisha. l don't think
it's working out for me.
l really like you. You
are a wonderful person.
But...something is missing.
What is missing?
l mean, am l not
intelligent enough?
Am l not goodlooking?
We are not compatible.
Compatible meaning how?
See,you are still in school.
And you are not exposed.
Next to next year l am
going to go to college.
There are many other things.
What? Tell me.
Look, we had gone to Habitat
centre to watch a film.
And you were talking.
Either you wanted
to kiss or talk.
l thought you also
wanted to kiss.
l mean, l couldn't
understand that film.
And l was asking you
about the film only.
l wasn't criticizing someone.
Our music taste is
also very different.
You put on your
headphone and listen.
l will put on my
What's the big deal?
You don't understand. We are
not right for each other.
Can we talk about this?
Tanisha, l really like you.
l wanted to fall
in love with you.
But you are not the
perfect person.
But no one is perfect,
right, Sameer?
l knew.You won't understand.
You have light?
You need light or space?
Upset about something?
Love and all that.
First crush.
Hello. l am 16.
Sorry.
Can someone be perfect?
l haven't seen a perfect person.
But you have also not
seen the whole world.
There are more things in
heaven and earth, Horatio..
..than are dreamt of
in your philosophy.
That's.. Hamlet.
l know.
Don't worry.
You will find someone special.
l found him with such
great difficulty.
What kind of music do you like?
l like music.. Have you
ever dumped someone..
..just because your taste
in music is different?
Got to go.
Thanks for listening.
lt's good, dear.
Having fun today.
Shall l make it?
Who will eat then?
Shut up. Kartik can cook.
lf he messes up, only
you will eat it.
He will cook good.
Kartik can do anything.
Don't get me into trouble.
Just chill.
Hi. Hey.
Please come and join
us for the party.
l think l am okay.
l thought you wanted
to be surrounded..
..by the vitality of the city.
Could talent live
at home and thrive.
Why should the Badakhshan
ruby wander worldwide?
Albeit in Deccan, Zauq, the
Muse commands respect.
Who would quit the lanes
of Delhi and suffer exile?
Wow! Wow! Wow!
There should be a dictator in
our country too. Like Hitler.
He killed more
than 60000 people.
l mean, a better version.
Rahul Gandhi is so
cute, isn't he?
Freud was just too
obsessed with sex.
But isn't it true?
Don't we all have the
Oedipus complex?
Gross.
l hate green vegetables.
l know a lot of publishers. l
can introduce you to them.
That will be nice.Thank you.
Yeah.
90% is nothing these days.
You won't even be allowed
to enter good colleges.
You need at least 94%.
lf you don't get it, you
should commit suicide?
Are you mad?
Truth or dare?
Truth.
When your first book was a
flop, how did you feel?
Great!
Greatest day of my life.
Yeah. And you thanked your parents
and your teachers. Right?
Dare.
Do a hot dance.
Wow!
Come on.
Nice.
Yeah.
Dare.
Okay.
Do striptease.
Tanu. Aunt, it's just a game.
Or else you do it, aunt.
Okay, guys. l also want to..
See you. So soon? Got to go.
What happened? Dad?
Yeah.
His dad is very strict.
He is lucky.
l had to reach home
before 8 o'clock.
Seriously. l hated
my dad for it.
But l don't hate him.
Goodnight. Goodnight.
Your PG is hot.
He seems intelligent too. He
is trying to flirt a lot too.
Maybe he is your perfect guy?
He is uncle.
Goodnight. Goodnight.
lndoPaktalks in
Kashmir fail again.
Both nations blame each other.
Obama describes Manmohan Singh
as a wise, wonderful man.
Mob fury kills 3 Dalits.
Latest sex survey reveals that
most lndian married men..
..have sex thrice a week.
Damn!
Here.
Nowadays we can't even let our
children read the newspaper.
Witch.
l hate her.
What do they think
of themselves?
Awesome!
Ask Anu whether she will
do this kind of modeling.
She won't even charge for
this kind of modeling.
Come here.
You don't talk to us.
You always cling to Tanisha.
Do one thing. lnvite
her for the party.
l will pay. But l
will have fun too.
Me too. Me too.
You just dance and
make her ready for me.
Why do you fight when you
don't have the strength?
lt's okay. Chill.
They are just idiots.
Shall we do one thing? What?
Shall we bunk? When?
''lt's you. lt's only you.''
''lt's only you.''
''You are with me.''
''You are my God.''
''Eco, algebra,
inflation, literature.''
''Questions, problems.''
''This boring labor.''
''This spitting and bunking.''
''lt's all fun.''
''lt's only you.''
''You are with me.''
''So everything is good.''
That was fun, man. Let's
do it every week.
We can do it daily too.
We don't have any
other work to do.
Will you eat? What?
Chocolate bar.
l don't have money, dear.
lt got over.
Why do you irritate
me time and again?
l asked for icecream,
not for money.
Sorry. Chill.
Give me two chocolate bars.
Thanks.
What happened?
What? No. Nothing. So
why aren't you eating?
lsn't it good?
How can chocolate
bar not be good?
Tanisha, l want to talk to you.
Yes?
The other day l was asking
you on the phone. What?
'Jaane Tu'film.
lt was okay. But lmran was cute.
Tanisha, wait a minute.
Tell me.
Look,what l was saying is that
you and l are also good friends.
So...
so...can we..
l mean..
Tanisha, actually, l
wanted to tell you that..
l love you. l love you too.
Not friendly l love you.
l am talking about
real l love you.
Man,this is the
problem with boys.
Why do you always think
in the same direction?
Look, we are best friends. Okay?
And l love you. l
really love you a lot.
But l can't think of
you in that sense.
Hope you understand. Okay?
And please stop watching
romantic movies.
Watch good movies.
Tanish, l am sorry. Shut up.
You don't need to say sorry.
Okay?
lt's okay. lt happens.
We are still bestf riends.
Right?
See you in school tomorrow. Bye.
How was the date?
He proposed to me.
Finally! l told you so.
Shut up. So are you
guys going around now?
Are you crazy? l refused.
The guy you don't love is always
the one who proposes you.
Hey!
What are you doing here?
You have come on top
to relieve yourself?
Will you drench Delhi?
Come.
What is this?
Your father is asking
you, what is this?
Since when have you
been studying this?
Since when?
ls this what you are studying?
Let it be.
l.. Go out. Go out.
Come on.
Since when is this going on?
What is this? Say something.
Yes, Anu. What?
What happened? Ashwin
killed his dad. What?
The boy has guts. Hats off.
That's true.
Where is Tanisha? Don't know.
l guess she went that way.
What happened? What has he done?
Don't know. He just disappeared.
He is nowhere to be found.
He did all this because of me.
l could see it in his eyes. He
was completely broken hearted.
l even tried his
phone last night.
But nobody picked up.
He loved me.And l ruined him.
How can anyone kill his own dad?
A father is a father after all.
Maybe his father deserved it.
Shut up. Whatever.
He has sired him.
You read so many times.
Father rapes his daughter.
l don't believe it. How can
anyone do so to his family?
They do.
One of my cousins. He
tried it on me. Who?
Forget it. l still
consider him my brother.
Will you guys please shut up?
Hello.
l got a call from your number.
To which place does
this number belong to?
Okay.
Who was it?
Aunt, l got a missed call from
New Delhi railway station.
We are going there. Okay.
Take care. I'll take them.
I'll take them.
So tell me,Tanisha.
Do you love him?
lwish l did.
Maybe, he hasn't
committed the murder.
So why is he on the run?
The police must be
implicating him.
Yes, it is so common. l
know he has done it.
You just need an
excuse to feel guilty.
Stop acting like the most
important girl in the world.
That is me.
Karthik says so.
Will you ever grow up?
Ashwin grew up overnight.
All of us have grown up.
Except Nidhi.
Hello. l am very mature.
Really? You tell me. Has
she said anything mature..
..in all this while?
As if you people have.
'The second over. He put a
towel in his trousers.'
He wasin your class, right?
Did you know him?
Of course, he was in my class.
l mean was he your friend.
He was.
Did he fight in school as well?
Did he ever threaten you?
His dad used to beat
him all the time.
He would harass
So he used to beat him
for his own good, right?
Now that doesn't mean you
kill your own father.
lndia has become America now.
l mean you can't tell
anything to your kids either.
Mom, you harass sister a lot.
Go. Go and study.
'Ravi Shankar Jha'swife Nirja Jha
has confessed to her crime..'
'..in Ravi Shankar murder case.'
But the police thinks that she
is doing so to save her son..
..Ashwin Jha.
Ashwin Jha has been missing
the night of the murder.
The jacket seems nice.
lt will look better on us.
Come on.Take it off.
Whom have you murdered?
'l am standing here in
Ashwin Jha's neighbourhood.'
'Here criminals are active.'
'When an ordinaryman steals
the brain of a sharp person?'
Ashwin Jha. Where
did you find him?
Pandey,get some tea.
Brother, you are all
over the television.
'According to the feed just received,
a 60 year elderly man's...'
Sit.
'Dead body has been found.'
'This news is shocking.' Sit.
We are creating a gang. Join us.
We'll share what we earn.
Partnership.
Yes.
Brother,this address...
Hey. Stop.
My cell phone.
Move it. Move it.
Stop. Stop. Someone catch him.
l have got a phone for you.
Thank you.
Nice, isn't it? lt's superb.
Mr.Jha.
This is Mr.Jha. My friend.
Hello.
Hi.
Shall l introduce himto Seema?
She's Babita's friend.
She's looking for a
boyfriend from a big city.
lf you say, shall
l speak to her?
Why? Do you have
a girl in Delhi?
Look, l took your picture. When
you were going to the market...
l did it. l am looking good.
You're beautiful. Yes.
l told you.
Love you, Aakash. Love you too.
All because of you.
Guys, don't take me forcibly.
You've got guys. Okay?
And l have no one. l had Ashwin.
Please, buddy. We are
going after so many days.
Let's celebrate. Have called
someone for you as well.
He's hot. l don't like
these hunk sand all.
Aman should have some brains.
So you should've called your uncle.
Shut up.
ls Aakash coming?
Aakash was busy.
Shrey is coming. Who is Shrey?
Just another guy. Someone
l met on facebook.
Hi, Anu. How cheap can one get?
You came and flirted
with me, right?
And said that l was so cute.
l have got my glasses corrected.
''We've lost ourselves
in all the madness.''
''Our brainshave gone numb.''
''We've lost ourselves
in all the madness.''
''Our brainshave gone numb.''
''We have gone numb
and are sloshed.''
''We are high. We are high.''
''Pressure. Pressure. This is
the pressure of addiction.''
''Get me some addiction.
l crave it.''
''l crave it. l crave it.''
''Let me lose myself. Let me lose myself.
ln your eyes.''
''Do whatever you want with me.
l am ready.''
''We are high. We are high.''
Should ltell mom?
She'll be hurt.
Your dad is hot.
Shut up,Tans.
Shall l drive? No. We
want to reach home.
Come on. Let me drive.
We had so much fun in
the party, isn't it?
But Aman was really bad.Yuck.
Are you listening?
Can you walk to your room
or should we drop you?
l can go on my own. Okay.
Ouch. l can see that.
Go on,guys. l am fine. Okay.
Good night. Bye. Bye.
Darn it. Why are you
clinging on to me?
Leave me.
Move your step.
Sorry.
l am sloshed. That's okay.
Move your feet.
Step out.
l have an idea for you.
lt'll make you rich and famous.
What? Write a book on me.
l think we should go in. No. No.
Don't come near me.
l am cursed.
No.You are beautiful.
Am l?
Okay.
Come on. Come on, let's sit.
Sit.
Scared of me?
You scared of me?
No. Why?
Because l know that you like
watching me from your room.
Now you're scared.
Scared, aren't you?
Don't worry.
l won't tell aunt.
You're a nice guy.
l like you.
Here. lt'saunt.
Hello, aunt.
l am outside waiting for you.
Tanu.
Tanu, you are here, dear.
l was worried.
Come on.
You alright?
Thank you.
Are you alright? Yes.
Anu.
Mom, l want to discuss
something important with you.
l know. lt's about your dad.
He had called up. Take it easy.
You're a grown up now.
We'll talk in the morning. Don't worry.
We'll talk about it.
Okay?
Hello. Hello, brother.
Hey, it must be
late in the night.
What time is it there?
lt's 2 o'clock.
So tell me. What's happening?
Nothing. Just missing you.
l miss you too. Are
mom, dad around?
No.They are out.
So are studying or
just having fun?
Having fun. l knew it.
So how are your
boytriends doing?
Who are you torturing these days?
No one.
Okay, listen. l got to go.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay. Take care. Bye. Bye.
Come in. Keep it there.
Oh. lt's you.
l thought it was the maid.
That's okay.
Well, l came to say
sorry for last night.
That's perfectly okay. Sit.
Want tea?
l just had. Are you sure?
Thanks.
So you had a great
time last night.
Yes, it's Anu's first big
modelling assignment.
So she wanted to celebrate.
I'msorry if l said something.
You did say something.
l am joking.
What are your plans for the day?
No plans. Sleep and study.
Sleep and study?
Great plan. Will
you come with me?
Where?
Bali Marang. Where is that?
Today Ramesh Chabbra has
his painting exhibition.
At Habibat center.
He has also invited me
for the party tonight.
I'll not be able to
make it tonight.
l have an investors meet.
By the way, Rashmi
called up yesterday.
How is she? Oh, she
is doing great.
ln fact, she's thinking of
settling down in Toronto only.
With Narain. Great.
Sorry. Just to draw
your attention.
Will anyone tell me? What's
happening in our house?
This is no way to talk.
This is not the way, dear.
Why the hell are you
guys acting like that..
..as if nothing has happened?
Dear. Listen to me.
Dear, your dad told
me about last night.
What did he tell you?
That he was with Saloni.
Mom, they were kissing.
Look dear. Listen to
me very calmly now.
You know Akhil uncle?
Your friend. Why?
He is not just my friend.
We are in a relationship.
See,your dad and l had
an open marriage..
..ever since you
were very young.
But we cared for you.
We never wanted to
hurt you, dear.
Just try and understand.
Don't take us wrong.
Anu.
Listen. Anu.
Dear, are you alright?
Dear, please.
This is Ballimaran.
And that used to be our house.
Had l been born 150 years ago..
..Galib would have
been my neighbor.
Really. Really?
l will show you.
That's my school.
Oh! Come.
l used to come here everyday
from Ballimaran on a cycle.
And she would come on foot.
A girl?
Roshni.
She was a year elder to me.
And l would follow her
on my cycle everyday.
Why? She wouldn't give
you any importance?
She would. She also
wanted me to talk to her.
l see.And then?
You know when first
time we fall in love..
..l was so happy.
With great difficulty l fixed
a date through her friend.
We had to meet the next day.
But she didn't come.
Why?
Let it be. Why do you want to know?
Let's go.
Tell me.
lt's getting exciting.
She never came. Why?
Her dead body was
found after 3 days.
She was gangraped
and then killed.
Oh!
l am so sorry,Vikram.
Delhi is not a city for women.
Hey!
Did you like my story?
Total Bollywood stuff.
Should l try it in Mumbai?
You were telling me a story?
Of course.
And you started crying.
Delhi is not a city for women.
l am so sorry,Vikram.
Shut up. Okay?
What?
The first time l came
here, dad was with me.
l cried a lot at the
light and sound show.
l was not even one year old.
That's what aunt told me.
After that, dad passed away.
So..
Dipti told me...
about that accident.
lt was entirely my fault.
My luck is such.
My first birthday.
And a day prior to it
this accident took place.
ls it because of that accident..
..that you think you are cursed?
Last night you told me.
Oh!
Maybe l was too drunk.
lt's okay.
l don't know why..
..l feel as if someone
is staring at me.
And whenever something
good is going to happen..
..he ruins it.
l know.
lt happens.
You feel as if nothing is
ever going to go right.
But don't blame yourself for it.
Life has its different
ways of screwing us up.
Not just you, he is
staring at all of us.
What happened? How did
you come so early today?
Just like that.
l was getting bored at home.
Don't cry.
l feel so lonely at times.
There is no one l can talk to.
Come on. We are best friends.
You can always talk to me.
Come on. Wipe your face. The
dance class is going to begin.
Sir must be waiting for you.
Screw him. He would love that.
No. l am not in the mood.
So?
Then mom said they are
having an open marriage.
What?
l was also shocked.
l am very angry with them.
l was so proud of them.
Since childhood you have
an image of your parents.
They must take care of it.
Because when that image
breaks, it feels very bad.
lt hurts.
You lose your respect for them.
You actually begin to hate them.
You are right.
My dad is super cool.
And l will never let him down.
But my mom...Gosh! She
is so embarrassing.
Thank God forgiving
you a good father.
Otherwise nowadays you don't
get to see good fathers.
But you also sleep
around, right?
My doing it is okay. l am young.
They are parents, dear.
They were supposed
to be in love.
Maybe they are.
Vikram. Yes.
Tell me something.
Why did you bring me with you?
l enjoy your company.
ls that the only reason?
What do you feel?
You elders are such hypocrites.
You think we don't
know anything.
We are kids, right?
lt's high time. Okay?
Stop treating us
like small kids.
l am not a kid. And you
know that very well.
What are you talking about?
Tanisha.A little girl
in this big bad world.
A young leaf that will
hit a big storm one day.
Some day soon.
l have read everything
on your laptop.
You watch me from your room.
And you write all that about me.
Why?
Say something.
l see Roshni in you.
That story l told
you...it's not a story.
lt was all true.
That day when l saw
you the first time..
..l felt l am seeing Roshni.
Just one look at you
and l decided to stay.
l don't know what
the similarity is.
You don't look like her.
But there is...
...there is something..
..that is common between
the both of you.
You remind me of her.
l wanted to be around you. l
wanted to see you everyday.
l wanted to talk to you.
l know this is
sounding a bit weird.
But...
...l couldn't stop myself.
Some people say that
there is nothing..
..like a coincidence
in this world.
You reminded me so strongly
of her that l wanted to know.
ls there something more to this?
ls there a deeper meaning?
A deeper connection?
Will this coincidence
mean anything?
l don't know if..
lt will.
''Let me walk with
you like that.''
''Let's make the
moments radiant.''
''Let it be vague.''
''Let it be hazy.''
''Let my dreams
be without you.''
''Let my heart do
as it pleases.''
''On the path of friendship.''
''Let's walk as two
individuals.''
''Blithe. We are carefree.''
''Let's hold our
dreams tightly.''
''We started living in love.''
''And distance started
disappearing.''
''We started
becoming carefree.''
''And hopes started soaring.''
How old are you? Why?
To decide that you are
not a pedophiliac.
What? Do l look like one?
Nowadays people are
not trustworthy.
People have multiple
personalities.
Okay. Let me guess.
3536?
32. Exactly double my age.
How many women have
you slept with?
What?
lf you don't want to tell me, it's okay.
l won't force you.
l love MJ.
Was he a pedophiliac?
God rest his soul.
lwas wondering since many days.
You didn't tell us.
Did you like it?
What?
Did you like killing
your father?
You see, l have never
murdered anyone.
You must have smashed his head.
lt must have made a noise.
You must have enjoyed it.
He killed his father.
He must have felt bad.
He must have had a reason.
Must have fulfilled
all his desires.
You took it too seriously.
Come on, sweetheart. See
you tomorrow in school.
l am scared. What happened?
l haven't got my period
since two months. Damn.
You didn't use protection?
Katrik said he has
good selfcontrol.
True.True.
Where are we going?
To the chemist.
To get a selftest kit.
l want to go home.
Nidhi, are you mad?
lf something is wrong, let's
take corrective measures. Okay?
lt won't be. l am sure.
At times it happens because
of stress too, right?
lt won't be. But
still, let's test it.
No. l don't want to do it.
l am okay.
l am going. Bye.
Why not? Anu, why are
you insisting so much?
Nidhi, just shut up.
How much? Rs.60.
So...who is the daddy?
Not you. Obviously.
One moment.
Anu.Anu.
What?
You did not tell me
why you dumped me.
Rishi, lwanted to be polite.
Butsince you insist, l dumped
you because you are small.
And l am not talking
about you rheight.
Witch.
Why do you guys worry? l
told you l will handle it.
You are talking as if you have
got it done 10 times before.
l will ask Vikram.
Don't be crazy. Men don't know
anything about these things.
Chill, guys. l said l
will take care of it.
That's it.
And...temperature set.
Have you been cooking
since childhood?
Are you crazy?
l had to learn it when
l went to London.
At home mom wouldn't even
let me enter the kitchen.
One moment. l hope
you like this.
By the way, does Tanisha
like Continental?
Vikram, it's really
nice to have you here.
Since your arrival
things seem stable.
Tanisha also likes you a lot.
She doesn't say it. But
she misses her father.
Don't bake it for more
than 30 minutes. Yes.
And...l will just come.
l have to make an important
phone call. Yes.
My friend's girlfriend also
got it done from here.
This doctor is very nice.
Guys, don't worry.
She will be alright.
You look more worried than us.
Your patient has developed
some complications.
Shift her to a bigger hospital.
No need to be afraid.
At times there are
complications in such cases.
Rs.10000 advance.
Here.
Patient's parents?
How is she?
You will have to sign
as her guardian. Okay.
She is my niece.
We will have to
tell her parents.
They will keep her in the
hospital for at least2 days.
Are you mad? No ways.
Do doctors discharge
someone so quickly?
They also have to make money.
She has informed
them for one day.
After that we need
a valid excuse.
lt's entirely your fault.
Now you think.
l will think. First let me think
what to say to my family.
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
Often silence says such a lot.
Let me say just one thing
and then I'll go silent.
l feel so secure when
you are with me.
l am really lucky.
You're my perfect guide.
Perfection does not exist.
Hi, aunt. What's up? Nothing.
What are you reading?
Vikram's first book.
ln the middle of the end.
lt's a nice book.
l have read it.
When did you read it?
Vikram had given me.
Why do you call him Vikram?
Don't you have manners?
He is so much elder than you.
He has told me.
Okay, listen.
How do you find Vikram?
Aunt, l am not of
marriageable age now.
l am not talking about you.
Are you serious?
Did you speak to him?
No. l will now.
l don't know, aunt.
l never saw him in that light.
Tanu.
Tanu, what happened?
Why are you crying?
Silly. l am not leaving you.
Tanu.
l think l just need time
to get used to the idea.
Tanu,
am l looking nervous? Why?
l am going to tell Vikram. Now?
I'll wait here.
Alright.
Wish me luck.
All the best. Thank you.
Yes.
Oh.
Hi. Hi.
l need to talk to you.
Sure. Come in.
See, Vikram. I'll be
straight with you.
l really like you.
Both of us are lonely.
We both deserve love.
And we are both
nice people, right?
So let us give it a chance.
Dipti, l need to think about it.
Yes. Of course. Of course.
Okay. See you.
Okay.
Good night.
What did he say?
He'll think about it. But
I'msure he'll say yes.
l hope so too, aunt.
Good night. Good night.
The family has left.
The old man is alone.
Let's attack.
I've arranged the gun.
You'll get it.
You're the only one experienced.
lf the old man wakes up,
shoot him in the skull.
l don't know to use a gun.
Pull the trigger from two feet.
Simple.
So why don't you do it?
But you are the
master of murder.
Aunt will get more suspicious
if you talk like a patient.
You are happy. Mind
you,you are in school.
Guys,you are making
me more nervous.
Okay, fine. Talk to her.
Hello.
Yes, mom.
l am fine.
l have to go for community
service after school.
I'll stay at Anu's house
if it gets late atnight.
I'll try, mom.
Yes, Vikram. But don't
worry if l don'tcome.
Anu has extra dress.
Hello.
What?
Oh no.
l know that Rishi has done this.
Okay.
Dad is coming tonight.
Vikram is leaving tomorrow.
What happened?
l have to go.
Sit.
Don't show attitude. Sit.
Dad, please don't irritate.
l am in a bad mood anyways.
Anu, this is not the way to talk.
Talk properly.
Come on. We have
to go to school.
l won't go.
But how could you do this?
You can do what you want.
You should've guided me.
You're elder.
Have you ever sought
our guidance?
We have done so much for you.
Education. Facilities.
And we were as friendly
with you as we could be.
Friends share secrets, mom.
Oh. So now you have
become so mature..
..that we need to share
our secrets with you.
l am not coming.
Mrs. Kalsi, we did a mistake.
You know how kids
are these days.
lf it had been any other
girl other than Anu..
..would you have let her
remain in the school?
She sets a bad example.
Ma'am, it wasn't my fault.
Whose fault was it?
ls this the age to
be doing all this?
Sorry, ma'am. l am sorry.
But you can not remain in
this school any longer.
But ma'am, we have always
paid your fees on time.
Shut up, Anu.
lf you want some more
donation, l can pay you.
lt's not the question
of donations.
Our reputation is at stake.
All l can do for you is give her
a good character certificate.
Well, in that case, thank
you so much, Mrs. Kalsi.
We had never imagined
that our family will..
..suffer ignominy
because of you.
Mom,you are more worried about
your reputation than me.
Reputation is at stake. Your life.
And your career.
And if this gets out, it can
ruin everything. l tell you.
Nothing's going to happen. So
many MMS are floating around.
And anyway,the
profession l am in.
Any publicity is good publicity.
Did you leak it?
l didn' task him to leak it.
Wait a minute.
Give me your purse. What
are you going to do?
l said give me your purse.
Give me the purse.
We have misused the
freedom we gave you.
Now you'll not step out of the
house till this matter dies down.
Hey Anu, nice job.
You've become a star.
Nidhi, I'msorry.
lt's okay.
Hello, aunt. Hello.
You know where Nidhi
is, don'tyou?
Hello, aunt. Please leave.
I'll look after her.
Sorry, aunt.
Are you alright?
Don't worry. Everything
will be alright.
Dad is going to come here
straight from the airport.
When are you going?
Tomorrow.
Have you told aunt?
l have realised in life
coincidences don't mean anything.
lt's your destiny that matters.
Maybe you are right.
l still haven't understood...
...as to why mom and
dad have to die.
Why did Ashwin kill his dad?
Why did Sameer break my heart?
Why aunt has to love you?
And the curse continues.
Maybe that's my destiny.
Come on. Quick. Come on.
Come on.
Go.
Shoot him.
Come on. Shoot him.
You guys are making a mistake.
Kill him.
Shoot the old man. Shoot.
Nidhi, your dad is here.
l want to sleep with you.
Mom, l don't want to meet dad.
These kids come
with a lot of hope.
And they know a lot.
Theyknow what's
happeningin the world.
They know about technology.
They think they know
how the world works.
And how they can manipulate it.
Hello. Hello, brother.
What are you doing?
Suicide.
Okay. Let's do it together.
Whatsay?
Why? Why would you?
Since l am so far
away from all ofyou.
l can do this at least.
By the way, l am
coming on Sunday.
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
But the problem is that the
world is a master manipulator.
And it is much harder to
understand the world's formula..
..than any maths, physicsor
chemistry for mula.
But this generation which
has grown up on fast food..
..want everything fast.
They are not ready to wait.
l want to sleep with you.
And the world doesn't
know it yet.
But it's changing.
And it's these kids that
are changing the world..
..without really knowing it.
Mom, l don't want to meet dad.
l don't want to meet him.
Please. Don't let him in.
I'll meet him later. Please.
How are you?
l am sorry, dad.
Did l say anything to you?
l am very sorry.
Stop crying.
Quiet.
l said stop crying.
You were crying even
when l had left.
And you are crying even
when l have returned.
lt is not easyto
understand these kids.
And you don't find the sensibility
needed to understand..
..them at any mall.
And nor can it be downloaded
from any website.
This is the biggest problem.
Shoot the old man.
Shoot him.
Come on. Come on.
ls this the age to
be doing all this?
My son is an lAS officer.
Sixteen is a tough place to be.
Hormones, dreams,
parents, police.
l wouldn't want to go
through them again.
lt's an exciting age.
And they are living
in exciting times.
Guys, l really
enjoythe study trips.
We go to a place near Bengaluru.
l am going to Lakshwadeep
for the summer holidays.
To learn scuba diving. Wow.
l just want to drop
out of this school.
l don't like girl's school.
No cute boys.
Well, you go for these trips.
Do you just study?
Buddy, l have applied or Miss.
lndia.
Let's see. Your MMS will
get even more hits.
Did you tell mom and dad?
They are being very supportive.
l really love them.
Goal.
''We don't care.
We don't judge.''
''We just want to live like
it's the end oft he world.''
''Young and free at sixteen.''
''Drinks, fights, girls, lights.
That's what life's like.''
''Sixteen.''
''Sixteen. Hats off
to sweet sixteen.''
''Lots of issues before time.''
''lnnocent minds have
been corrupted.''
''What life wants to give you,
take it away before hand.''
''Do everything
that is useless.''
''Hats off to sweet sixteen.''
''Hats off to darn sixteen.''
''This is an
addiction.To get high.''
''Just sixteen. But
yet is fire.''
''As if he is 100. Make
a name for yourself.''
''Hats off to sweet sixteen.''
''Hats off to darn sixteen.''
''Sixteen.''