OpenSubtitles.org require your login in mx player
for uploading subtitles, please login now
Too many pretty boys
were assaulted...
There's been curfew,
the government has ordered..
"not to come out of your houses.
I repeat.
Be careful.. be careful
- There's been curfew..
..ordered from the government.
Don't come out of your houses.
Slowly, Ok
- There's been curfew..
This pain had started three hours
before and you're telling me now
I thought I will be able to control
the pain till the curfew is over
Honey, this is delivery pain
No woman can control this pain
What do I know about this pain?
Be careful
First this curfew and
on top of it this weather
No one is going to help us today
We will get some vehicle
from the square.. Be careful
I can't anymore.. I can't.
Tidim square is right here
Thank god the rain has stopped
Honey..
Are you ok honey?
Slowly.. slowly
Sit down.. sit down.. sit here for
2 minutes while I figure something out
No, no I will come with you.
- Sit down..
lam right here honey.
- No I will come with you
lam right here Thoi.. with you..
just 2 minutes" sit down please
Oh Mother!
Freeze.. freeze.. who is there?
Hands up
Sir.. sir.. sir
Sir what are you doing?
You bloody rebels..
you wreak havoc whenever you feel like
lam not a rebel sir
Please have a look there
Don't raise your voice
My wife is pregnant sir.
We need to get to the hospital. Please
Bizhou Go check. Go
Go and see there. Don't move.
- Please Sir. help us
Honey
Hey! Whose daughter is this?
Take her away from here
Sir, he is telling the truth
A plane has crashed and
there is fire everywhere
and you let
Chungneizang go there?
And you?
What are you hiding behind?
Show it
You picked this up from there?
This is no girl's toy
Tonpa, help is needed
at the crash site
Yes yes.. I will be right there
Go to bed now and don't
you dare to get out of the house
Come on go to sleep
Mad girl
How did you hit her?
You like to fight with boy
Let her go Mangi
Move back..
Leave my hair..
Why did you beat her?
She is my girlfriend
- Answer me.
I can do whatever the hell
I want with her. What is it to you?
Leave me..
What is this ruckus here?
Go away from here!
- Coward!
I'm leaving you for the last time
- Where are you running, coward?
lam not running..
I'm having mercy on you.
OpenSubtitles.org require your login in mx player
for uploading subtitles, please login now