.: Team Telly :.
Do it properly man
what are you doing?
that much romance but not with wife
all is well that ends well
Mom, jewelry selection
I'm rehearsing I'm performing in
the evening
who do I ask then?
Cocktail one
Hurry up, take it.
you must come.
Send someone to get it.
what's the difference
What are you doing?
Dadi I'm going for mehndi
go child
you're rehearsing on cocktail song.
I want to learn too
you do whatever you want
on honeymoon
if you are opening beers then
send two here.
I don't even believe it. I'm getting married
I'm nervous
it feels like a dream
Don't know where is sonal? even
mehndi has started
She should dance here, we danced at
her mehndi
I think papa returned from shop
they were all saying that papa has
decorated the shop like a bride
Mom was saying that she'll wear Saree
but she didn't change
I've given my mobile to Chintu
he should take photos.
I want to upload photos on Facebook
Since Vijay returned from London
he looks handsome
he looked very nice
my first night. day after tomorrow
I'm scared
Come
will you have something?
no
where are you going one day
before the wedding
you called me so many times
you know how hard was it to come
everyone was asking.
It's not good for bride and groom
to meet before
I saw the tent guy when I was coming
Written Rani weds Vijay
looks beautiful in round shape
Rani, I can't marry you.
You're kidding.
I wish.
What happened? you got nervous.
No
It'll be tough for you
why?
what changed?
Nothing has changed. I'm the saying.
that's what. you're still the same
Rani, I've changed
but Vijay.
I'm doing this for you. it'll be tough
wedding is tomorrow.
what do I do now?
What do I tell my parents.
have you told your parents
yes.
what did they say
they understood
Rani this is right for us
it happens
I think you've found someone else.
no it's not like that
Vijay.
I'm being practical
listen you'll find someone your type
in Rijoli
he'll keep you happy.
you're so nice
and we'll be friends
we'll be in touch
talk to my parents.
not to me
Didi what happened?
what did he say?
Why are you crying?
Didi why are you crying?
Vijay don't end it. I'll do whatever
you want
If I tell my father he'll get a
heart attack
nothing will happen
I beg you
marry me. who will marry me now
they've made all the preparations
in my family
once we get married everything
will be fine
once we get married
how will I go home?
people are watching. what are you doing
You're not understanding
wedding is day after tomorrow
Rani
open the door
rani open the door
rani I will talk
rani papa is saying he will talk
open the door
brother give us a kilo sweets
take the whole shop
our daughter rani.
she's grown up
she's really sweet.
Father has his own sweets shop his
daughter must be sweet
Vijay come here
We've had very close relation with
their family
before marriage our evening tea
and samosas were together
you made this sweet
I make very good sweet
can I taste
very sweet
can you make barfi?
I can make Maggie
this a combination sweet.
ladoo...
and mix it with khoya
your father was saying you're
doing home science
from where?
HS polytechnic first year
from there you'll get mudrika
it goes straight to our college
its near by
my college is also there.
I'm doing engineering
my papa is right
do you watch movies?
Hey home science.
what are you doing here?
Are you making cake? no Chinese.
Chinese cake?
You know they sell really amazing
samosas outside your college
and potato quantity is very...
you must've had them.
are you a halwai taking interest in samosa?
Not in samosa
I'm taking interest in halwai
he's the son of our uncle dhingra
family friend
you're seeing him
you didn't tell me
no. I swear.
I don't even like him
he looks like shahrukh
he looks nice.
Let's go
I don't want to eat here
I've decided, I won't call you rani.
then what?
My Queen
10 actors have tried in ten movies.
what? talking to you?
No. this library method.
It has worked every time
I'm working right now.
and after that?
Hey queen
Chinese
soup
queen soup
man chow
man chow.
say yes
sweet corn.
You're very sweet
it's not hot right
can I tell a joke.
Chintu tells best jokes
there was an ant and it was white
mother asked why are you so white
it said I put fair and lovely and drink
and dance.
He goes everywhere with you.
no. whenever my parents send him
will he come in dowry too
Didi
tent guy is calling
I know it's last minute
yeah charge for cancelation
you go get some rest. no.
I'm here
sonal is calling
I can talk to her later
it's not important.
Didi, he's saying I love you to you
Rani I had a boyfriend fayzal.
He stayed in Pakistan.
he was cute
then I found your grandfather
in refugee camp
we had to share one tent
in the dark
he was looking very handsome
where do you find someone
who knows
you don't worry about anything
right now
just live your life
you get in life what you're suppose
to get. nothing can change that
today you're thinking that your life
is over
tomorrow everything will alright again
day after tomorrow you'll come and tell
me, Dadi whatever happened was good.
Quiet now.
I will miss you
won't I miss you.
It's just London. I'll call you daily
listen. get tattoo of my name
why?
even saif got one for kareena
you should get one then
I already have one for you on
my heart
my hearts queen
open the door
I've brought tea for you.
you haven't eaten since morning
eat something child
how can this go on
open the door
hey honeymoon queen open the
door. its open sonal
where are you? I've been looking
for you. where's my passport ticket
I couldn't get the passport
you gave me a heart attack
here's your passport and ticket
and go to your honeymoon
I'm more excited than you
finally you'll lose your virginity
Mom will hear you
you closed the account
where are you running off to
I have a dream of going honeymoon
of the country since I was 17
goa. no
foreign country
Paris is my favorite
and his Amsterdam
Amsterdam.
where is it?
It's by train from Paris.
Madam you're going to Paris
Let it go Chintu
close my account
I want to go on my honeymoon
you want to go
yes
is it important
but if you say no then I won't go
take Chintu with you
talk to us on computer daily
and meet Varma aunty
okay
myself rani.
I have a room here
Okay
be in good mood
Didi is coming
how are you?
everything okay there
mom I can't see you
sit down
now okay
you got here fine.
didn't have any problem in travel right?
How did you get to the hotel
how's the cold there.
yeah it is a bit cold here
if it's cold there...
you're not even wearing your sweater
mom, it's not cold inside
but take care of yourself
you catch cold quickly
Mom
did Vijay call?
No Vijay didn't call
did you meet Vijay's parents
don't worry.
everything will be alright
just go see Paris and come back soon
I have a headache I'm going to
bed
okay, my phone will be on
keep in touch
who's there?
Who's there?
No, I thought he hurt you
I don't speak French
passport visa
my hotel is near by
my passport is there
I have the key
I'm from Rijoli India
Namaste
you know Hindi
I am mix.
French Spanish
my mom French Spanish
papa Hindi
your father is Indian
Mom went to go papa boom boom
and I came
nice to meet you
you can call me VJ
my self rani
Rani
Queen.
okay queen
what are you doing here
very cute kid.
whose?
He's my life
Ricky
Your kid?
yes
you've maintained your figure very well
come lets go
hello Dadi.
what are you doing there?
Watching TV
if wanted to watch TV then why
did you go this far?
Go out I've heard it's the most
beautiful city of the world
and who knows you may find
a white guy over there
India gate is the best in the world
Eiffel tower in Paris is
Eiffel tower
I will take you there on honeymoon
we'll eat on the top of Eiffel tower
they serve food there
and a lot more
Chinese food
I want to go back to India
thief
my Passport
Rain
there's rain in India also
I'm from India
Rijoli, I came on my honeymoon
alone
I knew that I'm better looking
I'm better looking than Vijay
I didn't say that
everyone told me that I'm better
looking
my friend sonal used to call him
conductor
my life is ruined
come
alcohol
I obeyed my parents
I obeyed my teachers
I never cheated in exam
never lied
I listened to everyone.
I think Vijay had sex in London
SEX
convent girls in front our school used
to wear skirts so short
they folded it.
I never did such things
never flirted with boys
get right Vijay Lakshmi
you and your fun.
you'll be caught someday
look he left me alone
I'm doing everything alone
I'm crossing road alone.
seeing Eiffel tower alone
fighting thugs alone.
I didn't let go off my bag
I taught him a lesson
he will never mess with someone
from Delhi
my condition is like Gupta uncle
Gupta uncle got cancer
he never drank alcohol
never smoked
still got cancer
better if he had smoked and drink
Hindi song
VJ Hindi song is playing
Bollywood
Hindi song
Vijay.
what Vijay? have you lost your mind?
What are you doing here? dancing.
people were looking at you
at least think about my reputation
mom isn't here. if she were...
all girls were dancing.
am I marrying all of them
Sorry
one saying in English
my friend taught me. why fart and
waste it when you burp and taste it
you taste burp
back home we're not allowed to burp
girls not at all
girls aren't even allowed to burp
I told you. we must talk at fix time
rani. hi.
who is she?
I'm VJ Lakshmi
nice you to meet you.
Daddy?
Don't call me that.
call me Ashwin
Ashu for you
go Chintu go do your homework
what are you doing?
go do your work. what work?
What was I doing?
go inside
SOON
adult film is going on here
enjoy
what did I do last night
who told daddy?
Rani, your nature is very jolly
Ricky's dad.
he left for office?
Husband
child without marriage
is this common in Paris?
Sometimes
VJ, there's nothing in it
it's very hippy
it's not my style
VJ
Rani
are you serious
not good?
VJ how is it?
I like the jacket but...
VJ this doesn't look good on me
VJ return my clothes
Santa Banta are Indian
do you visit India?
Goa?
I like Banaras.
We also went to Banaras on
family holiday
it was fun
I even have photos
Banaras. they have the best Hash
why is it dark there?
Power gone. Delhi electricity.
this computer is running of inverter
when are you going to see
Varma aunty
you're taking her with you
she's a nice girl
where is she?
I can't see her
I'm saying Namaste. it's tradition.
I'm saying Namaste. it's tradition
it's sad.
Dolly, Rani is here.
Who Rani? our Rani
Mr. Mehra's daughter
right
child, what happened to my child
this is my friend VJ she's from
Paris
not to worry
sit
what will you have.
just water
just water.
Rani is here.
who rani
Mama's daughter.
our rani
how was my French.
listen
100 euro.
what are you saying.
11 is enough
it's 750 in India anyway
okay.
whatever you say
give the gift to the girl
this is for you
and this is for your mother
no aunty.
keep it child.
Keep it
what are you doing in Paris.
Are you here to see the friend
however she feels good.
I'm on my honeymoon
honeymoon!
Emotional
condom
thank you I need two
condom in my bag
your bra is here
I don't anymore clothes
you too come.
What will I do there alone
kurta suits you
I will send you more.
from Delhi in this bag
don't
I will come to India
true. I told Ricky when he's five
mama and child will go to India
and I also want to meet Chintu
Chintu will die when sees you
you too don't change
But cut off on alcohol a bit
and sex with strangers.
It's not good
Lakshmi is here
Hello.
How are you?
Vijay speaking.
I want to meet you
Rani is dead
brother give me some more jalebi
our status don't match now
we can't get married
Wait
hello Chintu how are you?
Vijay speaking.
what do you want?
Where is rani?
Hello I can't hear you
wait listen to me
asking about Rani Didi
Rascal
I made breakfast for you
Alexander
My self rani from India
Rani, what does this mean?
Rani means queen
What it is?
French toast
French toast. I'm French
it's not French toast.
Hi Didi
Chintu. hi.
where's everybody. they're coming
where is she? who?
VJ Lakshmi
Chintu, I'm in Amsterdam and she's in
Paris. stop asking the same question
Mom, talk to Didi
did he call you?
you want to meet him?
Did you meet him
not yet
look, you think
if you still like him
and if there's is something then let
them talk to us
yes, his parents told us he's in Paris
mom, I'm hungry
I'll go eat something
I will call you in the evening
sorry. family. don't know I'm staying
with boys
Papa mama
yes '
talk every day.
sometimes ten times a day
salt is less.
Everybody got scared
Lizard
Sikander is fine.
and it suits you
how many beers you drink in a day?
How much
are they buying the boat or rent it?
My sense is humor is very good.
you'll know
I don't like the boat plan very much
and it's expensive
let's go to the church
Rani.
Rani wait wait where are you
have you met hot guys
yes but they're cute
bring one for me in the suitcase
nothing, ayushman did a potty. you go
enjoy Amsterdam, I'll wash potty here.
This is electric massager
SEE
this is for joint pains
my grandfather has joint pains
it's a ladies belt.
Can be worn with dress or jeans
but you can get one India also
it's in Delhi
it was a very good shop I bought gifts
for everyone
words of heart on wall
why do you paint all this?
I want to do something
chada uncle told dad that I should
work in his company
I got 80 percent marks that's why
he's very impressed
he told me to handle accounts in
his company
what is dad saying
he said to ask you
what's the need.
I am working.
Don't you trust me.
It's not like that
tell him no
my business is also very good
my dad takes all his shop decisions
after asking me
and I'm going to tell dad that he
should put seating outside to extend
I think we're going the wrong way
now your name is sikander
I think we came to the wrong place
sikander wrong address
this feels like a very wrong place
is this the address.
this is the place right?
I need to give this parcel
this is for roxxette
VJ Lakshmi sent this
50 euros.
what for?
50 euros for half an hour
I won't talk half an hour.
I just need two minutes
please call roxxette.
You're roxxette
do you know VJ Lakshmi
yeah. you're queen. Rani.
from India
me ruksaar, here roxxettte
VJ Lakshmi sent this for you
my mom sent this
Vijay Lakshmi address she has
that's why you had to bring it
I can't give her this address and if
she finds out that I work here
she'll die
we're seven sisters and my father
is dead
I'm the son, I must earn money.
It's useless being sad
find some other job
this is very difficult job
I would if I could
resection and I even studied commerce
but until I get a job.. this is what I do
government say they will give all
the benefits and money is good
and when money goes to home
it's just money
with it one sister goes to school
two of them to college
and one of them just got married
I'll show you photos, are you on Facebook?
I will add you.
my email is happyrani@yahoo.com
pole dance time
your dance is very good.
thank you
come to Delhi
hopefully
asleep?
I will have to drive
drive.
there's a line behind us
don't push the break
you should travel by bus
you will never learn
your brushes and sikander your beer
we'll go to church today
Taka Japan
Tsunami
Mama papa gone
job gone
home gone
Taka has no one in this world
who is this
I didn't get married
he said no
What will I make?
I need cooker
they don't know cooker
spices.
hink
what do they call hink in English
mustard
what they write on the bottle
I never read it
child they call it hink in English
India
in Delhi it's called gol gappa
I told you no one will come
I will make one for you
Italian kiss best
it's not like that
India is best in everything
watch any movie of lmran Hashmi
all has best kisses of him
Indian best kissing
sure.
prove it
kiss
lip to lip?
yes lip to lip or what knee to knee?
I've been looking for you.
Why are you calling me now
don't say that rani
I've been waiting here
I haven't eaten since morning
are you okayv
Yes '
who are they?
my friends
you made friends in 5 days
anyways that's not important
I want to talk to you alone
I've missed very much
you drank alcohol
I drank Champaign
Champaign isn't alcohol?
Are you mad?
you started drinking
they must've taught you to drink
where did you find these hippies?
they're not hippies
they're my friend. people like you and
me. they're my roommates
you're living with boys
have you told your parents
if your mom finds out.
tell mom
rani I'm sorry
I made a mistake
I'm saying sorry
I came here just to see you
you know mom is planning everything
they're all missing you
they're renovating the top floor
just for us
let's go will sort out everything
I'm back
let's go from here.
I'm not going with you
I don't want to go anywhere.
They will help
rani, I will hurt someone
this is my fiancé
they're your friends
Vijay leave.
Vijay leave from here
I didn't do anything.
leave
what is my mistake. I came this
far to see you and your telling me to leave
I will meet tomorrow
we'll talk then
I'm apologizing. you want me to beg.
I missing you
Vijay we will talk tomorrow
he's still looking
come with me
I love you rani
we will talk tomorrow
and you will stay with them
at night
I will message you and let you
know
it's so bad.
doesn't look like me at all
I won't be able to come
rani
you look nice. I bought this from Paris
you look nice too
me and dad bought this shirt
will you have something
I'm okay
did you see Amsterdam
no
I'm not here to see Amsterdam
I've been looking for you
it's very nice. I even saw Paris
I went to Eiffel tower... alone...
rani I know I made a mistake
and I'm really sorry
you know they're all upset because of
me at home
you've become so modern
I mean, I'm just saying
I just want you.
I really love you
I really want you
we've been together for years
we can't just break up like that
I'm sorry about your friends yesterday
they were being...
and you don't know these foreigners
they're strange
I was just feeling protective
and obviously I'm your fiance who
else would feel like that
and whatever money spent.
papa will pay for it
whatever you guys spent
I know. you won't be able to live
without me
I ruined everything.
Vijay I need to go
go. where?
rock show.
I'm talking about our lives and your
talking about rock show
actually rock show isn't important
but my friends
all my friends are there. rani you're
leaving me for those friends
but
Vijay you weren't even going to
come here
I've been looking for you for five days
but my rock show plan was made earlier
and where are we going
we can talk in Delhi
what are you doing? talk to me
I will see you India
bye. I'm getting late
I will see you Delhi
she will come from here
plane landed
yes
she will bring luggage on her own
rani
mom look this is vj Lakshmi
she talked to you on Skype
same girl
whose house is this?
Mrs. Varma
I want to see the pictures
you drive
these boys are my friends
do you want us to wait
you go.
I will be there soon
we will wait
how will she come alone. leave Chintu with
her. she's seen the world.
Namaste
Vijay look who is here
Sit child
you've changed
even your hair are straight
deep neck.
you look beautiful
you know what. when you were
gone suddenly we were worried
you left without telling.
but didn't call once
forget about it.
these things happen among couples
now you're here in this house.
It's vacation for me now
you know what when they leave for
office we mother daughter will have fun
morning tea. magazines. parlor.
and kitty
you should join my kitty
we'll have so much fun
Vijay son
look who is here
you sit. I'll make you tea
what is it?
No rani
Rani don't do this.
I love you
thank you
Where are you? you don't even
log on Facebook these days
Send me photos. I'm uploading on
Facebook right now.