So... You think you are too big?
Too proud?
Very powerful?
It's an illusion...
Now watch!
How I break your arrogance!
You ruined my whole life!
I will slice through you!
Now watch the show!
Your game is over.
Hey, Dashrath!
Have you lost your mind?
Why have you started this fire?
You will die in this fire.
Your body won't even be found.
Have you lost your mind?
Now watch the show!
Dashrath...
You sold off the last goat
to buy a hammer and chisel?
I'm asking you.
Son of a pig... I'm your father!
Where are you going?
Shukla ji, this is the most backward
region of Independent India.
Nothing has
changed here for centuries.
It's been 13 years since independence
but there's not a whiff of it here.
No school, no hospital,
no road either here.
Do you see this mountain?
It has enslaved Gehlore village.
The nearest town, Wazirgunj,
is just four miles across the mountain.
But one has to go 40 miles around
the mountain to get there.
So many have died
trying to cross this mountain.
What is this?
So you want to wear shoes
and feel like a lord?
I made a mistake, Sir.
It won't happen again.
How can we believe you?
I swear on my mother.
Make him wear shoes, the kind
where he'll never need another pair again.
-Forgive me, Sir.
-Nail a horseshoe onto him.
Get lost.
Forgive me Sir.
How are you, Mukhiya ji?
We are honored, sir.
How are you?
What is going on here?
Just some minor repairs.
Your first visit here
since winning the election!
What can I say, Mukhiya ji?
Politics! It just sucks you in.
You literally have to hold on
to the damn chair.
But then you get to eat
the cream too don't you?
Just win the election once...
Your house turns
into the Taj Mahal!
Shukla ji, get a ticket for
my son, Ruab, in the next election.
Yes, yes, oh, meet him.
Who is he?
Alok, a very good journalist!
He's asking me to get a road
made from Gehlore to Wazirgunj.
Now think.
If the project is so big,
think how big the planning will be!
You are having a lot of fun!
Take a picture.
Come, son.
Name, Dashrath Manjhi.
Village, Gehlore.
District, Gaya.
State, Bihar.
The first time I saw him...
I knew he was crazy.
Hey, Dashrath.
Lower your head!
Can't you see who is sitting here?
What are you doing, Ruab?
At least don't hit him in my presence!
I am a Legislator and he is my voter.
I was doing it out of respect for you.
Forget the respect.
You don't know the reality.
Yesterday that fool set the
whole mountain on fire.
He's eaten so many rats
that they've got into his brain.
We know how to handle
these villains. Leave them to us.
For your sake.
Dashrath, what are you doing?
Breaking the mountain.
What! You'll break the mountain?
Yes.
-Alone?
-Yes.
Have you gone mad?
Yes.
You will die.
The devil has got into him!
Dashrath was born in a very poor
farm laborer’s house.
The lowest of the low caste,
"Moosahar" or "The rat eaters".
As per tradition,
he was married off as a child.
30 bottles of liquor and five pigs,
that was the deal.
Get up, Dashrath.
Making a fool of me are you?
The name of his child bride was Phaguniya.
What happened?
Sir, you called
me and I came running.
When will you repay the money
you owe Mukhiya ji?
I don't have anything, sir.
You can check.
Not a single penny. See...
You have money to get drunk.
What are you saying, sir?
If I don't drink, how do I live?
And if I don't live, how will I repay you?
Idiot, talking nonsense.
My lord, the child will hurt his hands.
I'll hit myself.
You wretched Magru, you worm,
son of a pig...
Take this! And this.
Get kicked...
Get kicked and die.
Hey, drama queen!
Are you going to pay up
or you want to be shod?
I'll pay up. I'll pay up.
Stay away.
But how?
My life is already bonded to you.
Well then get your
son's bonded now!
Take him, take him.
Now he will pay your debt.
Mother, I won't go.
Mukhiya beats me.
Really?
Shut up, you bum!
You have fun and I get kicked?
You are now bonded to the Mukhiya.
I won't go.
Won't go?
And who will repay the debt?
Your father?
I won't go.
You bastard!
You won't go?
Come on.
Run, Dashrath, run.
Catch that son of a swine.
Going to break the mountain again?
It's been two years now,
has anyone come to help you?
Don't you understand?
Or has your brain turned to stone?
One day you'll die
breaking those rocks.
Once there was a monkey king
who lifted a mountain
and now we have Dashrath here
who'll break one! Mad man! Mad man!
Here, I'm back.
Is everything fine?
Good.
You thought I wouldn't return?
Wrong!
I will not rest till I break you.
We are in for a very long battle,
you and I.
So are you ready?
He's ready!
Being smart with me?
I'll not leave you,
I'll never forgive you.
See what you have turned me into.
I can't forget anything.
That's the damn problem.
Like a film, it's got into my head.
It starts playing from any point.
Backwards, forwards
forwards, backwards...
Damn thing keeps dancing around
in my head.
I remember everything.
Everything.
As if it was yesterday.
Yesterday.
Toys, magical toys,
to stop the kids crying.
Toys, soft toys to keep your wife smiling.
Toys, toys.
Elephants, horses, Palanquin...
How great is my lord...
Toys, toys--
You blind scoundrel!
Wait till I cool you down...
Great! Fantastic! Alive!
First wash your face.
Hello, brothers!
The back of
untouchability is broken.
All are Equal...
Equal... Equal...
What are they celebrating?
End of untouchability!
The Government has passed a law.
All are equal.
What? We can touch anybody?
See! It's printed in the newspaper.
END OF UNTOUCHABILITY
Oh, my god.
We can touch anybody!
All are Equal...
Equal... Equal...
Untouchability is gone with the wind!
All are Equal...
Equal... Equal...
Dreaming of entering the temples...
The sons of bitches won't pipe down
until 10, 20 of them are hacked.
All are Equal...
Equal... Equal...
Want to come up?
You an outsider?
No, I'm very much from here...
ran away as a child to Dhanbad.
Worked in the coal mines.
Coal mines...
They call it "Black Diamond".
It's hard work...
if you do it well, you get money!
Hard cash.
And if you work hard, you get respect too.
But I am free spirited.
I just felt like it...
so I'm coming back home.
Which village?
Gehlore.
-Gehlore?
-Yes.
You'll cross the whole mountain?
-Sure!
-My God.
What name did you say?
When did I say anything, uncle?
Now I am saying it.
Dashrath is my name.
After seven years when he returned,
the village had not changed a bit...
as if it had been forgotten by time.
Your shoe, keep it on my head.
-What are you saying, Mukhiya ji?
-Keep it... Keep it...
Please don't make me sin, sir.
It is not your fault.
What happened?
The government has abolished
the caste system.
Next they will abolish the landlords.
The country will burn.
Has everyone gone mad?
Don't worry.
So what if a law is made?
Who will implement it?
Damn fools.
Good morning, Mukhiya ji.
How are you?
You have not changed a bit.
Still the same glow...
And you!
You have changed completely.
Handsome, healthy,
manly smile on your face.
Son...
forgive me.
I don't recognize you.
How could you recognize me?
It's been seven years.
How?
I'm Dashrath.
Magru Manjhi's son.
You trash!
Get away! You scum!
I heard, the government made
everyone equal, we can touch anybody.
You son of worm,
can a frog become a horse
by wearing a horse shoe?
The government loosens its grip...
So will you piss on my head?
Give him such a thrashing that
he never, ever...
forgets his caste!
Eyes down. Eyes down!
Hey, the government has said--
What government?
The government says
we can touch anybody.
What did it say?
That all are equal.
You scum.
Hey, the government has said--
They ruined everything.
Hey! Who is this?
Dashrath!
I'm Jhumru.
How are you, brother?
Great. Fantastic. Alive!
What happened to you?
Got a great welcome
from the villagers! See...
So did you get hitched or not?
Bhura, come here.
Hey, uncle!
How are you, Father? Long live!
Where did you go?
Those fuckers ruined everything.
My fate is bad...
-Your mother died and left me...
-I heard...
...the cursed one.
Now how will I live?
Hey, Uncle!
I won't live, I will die.
Why are you worried?
Now that he is back
we'll get his bride.
She'll feed you hot food.
In a week you'll be fine.
Hey, Lauki.
She is mine.
-Which one?
-This one.
And this is mine, the slow train.
Get lost!
Oh, my goodness, who is this?
We thought some English man
had come,
but this is a local rowdy.
You are looking absolutely bombastic.
Come, wash up.
Did you find a girlfriend?
Torn his clothes while having fun!
Yes, I met up with your sister!
Smartass!
Here, eat some food.
Eat first, then have your fun.
Uncle...
Hey, what is life without a wife?
Eating and sleeping
We have come to take
Dashrath's wife.
He ran away.
What's the guarantee,
he won't run away again?
Let it be.
I've seen a better boy in the city.
He has a government job in Gaya,
a watchman in the municipality.
What does this wastrel do?
You bloody pig thief,
You steal pigs from villages and sell
them to the butcher in the city
and you dare to call my son a wastrel!
You drunkard! Don't make me lose
my head or I'll thrash you.
-What's the problem?
-Hold your tongue
or I'll pull it out, you cheat.
They gave 100 rupees for her.
If you have any guts,
pay up 200 and take her.
-Forget it, Baba, I don't want her.
-No. No.
What does he think of himself?
I spit on him!
God knows who you got
me married to as a child.
Let's go.
You keep your princess at home.
That's your wife, Phaguniya.
This is Phaguniya?
This is my wife?
How is it possible?
She is mine.
You dare marry her to anybody else.
Just now you said you don't want her.
When did I say that?
Where did I say that?
Must have said it as a child.
Hey, Phaguniya.
You understand, don't you?
You come with me.
Kalua, Bilua, come here quick.
Get lost or your corpses
will leave this house.
You watch!
I will carry her away.
You dare marry her to anyone else!
A fair is not meant to be
enjoyed with one's father!
Come with me, we'll have some fun.
I thought you were going to
take me away.
Working on it.
I'll throw money on your
father's face and take you away.
Phaguniya? Phaguniya.
What is it, Mother?
See this.
-How much for this?
-Ten rupees.
I only have five rupees.
-Leave it.
-Wait.
The second one we will buy next year!
I got a gift for you.
This is the Taj Mahal.
An Emperor built it in memory of his wife.
So small?
This is a toy.
The real one is as big as our mountain.
I can't bear it any more.
Tell me one thing, are we not married?
Are you not my wife?
Then why does your father not
send you with me?
Baba says you don't earn.
How will you support me?
You don't worry, I'll go across
the mountain to Wazirgunj.
I'll beg, borrow, steal,
I'll sell myself, but I'll keep you happy.
-I know, but--
-No ifs and buts...
I can't live without you.
You come now.
Or I will eat you alive.
What are you doing?
Someone will see.
Let them see, I'm on fire.
Tell me the truth.
What is in your heart?
Show me.
Phaguniya.
Where are you?
Is there an animal in the bushes?
Yes, Mother.
When do I see you again?
What for?
To play with toys?
If you want me, speak to my father.
Or if you have the guts
then elope with me.
Oh, how she drives me crazy!
Hey, Bhura, what are you doing?
It has been two years.
You still don't have any brats.
We'll see when your wife comes
how many brats you produce!
You'll go straight into the pit.
Water, Jhumru, bring some water.
Bring some water.
Hey, idiot, you want to put out the fire?
If the bricks get wet,
I'll throw everyone in.
Get back, away.
He is dying, sir!
He will die.
So? Let him die if he
doesn't know how to work.
What will you do? Eat him?
You'll have to give compensation.
Get back.
What will she eat?
How will she live?
This asshole wants to be a leader!
The chicken is trying to be a tiger.
You want compensation?
Get back.
Damn it!
What kind of life is this?
Bhura's life is made.
At least he is out of this hell.
What game is this?
How much more will you torture us?
What's the use of killing the dead!
If you have the guts,
then stop the powerful!
Want to be called God?
Is this your world?
If you give life, why this torture?
Is there any kindness or not?
You make mistakes
and we get punished!
Why? Why?
Hey! Look at that!
See, that's Bhura, our Bhura.
He died and became a star.
His whole life, he was bonded...
He's shining after his death...
The bastard.
He is shining.
Dashrath...
are you a man or a mouse?
Mouse, no man.
Your father in law is marrying
off your wife to a city man.
Then you can keep shaking it.
-What did you say?
-Then you can keep shaking it.
Scoundrel! You'll marry my wife
to someone else?
Let's see.
Hey, Kalua! Bilua! Catch him.
Move away,
I want to speak to Phaguniya.
Phaguniya, what do you say?
Go. Go inside.
Don't you dare!
You think I'll give you my daughter?
Don't know where your next
meal is coming from.
-How you will take care of her?
-With Love.
Love will fill her stomach?
Phaguniya.
Open the door, Phaguniya.
Get lost, you loser.
Hey, you villagers.
He is marrying off my wife
to someone else.
Tell me, is it fair?
This greedy old man
is selling his own daughter.
Tell me, is it fair?
He'll ruin her life.
Tell me, Phaguniya...
will you come with me
or rot here for the rest of your life?
Tell me.
What are you thinking?
Get up.
You dare come closer,
I'll hack you to bits.
Move!
I'll cut you.
Stop him!
The rat has bitten off our nose.
Let's go.
Oh, my beloved!
I want to tell you
I'm covered in your color
I'm wearing your color
My body is adorned
With your arms
Oh my beloved!
You laugh after making me cry?
Now laugh!
Laugh!
As I break you from top to bottom.
There's a limit to everything.
How long can we bear your madness?
Till the mountain is broken.
What have you achieved in five years?
Have you even scratched the mountain?
What the British couldn't
do in a 100 years,
the government couldn't do in 20 years.
You think you can do it alone?
Stop it, old man, I'm tired.
You aren't bothered about us,
at least take care of yourself,
I can't bear to see you like this.
You feel sad looking at me?
Fine.
You won't see me anymore.
Phaguniya, Phaguniya
Calls out your beloved
Phaguniya Phaguniya
You live in my heart
You are my world
Phaguniya, Phaguniya
How much for this toy?
I'm not a toy.
But I want to play with this.
Let go of my hand.
Leave it or I'll cut off your
you know what!
Then you can play with it forever.
Come on, you'll have fun.
Leave my hand alone!
Come on, stop resisting.
Dashrath.
Dashrath, leave him.
Don't you trust me?
Phaguniya.
O', Phaguniya! You are my life. Life.
I love you so much,
so much, so much.
How much do I love you?
Should I tear open my heart to show you?
Get away.
Look...
for you.
A soft, soft pillow.
If we sleep with our heads together
on it-- It will be so much fun!
Why get a pillow?
Get a stone to break my head instead.
When you are angry,
you get wild.
Don't touch me.
Why? I am your husband.
If I don't touch you, who will?
You think I am some lemon tree?
Squeeze it whenever you wish?
Okay. I made a mistake.
I lost my head.
If anyone touches you,
can I just sit and watch?
How many will you beat up, Dashrath?
Mukhiya, the land lord,
the merchant, priest? Who all...
Everyone has an evil eye.
Whoever looks at you with
an evil eye I'll pull his eyes out.
-Oh?
-Yes.
-You are so powerful?
-Big wrestler, eh?
-Sure.
-Really?
-Yes.
Let me check your strength.
Hey! Hey! What are you doing?
Hit him!
He deserves it.
-The pig brought a pillow.
-I was stupid to elope with him.
You will stay an animal!
I won't stay another minute with you,
I am going.
-Where?
-To hell.
I'll come with you.
We'll play pillow games.
Where are you going in the dark?
Some wolf will eat you.
At least I'll be rid of you.
A scorpion will bite you.
I don't want to talk to you.
Listen, Phaguniya.
Forgive me.
Stop or I will jump off from here.
Is that why you eloped with me?
If anything happens to you,
what will I do?
He has brains in his heels
and wants to become a father.
Oh, what a miracle!
Show me, show me.
Hey, this is your father speaking.
What?
He says, "Nine months."
That's too long, come out soon.
What? "Boom"?
What? "Boom. Boom"?
"Boompati, boom, boom!"
O', Phaguniya!
Where is Dashrath?
Come out.
Where is the rat hiding?
Find him! Get everyone out!
I'll burn down the whole settlement!
Come out.
You dare raise your hand to me?
-What is it?
-Get him.
Check there.
The rat scuttled away.
Only this bag of bones is here.
You've bred a snake!
Where is Dashrath?
I swear I don't know.
-You don't know?
-No.
Fool!
Leave him.
Why are you looking for Dashrath?
A broken nose wasn't enough?
Want your leg broken too?
You damn swine.
Hey, Jhumru, stop.
Go inside.
Hey, Lauki,
now, here is a delicious one!
Everything is public property.
Get her.
Leave me... Leave me...
After few years ,
when I went back to Gehlore,
I heard he was still breaking
the mountain.
I was amazed...
and felt like meeting this crazy man.
Are you Dashrath Manjhi?
How are you?
Great! Fantastic! Alive!
I'm a journalist.
Name is Alok Jha,
I write for the Bharat Samachar newspaper.
Heard you've been breaking
this mountain for years.
Why?
Digging my own grave.
You are joking?
What should I say?
That I'm making a Taj Mahal?
You are offended.
Everyone says that I'm a mad man.
Wasting my life.
You don't waste your time.
It is an internal wound.
Till I break this mountain...
it won't heal.
You have taken on a big task.
Okay.
Let me know when you are finished,
I'll print your photo in the newspaper.
Trying to be a well-wisher?
Then come.
Lend me a hand.
Hold her. Hurry.
The baby is coming out!
Hold her in the water.
Careful, careful.
Call her husband! Hurry!
What happened?
Don't shout! Hold her.
Breath heavily, once more.
Once more.
What are you doing?
Dear Goddess, one request...
give me one daughter just like you.
Then you can take my life.
Get lost.
Melodramatic!
It has been a long time,
I really want to.
Let's play pillow games.
Your games lead to my bloated belly.
Nothing to eat and
he wants to breed a battalion!
Don't worry,
I got work across the mountain.
Once the daughter is born,
we will go to the city and earn a lot.
We'll make our son an officer
and daughter a teacher!
Life will sparkle.
Come on.
Now, when we go to the city.
My baby...
I will take you to the city.
So you'll never need to climb a mountain.
You won’t need to stay in the dark.
We'll eat good food.
Drink sweet water.
And have a lot of fun, my baby.
Dashrath!
Your wife has fallen
from the mountain!
What happened, Phaguniya?
The mountain was too high,
I couldn't climb it...
I slipped.
Doctor...
Hold on, don't give up.
Soon we'll reach the hospital.
Move! Move!
Where is the doctor?
We couldn't save her...
but your daughter is saved.
You think you are too big?
Too powerful?
Very proud?
It's an illusion.
Watch! How I break your arrogance!
You ruined my whole life!
I will break you.
You watch the show now!
Your game is over!
Must admit, he is true to his word.
He's cut the climb by at least an hour.
So, Dashrath, how much longer?
Till I break it.
The brave one!
Keep it up, kid!
When you finish the road,
We'll name it after you.
Rajkumariya...
how many times have I told you
not to climb the mountain?
You may break your leg, get hurt,
what will I tell your mother then?
Mother has gone to God's house.
You eat quietly.
Stop this tomfoolery!
Enough!
Driving me crazy!
Can't you see?
Do I take care of myself or your kids?
Listen, get married again.
Or find some work
and look after your kids.
Don't ever talk
about a second marriage.
What will I tell Phaguniya?
Moron! She is dead.
Not to me.
And regarding work, this is my work now.
What will you feed your kids?
These rocks?
Here! Nurse the buggers
and feed them rocks!
I can't handle your kids!
I will take care of my kids!
I will!
-Do it then! I'm off!
-You don't need to go crazy.
Come, Bhagirath.
See, I am nursing them! Happily!
Stop. Stop.
you fucking mountain cutter.
Why are you blocking
my path like a rock?
-Move aside.
-I can make you a profit.
-Profit?
-Yes.
Takes you four days to lug goods
from the market?
-Yes.
-In a bumpy bullock cart ride?
-And additional expenses?
Yes, so?
I'll get them across in a day.
Really? How?
The mountain is my friend.
The earth is his seat
And sky, the tent
He is covered with dust
And still remains pure
Little more.
Baba.
Why does everyone call you mad?
Those who do can't see.
What, Baba?
Magic. Want to see?
-Yes!
-Then close your eyes.
Abracadabra. Show magic to my kids,
show them a path
through that mountain!
-See it?
-Yes!
See the bullock cart racing?
-What else do you see?
-Cycle.
-Motor car! Bike!
God is great! God is great!
Baba, what was Mother like?
Exactly like you.
When will Mother come back?
When the road is ready,
Mother will be back too.
How are you, brother?
Great! Fantastic! Alive!
-Tell me one thing.
-Yes.
There are so many jobs in the world,
you couldn't find anything better than
breaking the mountain?
Everyone has their own skills.
You read and write,
I break the mountain.
How do you get so much strength?
It's love.
First, for my wife.
Now, for this mountain.
Such a deep thought
and you put it so simply.
Look at me,
I wanted to be an honest journalist...
but became a pimp of the politicians...
I hate myself.
Why not start
your own newspaper?
You think it's easy?
Is it more difficult than
breaking a mountain?
Long live the saint in the sack!
Let the earth split,
the sky fall, the floods come.
But the saint in the sack,
remains unaffected!
Great is the saint in the sack.
Let me fall at your feet!
What are you doing, Baba?
You fool.
There is a drought, you bastard!
All the villagers are leaving.
There is no water
and you are still digging!
Come to the city.
You won't survive here!
I can't leave the mountain.
-What?
-I can't leave the mountain.
Are you completely crazy?
Trying to be a hero?
In this scorching heat,
you want to break a mountain?
What will you eat? What'll you drink?
Fool! You'll burn to death!
So you go!
Go.
Here's some money.
Don't give them any grief.
I will stay here
and break the mountain.
Then break it you, idiot! I'm off!
I don't know what treasure
you'll find here.
A path.
I will find the path.
Come on, kids! Let this fool die.
Tinkle, tinkle...
Tinkle...
I only had one dream.
To buy the second anklet
for your other foot.
Don't have food to eat and
I'm dreaming of ornaments!
I've spent my whole life
with the tinkling of your anklet.
Tinkle, tinkle...
You saved my life!
Now you've become a true friend.
Come, let me give you some love.
Phaguniya...
You fair maiden of Gehlore
Will you come with me?
For you I made this path
Which goes to Wazirganj
Phaguniya...
Oh, my God, wonder of wonders.
The power of passion.
Cutting through hard rock.
Great, my son.
You have shown the world.
We were blind.
Couldn't see the road
hidden in the mountain.
Baba! For you.
Saved it for your hammer
and chisel.
Thank you, my child.
-Long live!
Shut the door! Hurry!
Baba! The Naxalites are here!
Go to your posts.
We are being attacked.
The damned Leftists are here.
Shut up!
As if you didn't have your fun.
Come inside!
Leave none of them.
So what did you think?
That I ran away?
See, bitch! I'm back.
To fix you.
This is a revolution.
It's spread like fire in the country.
Now everything will change.
No more rich! Or poor!
No high. No low.
All equal! Think!
We do the slogging,
and he has the fun?
We sweat and cry,
and he makes the money.
No more!
Today you will decide.
Speak up.
Anyone want to say anything about
this "landlord", Nirbhay Singh?
This village head gobbled up my land!
He killed my father and burnt him.
His son, Ruab,
kidnapped my daughter.
You have anything to say?
Forgive me.
Appeal rejected.
The people's court
sentences the accused to death!
-Long live the revolution.
-This is wrong!
This is wrong.
Dashrath.
Stop right there
or I'll forget everything,
This bastard is a blood sucker!
He killed my Lauki!
Ruined our lives,
I'm not going to spare him.
A gun gives one power, does it?
"Power flows from the barrel of a gun."
If I can break the mountain
I can break your head too.
Leave the Mukhiya.
The time to talk is over.
Now it's time to act.
Hang him.
Long live the revolution!
They hanged my father.
Dashrath, brother.
What happened?
"Great, fantastic, alive"?
Got scared of the guns?
I came to report
about yesterday's incident.
But no one is saying anything.
Tell me one thing.
Whatever happened...
was it right or wrong?
-Hey! Dashrath, brother!
-I'm a mad man!
Why ask me about right or wrong?
Am I responsible for all
the filth in the world?
I don't even know
what I am doing here!
Asking me about right and wrong...
Go mind your own business.
You asked me...
why don't I start
my own newspaper?
I've published my own newspaper.
The New Dawn.
Alok Babu.
Great! Fantastic! Alive!
-Can I take a photo?
-Sure, how do you want it?
-This way?
-Yes.
Long Live! Long Live!
He said if I ask Madam,
the road will be made.
Fool, see all the cops here?
They'll put you in jail!
Long live Indira Gandhi!
Long live Mother India!
I've come here to you,
to fulfill the dreams of
Mahatma Gandhi and Pandit Nehru.
It's a tragedy that even after
25 years of independence
people are fighting for basics like food,
clothing and housing.
Whenever I say "Remove poverty,"
the opposition says, "Remove Indira"
I want to know from you,
what do you want?
Help! Hurry!
Lend a shoulder, its falling.
This hand is your hand.
A symbol of your strength
and your labor.
This is the hand that will
bring about change.
This hand will write the
golden future of India.
This very hand
will eradicate poverty.
Today, the entire nation is screaming,
"Remove poverty!"
Indira Gandhi...
Long live!
Mother India...
Long live Indira Gandhi.
Long live Mother India.
Madam, I'm breaking a mountain,
please make a road there.
Madam, he is Dashrath Manjhi.
He's been breaking a mountain
for 12 years.
Alone, for the wellbeing of people.
If you can help him...
Move. Move away.
Dashrath, brother!
Come here.
See this.
You have become famous,
my friend.
See this,
your photo in the paper.
MANJHI - MOUNTAIN MAN
You have aged.
Sit. Sit down. Relax.
Now you need government help,
I will help you.
There's an officer, very big, the BDO,
I've spoken to him.
You'll get a government grant
to break the mountain.
-The government will help?
-Yes.
-For making the road?
-Then it'll break in a jiffy!
-Of course.
Now I am the village head.
Can't just see my own profit and loss.
Forget whatever happened in the past.
If the road is made,
everyone will benefit.
Yes, then a proper road can be made.
Yes.
Motor cars will zip around
in our Gehlore.
Reaching the hospital will be easy.
Zip! And you'll be in Wazirgunj!
-Zip and you're in Wazirgunj?
-Yes.
Dashrath is doing a noble job.
He's breaking the mountain
in memory of his wife...
She was like a... goddess.
Sit, brother Dashrath, sit.
Sit.
You're very hard working.
We are happy with your work...
I'm writing to the government
to help you.
-You'll get money.
-The government is like a parent.
Once the road is made
I can die in peace.
Now everything will change.
Everything will change!
Now, you go.
And listen, work diligently.
When the money comes from Delhi
I'll send it through Mukhiya.
I am an illiterate,
I don't understand money matters.
But I will break the mountain.
Just get a permanent road made.
Consider it done.
Mukhiya ji,
we are sanctioning two million.
He won't know how many
zeroes in two million.
BDO, sir, this is called finding
a diamond in a coal mine.
Hello, Baba.
Bless you.
Baba, recognize me?
I'm Gopal.
As a kid,
I used to throw stones at you, Baba.
And call you "The mad mountain man..."
I was wrong.
Bless you
I want to say something to you.
Yes, tell me.
Even I love someone as you did.
So do it.
I want to marry her.
Do it with élan.
But my parents are not ready.
What should I do?
I eloped with Phaguniya.
Love has a lot of power, my child.
Can I say something?
You won't mind?
Why are you talking in riddles?
Tell me.
The one I love...
is Rajkumariya.
Great! Fantastic! Alive!
Shut up, dimwit.
You'll fix my son's marriage?
Stupid, I'm not fixing it.
They have fixed it.
I've just come to give you
the good news.
Here! Have some sweets.
I don't agree. Get lost.
They are new age kids.
What if they elope or jump into the well?
For 16 years I've been
breaking the mountain,
I can break anything
but not the kid's hearts.
Understand? Don't insult yourself
and eat some sweets.
-You're threatening me?
-Why are you getting irritated?
Even I have a daughter.
Who will marry her without money?
How will I get the money?
Will you give it to me?
Oh, God.
Two birds and one stone!
Tell me one thing.
Your son, my daughter
and my son, your daughter?
Fine?
So what are you thinking?
Have some sweets!
Live long.
Make your own path.
Phaguniya would have danced
all night.
Why don't you dance?
Dance. Dance.
Why are you standing like a statue?
The kids are getting married.
You need to bless them.
You are even older than me.
You won't change.
Let me fix you.
What? Let it be today?
Okay, I'll leave you today.
Enjoy!
No more than two sips, now, you come.
Go, throw the stones.
You'll get more sweet water.
Remove all the stones.
We'll have more stones.
Come next week and collect them.
BLOCK DEVELOPMENT OFFICE,
WAZIRGANJ (BIHAR)
To maintain peace and order,
all necessary steps will be taken.
SURAJ TV AND RADIO REPAIR WORKS
Anyone who protests
will be jailed.
The government has declared
a State of Emergency.
Hello.
Hello, Reporter Sahab.
Welcome.
Tell me.
A grant was approved in his name.
We've come to collect the money.
-What is the name?
-Dashrath Manjhi.
Dashrath Manjhi.
Exactly.
For breaking a mountain, right?
Yes.
But you have already
taken the money.
I didn't get any money.
Must be a mistake, do check again.
There's an entry in the register.
Here, see, "paid."
But I got no money.
Trying to cheat the government?
But I didn't get any money.
Wolf in a lamb's clothing, eh?
-Relax.
-Trying to teach me?
-Go away.
-Okay, understood.
-Go
-Understood.
We'll speak to the BDO come on.
But I didn't get any money.
Ruab Babu!
BDO, sir...
Why are you pissing fire?
The money the government sent to
break the mountain, where is it?
What nonsense are you talking?
I went to the office.
They said the money's gone!
So where's it gone?
Gone? How would I know?
Do you think I'm stupid?
Think I can't see?
New car, this gold chain...
I want the money to
break the mountain.
What money?
Which money?
Go. Bang your head against
the mountain.
Does the government have no other work?
You are trying to cheat me?
What will you do?
There is an emergency in the country.
If I put you in the jail
you won't come out alive!
-I'll complain.
-To whom?
There's no government in Bihar.
Go, go to Delhi.
Go bang your head there.
The government is listening
to everyone these days.
I'll go to Delhi if I have to.
But I won't spare you!
Delhi is very far, you moron.
Do you even know
which country it is in?
I'll find out and I will get there!
-Go find it.
-The fucker's a lost dog.
Trying to cheat me?
Throw him out.
-That I don't have, sir.
-Where are you going?
Delhi, to meet the Prime Minister.
Twenty rupees for a ticket
and 20 rupees fine, shell out 40.
I've no money, sir.
Is this your dad's train?
Look at his guts!
They want a free ride!
Get down, you bum.
I'm going to meet
the Prime minister, sir.
Oh?
You fucking beggar! Get down.
That was a little extreme.
Have some tea.
Doesn't matter...
I'll go to Delhi.
On foot.
Are you out of your mind?
-Why?
-It is 1300 km.
Think it's a joke? Walk to it!
I need to go, so I will.
Longing for a glimpse
Crazed
An ecstatic Fakir
Standing alone
Embracing the sky
O' traveler, O' traveler
The soldier of light
Walk, and a path will emerge
Your dreams will illuminate the world
O' traveler, O' traveler
Come, get up, you fool
Make your path
Smile, and celebrate life
The world will change
Only if you change
The story now will start with you
If there is a spark,
there will be a fire
O' traveler, O' traveler
The soldier of light
Destination is just a limit
of your determination
Desires too many
and wishes boundless
Destination is just a limit
of your determination
Who know what will happen and when
Only you know what you will do now
Your deeds will create your story
O' traveler, O' traveler
The soldier of light
LET'S GO TO DELHI. REVOLT AGAINST
THE EMERGENCY. LAY SIEGE TO THE PARLIAMENT
O' traveler, O' traveler
Walk, and a path will emerge
Your dreams will illuminate the world
O' traveler...
Come on. Move from here.
This useless government
took your votes in the name of
removing poverty.
But removed the poor!
This poor villager,
all by himself,
has cut a path through the mountain!
He has walked with us all the way
from Bihar.
If it can't give us food or clothing...
The government is useless!
Break up, all of you!
Get lost! Get away!
-What is it?
-I need to meet the Prime Minister.
I know her, look at this.
Thousands come here every day!
By the Kilo! Crazy coot!
It's their job to get photographed.
And you useless sod,
get one photo clicked
and you think you are a leader?
"Long live mother India."
Take this! And after today,
If I see you here,
I'll shove you into the jail.
Load him onto the train to Bihar.
-Move.
-The bastard, take him away.
Dashrath.
Phaguniya!
You've come, after so many days!
What happened?
You were making a road,
weren't you?
Enough, enough already.
No hope anywhere.
Nothing will ever change.
Everyone called me mad.
Everyone else was right.
I was wrong.
A little stumble and
you shatter?
The world is a web of deceit...
ruled by the powerful.
And I? I'm alone.
I'm tired.
And old.
Can't do this anymore.
Remember, Dashrath.
You took an oath to make the path.
This path will be made and
you will make it.
It's no use.
No one cares.
Nothing will change.
I thought...
you were making me a Taj Mahal.
Why are you staring wide eyed?
Pick up your hammer and chisel
and break the mountain.
Or I will never talk to you again.
Baba, you are not alone anymore!
Everyone is with you.
This path will now
be made very soon.
Great! Fantastic! Alive!
He broke the damn mountain.
And that's their leader, Dashrath.
You start the proceedings.
Hey! Stop it.
With whose permission are
you breaking this mountain?
This property belongs
to the Forest Department.
Are you trying to grab it?
Who is this Dashrath Manjhi?
Catch the bugger!
Tie him up.
Bring him here.
Is this your dad's mountain?
And where are all the stones?
Motherfucker, gobbled them up?
Sold them?
He wants to become the stone mafia.
No, sir, we were making a path
for the village
-to make it easy.
-Make it easy, eh?
-Easy...
-Fool!
Let me make it easy for you.
Stealing a mountain?
You think it's a joke?
If anyone even steps up here again.
Your properties will be confiscated
and you'll rot in jail.
Take him.
Get in.
Messing with the law, eh?
Bloody mountain thief.
For 20 years he's been breaking
the government’s property.
Politics of the hammer!
Prosecute him in such a manner
that he dies in jail.
Oh, die!
Now, sing your hymns.
Your story is over.
Once you mess with the government,
even God has to surrender.
Phaguniya...
I feel I have lost...
I'll die before the task is done.
Maybe my love lacked something.
Maybe I was too weak.
Maybe God didn't want it.
Maybe...
It makes no difference.
Release Dashrath Manjhi!
Release him! Release him!
-Who are they? What do they want?
-Don't know.
Then don't just stand there!
Go find out!
-Yes, sir.
-Release Dashrath Manjhi!
Release him! Release him!
Calm down.
Why've you arrested him?
He's innocent.
Until you release him,
nobody'll leave here.
Release Dashrath Manjhi!
Sir, they have come
to get him released.
They say he's falsely implicated,
he's a saint.
They'll go on a hunger strike
until he's released.
Sir, I think he is a political man.
Release Dashrath Manjhi!
Release him! Release him!
Release the joker! Hurry.
What about the Forest Department?
They stuff their faces
with bribes and we face the crap.
-Get him out.
-Move, move.
-Dashrath Baba!
-Long live!
Come on!
-With all your might.
-Haissa.
-All together.
-Louder now.
-Haissa.
-Dashrath Baba!
-Long live!
An age has gone by, in your memory...
How much I love you!
So much...
that no mountain can stop it...
that sky cannot contain it,
that no one can imagine.
I know.
You've performed a miracle!
Dashrath Manjhi, you are a super man!
You are Mr. India!
Alone with a hammer and chisel!
Tell me, after making
the impossible, possible,
what would you like to say?
What can an illiterate
man like me say?
Say something.
I say, don't depend too much on God...
maybe God depends on us.
DASHRATH MANJHI PATHWAY