[Man humming in background]
[Prem Prakash]
There are three things in this world
which no matter
how hard one may try,
cannot stop me from shedding tears.
One, dad's slipper,
Two, English exam's question paper.
And three, Kumar Sanu's voice.
These three are loaded with pain.
["Mere saare imtihanon kaa" playing]
[music distorts]
[music resumes]
[music fades]
[Chandrabhan] He is glued to this place.
I have told you so many times
not put on headphones to listen to songs.
Your ear-drums will get damaged.
- What are you saying?
- What am I saying!
Priest from Hrishikesh had called.
- Have to go to see the girl for you.
- Ok!
He asked to come
to the temple tomorrow.
- Ok.
- So, I was thinking.
You come after finishing here.
And what the hell is this?
- Throw it away.
- Ok, dad.
[Chandrabhan] I am leaving
Rs. 20 here. Ok?
Yes, dad.
Be careful of the cows
entering the shop.
Yes, dad.
[indistinct chatter]
- Yes I took it.
- Jaya, you got the lemon pickle, right?
- I'll get it right away, mom.
- Check if I've left the gas on.
- Where are you off to?
- Did you keep the bag of coins?
- Kishor, what about the coins?
- Yes, I have it.
- Thank god.
- I took it from the tea shop guy.
[all chattering]
Hey, Prem, you sit at the back.
Hurry up, there is no time.
[Naina] Hurry up, come in.
[Naina] Jaya, what took you so long?
Hurry up.
[car doors slamming]
- Girl, hurry up!
- I am coming.
Quick! Hurry up.
- Mom!
- What happened?
- My Sari has come off.
- Oh dear!
I had told you to put
safety pin,
but you didn't listen. Hold it.
- Let him go. Go on.
- One minute.
Hurry up!
What have you done?
Breath in. I will shove it in.
Now hold onto it tightly, ok?
Give it to me.
Cover your head.
It's a temple and not your college.
Come on now.
[temple bells ringing]
Can't get hold of it.
- Let me see, son.
- What're you doing, mom?
Why didn't you put oil in your hair?
They're so dry.
Tell him to sit up straight before them.
- Sit up!
- No need to behave like an invalid.
You're the lone son of Tiwari clan.
Don't make sound while eating
and don't spit while talking, Prem.
You guys are talking as if
I've never seen a girl in my life.
Would you like to have some water?
- When will we reach, Jugnu?
- Ohh! Seems like
he can't wait to join his new family.
[everyone laughing]
[Priest] Let me introduce everyone.
You're Mr. Madanpal,
- [Madanpal] Hello!
- [Priest] And you're...
- ...working in BHIL.
- Yes, as a foreman.
[Priest] You're Chandra Prakash Tiwari.
- Hello!
- [Priest] Girl's mother, Subhadra Rani.
[Priest] And you're the boy's mother,
- Sashi Tiwari.
- Hello, ma'am.
[Priest] These are the boy's
two sisters, Jaya and Hema.
[Priest] And their sons-in-laws.
This is the boy's aunt,
- my younger sister, Naintara.
- Greetings, ma'am.
I feel that the boy and the girl
should talk to each other.
[everyone] Yes, of course!
Come on, darling, say something.
I... I am Sandhya.
- Sandhya.
- [Sashi] Ok!
Prem, introduce yourself, son.
You've introduced me, dad.
[laughter]
- No one introduced our Samar.
- [Sashi] Samar?
- Samar, her younger brother.
- I see.
His 10th grade exams are going on.
That's why he couldn't come.
- And what about Sandhya's education?
- She has done B.Ed.
- She always wanted to be a teacher.
- Oh, ok.
She would make her dolls recite tables
when she was young.
Why are you whispering in my ear?
Go ahead, ask for yourself.
- She's asking about his qualification.
- Who?
Our Prem has a degree in commerce.
He was always interested
in doing business.
He was more interested in making money
rather than in books.
[Chandrabhan] Even that's
important, ma'am.
[everyone laughing]
Son, think about your life.
Think and then speak.
I have spoken after thinking.
What have you thought?
The girls is so pretty,
so well-behaved
and to top it all, she is good-natured.
Did you guys see that?
Didn't say anything.
How do you know she's good-natured?
Hey! Isn't this called
being good-natured?
Girl who stays mum in front of elders,
she is considered good-natured
or the one who sits at the shop
and records movie songs all-day long!
Everyone, just listen to me.
I think the girl is good at heart.
Good at heart it seems.
Nobody is mentioning her face.
What's wrong with her face?
Is she lame or limbless?
What's wrong with her?
Mom, did you see her size?
- Like this!
- Like this?
Who do you think you are?
Couldn't even clear 10th grade
and you're dreaming of a movie star.
Listen son, this is all because of
today's food habits.
Now, just look at your sister Jaya!
She has put on so much of weight
after her marriage.
Jugnu hasn't abandoned her, right?
- They are together.
- But Jugnu loves her.
Mom, does my choice matter at all?
Damn your choice!
For your choice, your parents would be
begging on the roads.
Dad, please don't digress from the topic.
- Explain him with love.
- Then please do so!
Son, listen to me.
If you will marry a beautiful girl,
we'll not be able to bear the
cost of her make-up, you know.
This girl is well qualified.
She'll come into our house,
will work as a teacher,
- it'll help us financially as well.
- Mom, I will not marry her.
- That's it!
- Hey, what do you mean?
- Give me my slipper!
- [Naina] Leave it, brother.
[Chandrabhan] He's misbehaving!
Please understand. We are going
through tough times.
Please say yes.
[upbeat music playing]
I'll look for a lovely, special girl
Not someone temporary
I'll find someone permanent
[Group wedding]
I'll look for a big earner,
Sober and sweet
Not someone temporary
I'll find someone permanent
[group wedding]
Eyes like a golden fairy
A magic wand in her hand
I'll look for the perfect bride
With a golden heart
He should have a bike and a car
Good manners too
I'll consider him if he's loyal
She'd go with me to visit Shimla,
Kullu, Manali
But not forget to buy veggies
on his way home from work
I'll look for... I'll look for...
Ill look for
A bride with a difference
I'll look for a graduate, a lively,
Cheeky type
Not a fellow who looks old and grumpy
She is the one?
I'll look for someone
Who is excellent in household chores
Not someone ordinary!
I'll look for a Deluxe bride.
- Sit down quietly.
- What is the matter?
[traditional music playing]
What's the matter?
My head aches.
- Mom.
- What is it?
You have a pill for head ache?
Here, take it. Yes.
Pop one of these!
You'll be relieved in an hour.
What are you doing?
You want to kill yourself!
These are pills, not peanuts!
[camera clicks]
Told you so many times,
not to drink milk after having chowmein.
Now he's throwing up.
- He has eaten dahi-bhalla.
- What?
Relax, father, it's nothing.
This is because of allopathy!
You should have seen him popping pills.
He could not refuse the pills.
Do it properly.
Give him Limca, he'll be fine.
Oh dear!
Let him throw up.
Sister, I like the this smell
of marigold so much.
Hello!
Come in, dear.
Come, come.
See, how pretty it is!
Your aunt has done
all the decorations herself.
She got flowers herself.
- Give my nephew so much love...
- [sneezing]
Oh, dear, you sneezed.
- You have cold?
- I am allergic to marigold.
Ok, then let it be like this for tonight
and we shall remove them tomorrow.
Come on in now.
She has decorated with lots of love.
- Let's all go now.
- You can check these.
[indistinct chatter]
Let's go.
[door closing]
[Chandrabhan] Where's the girl?
Don't make any mistake in hurry.
Let her get a government job first
and then have kids. Got it?
Are you feeling fine?
[bangles jingling]
[distorted music from recorder]
[utensil falling]
Where is the bathroom?
You can change here only.
All right.
Wait! I shall go out.
[door closing]
[Mile sur mera tumhara
playing in Background]
[Sandhya] Come in, please.
[door closing]
[funny background music]
[funny background music continues]
[Prem snoring]
[Sashi] Dear!
[Sashi] Are you up, Sandhya?
- Yes!
- There is call for you.
Ok, mother.
[background prayer chanting]
[door opening]
- Hello!
- [Girl] Hello.
[Girl] Hope I didn't disturb you.
How did you get this number?
[Girl] Leave all that!
How was your first night?
Poor thing! He was behaving
like a calf
separated from the mother cow.
[laughing]
We both slept on either
sides of the bed.
- Ok, listen, I shall call back later.
- [Girl] Yes.
- Ok. Bye!
- [Girl] But please call me...
[Chandrabhan] Please go and wake up
your son. Blow the trumpets
so that he wakes up.
[Sashi] Why're you muttering?
[Sashi] You know sound travels.
You are worried about the sound,
but you're not bothered by him.
It's not entirely his fault.
She could have spoke to him.
[Naina] That's right!
She is also egoistic.
She thinks she has done us great
favour by doing B.Ed.
She didn't even respond to my 'hello'.
And with her family members...
[giggling]
Well, she is right.
We are not at par with her standards.
Why are you all blaming that poor girl?
Think about her,
this is a new place for her.
And her husband is so rude.
He refuses to talk to her.
Boys like him should be...
Let me just teach him a lesson.
Oh! Good morning, dear bridegroom.
Where are you off to?
Going to Saakha.
Shakha! This will ruin you one day.
Want to become a revolutionary!
Can't even kill a fly.
Will talk to you once I am back.
Wait a minute. Will talk for sure.
Just look here!
Look here!
What happened at night?
Dad, hit me if you want to.
- But I'll do whatever I want.
- Whatever you want!
One hit with my slipper
and you'll start speaking sense.
- Where the hell is my slipper?
- Don't hit him.
Stay blessed.
See, bride has got tea.
Please serve it to brother-in-law.
[Sashi] Come, well done.
He loves going to Shakha.
He loves to exercise since childhood.
Seems you people don't
believe in exercising.
Just father goes to exercise.
I practice yoga at home.
Yeah! I can see that.
[mantra chanting]
[mantra chanting follows]
Remember Bhagat Singh,
Neta Ji Subhash Chandra Bose, Shivaji
and Mr. Vajpayee.
Is anyone of these great souls
- directionless?
- [everyone] No!
So, let's take an oath
that we'll take inspiration
from their lives
- and follow their footsteps.
- [everyone] Absolutely.
- Shakha sir.
- Yes!
Prem got married.
[everyone] Congratulations!
We all deserve a party!
[everyone] Absolutely.
Father has told me not to
waste money on useless friends.
We condemn these kinds of useless feasts.
[Prem] Absolutely!
Study hard, Ok?
Ok, let's go.
Oh! take this.
- Give it to Jaya.
- Yes.
- Take care of my brother.
- Ok, sister!
- Give me ring as soon as you reach home.
- Ok, mother.
And you give two rings.
Ok, now go!
- Take care and go carefully.
- [Hema] Ok!
Shakha sir, I don't know what to do.
[all doing breathing exercise]
[Shakha] What's the matter?
What's stopping you?
I couldn't even clear 10th grade,
and the computer course is in English
which I don't understand.
On top of that, dad has
gotten me married!
You're suggesting me to run away
whilst doing yoga.
[breathing exercise continues]
One can't settle in a day, mom.
It'll take some time.
Today, I got up a little late.
[Sandhya] The alarm didn't go off!
What could've I done?
You didn't do anything
and got up late as well.
If you continue this,
your in-laws will send you back.
Mridula just can't keep a secret!
[loud counting] 10...
11...
12...
God has given you such great opportunity.
You have been married into a family
having tape-cassettes business.
At night, tell him
to put an English movie.
That'll set the mood right!
[water splashing]
You should revolt.
And continue doing so
till you see things clearly.
You are right!
At least I can revolt in bed
if not in the house.
Who is watching me there!
If he doesn't make the first move,
you seduce him!
You're equally responsible
for your marriage, isn't it?
Oh! Please walk slowly.
I cleared engineering, so father asked me
to distribute sweets.
Oh, Prem, listen!
First shop from right!
- You go, I've some work.
- You'll not come to Vijay's shop?
I've to give to everyone. Take less.
Ok, I'll give to aunt!
- [Nirmal] Prem!
- You know Vijay, right?
So what'll I do in a women's shop?
- You go, I'll join.
- Oh, listen!
[indistinct chatter on TV]
- [Sandhya] Hello, Vijay.
- Hello, sister!
See, sister, Prem's wife is here!
- Hello!
- Would you like a cup of tea?
No, please, it's fine.
Sister, Prem hasn't come?
No. He had some work.
- Brother, I need some stuff.
- Yes, of course.
These bangles will look lovely on you.
No, I don't want bangles.
I want something like that.
Here, take this, sister.
- These are very nice bindis.
- No, no.
One that's on the side.
This one, sister?
Like that top one!
Sister, can you please show?
- Sister, I have to attend to accounts!
- Okay. That's fine.
What shall I show, sister?
I want satin nightwear.
[Woman] Sure. You would like to see
undergarments also?
No, just that!
- [Woman] Nightwear!
- Yes.
[Woman] This'll look nice on you.
- See this.
- Ok, ok, fine.
[Woman] And this one too!
That's its inner wear.
- [Woman] Look!
- Pack it!
- [Woman] Yes?
- [Sandhya] Yes.
[sad music]
Let me know when you're done.
- I'll wait right here.
- I was looking at their bag.
They have gajar kaa halwa.
Oh, please. Don't lie.
[indistinct chatter]
Oh Prem, is this your wife?
Yes. I...
- Have brought her for an outing!
- Yes.
- Hi, I'm Sandhya.
- This sister Parveen.
She is very pretty.
Do come over sometime.
I don't live very far from here.
- Come over some day.
- Yes, will bring her over.
You keep quite! As if you will do so.
Oh! Tehmeena.
- Get my purse, quickly.
- [Man] Prem!
- [indistinct chatter]
- C'mon let's go now.
- Let's go from here.
- At least let me talk to her.
Listen, sister!
Sweets, I completed my engineering.
Here are some sweets.
Please take half!
Have to give everyone.
What was the hurry?
Didn't even let me speak to her.
Why are you getting so angry?
What did I do?
I am talking to you.
Please take us to govt. library.
Then maybe I should walk...
[background music]
Listen, I want to clearly...
It's a library.
I don't like talking to people.
I didn't ask you to talk.
I was talking. What's your problem?
These shopkeepers...
I don't like talking to them.
I also don't like people
interrupting me all the time.
Do you have a problem
if I talk to people?
Do you have any idea
what all happens here?
You'll go back home.
They'll chew my brains.
"Prem didn't treat us for his wedding!"
My father was right.
People from Haridwar are big misers.
Today, your daughter-in-law
wanted to see a movie.
So your father is setting up VCR
in their room.
She should have got
VCR from her house.
We'll miss the serial now.
One day makes no difference.
As if it'll move ahead.
The same thing keeps happening.
Ok, I'll disconnect now.
Ask Hema to call me
in the morning, ok?
Good girl!
Aunty, shall I close the window?
Sure.
Put a lock on the door as well!
[closing and locking door]
Listen!
Please close the window.
- What?
- Window.
Set the movie in the VCR.
[loading VCR]
[Sandhya] I'm ready!
You'll not see?
I don't feel like it.
Then send the TV back outside.
- I'll ask father...
- Why are you dragging father in this?
We shall see. We'll see it together.
[bed cranking]
Turn off the lights.
[lights off]
[sound from TV]
[girl moaning in TV]
[funny background music]
Blanket?
[girl moaning and smooching in TV]
Water?
Yes.
[bed shaking]
[bed shaking continues]
Our son has grown up!
By the grace of god,
everything is ok.
Where are you going?
I'll call Jaya and tell her.
She'll be at peace then.
Call her tomorrow!
[background music]
How long did you see the film?
Unlike you, I don't leave
things in between.
I saw the whole film.
Till the end.
Who lights coal at your place?
We don't have cinder,
we've a heater.
- Will you have something?
- No.
- Eat something.
- He'll eat, get him a plate.
What were you saying
about your exams, Samar?
Maths was tricky, rest was ok.
Just make sure you pass!
No one has failed in our family.
I'm struggling to get full marks!
Seems like god has given
all good things to your family.
Excellent, I'd say!
[Naintara] Here, take the offering.
May god bless you.
[Chandrabhan] This is Prem's aunt.
- What happened?
- Sister is here.
- See you, father.
- Oh, so you're leaving?
[Chandrabhan] Bride is leaving!
- Oh, let him eat something.
- I have had, aunty.
They definitely eat less,
but somehow they are healthy.
Here, take the offering.
It's called metabolism, aunty.
Bye.
Where's our Kumar Sanu?
What're you doing inside?
She's leaving, take her luggage.
[Chandra Prakash] Convey my regards
to your father.
- [Sashi] Be careful.
- Ok, mother.
Ok, listen!
I've left the list of songs on the table.
Make the mix tape.
Will do if I get time.
Come on the 4th, ok?
- What's on the 4th?
- My mother's marriage.
Let's go, Samar.
[scooter sputtering]
At the time of the wedding,
I couldn't say anything to dad.
Yesterday night, couldn't stop myself.
Gravitational pull of marital bliss
will pull me in, Saakha sir.
A man who could not
control his temptation.
What do I teach him?
I can't utter a word
in front of her and
- You're talking about controlling senses.
- No, no.
This is a lie, Prem.
Accept the reality.
I don't like her looks,
so how can I accept her?
[happy music in background]
How do I look?
No matter what you do,
you'll look like a witch forever.
I will wack you!
My life is directionless now.
There is no escape, Saakha sir.
Then give up, son.
It's no gravitational pull,
it's an attraction for your lady.
There's no shame in enjoying it.
Listen!
Women are not solace for me.
It's just a physical attraction.
Then enjoy the physical attraction.
Why do you come here then?
[Sandhya] Every object on Earth
is attracted to another object.
First rule of gravitational force.
Law of Gravity!
But why do they not
proceed towards each other?
Why do they stick to their own places?
Because these objects try
pulling each other
and hence, do not move
from their place.
[Man] Play it, please.
- [Prem] This one?
- [Man] Yes. Press this.
Now, listen to its sound.
- Is this the CD, or this is?
- Uncle, this is the CD.
Compact disc. Thing of the future!
Let this old thing go!
["Mohe Chedo" playing on CD]
[Man] How did you like it's sound?
The sound is indeed very good.
Will get you started in 100,000 or so.
If you want, I can organize
the CD dealing as well.
You'll get us some money
for all this, right?
Oh, uncle, no one wants this now.
If you get 1000-2000 for this,
you should be thankful.
- [Prem] Leave it then!
- [Man] No one wants it.
We will need to set up
the entire business again.
Take money from Raghubir!
Had taken money from him
for my girls' wedding.
Now, I just want to die!
Father, I warned you before...
...against taking loan
Why don't you suggest something then?
Shall we put radio under our pillows
and go to sleep?
Kumar Sanu will sing you lullaby.
We'll manage somehow!
When is Sandhya coming back?
- 4th!
- What?
[Naina] Today is 4th!
He's stuffing himself here
and someone is waiting for him there.
Feed him some more.
Go now!
He must have got some work.
Call him from Vasudha's house.
He could have also called, right?
Don't compare yourself to him.
You're right, mother!
There's no comparison.
Father, please have dinner.
- Just a minute!
- Samar, come and have food.
Please serve less, ok?
You're serving so much.
Leave some for him too.
No need to leave anything for him.
[scooter approaching]
[knocking the door]
I'll go and check.
[knocking continues]
[Madanpal] Welcome, please come!
- [Prem] Did you guys sleep already?
- We don't sleep before 12.
In the kitchen, since morning,
only your name could be heard.
- Welcome, son.
- Please get him some water.
Please come in.
Hello, brother-in-law.
Get a plate for him, quick!
No, it's ok. I need
to open shop in the morning.
Have something at least.
No. Festival season is going on.
So I have to record religious songs.
Get some water, go.
Shall we go?
Prem, just a minute.
- Here!
- Keep it.
It's a small token. Keep it.
Keep it, brother-in-law,
buy me something later.
- [Madanpal] Take care!
- [Subhadra] Be careful.
[Subadhra] Hold him tightly!
[scooter throttling]
[scooter stops]
What happened?
I'm hungry.
You said you have eaten.
[water flowing]
[food frying]
Sit there.
I...
It's fine here.
Rohan, give me kachodi
with onion and raddish.
You eat onion?
Yes, just I eat in our house.
Everyone eats in our house.
You all like to brag
about yourselves?
"We all eat onion,
no one has ever failed."
If you all just lie,
then what can we do?
But it's good,
at least now I know
something about you.
You smoke also?
I even drink.
In your family?
No.
[playing "Ye Moh-Moh ke
dhaage in background]
No need to tell anyone.
Why? You'll get belted?
I'm not scared of anyone.
That's why I go to Saakha.
That's right!
You are after all a king.
Have your kachodi.
- You want?
- No, thanks.
["Yeh moh-moh ke dhaage" playing]
[scooter starts]
[song continues]
What happened?
I want to have water.
I'll bring it.
[door opening]
Girls these days, they know everything.
What's good for them,
what's not, they know it all.
Good and bad, they know it all.
They know the power of youth, sister.
Our son is a simpleton.
Weren't you aware of
the power of youth,
or wasn't I aware of it?
Now, it's their time.
Dear, you want something?
Mother, he was sweating
and was feeling hot.
- I came to get water.
- I see.
Stupid girl, keep quite.
[muffled laughter]
[door closing]
[Sandhya] Here, take it.
Did you make me a mix tape?
What?
[mantra chanting]
[Sandhya] I've kept spices on top,
sugar-tea at the bottom.
Where is my rice husk box?
I threw it away, aunty.
It had expired!
You threw it away?
Had bought it two months back
and you threw it?
Aunty, we shouldn't use expired items.
It's not good for health.
Don't brag about qualification.
- I know what expiry means.
- I did that for you, aunty.
Why are you so mean to me?
[Naintara] What did I do?
[indistinct argument]
If you're so interested to die,
please go ahead and eat it all.
How dare you argue with me, girl?
I'll talk to you later.
What about you saying things to me?
You're making a mountain
out of a mole hill.
You should thank me.
Had I not been here,
Prem would've never married
a fatso like you.
Oh really! Because your Prem
is a superstar himself?
[Sandhya] Should have taught him
how to behave with a newly wedded bride.
Are you listening, sister?
We also got married,
ran a household,
but never raised our voice
- in front of elders.
- It's evident, aunty,
- the household you ran!
- Enough! At least respect her age.
No one cares about me,
everyone cares about themselves.
- What's this commotion?
- Ask aunty.
Where are you off to?
Say you're putting clothes in almirah.
Why did you marry me?
I am getting late for work.
Take out my clothes. I'll take bath.
"Getting late, take out my clothes."
Go to hell!
["Woh meree neend" playing]
[music stops]
[cassete sound]
["Abhi zinda hoon" playing]
[music stops]
["Bin saajan jhula" playing]
["Samjhauta ghamon Se" playing]
[music stops]
["Kagaz kalam dawaat" playing]
Stop it.
- [whispering] Why have they come?
- Did you call them?
- Hello!
- Hello.
How come you, Raghu?
This is for you.
What is this?
- Sweets!
- And this...
Invite!
- Wedding invite?
- Yes.
- His wedding?
- Yes!
Oh my!
Blessings!
Listen, everyone! Prem,
He chose a girl in college.
Is this being taught in engineering?
No, no. The girl is a dentist.
Poor Prem was ruined by English.
Otherwise, he would have...
What are you blabbering?
Please call our daughter-in-law.
She is working inside.
Why're you calling her?
[Sandhya] Yes, father?
Hello, sister-in-law.
That day I called out,
but you didn't listen to me.
He just vanished with you.
You have to come.
Both of you, for sure.
- Ok, will come.
- What, ok?
Sister-in-law, he'll not listen to me,
he'll just listen to you.
You have to drag him to my place.
- It's your responsibility.
- Have tea.
Please have tea.
It's getting cold.
[Nirmal's father] You too.
[Chandrabhan] What's the point now?
[wedding music]
[Nirmal] Told Dipti's father
that at least 500 guests will be there
from our side.
Park will not do.
Arrange community centre.
Told her uncle
that we need 21 gun's salute.
They both agreed!
This is a gift from them!
Made in Japan. Very nice!
Very good sound!
- [Nirmal] Shakha sir!
- Hmm.
[Nirmal] Request a song.
Play any, son!
Tell the number and it'll play.
See, I'm old school,
a fossil, really.
This guy Prem is new to marriage,
so ask him.
Even I want to venture, Shakha sir.
The girl's father is playing a villian.
Shakha sir says marriage serves
no purpose.
Isn't it, Shakha sir?
No point thinking
after entering lion's den.
Dipti is not a lion,
Dipti is a lioness. Right?
Show Prem your lioness's picture.
Shall I show him the picture?
Prem.
She is looking so pretty
in such a small picture.
Pretty, isn't she?
Leave this, you tell!
How's it going with you?
You can see it.
[people singing and dancing]
Prem, you have had enough.
- Sister-in-law will get upset.
- To hell with her.
Prem, control yourself.
Give me the glass.
I respect you, Shakha sir.
Your word is gospel's truth
But today, don't say a word.
Leave it!
Leave me. Don't touch me.
My father has ruined my life.
I am totally ruined.
Few friends like you, left me alone.
Lower your voice!
- It's Nirmal's wedding.
- Hats off to you, Nirmal. You are set.
You worked hard, studied hard
and became a gentleman.
I am the opposite of it.
I'm a failure. You fiancee is so pretty.
Your life would be heaven,
trust me on this.
I had no clue what was going on.
Couldn't say yes or no.
Dad had put a leash on me
and now I'm just a dog,
going here and there.
- Oh, Prem!
- Prem.
[wedding music playing]
Sister-in-law is good-natured.
Looks are not everything.
Why shouldn't it be so?
Why is he showing me Dipti's picture?
Why do you circle around Sonu, tell me!
- Because you're my brother!
- Leave, it, dude.
She's such a fat cow.
Don't feel like touching her.
Leave alone doing anything else.
- Shut up!
- I should shut up?
Vijay, if you had to sleep in my place
with Sandhya for a night,
that's when it'll feel like hell.
[dramatic music]
[door closing]
So you've started drinking now!
- Oh, brother stop!
- [Prem] Aunty, save me.
- Stop it!
- Tried explaining to him so many times.
I'll kill him. You move aside.
Oh, brother, what are you doing?
I'm hurt!
I hit my younger sister, see!
It's all because of you.
I'll not leave you.
[all in chaos]
Dear, where're you going?
We can sort it out.
Look, how his father is hitting him.
- Stop him.
- He's his father, he knows well.
- Listen!
- What happened? Where is she going?
Wait! Listen to me.
Take this slipper
and go, hit him.
Leave it, father!
I'm not angry with Prem, but you!
Helping him in studies
instead of marriage would have helped.
Wait please!
[Sashi] Wait up!
[marriage band playing]
[throwing books]
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
At least tell us!
- Why are you throwing stuff?
- Why did you give my room to Samar?
You didn't intimate us about your coming.
I've left Prem.
Now stop asking questions.
Left him? What do you mean?
At least ask her, what happened?
What nonsense is this!
Did he hit you?
- Then I'll teach him a lesson.
- Why are you dragging me?
All my books are already destroyed.
Now I'll not get full marks in biology.
Dare you come into my room again,
I'll do the same to you as those books.
Don't stand here,
go and call them from a PCO.
Ask what happened?
Nobody will call them.
I promise I'll kill myself.
What is this behavior?
Tell us what happened,
why have you come here?
He doesn't need me
and neither do I, mother.
He wanted to get married, right?
But he has no manners.
He embarrassed me in front of everyone.
He called me fat and other names, mother.
- So, what's wrong in that? You're fat!
- You shut up!
[Madanpal] Move!
Why bother listening to men?
Men say darnest things in anger, so...
[Subadhra] Why do you
compete with him?
Even if he said something,
you should've ignored.
You should've kept quite.
Why should I stay quite?
I slapped him hard.
Now he'll not dare to speak
to a woman like that.
Oh dear lord!
Educate her and make her upstanding!
- She has destroyed her household.
- Mother, stop crying.
I'm ok!
I'm just the same, as I went from here.
Behave yourself.
You're talking nonsense
in front of your father.
Teach her something.
[Subadhra] See, child!
- A woman has to...
- Enough, mom.
- That's what gives meaning to...
- That's enough, mom. Now go.
You're not listening...
[door closing]
A woman's life
is governed by a man, dear.
[poem reciting]
- [clapping]
- [Shakha] Enough!
[Shakha] We've limited time
and the job is very difficult.
We've to make it easy.
- [everyone] Absolutely.
- Saying "Absolutely"
- won't help us achieve the target.
- [all] Absolutely.
[Shakha] Ok,
in "Give in all your energy" competition,
along with power,
use your brain as well.
[Shakha] How?
Like this! Joshi ji...
[clapping]
That's it!
Like this, you achieve your target.
Now, Joshi ji, please get down.
Now start the exercise.
What happened, Shakha sir?
You're ignoring me.
No, son, nothing like that.
"Give in all your energy" competition
is coming up.
So, preparing for that.
You didn't invite me to exercise!
You know what all happened, right?
- Had I called you...
- Yes, right.
You teach about revolt,
- but you suck Nirmal's feet.
- Prem!
Don't misbehave.
Otherwise you"ll be in trouble.
Misbehave? Since my wife left,
nobody is talking to me.
Cool down, now.
- Let's sit and talk.
- Not interested! I've thought it through.
Everyone is gloating in my misery.
What nonsense are you saying?
Let's move aside!
- Leave my hand, I'll hit you.
- You'll hit me?
You scoundrel!
You tease me by showing picture
of your pretty wife?
- Don't mention my wife!
- I will throw you in the pond.
- [Shakha] Quite!
- How's he talking? Is this the way?
- Go now.
- [Vijay] He's upset. I'll take care.
Enough, I've had enough.
We don't need people like him here.
- [Vijay] I'll explain to him.
- Take him away.
Take him from here, go.
Take him away.
[Shakha] Tell him to cool down.
It's too much.
[Shakha] Wants to revolt it seems.
[Lawyer] Aunty, you don't worry,
These days, law is with women.
You should believe in yourself
and believe in the power of women.
There're so many amendments
that favour women these days.
Sandhya's case is very strong.
So, they'll be together?
- She's talking about separating them.
- Then why is she smiling?
You want her to cry and say that?
- [Sandhya] Water.
- Thank you.
- Move.
- Ok.
[Lawyer] Sandhya, did you change
your last name, in passport
or in any other papers?
No.
Did you give any dowry?
Any TV, VCR,
sofa set, scooter, anything?
Whom to give TV?
She's asking if we have given dowry.
- I'm talking!
- Ok, do then.
No, we didn't.
We may have spent about
15-20 thousand
on clothes and jewellery.
We didn't spend a single penny.
Her jewellery is already
with her mother.
It's safe in my bank locker.
Wait a minute.
What about mental trauma?
Who'll pay for that?
Sandhya, that's no way
to talk to your parents.
They want your good as well. Say sorry!
Don't instigate her.
We've given her good education as well.
[Lawyer] Ahh, sorry?
She asking her to say sorry.
Say sorry to whom?
To you.
Sandhya, don't loose heart, ok?
Just concentrate on your studies
and give exams.
Thanks a lot, sister.
Aunty, you also don't worry.
Divorce and all is very cool these days.
This is just a way
to spend your life happily.
Madam, we know nothing about law,
but this much I know for sure that
I've lived my life happily with him.
I'm sure!
Please come!
Yes.
- Keep it inside.
- Will do.
Are you drunk?
Don't be stupid.
Go and get her back.
No way!
I don't want to live like this.
I'll try and make something for myself.
Oh, hello!
Is this a movie dialogue?
It looks good in movies only.
People like us
should stay connected to reality.
I'll reappear for my 10th standard exam.
I'll not stay with these people.
Are you crazy?
You're a married person.
Wife is a teacher
and he wants to be a student.
Look at me!
Would I not like to go to Mumbai?
I would want to be an actor.
But my father refused and
made me sit here in the shop.
Now, my only dream is
that Suman's father
agrees for our marriage, that's it.
But you love Suman.
If her father gets her married
elsewhere, will you not do anything?
Prem, reel and real life are different.
Do you know the reality of my life?
See this.
"Ma'am, 36 B."
"Ma'am, 36 D."
"Elastic is good and long-lasting."
Rascal, you too are against me.
I was ok alone here.
[Vijay] Fine, do as you please.
- Saraswati Coaching Centre?
- [Man] Yes, come in.
I wanted a form for 10th grade board exam.
- Have you brought ID proof?
- Yes.
[cookery show in TV]
She's going to feed us boiled food.
Why're you interrupting? Let me see!
To treat herself,
she'll make us all sick.
Have I stopped you?
[Sandhya] Make whatever you like.
I'm making for myself only.
This was left now. Ending your marriage,
you've come home
now wants to have a separate kitchen.
- Now what are you making?
- Poison.
You want some?
No, you can have it.
Father!
A new shop has come up?
Who is it?
This is the address.
- This is Nirmal's shop address.
- Let's see.
Nirmal has opened a shop?
[Chandra Prakash] Two recording
shops in the same location?
Listen, is this Nirmal Nautyal's shop?
It was rented out last week.
Meaning, new shop has opened?
Have done rituals now.
Will open on the 1st of next month.
Here we go!
MELODY MUSIC CENTRE
[Chandabhan] Nirmal, if you open a
recording shop, what'll happen to us?
See, son, you have everything.
That's right.
You even have a wife!
You know how he behaved at Shakha?
I didn't want to come here after that.
- Father insisted me to...
- Nirmal, cool down.
- Cool down!
- Look at you, all cool!
You didn't waste time
opening the new shop.
Look at him, he is disgusted in life.
What shall we say!
It was bound to happen for sure.
Without his consent,
you all forced him to marry.
[Nirmal] A fat cow that too.
- How can a goat and cow be together?
- Shut your mouth!
See, look at his behaviour.
- How is he behaving?
- Listen, son!
Naina, why can't you keep quite?
- [Naintara] What did I say?
- What, what.
See, son,
this shop is our livelihood.
Look Chandrabhan, whatever it is,
we can't leave our household
and start a charity, right?
You must be very happy, uncle.
Adding insult to injury.
You're jealous of other's progress.
I can see that.
Progress, what progress
are you talking about?
You became an engineer
because of the donation.
Then you do the same.
No one is stopping you.
Have we tied your hands?
Is your mind chained?
Look, Prem, only a thing does
not cost a dime - crying!
You can keep on doing that.
I'm talking nicely and you're taunting.
I'll kill you!
What're you doing?
Fight afterwards, have pastry first.
It's her birthday, show some respect.
[everybody] Happy Birthday!
Let's sit there.
- Wish you a happy birthday.
- Ok!
Happy Birthday!
Want to save your shop? Fine.
Save it.
"Give in all your energy" competition
is coming, take part and win it.
If you win, will not give the shop
on rent and you'll save your shop.
[Nirmal's father] Nirmal, what is this?
[Naintara] This is too much.
I'm right, now you say.
You are despicable!
You want to start a shop?
Ok, go ahead, open it.
We've been in business for 15 years.
[muffled] Will see.
Listen!
Had I been married,
I would've taken part
in the competition.
I'm telling the truth.
[Sashi] Naina, shut up!
I have heard enough from father-son.
Listen, you'll participate
in the competition.
Mother, I will not!
Your husband will run with you.
You'll run with your wife!
You'll say whatever on your birthday?
I have decided.
He'll participate.
- Mother, I'll not.
- You'll run.
Mother has lost it!
As if we've not been humiliated enough
in the market.
- [utensil falling]
- What happened?
What is the matter?
- Why are you lying down here?
- Father, she has fallen down.
[chaos]
What happened?
Sister!
These are divorce papers.
There goes the condition for the
competition invalid.
Understood. Pick her up.
Come on. Pick her.
Understood. Will do whatever you want.
- Once judge leaves, then don't say.
- Before the judge goes...
- Let's go, Jugnu. Are you ready?
- Yes, father.
What's the matter?
I'll sit in the front.
- [Naina] Brother, help.
- [Sashi] Will you do something?
What should I do?
[indistinct chatter]
[Sashi] Push me, help me sit.
Seems the Tiwari clan is going to
get the bride back.
Seems you can't pass stool without
calling us out, brother.
[Sashi] Drive carefully, ok?
This house is inauspicious.
It hasn't been good to anyone here.
Your sister's husband became a sage.
Parveen's husband is still in jail.
Underwear guy, Vijay
is not getting married.
Prem's marriage has ended in court.
Now, chant in the name of your mother,
not in the name of God.
She keeps talking nonsense even now.
Did I say something wrong?
There'll be lots of crying. Stay calm.
It's better to cry once and for all.
I'm very proud of you, Sandhya.
Is everyone here getting divorced?
[indistinct chatter]
Please, don't talk nonsense.
Listen, Sandhya, tell me.
Anything else I should know?
- [indistinct chatter]
- Listen to me carefully,
No need to beg in front of Sandhya.
Papa will carry you and run.
[indistinct chatter]
- Hello.
[Subadhra] Why is God punishing us?
What to do?
[Sashi] What has happened, sister?
Why're you crying?
We've been given a bad name.
I pray that even the worst
enemy should not face this fate.
Look, what has happened?
What have the kids done?
[crying continuously]
[Man] Sandhya Verma
and Prem Prakash Tiwari, Divorce Petition.
Husband, Prem Prakash Tiwari is accused
of insulting Sandhya Varma in public.
Hurting her physically and emotionally.
Sandhya Varma asks the court
to grant her divorce.
The Tiwaris must pay a
divorce settlement of 50,000 rupees.
[Judge] She has filed for divorce.
Do you agree?
Yes.
Was it a love marriage?
There is no love, only marriage.
Why did you agree then?
I liked him.
And you?
We were financially strapped,
Sandhya was doing B.Ed.
Everyone pressed marrying her would
improve our financial condition.
I agreed!
[Judge] Relations, consummation,
physical relations etc...
These household matters
are not to be discussed in court.
But want to disgrace his wife before all?
- I...
- Hitting her
- is a matter of great pride?
- I'm sorry for that.
I can't move out of my house now.
Yeah, we live in a jungle.
We've no neighbours. What?
And what's this ridiculous
settlement demand of 50,000?
- Aren't we suffering enough?
- Have you ever thought about me?
- Did you think before slapping me?
- [Sashi] Prem.
[Judge] Order! Order!
[Judge] Keep quiet.
Family members want to say anything?
What can we say?
You are wise enough.
Please, tell them.
Utensils will surely will make sound.
Why leave the house, daughter?
Come back!
This is correct, Sir.
Prem's father and I fought too many times.
Once I put a little more salt
in his mother's food.
And he hit me so hard with his shoes.
- But I didn't leave my home.
- Am I talking Greek?
Your honour, I am asking her to come home.
Ok, you men will only talk!
- You just order us to cook and clean.
- Yes, mother, this is the right time.
File a case of domestic violence.
[Judge] Order, order.
Listen, these emotional talks should
be discussed outside the court.
As per the marriage law, court will
ask you to stay together for 6 months.
And if even after that,
you're unable to sort things out,
the court will approve the divorce.
[Judge] Next!
See, it has been enough!
Now, come back.
Everyone is requesting you.
Go now, I'll get my room back.
Sandhya, if not for the law,
come back for us at least.
- First ask him to say sorry.
- Hey, come here.
Who slapped first, shall say sorry first.
Ok, and who forced me?
You'll say sorry first.
I'm saying it.
Sorry!
[laughing]
See Sandhya, now she's your
real mother, ok?
She is your responsibility, ok?
Here, hold this!
Please come, daughter!
The moment you held it,
I'm feeling better already.
[Announcer] It's time to carry the weight
of your relations on your shoulders.
'Because the pride of Hrishikesh
and Haridwar is back again.
All husbands! Flex your muscles.
All wives, lose some belly weight.
Because, "Give in all your energy"
competition is back.
Attention, friends.
The winner gets 10,000 rupees, cash.
It's direct telecast
will be shown on cable TV, friends.
Friends, keep in mind.
"Give in all your energy" competition.
Shall I say something?
- Yes.
- See.
It's not "of" Monday.
It's "on" Monday
And we say "in" August.
Not "on" August
Usage of preposition for day and
month is different.
- Why did you touch my book?
- But I was...
But why? Don't show off your education.
Ok. I know you're very smart, intelligent.
I know nothing.
I'm a fool and illiterate fellow.
This isn't going to work.
Look, it's an act for 6 months.
So, the happier we are,
better for both of us.
I'll go in 6 months,
"In" and not "on". Understand?
[humming music in background]
Give all these sheets in room 12.
I'm a student.
Roll no. 317.
- Sit down.
- Thanks.
[Prem] Respected teacher,
I'm 25 years old.
This is my third failed attempt
to clear the English exam.
My father is right. I am a useless fellow.
The struggle to do something,
to prove myself worthy, ends here.
If you have a kind heart,
and if this letter makes emotional,
and your eyes get filled with tears.
And if nothing else
but you wish to tear away this paper.
If you feel like giving a big zero.
Just remember this please,
today a family has turned zero.
[sad music in the background]
Today, I accept my failure...
towards my family...
towards my wife...
and towards myself.
Sincerely, Prem Prakash.
[indistinct chatter]
Why're you standing their sullen faced?
Go wash up and come.
Bride has made food. Go.
We'll eat together.
- [Sashi] Come. come.
- I am not hungry.
How come you are not hungry?
We've been waiting.
Your father closed the shop early today.
What happened?
Have you eaten already?
What happened? Go, wash up.
He's coming.
- Yes, give it.
- I'll say one thing.
- I like boiled veggies.
- You're right.
Spices don't help,
they just boil our blood.
[Sashi] Bride has taught us
such a wonderful dish today.
- [Naintara] What's that?
- Dal soup!
- Looks nice, right!
- [Sandhya] Mother, forgot to put caraway.
[Sandhya] Father, I shall put it tomorrow.
Will taste even better.
- It's fine!
- Take some more, please.
Take it!
Here.
Boy, you leave the cheese.
Have the green gourd.
- Cheese, she'll have.
- No, no, father,
Please give it to him.
We make it often at my house.
You please have.
You know, what I'm thinking, daughter?
Prem, you also listen.
You both should participate
in "Give in all your energy" competition.
- Correct!
- No, no, father.
I'll feel embarrassed, father,
and it'll look funny too.
[Sashi] What funny!
Your father took part, four times with me.
Four times?
Yes. But we never won.
That's a different thing.
[laughing]
This time, Prem is keen
to take part in the competition.
Isn't it, son?
Of course, mother.
I brought her back
for this competition only. Isn't it?
This guy is good at crack jokes only!
[vessels clanking]
Did you see?
You could've had your food peacefully.
What would it matter?
I can't put up an act.
You all are worldy-wise.
So you know me by now?
I know nothing of the house,
nothing of the world.
You think I'm a troublemaker?
Lets go out!
What are you doing? Stop it!
This is family's love. Lies everywhere!
- Here they're feasting.
- [indistinct]
- We were hungry!
- It's my mistake.
I planned to bring her here.
She'll take part in the competition,
save the shop and earn as well.
And all abuses are for me!
Let me finish myself.
- [Naina] Are you crazy?
- [Chabdrabhan] What're you doing?
- I want to kill myself.
- [Sashi] What're you doing?
[chaos and indistinct chatter]
She is acting, she doesn't
love anybody here.
- Where's match box?
- [Sashi] What're you doing?
Sandhya, you do whatever,
do exercise, lose weight.
Nothing will work. If someone has to fall
in love with you, it will happen.
[Prem] Rest all is a show.
Set me on fire and have direct telecast
of me committing suicide.
- Where is the match box?
- [Man] Prem Prakash Tiwari? Roll no 317.
[Man] Prem Prakash Tiwari, Roll no 317?
- What happened?
- What hasn't happened?
Writing the English paper in Hindi.
Prem Prakash was
planning to commit suicide.
Suicide?
Oh, no, no. All is well.
[sad music in the background]
[sobbing]
[sniffling]
Had the match been lit,
would you really set yourself ablaze?
Did you really love me a lot?
When did you give me a chance?
Neither to tell.
Nor to show.
I don't deserve to be loved by anyone.
What do do?
You know...
I was very eager to get married.
But no one told me.
What actually getting married is?
And did anyone tell me?
They told all wrong things.
Do take care next time.
If you plan to get married again,
will you invite me?
Who'll marry me?
I'll find a boy for you.
One who would respect you.
Who would take care of you.
That's what I thought after meeting you.
Really?
[soft music]
Ok, it's all right.
I'll find a girl for you with whom
you'll be happy to go to the market.
One who doesn't show off her education.
Where will I find a girl like this?
Yeah, as if boys are lining up for me!
[soft music]
[laughing sound]
Father, get the shop valued.
You go ahead and do it,
you wanted to listen to songs.
- Mother, aunty, I shall take your leave.
- Ok, daughter.
- Father, I'm going.
- Stay happy!
Listen, I'll come with you.
You see all this?
That's why everyone want you back.
To get their things done.
One needs a lot of
coordination for this game.
You are right.
We are far from coordination.
It's ok, fine!
Listen!
Best of luck!
Thank you.
[Prem] Bro, take me home.
- Hello.
- [Woman] Sit down, please.
- Sandhya Varma.
- Yes.
- [Man] Show me your papers.
- Yes, Sir.
I can't find my file.
I have brought it, though.
You've come for an interview
and have forgotten your file?
I don't know where it is?
I had brought it.
You ought to bring your file.
[indistinct chatter]
Hello everyone.
Sandhya, you had left it in the rickshaw.
The papers are intact?
[Woman] Who is he?
He's my husband.
He... your husband?
Yes. Here are the papers.
[Man] Your papers are ok.
- [Woman] So, you have seen it?
- Yes,
Sandhya, we don't have a vacancy here.
But we have a vacancy in Meerut.
If your family lets you shift there...
- You can join there.
- Ok.
I'm ok and I'll make agree.
You please don't worry.
- [Woman] You think so?
- Yes, absolutely.
[background sound of vehicle and song]
- 12 feet.
- 12 feet!
This shop is no good. Do something, bro.
[Man] I've been telling you for so long
and you are deciding today.
He's saying now, rent out this shop.
- Blessings. Get an answer quickly.
- Ok
[background song playing]
[loading of cassette]
[music playing]
I have filled in your songs.
Cassette is lying there.
Listen to it later.
[door closing]
- Thank you.
- [Prem] It's ok.
Interview's result has come?
No.
You'll surely get the job.
How do you know?
I... just know.
- May I say something?
- Yes.
Whenever you feel you can move out.
No one will stop you.
There's nothing but ill-fate here.
There's no point wasting you time here.
- You think about your future. Ok?
- Hmm.
All will be good.
I have got the job...
...in Meerut.
You've decided to go to Meerut?
Who is there for me here...
...for whom I should stay on?
There aren't
many buses to Meerut from here.
If one really wants, one can
change 2-3 buses to visit.
Have you stayed alone before?
No.
But I have never left
anyone before as well.
[phone ringing]
- Hello!
- [Man] Hello.
[Man] Sister, It's me,
Sidhesh, Rameshwar's brother.
Yes. Speak up, Sidhesh.
How come you have called
your sister-in-law after so long?
[Sidhesh] Sister-in-law, you!
Sorry, couldn't recognize your voice.
I have bad news.
Rameshwar brother is no more.
He had gone on pilgrimage to Amarnath,
and died in landslide.
For me, he had died 15 years ago.
Sister, would've been nice had
you come one last time.
What relation do I have
with your family, tell me?
In so many years, did you even
come to find out about my well-being?
Sister, I thought at least
I should inform you so...
Who was it, what happened?
Sidhesh had called.
What was he saying?
Your sister is a widow now.
As if he had left me, married!
[sobbing]
Hello, uncle.
Where is Prem?
Aren't you participating in the race?
Son, you participate in our funeral, ok.
What happened?
[Sashi] It's ok, stop crying, dear.
- [knocking at the door]
- [Naina]Son, shall I come?
Yes aunty, it's open. Come in.
[door opening]
Vijay was here. He was asking
to take part in the competition.
Your father drove him away.
[sniffling]
Son, I never got a chance like this.
Never got a chance to be somebody's wife,
or settle down in life.
Just spent my whole life like this.
Till the time both of you are together,
make some memories, that's all!
Aunty, you know,
no one is going from our house.
Then what's the point of all this?
Everybody did what suited the point.
What did we achieve?
Did we get anything?
Try and do something without a point
just for each other.
Aunty, there's no point forcing anything.
If someone doesn't want to do it...
Do you want to do it?
When you don't want to take part
then what's the point in asking me?
As if we've not been embarrassed
enough before?
We have lost everything, Sandhya,
there's nothing left to be embarrassed.
Prem, if nothing is left,
at least do what your heart desires.
Won't be able to lift me?
What are you saying?
What do you think I did at Shakha?
Ok, then, shall I tell sister
to call Jaya and Hema?
Yes, ok.
[piano music in background]
[conch blowing]
GIVE IN ALL YOUR ENERGY COMPETITION
[clapping]
I'll just be back.
Hello, uncle, greetings!
- You've come?
- Hello, sis-in-law, hello, aunty.
Come here. I have got you registered.
[announcement in the back]
- Daughter, take care, it's up to you now.
- You ok?
Father.
Here. Win and come back!
Don't pressurize, mother.
- We're participating, that's enough.
- Why do you always give up. Let's go.
[indistinct chatter]
[announcement in the background]
[Shakha] Careful, don't pull your veins.
- You'll not able to run.
- Here he is!
[Nirmal] Let him come.
Prem, will you be able to lift your wife?
Or you'll need uncle's help,
Isn't it, Shakha sir?
[mocking laugh]
- What are you doing here?
- I don't give a damn!
To hell with her father
and my father too.
Got married in Shiv temple this morning.
That's great news. Congrats!
To you too!
[Announcer] Ladies and Gentlemen.
Time has finally come, to take on your
relationships onto yourself.
Let's see who completes this journey.
[Announcer] I t has obstacles
and hurdles also.
Let's see, who puts in all energy
and reaches the finish line
and claims the prize money of Rs.10,000.
Friends, to inaugurate this competition,
we have with us, our favourite,
voice of all of us,
the famous...
[singer humming]
[humming continues]
[clapping sound]
- [humming stops]
- [clapping]
Now, I would request Mr. Kumar Sanu
to ring this bell and start this race.
[Announcer] One... Two...
Three. [bell rings]
[Commentator] As the sun rises,
the heat of the competition
shall increase as well!
Nirmal Nautyal and Dipti Nautyal
have left everyone behind
and racing with great speed.
[Commentator] Prem Prakash Tiwari's feet
is still fixed to the ground!
Run! Prem Prakash Tiwari! Run!
[crowd cheering]
[fast music in the background]
[background song]
Be careful.
Put both the feet in one tyre
and then on the next.
- Is it so easy? Do yourself and see.
- Really?
Hold tight.
- Get along on the way.
- Now, take care of your Chetak!
Prem Prakash Tiwari and Sandhya Varma...
Slowly and steadily
they are marching ahead...
...and they are
leaving behind all the participants.
You two are looking amazing!
Even you too.
Why are you getting involved again?
You will never listen.
[Commentator] It is rightly said,
It is a very difficult journey.
[background song]
Be careful.
Will you be able to do it?
Don't you see? I am doing.
- Hold tight. Don't leave.
- I am holding tight. You, look ahead.
- What's wrong?
- It tickles.
- Okay, now?
- Yes, yes.
Are you okay?
Dipti... Dipti... Dipti
- Come here.
- I am hurt.
Hurry up. Have you gone mad? Hurry up.
What are you doing?
[laughing]
Hey! What happened?
- What happened? Why are you laughing?
- Look at your face!
As if you are looking so beautiful.
[crowd cheering]
[background song continues]
I don't want to go back.
Please, stop me!
This is the final result of this year's
"Give in all your energy competition."
Prem Prakash Tiwari and Sandhya Verma
are the...
Seems like they haven't had their fill.
Someone please go and tell them that
they have already won the competition.
["Ye moh-moh ke dhaage" playing]
[Prem] Oh, yes!
Now I am not worried about my tears.
But now there's someone
whose tears I can't bear to see.
Sandhya!
Let's hear a song.
Composed by Anu Malik.
Lyrics by Varun Grover.
And sung by Sadhna Sargam and Kumar Sanu.
[background song playing]
You are my language of love
I write you a little everyday
Blank pages, on which, helpless
I write this revelation
When I met you
There was a crisp pain in the heart
Only the one who was killed by love
Began to live
When I met you
There was a crisp pain in the heart
Only the one who was killed by love
Began to live
You are my language of love
I write you a little everyday
Blank pages, on which, helpless
I write this revelation
When I met you
There was a crisp pain in the heart
Only the one who was killed by love
Began to live
When I met you
There was a crisp pain in the heart
Only the one who was killed by love
Began to live
Just now, there was sunshine here
Now see it's raining here
The pockets are empty
We'll manage with the coins of love
Sometimes I have asked the mirror
Who beautified me
Sometimes I look like an enchantress
Sometimes I look like the moonlight
Sometimes like a shining star...
However much we control ourselves
And walk carefully
The heart is a vagrant insolent
When I met you
There was a crisp pain in the heart
Only the one who was killed by love
Began to live
When I met you
There was a crisp pain in the heart
Only the one who was killed by love
Began to live