SILLINESS
This isn't done, sir.
You guaranteed you'd teach me in a week!
I'll be promoted today,
so life will be moving forward...
- I can't even reverse the car!
- Relax, I'll make you an expert.
See this watch?
A gift from my student.
The watch is local, but not my student.
It's a reward for being a teacher.
Don't you forget.
Come on now, try once more.
Why are you wasting time
on teaching manual gears
when mine's gonna be an automatic one?
You'll be able to drive any car
in the world if you can learn this.
Today you have an automatic car,
later, you might not afford a bicycle.
Must you utter such evil words?
My promotion is due. Say something nice.
Listen, mister!
If I receive my teacher's reward today
you will get your promotion too.
I'll never reach the office if it goes on
like this. Forget promotion, car and...
- Got a girlfriend?
- Does it matter?
What's her name again?
Mayera.
Start the car.
Now focus on her face
and leave the clutch with ease.
Mayera!
- Yeah, baby! Mayera!
- See the magic of love?
Hey jigida jigida
Hey hey jigida jigida
Someone tell the stars
not to bend so much
The sun lights my nights like a candle
Impatient goals knock at my door
with such eagerness
The lines of my palm
change with my will
I've been given a blank sheet in my hand
My days will be the way I write them!
What is to fear
when God is a childhood friend?
I am the master of my will
Hey! jigida jigida
Hi, hotness! Is it new?
From Zara. You like?
Very hot. Shall I gobble you up?
See you at lunch.
Your promotion is due today,
so eat in your cubicle, okay?
Look extra busy, okay? Bye, bye, bye, bye!
Mornings come at my will
The moon revolves around my roof-top
what is ours is yours
and yours is ours.
Our horizontals and your verticals
got integrated
by forward planning
and long-term thinking.
I've an account at the shop of wishes
Even destiny is designed
to fit my desires
Like balls of wool
My ways unfold below my feet
If my destination is out of the world
It will come to me running for sure.
Congratulations, sir.
You made the right decision.
I'll mail you the contract
right away, sir.
I got it! Am I not the coolest?
- Promotion?
- Post-lunch.
Post-lunch.
Those better than me,
Try a hundred schemes
But I'm not afraid of them
If you block my road,
I will try my best
I will move ahead somehow
I will bolt my plans in place
I will turn the spanner strong
Thus, I will secure my victory
no matter what
Far from the sky
Even if you tie me to the ground,
I shall still fly away high
Damn it! What a crappy raise!
What about you?
Pity, they took their sweet time!
If they'd done this a year ago,
productivity would've been doubled by now.
- Guess the credit limit.
- Hmm... two?
Huh! Three!
Mayera, no. Mayera!
You just bought sandals last month.
Shall I gobble you up?
They're a little expensive.
Should I buy?
- When did this happen?
- Today!
And the credit limit?
Four hundred thousand?
And here I'm showing off
my 300,000 gold card.
I didn't want to spoil your excitement.
That's why.
Mayera! You...
Not that, silly!
We've been together for two years.
- Now what?
- What?
Dad is looking for prospects.
That too, multimillionaires.
Very well. I will say yes
to the richest guy.
If I was promoted a year ago
I would've proposed
and saved you already from
your dad, Osama's bombardment.
Anyway, now that I'm a Senior Executive...
So...?
Let me tell dad.
Mention Senior Executive Mohit Chaddha.
Osama will be impressed.
Call my dad "Osama" once more
and I'll mix RDX in your coffee!
- Tell him about my car, okay?
- Okay.
- Tell him that...
- Shush... it's ringing.
- Hi, Dad.
- What happened to the lunch-time call?
I was in an important meeting.
I sent you a message, you never read them?
Should I read my transfer
orders or your messages?
Just a month away from my retirement
and they've transferred me
to bloody Animal Husbandry!
- Animal what?
- Husbandry...
It's under the Ministry of Agriculture.
Isn't there one decent posting in my fate?
I swear I'll resign, today itself.
I'll write such a resignation letter,
it'll shake up the whole government.
Like all your resignation letters that you
wrote after the last six transfers!
Is it? You'll see this time.
I'll do it this time. Just wait and see.
- He's very jumpy right now.
- More than normal?
I know. Poor animals!
You've to come and talk to him
when he'll be in a better mood.
I'm not coming over to talk to him
about marriage and all, okay!
Do it for his sake, man! He's old school.
He'll be happy, we'll be happy.
I love you.
I love you. You just make me
do everything by saying "I love you".
Sir, dictation... now?
We need to vacate
and shift to Animal Husbandry, sir!
No, first dictation.
Gursharan, don't ever
let your son become an IAS.
He's very interested, sir,
and very much into the preparation.
Isn't he just twelve?
But, sir, you have to start early, right?
Wouldn't he face the same hazards?
My son is very bright.
He will definitely reach the top.
And I'm not bright?
What? No! You are bright, sir.
You are shining bright.
You came fifty-eighth in
the All India Entrance Exam, sir.
Only if there was some smartness
to go with the brightness, sir.
You mean, "make me work
by lining my pocket" kind of brightness?
I could've reached the top then, right?
- Lining pockets is wrong, sir.
- Hmm...
That's why I encouraged my daughter
from nursery to take up a private job.
Mayera's salary is more than what
I get after thirty-five years of service.
You just write.
You're just a month
away from your retirement.
You'll lose your pension, sir.
Bear it for month.
What dictation?
Let's move to Animal Husbandry.
I'll come with you.
He won't lose it in front of me.
- Really?
- Really!
Let him just try.
Osama, Obama, I don't care.
What is he? A dinosaur?
Who sets curfews these days, man?
- I'm not afraid of anyone, okay!
- Mayera!
How many times have I told you...
Is anyone talking to you?
No, right?
Who is this?
Mohit Chaddha, Dad. He's my friend!
He'd got you cake and wine
on New Years Eve?
He was here on my birthday too.
He got me those expensive shoes
and you said what kind of
moron gifts shoes on a birthday?
- We even had a fight over it!
- Oh, right, yes.
- Right., Air Connect, Junior Ex...
- It's Senior, Mayera! You...
You?
How dare you speak
so rudely with my daughter?
You... err, ma'am!
- Senior what?
- Excuse me?
Senior peon, senior clerk,
senior typist, senior what?
It's quite late. You must be sleepy.
I've bought a new one, it's automatic.
Would you like to check it out?
It's so cool.
Executive, my foot!
Mayera, I love you, but today is Sunday!
Get up. We're going on a picnic.
- Are you good at frisbee?
- Huh?
- Three two five?
- Three two what?
It's a card game. I'll teach you.
Humayun's Tomb by 10:00, okay?
No way I'm wasting my Sunday on a picnic.
Mohit! Dad's in a good mood.
He's gonna retire after a few days.
God knows how jumpy he'll be then.
Talk to him today if you want to marry me.
Ask for his permission.
- Now?
- Just go!
- Hey, Mohit!
- Yes, sir?
- Help me out here, boy.
- Coming.
- Just fix this.
- Right away.
It's just a frog, not a crocodile.
What a coward he is!
Talk to him about us.
What are you thinking?
Why aren't you doing it?
- Ask, man. What are you doing?
- I can't do it.
- Just do it.
Hey! What are you two up to?
Are you cheating?
No! Not at all.
I'm telling him
to ask for your permission.
Right. I lost the last round too.
Okay, ask away.
Come on. Ask for my permission.
I was saying if you could please let me...
have the third one from below?
Third last, right?
One, two...
- What is it?
- That's an ace, an ace, Mayera!
I'm not playing this game, bloody cheats!
I'm going for a walk, you cheaters.
You just have to ask for his permission.
Can't you do that much?
Humayun's wife got this tomb built.
Shah Jahan got the same
made in white marble
for his wife, ma'am Mumtaz.
Taj Mahal, Agra.
After Taj Mahal there wasn't any
grand tomb made.
Everyone, the architects,
artists, who made the Taj, workers...
Shah Jahan lined them up
took out his sword and whack
cut their hands off.
Dad, Mohit wants to marry me.
- What?
- Didn't you hear me?
What did you say?
Not me, Mohit. Go ahead, Mohit.
Sir, my love will remain
as solid as Humayun's tomb or the Taj.
You're talking about chopping off hands.
I'm asking for her hand in marriage.
Hey, Dad, why are you packing up?
We've not even eaten the dessert.
Dad makes wonderful halva.
Dad?
Please wait, Dad.
Dad, at least answer his question dad.
People elope. We are still
asking for your permission.
You want to marry him? Seriously?
He who talks about eloping?
Criminal-minded.
Don't even think about it!
The Home Secretary is my batchmate.
The Police Commissioner of Delhi
sends me naughty messages.
I can make you rot in jail
for the rest of your life.
Dad!
In the car.
Get the rest from that boy
and check everything.
Come on, Mayera.
No. Say yes first.
Shall we go home and talk, please?
Look, Mayera,
the entire IAS crowd shows up here.
I don't want unnecessary gossip to spread.
So come, please.
Very well.
I will never speak to you again.
- Mayera?
- Let's go, Udhay Singh.
Good girl. I'll solve all your problems.
Don't worry.
Come on.
What is this? Emotional blackmail?
What emotional blackmail?
It's just chicken biryani with saffron.
And then some delicious,
sweet halva, that's all.
You think you'll compensate this way?
With my favorite dishes? Forget it.
All right! You just enjoy the biryani
and forget that bloody loser.
Dad, he's a Senior Executive!
And why does that matter?
- He's not the owner of the company, is he?
- It doesn't matter as long as he loves me.
Love is not the only thing.
Love is everything.
Love is everything?
What would I have done if you
hadn't felt love even after mom's death?
Why did you play mom's role too?
Other IAS dads spent their evenings
at the club with their friends.
But you stayed home to play with me.
There was no money, but I had you.
I had your love.
That was enough for me.
Just like Mohit's love is enough for me.
What more do you need?
Money! You need money.
And I'm saying this from experience.
Look, I had a government job.
I held a big post,
but my pocket was empty.
All my life I have been depriving you.
I could never give you the pocket money,
clothes or toys you deserved.
You wanted to go to the US for an MBA.
I couldn't even afford that.
But now I'll get you married to a rich boy
who can make your every wish come true.
And you'll refuse my biggest wish?
Yes. But Mohit is an absolute no.
Who's asking you to
get married to just anyone?
Here's the file. Select from here.
Each one has a net worth
of 250 million.
Dad, I will only marry Mohit.
Fine. Do what you want.
What do you care if I live or die?
Dad is not ready to listen at all, Mohit.
He's being so stubborn!
Do you know Mohit Chaddha?
From marketing?
How is his character?
He is always seen with one lady.
Always seen, huh?
She comes here too. No scoop, no scandal.
- But why are you inquiring about him?
- Survey. Family planning.
I was just passing by.
Would you like to buy me coffee?
And why? Who are you?
- I'm Sehgal.
- Sehgal, who?
Sehgal from Income Tax.
I've come to file a case on you.
I've filed all my returns.
I'm Mayera's father Sehgal, you bloody...
I'm calling from your office reception.
Sorry, sir. I didn't recognize your voice.
It's the first time on the phone.
Did you have some work here, sir?
What's your salary?
- Sixty-five thousand.
- Sixty-five only!
I'm bad at counting in Hindi.
Just like your salary.
My daughter, Mayera, seventy-two.
Her salary is seventy-two thousand.
What kind of a man are you?
My daughter earns more than you and
you don't care?
Come on, sir.
We both love each other. It's all cool.
Look, Mr. Sixty-five, sit here.
You know that song,
"Let the love never be less
love conquers all the loss?"
It's all nonsense.
I don't know what Mayera sees in you.
Since I don't give my approval
Mayera will not marry you.
You know that, right?
Hmm. Your probation period starts
from today.
I will examine you thoroughly.
If I don't detect any problem in you
I will say yes for the wedding.
But if I find anything wrong,
I'll reject you.
Understand Mr. Sixty-five?
You'll leave quietly then.
How can I agree just like that?
You will take the exam
and give the result as well.
- I don't think I stand a chance.
- Don't you have faith in yourself?
That I have. But then...
- You think I will cheat?
- Who knows?
- It's not written on anybody's face.
- Look, boy...
This is me being polite
to pretend you have a choice.
Actually you have no choice.
Speak up if you're ready to go on
the probation.
Otherwise, forget Mayera forever.
Mayera says you have no family.
Your parents died a long time ago.
Well, at least you'll be saved
from the insult if I reject you.
Goodbye.
Sir, please wait for the coffee at least.
One more thing.
Start taking interest in sports.
Listen, Dad doesn't like losing.
He'll never marry me off to a man
who defeats him.
It's a test. If I can't perform then...
Trust me, Mohit. This win will make you
a loser forever.
Hey, come on.
Poor guy!
The ball has to be picked up like this.
He's very bad at this. You lost in
three straight games.
You lied, right?
I hate lies. Ask Mayera.
Dad hates lies.
Where did you find this guy?
There are at least seven boys in my file
who've played national level
football, badminton, tennis and cricket!
Practise with me every day.
Chances are slim but if there is
some improvement
we will see.
- Sir, tomorrow I have...
- Yes?
He will come, Dad.
Get my kit. I'm going to the locker room.
I'm not gonna leave you no matter what
Dad Osama does!
Oh, really?!
What is it, huh? Staff is calling?
- Please, just come.
- Sir!
Here's a small farewell gift
from all of us.
Oh! You shouldn't have...
It's just a little something, sir.
- Thank you so much!
- Please open it, sir.
Just a minute, sir.
Here it is!
What is this?
You'll have a retired life from tomorrow.
- Isn't it true?
- Huh?
You won't be going out as much.
You won't be as active as you are now.
- So?
- This is for your fitness.
It helped me a lot.
Amazing, isn't it, sir?
Th... th... thank you.
- P... p... p... please stop this.
- Welcome, sir, welcome!
Whatever it is, it is a gift after all.
I've got to arrange something in return.
It's a total of 17 people,
including the peons.
How will you manage for everyone?
Let's get one thing that is of use
to everyone!
These seem expensive.
Can you show us a medium-sized TV?
Sure, sir. This way. Are you looking for
a specific brand, sir?
Something cheap, charming
and long-lasting...
The turbulence in the airline industry
has grounded many...
This is our smallest 22 inch LCD...
Increase the volume, please.
For the last two years, airline companies
have been bearing
the brunt of the unreliable markets.
But Air Connect is the first company that
has ousted 1200 employees at one go.
That's right, 1200!
Starting from the cabin crews,
technical, ground staff
to the marketing unit.
AGITATION OUTSIDE AIR CABINET'S OFFICE
She's not answering her phone.
NO FURTHER INFORMATION ON COMPENSATION
RESIGNATION LETTERS WERE HANDED OUT
WITHOUT NOTICE
Neither is Mohit.
Gursharan, Mohit's job is gone!
- Congratulations, sir.
- Congratulations to you too!
This will be your apartment, sea-facing
on the Dubai Marina.
One of the poshest localities in Dubai.
It is a four BHK. Look at the kitchen.
- What if I say no, sir?
- I'll send you to a mental asylum.
Sir, I'm going to get married.
Well, I didn't on count this. That you'll
refuse this offer to get married.
Sir, we love each other
and we can't stay apart.
Don't you want to see what car
they're offering you?
Your dad is here?
My Dad?
Mayera? Are you feeling okay?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Mohit has lost his job and you're okay?
- Mohit lost his job?
- Didn't you see the news?
If a big company like Air Connect
couldn't save its employees
then what about the smaller ones?
Demands for safe and secure jobs
in the Government are increasing.
Applications for Civil Services
entrance exams have risen by 21%...
In these tough times of recession,
private company jobs are...
When he had a job,
I was willing to compromise.
But I will die
before I let you marry a jobless man.
Hey, Mayera, Immy here.
Mohit, you haven't lost your job,
have you?
Hey... this is Immy!
Be serious.
Honestly, I'm Immy speaking.
Mohit's gone to fight with the boss.
He left his phone behind.
So everything is safe?
Yes, my job is safe, but Mohit's is gone.
I'm so relieved that your job is safe.
I know. But Mohit's really sad.
Even dad was so worried.
He came to my office! He's right here.
Dad, please go home and rest now.
I have to attend a very important meeting.
Dad, Mohit's job is secured.
And he will never lose it.
We will get married
and he will be very successful.
- No... look...
- Bye.
I heard them say...
all the marketing guys are gone.
- Look, I'm sorry about this.
- But I just got promoted!
What can I say, Mohit?
The salary you get after promotion
can save the jobs of three people.
Consider this a sacrifice
for your juniors.
Why don't you sacrifice?
Your salary could save
the jobs of at least eight people.
Playing CEO without knowing
anything about operation.
If it was me running Air Connect
there wouldn't be a loss of a single penny
even in the time of recession.
In fact, I was going to quit myself.
I'll get a job like this.
Double salary. Mark my words.
Mohit, relax. Don't get so agitated.
- What did she say?
- What will she say?
- Say thanks, I saved your job.
- How come?
I got promoted and I got sacked.
It could have been you too.
- Thanks.
- Come on, buy me a beer.
Not beer, but slogans. Stay with everyone.
What if they withdraw the orders?
Why don't you say sorry to the boss?
I've never done that in my life.
To this moron?! Buy me a beer.
Fine, don't say sorry.
But right now all the news channels
are gathered here.
Go for an interview, be famous.
I'll check girls out the whole time.
We want our jobs back.
We're telecasting from outside
the Air Connect offices.
- Give us our jobs back...
- People are really worried
and here with me is Mr. Imran Rizvi.
Mr. Imran Rizvi, how are you feeling?
- Really bad.
- Tell us in detail.
How did you feel when you lost your job?
I haven't lost my job, my job is safe.
Stop. Why are you giving
this interview then?
Because of my friend here.
How are you feeling?
I'm scared.
- He's scared.
- Scared? Of what?
- For Mayera.
- Mayera? Your sister
who'll commit suicide
if she doesn't get married?
Use one shot of his and I'll sue you.
Let's go from here.
What did you say your name was?
- Why were you giving an interview?
- Everyone was.
Is everyone getting married?
Is everyone's father like my dad?
I've convinced him that your job is safe.
If he sees this, he will never agree.
Let him not agree, man!
I'm fed up of his terms and conditions.
There's an economic crisis going on.
My company went bankrupt today.
Mayera, I'm jobless.
And you're worried about the lie
you've told your father!
Mohit, please don't panic.
You're so smart.
You'll get a job immediately.
But one lie will save our relationship.
To hide one lie,
one has to tell a hundred more.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Hello? I'd like to speak to
the Police Commissioner Mr. Khattar.
Me? I'm VK Sehgal!
Secretary to the Government of India.
Now retired.
Hey, Khattar. VK speaking.
How're you doing? Okay, listen.
I have a favor to ask.
I need you to investigate a guy.
Write the name down.
Mohit Chaddha.
Yes, Mohit Chadha.
Murder, rape, robbery, molesting
eve-teasing, rioting,
sending dirty texts
or any other public offense
or criminal activity...
Please report to me.
It's a matter of life and death for me.
Hello.
Yes, sir?
- Where are you?
- At the office.
Whose office?
Sir, my office.
Why are you whispering then?
Sir, I'm in a meeting. Let's talk later?
I'm retired, not jobless.
You think I have nothing better to do?
I'm a busy man, I have no time.
Okay, do one thing.
Give me your PAN card details.
Why do you need my PAN?
Why?
You want to marry my daughter.
I have full right to ask
for your PAN card details.
And if you don't have a PAN card
you have no right to marry my daughter.
Understood?
I'll give you my PAN card details.
I am giving it.
And your passport number, voter ID number
your car registration number
and most importantly,
your Aadhaar Card number.
- I want it all! Got it?
- Yes, sir.
Bring the photocopies of all documents
to the club this evening.
And remember,
without document verification
the marriage is canceled.
Sir, I was a Senior Executive
at Air Connect.
And they fired you.
I'm at least giving you a trainee's
position. You are not even thankful.
Where will you find a position
better than this now?
I will get much better.
Junior Manager, Global Assist,
salary Rs. 50,000.
Sales Manager, Bling Entertainment.
Salary Rs. 40,000.
Assistant Marketing Manager...
Inner Beauty, salary Rs. 85000 to 90,000.
Inner Beauty?
You mean lingerie and underwear?
No, no. I can't sell underwear.
- How much fuel, sir?
- Full.
What's wrong with selling lingerie?
Inner Beauty is offering a higher salary.
And before dad finds out...
I won't take any stupid decision
in fear of Osama.
And come on,
I am not selling bras and panties.
- It's Rs. 2865, sir.
- Here.
You know airlines are my thing.
It's just a matter of time.
I'll get a job. I'm good.
Looking hot! Shall I gobble you up?
Look, I will play two games of squash
with Osama
and let him win both.
Everything will be sorted.
I can handle him.
Sign, please.
We have firecrackers tied to our worries
Our spirits are free as kites
With willful determination
We take on our troubles head-on
We teach all the funsters
The meaning of fun
Our whole world is soaked and spoilt
With notes and coins
Our pockets are filled with good times
Our only wealth, good times
They strut, they shine, good times
They fly in style, good times
Good times, they're flying
just called an hour ago...
Mohit Chadda speaking...
The posters of dreams
Can be seen in the daylight
They are sold in markets
In colorful packets
If they are on sale
We'll even buy the moon and the stars
We make sense out of nonsense
We laugh at our sorrows
We are not alone in this game
The whole world is with us too
Our pockets are filled with good times
Our only wealth, good times
They strut, they shine, good times
They fly in style, good times
Good times, they are flying high
Why think of tomorrow?
Let's seize the day
The unseen days that we know not of
Why should we depend on them?
Not years,
Things happen in moments now
Like noodles, everything is instant.
Happiness is momentary
And comes for a brief period
All you have to do is ask for it
Our pockets are filled with good times
Our only wealth, good times
They strut, they shine, good times
They fly in style, good times
Good times, they fly high.
Mohit's father-in-law is coming.
Just pretend like Mohit still works here.
Okay?
Come on, move!
Move back, you! Hurry.
Come on! Move the car!
Move a little ahead.
- What's going on, man?
- Don't know, man.
What's going on?
Come on, aunt, leave.
Let go of me.
Get to the side.
Move on. What's the fight for?
Will you go?
I'm dead!
People came, people left.
But Mr Mohit stayed put in his seat.
I'm Mohit's best friend, Immy.
- Mohit's cubicle is that way...
- Not that way. Coffee is this way, sir.
Is it a lunch plan, sir?
Son-in-law and father-in-law, together?
The mad... the mad...
the mad son-in-law...
Isn't it funny?
Mohit is with the boss right now.
Why don't you come to my cubicle?
You like Chinese food?
Going somewhere, Mohit?
Or have you come to apologize?
Wasn't it here somewhere?
No, it's there.
Yes, this is it.
- And you're here.
- I am here.
I'll surely recommend
your name for a promotion.
No promotion, thanks.
I'm very happy in my cubicle.
Okay? So, bye.
Very irritating man.
- Let's talk. Come in.
- Sir, over lunch?
Fined three times for driving offenses?
Once for breaking a signal.
You always file your IT returns
after the due date.
Your US visa was refused
after the first attempt.
I'm sure something is wrong with you.
Otherwise one gets it
in the first attempt.
It's a detailed inquiry.
RTO file, IT, police inquiry,
passport office.
So many criminal cases are there.
How can I let my daughter marry you?
Did you do it all by yourself?
Obviously! It's a confidential matter.
What if it gets leaked?
You are so cool, sir!
Excuse me!
How did the government let you go?
It's a rule, retirement at sixty.
It's a damn useless rule, sir.
At sixty a guy comes into his own.
There's a job opening in our company.
GM, Research and Analysis,
age limit is seventy.
- Seventy?
- Salary is 300,000.
Three-hundred thousand per annum?! Good.
You spoke just like a government official.
- Three-hundred thousand rupees per month?
- Yes.
Sir, you are an unutilised resource
of this country.
You are wasting the talent
and knowledge of VK Sehgal.
Sir, guide youngsters like me.
India needs you, sir.
You can win the Padma Shri,
the Padma Vibhushan.
I mean you can definitely
get Bharat Ratna.
You can't get Arjun Award
by playing squash, now.
Yes... I'm not going
to sit idle at home anyway.
I get many job offers.
There's an important task to finish.
I'll think about job after that.
Must be the machine. Try again.
The machine is fine, sir.
The transaction's not being approved.
Let me pay. I have my card.
No, sir, I have cash with me.
No, sir, I don't have cash.
No cash?
Let me pay. Why are you creating a scene?
How much is it?
Two thousand rupees.
I'll withdraw and give it to you.
Two thousand! Here it is.
Who keeps so much cash nowadays?
How can Mayera be the daughter
of this terrorist?
Always ready to drop a bomb!
What?
I don't know, sir!
My credit card and ATM is not working.
What bank is your account in?
So you didn't get the money?
No.
Are you bankrupt?
So funny, sir. What a thing to say!
Bankrupt!
I'm in a hurry right now.
This matter of offenses is pending.
Of course!
I have to return your money too.
Squash at the club, this evening?
Yes, I will pay this month's EMI by check.
Fine! I will give you cash.
I'm telling you I will. Or else what?
You'll take the car away? Then do it!
Nothing much. Just needed some help.
- Here.
- How much is it?
Fifty thousand.
I asked for forty, right?
- Extra ten, pocket money.
- What pocket money?
Am I a kid?
Of course you're a kid!
You used all your money
and you didn't even know?
You should maintain detailed accounts.
I'll check at the end of each month.
What do you mean?
You mean I'm such a big idiot
that I won't find a job for months?
You surely will not
get anything in airlines.
I have mailed you a new job list.
The Inner Beauty position is still open.
If you get the job,
I will get free lingerie.
If I became a waiter,
you'll get free food.
On today's menu
we've plain paratha, plain butter
plain ghee, potato stuffed paratha,
potato butter, potato ghee.
Cauliflower stuffed paratha,
cauliflower butter, cauliflower ghee.
- Today's special is mix veg paratha.
- Shut up, you clown!
I have a meeting. I have to go.
Okay? Bye.
- Mayera?
- What is it?
What if I really become a waiter?
Standing at the cross-roads...
Will you marry a waiter?
When someone asks a question
You won't become a waiter.
You never know.
What if I have to?
Nothing seems real
Even then I'll marry you.
Now I really have to go, okay.
On these crossroads
Except imaginary indifference
Isn't it ironic that the man
who's keen on making you an orphan
you want to marry him?
How wonderful is that?
Please go and change, come on.
Taking out your frustrations on the ball?
I have tried all the companies
on your list.
Looks like I'll have to become a waiter
after all.
Your girlfriend is too good.
I've already made a new list.
Go and change now.
Okay, listen.
What is this "new job" story with dad?
"I'll take on a job too."
He kept on like that.
I've shut him up.
He's worked hard enough
for the last 35 years.
From home to office and back again.
He's worked so hard.
It's his time to relax now.
Is there even a need?
I can take care of him.
Don't allure him with
this 300,000 package.
Okay. Who's going to
hire him anyway?
- Mohit... Hey, Mohit!
- Sir...
I'm ready for a new job.
Mayera will not agree.
Who's going to tell her?
You frighten me all the time,
and now you'll lie yourself?
Nobody is going to lie, you fool.
When I get the job, we'll tell Mayera.
Till then start job hunting for me.
Why should I?
Because it was your idea, you will do it.
No, sir, Mayera has categorically said no.
Okay, then the wedding is canceled.
Hey, Mohit.
Let's send the application
by registered post.
That way you'll never get a job.
Email, sir. Email.
The real problem is that I don't know
how to use a laptop.
It's the same as a computer.
I don't even know how to use computers!
You don't know to use a computer?
No! I don't.
You know how to make chicken biryani?
No, right? Just like that,
I don't know computers.
In that case, I've to search
for layman's jobs for you.
You called me a layman? Fool?
You bloody fool!
- Mayera!
- Where?
Hello?
Yes, actually I'm in a meeting.
Yes, in an interview.
Stop right here.
- Here?
- Yes, yes, stop it.
- The house is ahead...
- You argue too much.
- Sir, but why?
- Again why!
Now, you go jump the wall,
then hide and cross the garden...
Yes hide, and come in
through my bedroom window.
Isn't this ironic?
Romeo hides from Juliet's
father and goes to meet her.
He doesn't hide from Juliet to go
meet her father.
- Does Radha work in Juliet's house?
- No!
Radha'll see Romeo and inform Juliet.
Juliet will ask her father
about why Romeobunked his office
to roam with her father.
- Logical!
- So, do it.
Let me send Radha out for some work.
Then I'll signal you to come inside.
- Radha, Radha!
- Yes, sir.
Come here.
A few of my shirts and pants are lying
outside the cupboard.
Take them to the washerwoman
and get them ironed nicely.
And don't come back till they're all done,
even if takes an hour.
But Shah Rukh's film is on TV...
Hey, don't talk nonsense.
Stay with the washerwoman
till the job is done.
What can I say. I'll miss the film.
There's always so much work here.
- Have you seen it?
- Not yet.
Oh, you haven't?
I'm crazy about Shah Rukh.
But ever since sir retired
he just doesn't let go off the remote.
It's you guys, not us.
Immy's record-breaking relationship...
Two months and still going strong?
Yes!
Just when Mohit lost his job,
Swati came into my life.
What? Will everything be with reference
to my job now?
Bad mood?
Come on, show us your dimples, man.
Smile with your dimples.
I'm on antibiotics.
Do you have flu?
Sir, if my girlfriend
would tell me so lovingly...
What would you do, huh?
Shower in rum and coke?
Go, shower.
Why do you keep ranting
about paying all the time?
I don't want it, that's it!
Is there some compulsion?
Okay, no compulsions. Sorry.
Rock show on 25th and we're both going.
On Rs. 5,000 tickets?
I'll pay. You can return the money
when you find a job!
By then I'll be a bus conductor.
Better if you find someone else.
Then I'll be the bus driver
and will kidnap you and your bus forever.
And what if I become an ice-cream seller?
Then I'll buy the van.
And I'll gobble up all the ice-cream,
and you!
That's my job to gobble up.
What about an auto-rickshaw driver?
Then I'll be the traffic cop.
I'll issue you a ticket
and lock you up in my jail for life.
What if I land up being a postman?
Needlessly, you make and break
Needlessly...
You count each penny
Without any reason
You're afraid of love
You push me away
My love...
Needlessly, you make and break
Needlessly, you count each penny
Needlessly you're afraid of love
Needlessly you push me honey
I'm the heroine of your every story
I'm the happy ending
The moment a storm came
You packed up your things
And left for good from my heart
If I couldn't pay the rent
Of your heart, my dear
You would throw me out anyway
It was a promise for ever after
When the deal was made
When my pockets are empty,
How can I repay the debt I have raised!
I will stake my claim
And take you home
Let me prove my worth
Then only there'll be profit
Needlessly, you make promises of love...
Needlessly, you raise your hopes
Needlessly, you dream crazy girl
Without any reason our story's done
I'm the heroine of your every story
I'm the happy ending
If you were booze,
I'd gulp you down
I'd be the addiction itself
I'd be the cloud,
To stay with you
If you became my sky!
Sweet to the ears...
Not easy to do
To turn yourself into
Someone else's dream
It's not easy to do
Hues pale away
Only love remains...
Everyone else changes
Except red, orange,
yellow, blue and green
Needlessly, counting pennies
Needlessly, being calculative
Without any reason
You are being afraid of love
You are pushing me away
I'm the heroine of your every story
I'm the happy ending
Needlessly...
I'm the heroine of your every story
I'm the happy ending
Of your every tale
Not bad, Mr. Sehgal!
You must've thought of an email ID.
- Vinod Kumar Sehgal.
- No, it's too long.
Wow! So many jobs?
Yes, but around 80% are useless.
What is this now?
It's a game... just...
Move then... move, move.
Start it, please.
Just press 'enter' and click.
Oh! Cool!
I killed the damn guy!
Super cool game, man.
Okay, do one thing.
Let's see how you play!
- Me, sir?
- Play this game.
Tell me something...
You come here every other day
giving excuses as client meeting.
I won't come from tomorrow then.
No, no... l was just asking...
My job shouldn't create
problems for your job.
My job?
There won't be any problem.
Don't worry.
Radha!
Take your coat, come on.
Coming, coming... have patience!
What took you so long, sir?
What were you doing?
We're an insurance company, Mr. Chaddha
and your experience
is in airlines marketing.
- It won't work for us.
- Sir, just give me a chance.
Not just insurance,
I can even market the Qutub Minar!
Qutub Minar!?
It's not that easy, Mr. Chaddha.
It's the era of specialization.
Thank you for coming.
You just give me the job.
I will become a specialist.
You become a specialist,
we'll give you the job.
Please, sir,
I am asking for just one chance.
I was an MBA topper.
I'll prove it to you, sir!
- I'll work really hard, sir!
- Mohit Chaddha!
Are you begging for the job now?
Only six tickets are left.
Should I book tickets for you and Mohit?
Yeah, book them!
You ditched us the last time.
Seven hundred rupees were wasted.
Confirm and tell us, Mayera.
- 18:30 movie?
- I can't come.
Why, what are you doing?
Everyone is going.
Everyone is so worried about my job.
That's why I've come for this interview.
To end everyone's worries.
So I should avoid watching
the movie with everyone
and focus on my interview.
I'm sure everyone will understand.
Mohit, these are your friends.
That's why they're worrying.
There's no need to be so sarcastic.
Anyway, no chance for the 18:30 show,
right?
No chance.
There are around ten, eleven candidates.
The interviews are extensive, in-depth.
In case it gets over earlier...
Damn it! I said there's no chance.
Okay... best of luck.
- Hi, sir.
- Hi.
Mayera is in her room.
Mohit! Mohit.
Did you email my application properly?
There's no reply.
You'll get a response soon.
- Wait one second.
- It's her birthday.
Assault mission game! Cool, huh?
Where did you get this from?
Palika market. Six hundred.
You could have told me.
I could have got you this for half.
Your guy wouldn't even
get the cover for three fifty.
I have a reliable source in Palika.
How do I look?
Super hot! Shall I gobble you up?
What did you get for me?
That's it?
How could I get a gift
with the borrowed money?
It's my birthday!
I wasn't expecting a diamond necklace.
Just a rose would've done.
You have pocket money after all.
Open the door,
or else we'll break it down!
Happy birthday to you!
Open the gift.
Your check bounced again.
The landlord's fuming.
Arrange for the rent today somehow.
Dude, please help me out.
I'll arrange it by next week.
Dude, you haven't
given the last one either.
I need cash badly.
Please return my cash as well.
You know what, forget it.
Just arrange for this month's rent.
And Mohit, bro,
do something about your job.
I'm working on it, I am.
What is it, huh?
You're busy flying high in the air!
Come back to earth, bro,
accept a job in a lower position.
Why should I?
I'm an MBA for God's sake.
Top of my batch.
And who got promoted, you or me?
I was, and because of that
promotion, you still have your job.
Is this how I have to return the favor?
By paying rent?
Maybe you've started enjoying
being unemployed.
You want your money? You'll get it.
Now, just get lost!
I don't have fifteen thousand.
I spent a lot this month.
I got a new dress. There's the party.
Your car EMI, credit card bill,
your phone bill and pocket money...
So, I've to listen to the list now?
If you had told me
about the rent in advance
I wouldn't have
bought the rock show tickets.
Tickets for the rock show?
Did I ask you for that?
I would've sacrificed this too
if I knew it before.
- Sacrifice? Are you insane?
- Yes, sacrifice.
You don't realize at all. I haven't bought
a new pair of sandals these two months.
I gained two kilos with
your pizzas and oily omelets.
I work hard so that I can enjoy my life.
But thanks to you,
leave alone malls and night-clubs
I even forgot
the smell of multiplex popcorn!
It's one rock show that I wanted
to go to and even for that...
Mayera, one rock show!
It's just a rock show!
You should be given a Nobel Prize!
Somebody, please, give her a Nobel Prize.
A half sensible person
would've understood.
Why prize? I'll give you your money back.
Don't stress, I'll settle everything!
Yes, of course! And you're Mother India!
I said I'll return it.
I don't want to sit
in your dirty rotten car!
Get lost, bye. And never sit in it again!
Going somewhere, ma'am?
What do you want? Move ahead!
Hey, rickshaw... rickshaw.
There is a vacancy...
I would like to welcome...
Sir, it's a car not a bicycle.
A latest model.
No dent, no scratch,
hasn't run even a thousand miles.
Your quotation is a shame for me.
Make an offer I can't refuse.
The car is in your garage
as soon as the money is in your pocket!
Or else I can go to Mr. Bhalla.
- Yes, sir.
- Yes, Mohit?
I've called to inform you
that finally, I got a call
for an interview.
They had to. The application
was filed so neatly.
Neatly means nothing.
My five page, mind-blowing bio-data
must have impressed them.
Anyway, reach home quickly.
We have to prepare for the interview.
No, sir, not now. There's an emergency.
Is there?
If you can't come,
I'll come to your office.
No, no...
You don't have to. Let me see.
Good, come by 17:00.
And listen... thank you for all.
Okay then.
Yes, Dad?
Mayera, come home early today.
But...
Look, have I ever asked you
to come home early? No, right!
But today please reach home by 18:00.
Otherwise, I'll never speak to you again.
18:00 means 18:00. Bye, bye-bye.
Radha!
- Oh, Radha?
- Yes, sir?
Order two chicken from the meat shop.
And prepare the biryani spices.
Mohit and Mayera will have dinner.
- All right!
- Make halva as well.
Gursharan? You know PC Jewelers, right?
Can you get me a discount?
So meet me there!
At the South Ex showroom, in an hour.
Study the detailed account date wise.
There is 5,000 extra. Just in case,
if there's a mistake in the calculaton.
Mail me if it is more than 5,000.
I'll send you a draft.
Where is the damn accounts slip?
It's okay.
I'll make a fresh one.
I remember everything.
What impression would I create
on my son-in-law with such rings?
Show me a good one,
not these flimsy things.
Ma'am? Mr. Sehgal is Secretary
to Government of India, IAS.
Show him something of his worth.
Call the owner.
No, sir. I'm showing.
Take a look at this.
Look at this, sir.
Matching rings for the bride and groom.
These are single diamonds, right?
- What's the name?
- Solitaire.
Solitaire. solitaire. They are good.
This will cost you around 450,000.
No! That's a little too much.
Show something reasonable.
No, please pack these.
Here you are.
Please check.
I added the stupid rock show tickets too.
Guess everything is cleared between us.
All clear.
The rock show's stupid,
because it's my plan.
And being a cry-baby
and staying at home is very clever.
I'm okay as stupid.
You know what? Clever and stupid
shouldn't get married either.
As if I want to get married.
In any case, I can't afford the stupidity
of love and marriage anymore.
This boy that Mayera has chosen...
His market value may be less
but his character is priceless.
In my humble opinion,
character is the only value, sir.
Today when I got the interview mail,
I thought I've tested this boy enough.
I should agree to their marriage.
But Mohit should never know
I was praising him.
- Don't let praise go to your head.
- Top secret, sir.
Now even this expensive ring
seems reasonable for him.
Actually, there isn't any point
in meeting again.
As if! I've just come to return the money.
In fact, I was going to say it first.
You're first and I came last. Happy?
This is my office, Mohit.
You get lost.
Your office, your money.
Why do all answers
Seem fickle and dubious?
Nothing seems real
On these crossroads
Except for an imaginary indifference
Here's the entire history of the company.
Put away the games and read it.
Why should I read about them?
Are they taking my interview
or am I taking theirs?
I did my complete homework on you
before I came and asked
for your permission for marriage.
So that I don't say anything wrong.
Wow! You're very cool.
- Okay, I'm leaving now.
- Wait, wait.
- Let's have a beer.
- I have to go to work.
Beer is just a cold drink.
No cold drink before the interview.
Load the game then.
I'll just come. Load the game.
Now where's this Mayera?
- Must be on her way.
- It's 18:00 already.
I told her to come early.
I can't make Mohit wait that long.
Great! The smell of the halva
is irresistible.
The thing is, son,
this is not a chilled beer.
It's a child beer.
We're here, Mayera.
Where are you off to?
Mohit?
What the hell?
What are you doing here?
- I... I...
- Hey, you Romeo.
Your Juliet is here.
Leave the window and come in.
- Dad, please...
- Nobody will speak.
- Radha!
- Radha is at home?
Where else would she be?
Come on, Mohit. Show some enthusiasm.
Sit down, both of you!
Congratulations, sir.
Miss Mayera?
Surprise... Congratulations.
One for you and one for you.
Take it. Shall I keep on standing?
Now tell me. Do you like it? How is it?
The rings?
What is it?
Someone say something.
This is the report card of your probation.
You're not perfect, but we'll manage!
Now before I change my mind,
exchange your rings.
What's wrong?
They're solitaires.
Don't you like the design?
At least, just wear them for ceremony.
Tomorrow you can go select your own.
All right?
So who wears the ring first,
the boy or the girl?
Why are you laughing?
Dad, we're not getting married.
- She's serious.
- It's over between us.
Hey... sit, sit down!
Did I simply play all this squash?
Sweat away?
Made inquiries in various departments?
And do you know how many
phone calls, photocopies,
plastic files I've spent on...
on your Mohit?
Not mine.
Not mine?
Now I'm not going to investigate
any other boy.
Talk to each other
and figure out a solution.
Say sorry, and exchange rings.
- Dad, it's impossible. It's a huge gap.
- Requires a lot of money!
Which your daughter has, but I don't.
Who fights over money?
Did you borrow money from him? Return it.
If I had money then only she would borrow,
right?
I haven't had a salary for three months.
And the fact is... I'm unemployed.
I'm looking for a job.
You lost your airlines' job?
You lost it then itself, right?
I knew it.
- You lied to me?
- Yes.
I lied to you.
Now tell me, should I?
Like hell you will!
You've failed, for sure.
- You've lied.
- And you're Gandhi!
You lied to Mayera too.
What lying?
I'm trying for a job. He's helping me.
Was helping me... was!
You promised me.
Miss, halva.
Please forget about the job, okay?
Mohit's gone. New job search is also gone.
Sir, is the Dubai position still open?
You took too long, silly.
He's joining next week.
If you can go before that...
Can you leave tonight?
The travel desk will arrange the visa.
If you can convince them there,
I'll get all the approvals here.
Once you get the appointment in Dubai,
come back over
the weekend to shift properly.
For now, this is between us.
This is just a regular assignment.
What's going on?
Hello, sir. I'm Nawab Master,
the driving instructor.
I also sell secondhand cars.
I sold Mr. Mohit"s car
at a good price just yesterday.
Call me if you have anything.
Accounts are all settled now.
Where are you going?
Today they are.
Tomorrow they'll be unsettled again.
I actually might start
enjoying being unemployed.
Murit, sorry...
I swear I'll never read your newspaper.
I'll never watch Big Boss.
I'll buy you beer for a month.
You can have my entire Playboy collection!
The remote as well!
You make your heart understand
You make fool out of yourself
And carry on with the misreading
Something which is not broken
Someone who's not angry at you
Even then it hurts so much
False concessions...
Fake confessions...
It hides all your mistakes.
It fools everyone
And blames itself
Looks for gain even in losses
All this silliness...
Meaningless and pointless
Needless and thoughtless...
Unnecessary silliness...
All this silliness...
Meaningless and pointless
Needless and thoughtless...
Unnecessary silliness...
There isn't any position open.
Why don't you leave your resume behind?
Okay. All the best.
In a still high temperature
You show no improvement
You fall on your face time and again
There's still time
Not all is lost
Why wear a long face then?
You spend your days cursing others
Such stubbornness!
Someone must stop you
How long will you fool yourself?
Meet Mohit, our new counter manager.
Meaningless and pointless
Needless and thoughtless...
Unnecessary silliness...
Super hot! Shall I just gobble you up?
Silliness...
Meaningless and pointless
Needless and thoughtless...
Unnecessary silliness...
It's actually easy
To gather and fix the broken parts
Fret not, fear not
Just utter the sounds of sorry
Why are you faking?
Posturing and raving?
What can you gain from this?
What to calculate now?
Why weigh things so much?
What would you lose and win?
All this silliness...
Meaningless and pointless
Needless and thoughtless...
Unnecessary silliness...
Silliness...
Meaningless and pointless
Needless and thoughtless...
Unnecessary silliness...
Negi, who are those couples
at table three and twelve?
It's been three hours now.
- Get them out!
- They're penniless lovers.
Where will they go for their love-talk?
Parents at home, police in the parks.
They're not making any scene, sir.
Why get into the business of love
if they're penniless!
Yes, sir. Boss's order after all.
Let's shoo them away.
Put that stick aside.
Give them a cappuccino each.
But, no free business after this.
They'll have to spend to sit here.
Or else, out in an hour.
You're touched too, right, sir?
Yes, bro, really!
- Brownies too, sir?
- Shall I throw you out too?
What's this, sir? Be happy.
Hey, you're back!
Sir, this is Manju.
She went to Rohtak
for her cousin's wedding.
This is our Mohit sir.
Sir, I'll just be back.
Sir, Manju is my girlfriend.
I can see that.
Now I'll enjoy my work.
Don't mind, but your
professional story is very sad.
But there's an easy solution
for your love story.
- Just by by saying sorry to each other.
- By God, Manju...
Her mother calls her "Big-mouth Manju".
I'm never gonna tell you anything.
I'm sorry I told her, sir.
And no one else.
It's her fault. She should say sorry.
- But, sir, just try once. Talk to her.
- Manju, he's in a bad mood, come.
Let me just talk to him for a second...
That liar!
That jobless...
Been dependent on Mayera
for the last two months!
I should have sent him to jail!
Don't know why I'm so confused about him.
Sir, the government never
respected your work, your honesty.
Transfer upon transfer.
But God is watching.
He saved you
and our Mayera at the last minute.
No more scope for confusion.
Tell that ma'am to finish up the bill.
Be patient, sir. Patient.
But there's one thing.
Even after breaking up with Mayera,
he went out of his way to help you.
Logically, it doesn't add up.
I think it's a big conspiracy, sir.
In my humble opinion,
pull some strings and send him to jail.
It's your lucky day, sir.
Gold prices have shot up.
You've made a profit of 37,580 rupees.
Thirty-seven thousand...
Why did my luck have to change today?
Bloody...
I don't want to sell.
Thanks a lot for your assistance.
You raised one question
and cleared the entire matter.
Couldn't you ask earlier?
I didn't have to bear such a loss!
What question, sir?
He had made me a promise.
How could he break his promise?
He came to help me
even after the break up.
Wow! Look at the character of that guy.
How can I leave such a guy?
Anyone can get a character certificate
by paying extra money.
But the boy is jobless.
Exactly my point.
But he taught me that
life doesn't end but starts at sixty.
That duffer made me... what is that?
He made me cool!
He's an MBA,
sooner or later he'll get a job.
That's okay, sir... but...
They don't think the way you do.
They are fighting.
Can there be a Romeo and Juliet
without a villain?
This time the villain will unite them.
Mayera!
Where were you?
I've been trying to call you.
Give me the keys, I need your passport.
Passport? Why?
- What?
- Sit here and hear me out.
What is this?
Our new house, in Dubai.
Our new house?
A kitchen that's bigger than
our living room, fully equipped.
New vice president of the Dubai office.
Double the salary, that too in Dirhams.
See, I did what you wanted!
What?!
Don't say you don't want to go
because you don't have a choice.
No, silly! I'm shocked with happiness.
It's the best decision of your life.
Here are the keys.
We have to pack
everything in two days.
- Monday is the joining, or else no offer.
- Don't worry, I'm there.
I'll do what's right for you.
That good-for-nothing Mohit...
Just think, would you be able
to move to Dubai if you married him?
Radha, did you get the cartons?
Yes, I am getting them.
We'll have our revenge before we go.
I've told Gursharan to
make a fake case against him.
He'll be sent to Tihar jail for a week.
They will break his bones first.
Then only the break-up will be completed.
- Wouldn't it be fun?
- You're just too much.
Call Mr. Gursharan right now and stop him.
Will you feel bad if he gets hurt?
Why are you running away to Dubai
if you love him this much?
I'll be out of your way.
See? You're getting confused about Dubai.
To be or not to be...
Romeo and Juliet...
There's no confusion.
I just don't want
any problems, that's all.
Talk to Mr. Gursharan.
Yes, Gursharan. Tihar-plan canceled.
Happy?
Hey, Gursharan, my friend.
Nobody has to be sent to Tihar.
Mayera has taken both
our passports to Ajanta Travels
for the tickets and visa.
Do something with the agency
so that we don't get the visas.
Do you understand?
Yes, we shouldn't get the visas!
Come on, Mohit, answer the phone.
Oh, hell!
Now how do I contact this duffer?
- Sir?
- Yes. Mohit...
Mohit was just here.
Maybe in the conference room?
Will you keep lying all your life
to save your friend?
I'm not lying.
Where is he? Tell me the truth.
He's changed his number,
doesn't reply to emails.
He's just vanished into thin air.
Think hard.
There must be someone
who can tell us about him.
Think hard.
The Home Secretary was my batchmate!
By God, what an unfortunate case.
I told him not to boast
about an automatic car.
What if you don't have a bicycle tomorrow?
He didn't listen to me.
But where is he?
Stop, man, stop. Over there, sir.
Very good. Thank you, Master.
- Okay, Immy, thank you.
- Welcome, sir.
Do you get a salary,
or are you on daily wages?
Get me a cappuccino
and a cup of tea for you. It's on me.
No, thanks. One cappuccino, please!
Anything else?
Let me help increase your sales.
You must be getting a commission?
Don't you ever stop loving me
I can live without everything but love
Hey, boy!
What kind of service is this?
Clean the damn table!
Take it.
You can get your new girlfriend peanuts
with it.
This time look for someone of your status.
Why have you come here?
To tell you that Mayera
is moving to Dubai.
It hurts, doesn't it?
How you both used to boast...
Love is everything and all that bullshit!
"We can fill love in the gas tank
and drive off!"
So, where is all that love?
Now do you understand the value of money?
As always, Mayera is smarter than you.
She's taken a transfer to Dubai.
In a week, Dubai will make her forget
you and the pain.
You just keep selling your tea
and coffee here.
You think you're very smart?
But you're just a big duffer!
Don't you understand?
Mayera is spoiled rotten.
She's gotten used to the five-star life.
You would have gone bankrupt
if you'd married.
See, as soon as you lost your money,
that snob tossed you aside
like an insignificant fly!
It's your own daughter!
Why are you feeling bad?
What does she mean to you now?
Anyway, she dumped you
and now she's leaving.
That too, in business class!
Remember not to
fall in love with a money-minded,
selfish, opportunist like Mayera...
You've said enough.
Now if you say even one word
against Mayera I'll...
You'll what? What will you do?
Empty pockets with Romeoesque zeal
doesn't suit each other.
You flaunt your love
like you're some millionaire.
But you're just a bloody waiter!
We're leaving for the airport
in about three hours, understood?
If I see you within a five kilometer
radius of the airport...
Remember, the Home Secretary
is my batchmate!
Your photo will go to the home department.
Then it will flash to
every PCR van, Black Cats,
NSG commandos, CRPF, RAW agents etc.
She's moving to Dubai.
She could have at least told me!
No point in being sad right now.
- Go say sorry to ma'am and stop her.
- How can I?
She's the one who broke up,
she has to say sorry.
It's not a race, sir.
What would you do with your king-size ego?
Ma'am will be gone
and you'll be left alone to wonder.
"Bloody waiter."
Sir, that old man's insulted us all.
You have to give it back to
that rotten fellow!
Yes, sir, steal Mayera away
from right under his nose.
That'll be a fitting reply.
Are you done?
Enough of me and my life.
- Get back to work.
- Sir, please listen to me...
Hey! Stop right here.
Stop here, please.
- How much?
- Forty-five, mister...
Keep the change.
Where were you, Dad?
Get ready or we'll be late.
I'll just get ready.
Radha, you've latched
all the windows properly?
- Yes!
- Switched off the gas?
- I have.
- All right!
Give all the papers to Mr. Gursharan.
Clean up every Saturday,
else I won't come back to get you.
Miss, please don't go.
Why are you crying?
I'm coming back to get you, okay?
- Please don't go, Miss.
- Silly girl!
I will miss you a lot...
Now stop crying
and take all the bags out, okay?
What do we do about the rings?
I've never abused so much in my life.
I called my own daughter a snob!
These two are more stubborn than me.
God knows how the gold prices are now.
Sell them anyway
irrespective of profit or loss
and deposit the money in my account.
I guess, this time too
Romeo and Juliet will have a tragic end.
- Come here, sir.
- What's the matter?
Now let's make sure he doesn't go free!
Gursharan, pick up a weapon!
- Wait, sir, I'm coming too.
- No.
That old man is dangerous.
I know, but after all
he is my father-in-law.
Mr. Mohit!
Beware!
Don't you dare take a single step,
or I'll make you a cripple.
Gursharan, call the Police Commissioner.
- The Home Secretary...
- Yes, I know, he's your batchmate.
I don't want to talk to you.
Call Mayera. Call her.
Why should Mayera come?
Who are you, just a waiter?
First, earn some money,
have a hefty bank balance.
My Mayera won't go with a loser.
She's come to her senses now,
you bloody penny-pincher!
Sir, reality check.
You're behaving utterly
uncool right now, sir.
Insulting my waiter friends is uncool.
Calling Mayera snob and selfish is uncool.
And your hundred-year-old money theory,
that's uncool too.
If one followed your theory,
the poor would not have life or love.
If there is love...
thirty rupees and one cup of coffee...
is enough to be happy.
What if there's no money...
there's unlimited love.
Money or no money, love finds its way.
If there's love, right? If?
She hates you.
And you must know, we were going to pray
at the Hanuman temple
on the way to the airport
for your unhappy ever after,
- You bloody loser.
- Dad, enough!
What's Mohit done to you?
He agreed to the probation.
He lost matches against you.
He's the national level under-16
silver medalist in squash.
Yet he lost all the matches for you.
He helped you with your job-hunting,
lied to me for you.
He calls you Osama
and you really are like a terrorist.
He kept tolerating you for me.
If he can do so much for me,
he can also give his life for me.
A waiter or a manager,
a prince or a pauper...
I love him.
Some sacrifices will be there.
I won't get to go to rock shows,
dinner once a month, shopping once a year?
I ain't gonna work
at a coffee shop all my life...
Until you do,
we will still have fun.
I don't enjoy shopping at all without you.
Irrespective of the amount
of money or the credit card limits.
If you're not around then who'll say...
Very hot! Shall I gobble you up?
No hankypanky before marriage!
Weren't you very happy with our break-up?
Your generation always has to do
the opposite of what the parents say?
If I had listed his good qualities,
would you say sorry
and patch up with him? No!
I abused him,
only then did you understand.
Hey, stupid!
You called me "uncool", you bloody fool!
Seek my blessings, son-in-law!
Not like this, give me a hug.
A good one...
Stupid fellow...
Come here!
Now give us the rings.
Your wish means everything,
and mine means nothing?
Which wish?
I have an interview today.
I have to go there.
Let him go, else
he'll never leave us alone.
- The pressure of a private job at his age?
- He's letting you decide for yourself.
So? How am I looking?
- Don't you have a suit?
- Suit?
I got a new safari suit made for this,
from Singh Tailors...
- Where are you taking me?
- Come on.
You guys have sandwiched me in between!
The sandwich needs a good tie!
I can't leave you and go to Dubai.
Thankfully the heart is smart
After having been someone else's
You'll shift out of this
hole after marriage, won't you?
Say sorry, sir.
Say sorry, sir, or no tie.
Sorry, sorry!
Please get me a sober tie
that suits my age.
- Where are you going?
- He'll get something silly.
Okay, choose a good one.
We've saved this day at last
We've solved the issues
You and I, together
Oh, so romantic Utterly romantic
You and I, I and you
- I missed you.
- What took you so long?
Sir, don't show off
about the Home Secretary
in the interview.
It'll make a good impression.
You won't understand.
Dad, it doesn't.
I thought that's why
Mohit is scared of me.
You're not scared of me?
Don't scare anyone.
It's an interview.
- Sehgal VK.
- They're asking for your name
- not your email ID!
- Vinod Kumar Sehgal.
Sir, your girlfriend is top-class.
Peter.
Top-class coffee
for the top-class girlfriend.
Sir, take one cup and share.
Your financing skills, and my marketing,
let's open a coffee shop.
I've understood one thing from all this.
People don't stop drinking coffee
even if there's no money.
Brilliant! We'll call it One Cup Coffee.
- Nah!
- Why not?
People will drink only one cup, then!
Listen, I'll select the name.
The Home Secretary is my Dad's batchmate!
I'm going to gobble
this Home Secretary up!
Osama.
Our story will be there
On the no-good's books
Chapter by chapter
We'll recite our fairytale
Unfinished and broken
Authentic yet miserable
Is the story of our life
What do we care about the world
We'll recite it to us anyway
Oh, so romantic Utterly romantic
You and I, I and you
This journey of love
The vast land of promises
Either at high price
Or at low
Wherever you get this land
No matter how or when
That's the road to love
Long and precious
During long lazy afternoons there
In between mischief and laughter
We'll steal away the warmth from the sun