Back. Back.
Go back.
Move.
Move back. Move.
Otherwise I will turn you into Anarkali.
Children, what did I write here?
Bablu, you tell me.
Fature!
Does this look like 'Fature'.
How many times have I told you?
It's 'Fature' (Future).
Teacher, someone here to see you.
I'm coming.
Kneel.
Shell it out. Come on.
Quickly. - Open it.
Bring more tomorrow.
Where's your lunch-box?
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Lunchbox. - Quickly.
Quickly.
Stand up.
Stop laying eggs, where's your lunchbox?
Hurry up, or that baldy will catch us. - Open your lunchbox.
Lunchbox.
Get it tomorrow, or I'll shoot you.
Give it.
Otherwise your 'fature' will be in dark.
Next time I won't spare you.
Rascals...you're back again.
Run! Run! - Stop.
Scoundrels, I won't spare you two.
Hey...it's got a twisted barrel.
I see.
It's fine. What's the problem?
If it's okay, why do I keep missing?
You won't if you know how to.
You little rat, why don't you show me how?
Rascal, even Pali can do that.
What's the target?
I see...
Bhure, take this.
Go. Go.
Come on.
Come on. I'll show you.
Rascal...
That's your target, not this.
What's this? - Fine, keep it.
I'll pay the rest later.
I am not going anywhere.
"May our friendship begin.."
"..where all bonds severe ties."
"At every step, every second.."
"May our friendship begin.."
"..where all bonds severe ties."
"At every step, every second.."
"If you've read my heart."
"There's nothing more can I say."
"My companion."
"You're my friend."
"Our bond is the most unique."
"My companion."
"You're my friend."
"Our bond is the most unique."
"I believe you, even when you lie."
"I know even before you admit."
"Whether you're good...or bad."
"Whether you're right...or wrong."
Where were you?
And why bring these roosters?
Why are you getting so restless?
He wasn't paying up, so we brought these.
So what if he wasn't paying up?
He's an old customer.
We don't like giving credits.
Look at their attitude.
If we lose this client..
..then, we'll shove your attitude up your back.
Get that?
Stop staring.
Get back to work.
Rascal...first we slog all day..
..and then listen to their abuses.
We don't want this.
What else will you do?
I..
Will become a judge.
You want to be a judge?
Rascal...
Why did you hit us?
What else did you expect?
He wants to be a judge.
Do you know how hard one needs to study to become a judge?
I don't know about education.
But one should know how to fire a gun.
You..
Greetings, sir.
Why are you punishing me?
I've been legally acquitted.
The law is blindfolded..
..not me.
In my court, there's just one punishment..
..for raping a girl.
Slice a cucumber...and rub some salt.
There's only one punishment...for such a crime.
Judge sir, the verdict's been given.
But...what section shall we charge him with?
Got it. Got it.
Hari, my mind's going numb.
I can't think of anything.
First of all, the administration slipped from my hands.
And that Bramhanand got you jailed.
Control this bloodshed.
Otherwise...your 7 year prison term..
..will turn into life imprisonment.
Why are you worried?
These bars can contain me..
..not my reign.
What is it?
I need water to wash my face.
Come.
Are you done?
Then leave.
You haven't taken a bath yet.
You know Bablu's coming.
I am not asking you to marry him.
You just need to spend few hours with him.
Hurry up.
My master won the elections.
Now I will rule this place.
Let's see what that Bablu or anyone else can do about it.
Wretch, can't you do it properly?
Are your hands tied up?
Do you want a slap?
Hey...take that poster out!
Rascal.
Move.
Idiots, what did you think?
Just because Brahmanand won..
..you thought you could threaten us. - Bablu..
lower your voice.
No matter who controls the government..
..but, Bablu Chaudhary will always rule this place.
You did the right thing. He's a lowly man.
Listen carefully.
If you're not with Bablu Chaudhary..
..then consider yourself dead.
Get that.
He died too soon.
"I am from Patna."
"I am a cannon ball... about to explode."
"No one dares to face me, because they're all afraid."
"My eyes are lethal, they always find their target."
"They are amazed."
"Bewildered."
"The entire town...by my grace."
"Take a chance."
"Cajole me."
"My grace has made everyone my slave."
"These cowards don't scare me."
"I am from Patna."
"The pistol maybe local make, but the fire's real."
"Those who attack behind the back, are cowards."
"They die."
"They are scared."
"These goons try to protect my beauty."
"It's going crazy."
"It's falling."
"The prizes in the market, the traders are scared."
"I can deal with these thugs and goons alone."
"I am from Patna."
Little twerps, You can hardly keep your pants up..
..and your blood's boiling already.
Get lost!
What's wrong?
Are you still upset about yesterday?
How dare he hit you?
Forget it.
When the time comes, we'll spare a bullet for him too.
By the way, Pali...were you showing attitude..
..for me or...for Guddi?
No, I didn't mean it.
I was joking, really?
You dare joke with me. - I was joking, really?
I'll show you.
Believe me. - Stop.
I won't spare you.
"May you always stay ahead.."
"..and your sagas follow you."
"Even if our paths are separate.."
"..but all I think about I you."
"Even if our destinations are different.."
"Crossing all barriers...
...breaking every limit."
"My companion."
"You're my friend."
"Our bond is the most unique."
'Lord, what sin did I possible commit..'
'..that everyone treats me as a object of pleasure.'
'Is there no one who will accept me...wholeheartedly?'
I see.
I've been slogging like a dog..
..while you're getting some eye-candy.
Great.
Tell me something.
How long will you keep staring at her secretly?
Why don't you go up to her and say something?
Otherwise you'll be watching her all your life.
Get lost.
You won't understand.
You'll know...once you find true love.
No, no, I'm not interested in finding true love.
Where one can never see the horizon, no matter how far you see.
Come on.
Get back to work.
How are you? - Fine.
Will it burst?
This is a pistol...not a condom...which will burst.
I see... good going.
You could've warned us before firing.
Come on. Let's go.
You can collect your payment later.
We don't give credits.
You dare ask us to pay.
Us.
Hey man...
...pay up quietly..
..or else I'll blow your brains out.
Do you know who you're messing around with?
If Bablu finds out, you'll be smoking without the gun.
Don't talk like a fool.
First save yourself.
Then you can worry about me.
Understand.
Now come on.
You'll regret this, I am warning you.
Pay up. - Pay up.
Come on...pay up. - Cash?
Yes. Keep all of it.
And the rest? - Rest?
I paid you full.
We wasted so many bullets on you and your thugs.
Who's going to pay for that? You or your mum?
You mean I.. - Yes.
Pay up, 2750 rupees.
Keep it. Keep it all.
Pali, this is 3000. - Keep it.
Why are you still shooting at me?
We didn't have change of 250.
Well...see you.
You..
Move.
Hey my bangles..
I'll deal with you.
I'll deal with you too.
Thanks for saving our lives.
You..
Major.
Major Suryakant Rathod.
Seems like you've an old acquaintance...with pistols.
How long have you been playing around with it?
Since we were kids.
We never got toys, so we played with them instead.
I saw.
You two are good shooters.
But your aim's...
...wrong.
Meaning?
Use your talent...for the country.
Fame, fortune, money...you'll get it all.
We already have that.
We're famous all around Kanpur.
You can ask any criminal.
He'll take our names with respect.
And since we have this..
..we'll make fortune too.
Yes.
And as far as your favor's concerned.
We'll repay it soon.
We hate debts.
Let's go, Pali. - Come on.
They were all such loudmouths.
But brother Pali showed them.
You can't weave a quilt with thorns.
Brother Pali, he's right.
You can't make soup from bones.
Brother Gyani, eat slowly.
Slowly.
It's all yours.
No one's going to snatch it. - Hey!
Never comment on food.
I spent my entire childhood starving.
I can't remember when the last time I ate properly was.
Commenting on food.
Rascal...
...why are you worrying so much?
There will be a day..
..when all the delicious food in the world..
..will be served before you.
And you'll be wondering...
...where do I start from?
Brother Pali.
Thank God I found you.
What happened?
Why are you panting?
Bablu's calling you.
Why?
I don't know.
But I do know that he's furious.
You won't say a word.
I will talk to him.
Let's go. - Yes.
What's wrong?
Why do you look so scared?
As if I'm touching you for the first time.
Or am I making you restless, darling?
Let me go. You're hurting me.
Pain is the key to pleasure, sweetheart.
Brother, those rascals are here.
What's wrong?
What are you looking there for?
You...
Make me a drink.
What?
Just because you've outgrown your pants..
..does it mean you can do as you want?
You dare threaten my man.
Move back.
Lower your eyes.
Rascal, you want to be like me.
Listen to me.
What do should I listen?
This wasn't our fault.
So, what is my fault?
Rascal, how dare you try to shoot my brother!
My brother!
We were just kids back then.
But I won't endure it anymore.
Everything stays the way it has been so far.
But...we'll be giving the commands.
If anyone has a problem..
..he'll meet the same fate as Bablu.
Now disappear.
Come on.
Let's go.
Or else he'll shoot us too.
You...please stay here.
Tell her...
...about your feelings today.
Please look at me.
I've loved you since I was a kid.
If you...don't see the love in my eyes..
Then you can shoot me.
Or you can come to me..
"There's a veil that's taunting me."
"That's taunting me.."
"When my lips tremble and hesitate...I realized."
"I realized."
"My freedom's turned into captivity."
"My sweetheart...you're my benefactor."
"Has the mirror changed, or have I turned new?"
"You're my benefactor."
Yes, sir.
Minister's on the line.
You're working really hard for your age, Shukla.
Yes, sir.
Greetings, sir.
Bless you, Hari.
Where are you?
It's quite a task finding you.
You're my Guru, sir.
It doesn't suit you to say such things.
Listen, I've arranged for your release.
Why?
Are the elections close?
Yes.
And leave no stone unturned in this election.
Just give the word.
I'm always ready to do my duty.
But pay some attention to me too.
What is it?
I'm done with bloodshed.
Now, I want to enter politics.
Yes. And you've served enough time in prison.
Prepare for the elections.
I'll announce your name.
Hail Lord. - Hail Lord!
Shaukal.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
I am a devotee of Lord Mahadev as well.
Hello.
Sir...Ballu's been shot.
He was murdered.
Shaukal.
Yes.
What's wrong, sir?
Get lost.
Let's go.
My job's..
Yes, sir.
Hand me your gun. - Sir it's my service weapon.
I'm talking to you, hand me your gun.
Try to understand, it's my service weapon.
I am the government.
Hand me the gun!
Here you go.
Let's go.
Sir, please be careful.
Which one is Pali?
Greetings.
I'm the pali..
I want to fill your brains with bullets. Now!
But I won't kill you so easily.
Forgive him.
He will definitely die.
Get lost.
Then kill me first..
Then die.
What happened?
What's wrong with you goons now?
Trying to boss around after killing my man.
If you're really brave, then hit me.
Hit me.
We would rather die, then hit you.
Why? Am I your father? - God.
You're our God!
We've your picture in our temple, instead of God's.
Look.
We've always revered you since childhood.
If I am your God..
..then why kill my right-hand man, Bablu?
The one he's been bothering for years, was special to me.
Who?
Guddi.
I endured as long as I could.
When I couldn't, I shot him.
You can punish us in any way you want, we're ready.
What do you want?
To rule the underworld.
Can you prove it? - Of course.
Fine, now you two will do..
..Bablu's job.
But remember, in reward I give life..
..and as punishment, I take it.
"Sweetheart..."
"Sweetheart said to me..."
Uncle, work faster.
Pali and Gyaani must be on their way to collect the goods.
Fine, I'm working faster.
Salim, hurry up.
Yes, uncle. I am hurrying up.
Don't let anyone escape.
Arrest everyone.
No one goes out. - Stop.
Don't let anyone out.
Arrest everyone.
Come out.
Seize the weapons.
Don't hit us. We'll do as you say.
Arrest everyone.
Come.
Police. Police.
Run.
Come on.
Go inside.
How will we deliver the goods? - Stay calm.
Stay calm. - Go inside.
Get everyone in.
Go inside.
Him too.
Let's get to the police station, and I'll show you.
We'll have to do something.
What happened, Rafiq?
Why are you panting?
The police just conducted a raid. - What?
They raided all our pistol-workshops.
Arrested many of our people.
Who's the officer eager to attain martyrdom?
It's the new SP.
The rascal believes in honesty.
I even called the Commissioner.
But no one wants to interfere in this matter.
Hari, how will we handle this mess now?
My brain's gone numb.
You're my Guru.
It doesn't suit you if your brain goes numb all the time.
If Bablu had been alive..
..we would've never faced such a situation.
Greetings, Judge sir.
The job's done.
Job's done? What job?
Police seized all the goods. - Hey!
What job? - Shut up.
Let us speak.
Come, sir.
Why bring this dung here?
Do you want to butter it?
Be patient.
Amazing.
Hari, finally my brain's calm.
"Those who were to seek have plunged deep."
"I like an old man fearfully sat beside riverbed."
Great!
What's all this?
Move back. Move.
What's this? What are you doing?
Get out. Everyone.
Get out.
You can change the country later.
Here you go, start.
Glory to you!
Mahadev!
Stop. Stop!
Stop the car.
Get out of here. Get out.
No one's going to vote here.
What's this charade?
I'll shoot you.
There'll be no booth capturing as long as I am here.
We'll capture this booth in your presence.
18x5 is 90.
Come on, seize the booths.
Phulchand, get me something sweet, quickly.
Right away, sir.
What do you think policemen are?
Something you can rattle as you like.
Now I'll thrash you two to bits.
You dare kill a police officer.
How dare you?
We've told you before that we didn't kill him.
So tell me who did.
Otherwise, you'll spend the rest of your life in jail.
You will set us free tomorrow morning.
Respectfully.
Oh my.
This is what you call, Life's all messed up.
But you still got pride.
But you see, son, dreams don't really come true.
Do you know who we work for?
Yes, I know.
Constable Mewaram informed me..
..that you two work for Gabbar Singh.
But you two don't know..
..that man you're so arrogant about..
..is in Delhi right now.
And by the time he finds out..
..Raghavendra Singh Chauhan will close your files.
End of news!
You two have until tomorrow evening.
Admit to your crimes, otherwise..
Sir, what about their food?
These two won't get food.
All they will get are bullets.
Pali. - Yes.
Look.
Mewaram, release those two.
Don't think too hard.
I did what I thought was right.
Now you can do...what you feel is right.
The election committee has cancelled..
..some of the votes cast in the Kanpur, Shuklaganj region.
According to the police, Harishankar Tripathi's goons..
..had forcefully seized these polling booths.
It's believe that, this is the same polling booth..
..where police officer Satbeer Adhikari was murdered.
You look more worried than me.
We won't lose if few votes are cancelled.
The only difference is..
..earlier we used to win by 125,000 votes..
..but this time we'll win with 100,000 votes.
Yes.
So...Hail Mahadev. - Hail Mahadev.
He isn't answering.
Everyone staring at you?
What are you doing? - He's rebuking at me.
Why aren't you answering our phone?
Did you shove it up your back?
Are you two stupid?
I've been disconnecting your calls, but you still keep calling.
Rascal, we've been waiting for over an hour.
So what?
You're not doing me a favor.
I didn't call you here.
Hey, don't make me furious.
We came here to meet sir, and we'll meet him.
Look, you'll be called if required.
And you won't die, if you don't come here.
The police would've killed us..
..if that man hadn't saved us.
Right.
You should've saved us instead. - Why?
You're not my responsibility.
I've other things to do.
Get lost.
Hey...
Don't try to act too smart.
Otherwise...I'll shoot you, and call it an encounter.
Rascal, we spent one bullet on Bablu.
We'll spend two on you.
One from the front...and other on your back.
Hey...get lost.
Get going. - Let's go, Pali.
Get lost.
Oh, my!
Pali...
...where are we?
Hey, mister. What do you want?
Who do you want to meet? - We're here to see the Major.
Major? - Yes.
Uncle. - Yes.
Let them come.
Heard that. - Go on.
Uncle. - Yes.
Prepare a room for them, please. - Yes, sir.
Good, nice to see you two here.
Proves that you still have some humanity..
..and a will to live a better life.
You two must be tired.
Get some rest. See you tomorrow.
What the...
Yes...nice guns.
I see, we've to make these.
It'll be done, Major.
Yes, just leave the box behind.
These are the best pistols in the world.
Used only...by professional shooter.
Major, why tell us about it?
Because...they'll be useful..
..in your journey ahead.
Journey?
But what do we have to do?
Relax. You'll know when the time comes.
For now, watch carefully what I do.
Excuse me.
Come.
The gun should always be facing down.
Always this way, not this.
Feet...at a comfortable distance.
Shoulders straight.
Look up...head straight.
You can keep your hand wherever you like.
You should see the target through this.
Okay? Got it.
Come on.
These are your pistols?
You just need to take aim for now.
Not shoot.
Major...
...what are you making us do?
This will jam us.
Just tell us where we need to aim.
Leave the rest to us.
Just.. - Brother.
What happened?
Are these two the shooters you were talking about?
Brother, why are you pretending to be so ignorant?
They can't even hold a gun properly.
You think they can aim.
Why don't you show us how?
Move.
It takes time to adjust to anything.
These pistols are still new for you.
First adjust yourselves to it.
Then you'll be able to aim properly.
Now do as I said, come on.
You have no clue how good they are.
Give me one chance.
One chance.
And watch what I turn them into.
Brother, you can change their looks, not their fate.
Bet? - Bet.
From one confinement into another.
The only difference is, earlier we were in hell..
..and now he's making our lives hell.
Are you listening?
Hey.
What are you saying, Pali?
Back there, we would've definitely ended in hell.
But here...
...we get to start a new life.
Hey, Gyani.
Gyani.
After we leave, even we'll make stuff like these.
Chimanganj, Cooliebazaar, all of Bhusatoli...and the old town.
They will all be shocked.
She's coming.
What are you saying?
Look, Pali. Major said stomach in and aim straight.
Close one eye and..
Paridhi.
When did you come?
Actually, when we're shooting..
..we don't know what's going on around us.
That's why we didn't realize you're coming.
And anyway, your brother..
I mean, the Major always says..
..a good shooter never lets his mind deviate..
..stays focus and shoots.
Are you done? - Yes.
Now listen...brother isn't at home.
I see. - So you two can get lost as soon as you can.
Because this is not your cup of tea.
And I know this is brother's first mistake.
So get out of here.
Understand?
Fire!
Good.
Good!
Very good!
Now...I would like to call upon..
..the new fearless leader of my party, Mr. Harishankar Tripathi..
..who will address you all.
Har Har Mahadev!
I've always considered everyone as my kin.
By making me victorious..
..you've proven that you've the same feelings for me.
And I am deeply indebted to all of you for it.
I promise...
...that I will always meet your expectations.
Actually, I want my reign to be peaceful, like Lord Ram.
But if required..
..I can wage war like Lord Krishna to annihilate evil.
Har Har Mahadev!
Come, Hari.
Call Pali, Gyani.
Just give the orders, sir, I am there.
Polls are over, Rafiq.
Now we rule with an iron fist.
Don't be surprised.
Surprise the world.
What are you thinking?
Come on.
Superb. Wonderful.
Very good.
Superb. Very good.
You two will go to Lucknow with me.
Lucknow?
What for?
For the State Shooting Championship.
Where you two..
..will face the best shooters of the state.
But I've no doubt that you guys are the best.
You're better than all of them.
This championship will change the meaning of your life.
Trust me.
Any questions?
Any doubt?
No.
Consider it done.
Good.
Take rest. We'll meet again.
Come.
Told you they're the best.
So...what's wrong?
I never imagined life will bring us here.
I mean...imagine where we started, and where we are.
We'll just shoot and have fun.
Right, Pali!
Where are you two?
Judge sir.
You two just disappeared.
Sir, we did come to see you, but..
Rafiq didn't let us.
Didn't let you meet me?
You were busy, in a meeting with Jwala.
You could've told me after the meeting.
It's time to fulfill your dreams.
Come with me.
What's wrong?
What are you thinking?
Let's go. - Go where?
And what about the promise we made to the Major?
Gyani, we aren't born to shoot at target-posts.
Our Lord is calling us.
Wasn't that our dream?
We've just one chance.
If we lose this, Gyani...
...then everything will be over.
And if I go with you..
..I won't be able to live.
What are you still doing here?
Why don't you leave, like your friend?. - Paridhi
He could've left...if he wanted.
Brother, you still trust him. - Calm down.
He's still here, this proves that he's trustworthy.
You calm down.
I'll handle it.
It's okay.
Gyani.
I am really sorry... for rebuking at you.
Please forgive me.
Please, I am really sorry.
Please.
"The sky and the earth...are meeting at the horizon."
"The colors of joys are flying around."
"A fistful of sunlight."
"A reflection of desires."
"Life is unveiling itself."
"The significance of love's changing.."
"..it's season of union again."
"It's pouring...from the sky.."
"..the new meaning of love."
"May Lord make love make immortal."
"The grace of God.."
"It's just you."
"Only you."
"The staggering fragrance."
"And the wavering intoxication."
"With you by my side... I can live forever."
"When I fell in love."
"Allah sent me a message."
"It's just you."
"Only you."
Ladies and Gentlemen.
This is State Shooting Championship.
Rapid Fire Pistol, men. Qualifying round.
What's wrong? - Nothing.
Why so nervous?
It's another thing to shoot in a closed room.
But here, amongst this huge crowd..
Relax. Just imagine there's no one here.
No participants, nor me, nor these people.
No one.
Just your target and you.
Come on.
You can do it. - Shooters, to your firing point.
Gyani Singh from Kanpur..
..who didn't make an impressive beginning.
But he has managed..
..to secure a place for himself in the top 10 position.
Oh, God!
Congratulation. - Thank you.
It's okay.
After watching your initial performance..
..I doubted whether you'll even qualify.
But you did it.
You qualified, Gyani. - He did what?
Brother, he qualified.. - He came ninth!
Qualified?
He didn't come here to qualify. - But..
He didn't come here to qualify.
He came here to win.
There's just one...
...and only one winner.
And the rest are losers. Qualifiers.
Everyone wants to win, but those who forsake everything else..
..and lives only for his goal, is the winner.
My brother was supposed to represent India in the World Championship.
But, one of his colleagues framed him..
..for selling ammunition.
Major Rathod, we checked your record and service.
On the basis of your 10 years of honest service..
..we feel we should give you another chance.
10 years of honest service, sir.
And you chose not to believe me.
When you've pressed allegations against me..
..so be it.
And I don't want to lose my self-respect, sir.
Here's my resignation.
Brother knew it was a conspiracy.
And so..
..ended brother's dreams of winning a gold medal.
I swear...
I will fulfill the Major's dream.
18x1 are 18. - 18x1 are 18.
18x2 are 36. - 18x2 are 36.
18x3 are 54. - 18x3 are 54.
18x4 are 72. - 18x4 are 72.
Well done.
18x5 are..? - 18x5 are..?
18x5 are..
18x5 could be 23
When 18X4 are 72, so how can 18X5 be 23?
I'll check on my calculator, in my mobile.
Yes, 18x5 are 85.
But teacher said its 90.
Teacher could be wrong.
Your calculations are off, Rafiq.
Something wrong with the mobile.
Better set it straight.
18x5 is..
.. what your teacher said.
Hello, sir.
Come, my boy.
Bless you.
Go on, dear.
Mother will help you with the rest of your lesson.
You've become quite famous these days.
It's all because of your grace, sir.
With your blessings, soon I'll be the king of underworld.
Well...
...not all thundering clouds shower.
But this cloud will.
The partridge died yearning for a drop of water.
What's the point if the rain drenched his dead body?
Know..
..where you need to shower.
First, you've to kill Brahmanand.
Bharat lala.
The owner of 90% nightclubs in our country.
But his real business is flesh-trade.
Jugnu. Contract killer.
He's also associated with the drug business.
He easily carries out his jobs..
..under the pretext of his garage.
Vishram Singh. Land Mafia.
He invests on Sultan..
..and also throws his weight around.
This is why the other groups have turned against him.
In the last few years, this man's been funding a group..
..which spread terror in our country.
So it's very important for him to die.
Last night, someone attacked Sultan's men in Mumbai City.
Hari, my mind's really cool now.
I must admit.
You raked up a storm with a single blow.
You've no idea how many storms are raging inside me.
Greetings, sir. - Come, my boy.
Hello.
Come. Come. Well done
Bless you. Sit.
Bless you.
Hari, I must admit your assessment.
You fished out a real gun amongst the pistols.
You're my Guru..
..it doesn't suit you to call this cannon, a gun.
Fine, Hari.
Pali.
From tomorrow put a black dot on your forehead.
Or someone might cast an eye on you.
When sir's my benefactor, no one can harm me.
Just give the orders, sir.
Slowly slowly O mind, everything in own pace happens..
Gardener may water with a hundred pots..
..but it bears fruits only in its season.
What's this?
Well...
I don't go to Mumbai.
So my bungalow in Mumbai is now yours.
Go live there Guddi...
...a prosperous life.
Shower lots of love on her.
"Everywhere I look...you're the only one I see."
"But whenever he looks at me, I hide my face."
"My dreams are finally come true."
"His passion and my heart is uniting."
"There's joy in surrendering yourself.."
"..how do I say it?"
"I look like someone else.."
"My sweetheart...you're my benefactor."
"You're my benefactor."
Look, sir.
Right now when he fired, this was his state of mind.
Score 10.5.
Here.
And when his score was 10.7, this was his state of mind.
And when his score was 10.2, then this was his state of mind.
You mean, basically..
..this is the best state of mind..
..he should be, when he's shooting, right.
Yes.
Right. - Yes.
Shot's best, then.
Yes.
Sounds good. - Okay.
Gyani, listen to me carefully.
Listen to your heartbeats.
Recognize the gap between the two heartbeats.
That is the right time to get your target.
Okay?
Try!
Awesome.
Very nice.
Gyani Singh from Uttar Pradesh..
..has won the National Championship.
"Lend me...a kiss.."
Sweetheart...
Why did you stop? I was counting.
Come on, do it again.
Paridhi, what are we doing?
We never do what we should.
Shut up, now concentrate.
Let's do one thing.
Give me a kiss, and I'll focus on my task.
Honestly.
Kiss?
Yes.
First hit a bulls-eye.
What's that got to do with my kiss?
Same thing that your kiss has to do with my physiotherapy.
Oh no...this girl's too much.
She doesn't understand. - Come on.
Who or what he was, how does it make a difference?
Why are you giving such an importance?
All that matters is that he's got superb quality..
..of a true international champion.
And he's proved that, by winning the national Championship.
Sir, I can give you in writing.
In future, this boy will rewrite history..
..in every international shooting Championship, with gold.
Major Rathod, you don't understand.
We can't change policies.
What kind of policy is this, sir..
..where a man isn't allowed to forget his past..
..and pursue a new life?
Major..
..you're getting emotional now.
You've to understand, we can be questioned too.
I'll answer those questions, sir.
That's not the point, Major.
Sir.
Sir, I take full responsibility.
But..
Hold on, Mr. Rathod. Calm down.
Take these medals back.
Keep it safe.
Sorry to interfere, but..
Just like you can't fly kites with nylon threads.
Similarly we can't allow criminals to take part in a shooting championship.
That's right. - Understand?
That's all.
In a clearer language, full stop.
Jai Hind. - Fine.
Fine.
Today this boy wants to represent India.
Tomorrow if he turns into a criminal..
..then you'll be responsible for it.
Patil sir.
Please, Patil sir.
Don't disappoint me.
That boy's only few steps away from his goal.
If he has to go back, he won't be able to live.
Look, this isn't possible.
You know that boy's background.
And you're still asking me for permission.
Patil sir, it's not like that anymore.
He's a talented boy.
He can win the gold medal for India.
Look, don't argue.
You're just wasting my time.
Come on. Let's go. - Please, Patil sir.
You're a dog.
What?
You'll be a great shooter. - No.
You said something else? - What?
Did you call me a dog?
Are you crazy?
Yeah. Right?
Brother.
Is everything okay, brother?
I lost.
Why? What happened?
Paridhi..
..Gyani's application was rejected.
What?
I am sorry, son.
Forgive me.
I couldn't do anything for you.
I am sorry.
But...brother...listen to me.
Gyani.
Gyani, it's quite late. Get some sleep.
Gyani, I am speaking to you. Get some sleep.
How?
You've already snatched our sleep.
Tell me one thing..
Why did you give us hopes..
..which could never be fulfilled? - What..
You know everything about us.
And you came to us.. - Gyani.
I am player.
..and I know how to play my game.
I don't care about any permission.
I just want to win the gold medal.
And yes...
...until now, this was just your dream.
But now...
...it's mine.
And I will achieve it at any cost.
Brother!
Major.. - Just stay away from us!
Who do you think you are?
I never thought you would be so mean and selfish.
My brother did everything he could for you.
And this is how you repaid him.
Brother..
Paridhi, listen to me. - Go away.
We don't need you.
Just go.
Just get out of here.
Get out. Go!
Brother.
Ramu uncle.
Gyani?
At this hour?
Hello Gyani..
Gyani. - Yes, Pali.
What happened?
Why are you calling at this hour?
I was just missing you.
So I thought I'd call you.
But it's too late, isn't it?
Fine, get some sleep. We'll talk later.
Hold on.
What's wrong? Tell me.
Nothing. - Nothing?
Then why do you sound so different?
I am not.
You're crying?
Are you crazy?
Why will I cry?
Don't try to lie to me. Me.
I know you better than you.
Understand.
Tell me...who made you cry.
Just tell me his name.
I will kill him.
It's not what you think. - If not, then you're coming to me tomorrow.
Or else, I am coming there. - No, no, no.
You won't come.
I'm coming, okay.
We'll talk tomorrow.
Hello.
Is everything okay?
Earlier you couldn't stop chattering.
And look at you now. As if you've lost your voice.
Tell me what's wrong?
Due to my criminal background, my application was rejected.
I can never compete again.
That's all.
Is that all?
Rascal...that's good news.
You scared me.
This is what we wanted since we were kids.
And look where fate brought us.
Back together.
I've yearned a lot.
No more.
I won't let you go away.
We'll work together... and have fun.
Look happy.
'Today this boy wants to represent India.'
'Tomorrow if he turns into a criminal..'
'..then you'll be responsible for it.'
Don't drink too much, Pali..
..or you might get out-of-control.
Today I am going to drink up a storm.
Drink up a storm!
My friend's back...to look after me.
Paridhi. - Where are you?
I've been trying to reach you for 10 days.
But it's always unreachable.
Isn't this what you wanted?
I said something in a fit of rage, and you left.
Is this your love?
I am really, really sorry.
It's my fault.. - No, Paridhi.
I was wrong with you.
Please forgive me.
Guddi. Come here.
Guddi.. - What's going on?
Pali..
..why are you drinking so much?
Because I am very happy today.
You know...there was a time..
..when we couldn't afford a square meal.
And now...
Look..
I've everything.
Everything.
Money. Power.
Today...
...I can throw a feast for the entire village.
Right, Lokesh? - Right.
Well, forget that...and tell me how are you?
And how's the Major?
Gyani.
Hello, Gyani. Where are you?
Don't you want to practice shooting?
What?
You've been granted permission.
Hang up the phone and come back quickly.
Yes, Major. I'm coming back.
Good.
Really, brother, did he get permission?
Have I ever lied to you?
Oh, God. Brother, I am so happy.
I'm so happy.
On this joyous occasion, have a drink with me.
Come on.
Pali.
Gyani. What is it?
You look really happy.
Yes, Pali.
Your brother's been granted permission.
Now just watch. I'll beat everyone at the championship.
This time I'll win a gold medal for India.
Well, Pali, I'll leave.
I've to prepare.
You won't go anywhere.
Pali, I have to go.
I said you're not going, and that's it.
Who do you think you are?
You can come here whenever you like.
And leave when you want.
I have feelings too.
I feel hurt too, Gyani.
And you...want to leave your friend, for those strangers.
That's not it, Pali.
Pali.. - Leave me, Guddi.
Pali...
Pali, try to understand.
I have to go back.
It's my dream.
You don't have to see any dream.
You don't need it.
You don't. - I have to go.
Rascal..
Pali... - Let go.
Pali... - Leave me.
Come on, Paridhi. Come on.
I need more, more, more.
I need at least 5 more. Quick.
Now why are you so slow?
Brother, let him come first.
He's on his way, we just spoke.
There's a lot to do.
He hasn't practiced.
But mark my words, that boy's gold medalist material.
Gyani. We were just talking about you.
You have a long life.
You'll live for at least 100 years.
What's wrong?
Why are you so sad?
Forgive me, Major. - For what?
I made a big mistake.
Gyani.
What's this, Gyani?
It's just... - What?
It's just a minor injury, that's all.
Minor wound...or bullet wound.
Gyani, what were you thinking?
Gyani..
God. There's no point.
You will never understand.
I did everything.
How will you shoot now?
Gyani.
Pali's your true friend, isn't it?
I don't just believe it..
..I know he's my true friend.
What kind of a friend is he, who tried to kill you?
If he wanted to kill me, he would've shot here.
Not here.
So what's this? - This.
This was his pain...
...of separation.
Then keep you can keep your friend and his pain.
Paridhi.
What's wrong, Paridhi?
Paridhi?
What are you doing, Pali?
Why are you ruining your life?
What else can I do?
I can't think of anything.
Go away.
Your brother's been granted permission.
You won't go anywhere.
Pali, I have to go.
I said you're not going, and that's it. - It's my dream.
You will desert your friend for those strangers.
Rascal..
Gyani!
Pali.
He's gone.
He hasn't gone anywhere.
He will come back.
He won't come back, Guddi.
I shot him.
I...shot him.
I shot my brother.
Pali, it was a mistake.
Pali, you didn't do it intentionally.
Pali, calm down.
But I am responsible, Guddi.
I committed a big sin.
I can never forgive myself.
Pali..
Brother...Gyani will get tough competition..
..from Australia and Germany.
You're absolutely right.
These two have been securing no.1 and no.2 positions..
..for past many events.
But you cannot underestimate any of the other teams.
Gyani will have to work hard.
Gyani.
What are you thinking?
I am missing Pali.
My mind's clotted with strange thoughts.
Call him.
I tried calling him, but he didn't answer.
I am scared.
It's very important for me to meet him.
Please, sir, just once.. - Sorry.
This isn't possible.
Pali.
Hello, Pali.
Where are you? I tried calling you.
I am at our old hangout, come quickly.
Our hangout.
I'm coming.
Major...
...please let me go.
Please.
As a coach, I cannot allow you to go.
But as a human being..
..I won't stop you.
Thank you, sir.
Pali, my brother.
Rascal, you trouble me so much.
And...why weren't you answering my calls?
Tell me.
Rascal...
...how could I answer your call?
Forgive me.
I made a big mistake.
So...you're still stuck on that.
You shot me here.
Well, you can shoot me here too.
I can even give my life for you.
Buddy, take care of it for me.
Pali, there's still time.
Leave everything.
You'll gain nothing through shedding blood.
You've really turned wise.
You don't understand.
It's still not too late.
But you know...
...I never look back.
Forget it, keep this.
When you play for India, keep this close to you.
I'll feel that I'm standing next to you.
Now this is your world, your goal.
You made this possible, Major.
Your efforts did.
A journey which started from a small with a pistol..
..could've never made it this far.
Go grab the opportunity.
"When you've just one life."
"Don't think, it's either cut or cure."
"An honorable life...
"No matter how strong your body is.."
"..without courage, you'll always be a prey."
"When the fire's burning."
"When the balance is just right."
"Whether its attack or defense, whether its check or mate."
"Aim at your target with all your rage."
"Shoot..."
"Don't miss your target."
"Shoot. Just shoot."
"Don't let your desires die."
"Create an uproar with your unmatched skill."
"Listen to your heart, and no one else."
"Shoot..."
"Don't miss your target."
"Shoot. Just shoot."
"Don't let your desire die."
Pali.
Why are you so sad?
Gyani hasn't left you.
He's just not close to you.
Pali..
But Suraj's coming.
Suraj? - Yes. Suraj.
Pali, do I have to explain you everything?
Guddi.
Guddi. What happened?
Guddi, you'll be fine.
You'll be fine.
Guddi.
Guddi, I will come back.
I will come back.
Guddi, are you listening?
Look, Pali.
Look, Pali. - Rascal..
Pali...don't hit me.
Guddi, get up.
I was deeply hurt...
...when I heard about Guddi.
People come and go.
But life doesn't stop.
You've to do many tasks.
Life means moving on.
Hari.
Greetings, Guru.
Bless you, Hari.
What's wrong, Hari?
Why did you call me?
I am in a dilemma. - Really?
Since you're my Guru, I thought I should discuss it with you.
Yes, of course.
Tell me the problem, and I'll solve it.
He who remembers God knows no sensual pleasures
He who doesn't remember God takes delight in sensual pleasures
God and sensual pleasures won't unite
as there can be no union of the Sun and the night.
Don't confuse me.
What's the matter?
If a kin deceives you...
...then what should we do?
Is that all?
If it's someone special, then he should be given a chance.
Otherwise..
Hari...
You were special...
...but not too special.
Mahadev.
When a pupil exceeds his mentor..
..and makes him proud..
..the mentor feels proud.
But when the same pupil treads on the wrong path..
..the mentor feels humiliated.
I can't kill you, because you're like a son to me.
But I can distance you from me.
Judge sir, how can you say that?
What did I do wrong?
You've to think what right..
..or wrong you did.
Mahadev!
Ladies and Gentleme.
This is World Shooting Championship..
..Rapid Fire Pistol, finals series 1.
Shooters, to your firing point.
What is all this?
Tell me.
Every kid from my village wants to be Judge sir.
And now...
...it's my turn.
What's all this?
Tell me. Tell me.
Guru, I don't think this gun's ever going to fire again.
But this one will, won't it.
Don't worry, sir.
Just keep sending your orders from across the border.
We're here for you.
This time India will be mortified in front of the entire world.
I promise you that.
Goodbye.
Lokesh..
..I want you to turn this shooting championship into a bloodbath..
..which should take India ages to wipe the stains.
But, sir, what about Gyani.
Nothing's more important than your objective.
Rascal, you forgot...my brother's competing here.
If I give my life for the sake of friendship..
..then, I can take one too.
All the best.
You will win.
Go.
You can shed all the blood you want.
But you cannot stop this mission from completing.
Try and save the one you killed my comrades for.
India's just one step away..
..from winning its first Gold Medal..
..in the World Shooting Championship.
The entire responsibility lies on Gyani Singh, from Uttar Pradesh.
We've to watch whether..
..Gyani can win this round and fulfill India's dreams.
India! India! India! India! India!
Oh my, God!
Pali!
What has happened?
Brother...
...everything's fine now.
Now no one can stop you from achieving your dreams.
Pali!
I've made things right.
You're bleeding so much.
Doctor!
Doctor! - No.
Let me go.
No, don't be crazy.
I won't let you die. - Gyani.
Try to understand.
Guddi's alone. - What?
Sister-in-law Guddi..
I have to go.
My brother.. - Pali.
Promise me...that you will fulfill your dream.
I will always be with you.
Pali.
Pali, no..
Go and win.
Someone call the doctor.
Doctor.
Pali.
Pali. Get up.
Pali!
Pali! Get up.
Pali, don't fool around with me.
Look, we've to return to the village together.
What are you doing?
Get up.
Major..
Major...he likes to fool around.
He'll get up...now.
Now..
Pali, get up.
Why are you crying?
He'll get up.
He'll get up now.
He's a big ham!
Get up.
Pali. Get up.
Pali!
No, son.
No, Gyani.
Don't cry.
If you shatter now..
If you shatter now...
..the millions of dreams will shatter along with Pali's.
You will have to get up.
You have to get up and go win that gold.
And go make your friendship immortal.
Everything will be okay.
God!
Finally, India's dreams have come true.
Gyani's won the Gold Medal..
..in the 25 meters Rapid Fire Pistol round series 1..
..and created history.
Gyani. - Pali.
"My companion."
"You're my friend."
"Our bond is the most unique."
"My companion."
"You're my friend."
"Our bond is the most unique."
"May you always stay ahead.."
"..and your sagas follow you."
"Even if our paths are separate.."
"..but all I think about I you."
"Even if our destinations are different.."
"Crossing all barriers...breaking every limit."
"You're my trial."
"You're my obsession."
"Our bond is the most unique."
"My companion."
"You're my friend."
"Our bond is the most unique."
"My companion."
"You're my friend."
"Our bond is the most unique."