Fixed & Synced by bozxphd.Enjoy The Flick
My name is Kapil.
I am a search & Rescue Trainer
and mountaineering Instructor.
I train people to fight adversities
and win over them saving
others and themselves.
Look at the coincidence,
Jaideep.
These roads are the same, Same is the view.
But that time is lost somewhere.
Silence has just passed by the ears.
Perhaps something was said mildly.
These roads are the same, Same is the view.
But that time is lost somewhere.
Silence has just passed by the ears.
Perhaps something was said mildly
it is the well known aroma.
That I feel in the dreams.
Where is that dream destination.
That is often visited by the clouds
it is the well known aroma.
That I feel in the dreams.
This is Gauri, Kshitijs fiance
both used to teach in the
school for special kids.
Dipankar, Kshitijs friend.
Children would also join us one day, Sure.
Looking at them as mountaineers
will change people's perception
and they will get respect instead of pity.
Kshitij...
probably a mountaineer like him...
But destiny had other plans...
Kshitij...
Both of them come here every year...
To remember lost friends...
and to remember kshitijs dream...
dream that is still unfulfilled.
In search & rescue training camp,
today we will talk about disasters.
Do you know why so many people get
killed in disasters and accidents?
Have we ever thought about it.
Because we lack life saving skills.
Rather than first-aid during accidents,
we handle victims like dead wood,
We cannot deliver CPR, instead start to
manhandle the doctor in case of deaths.
Bisht...
just check
and then we have neither a
plan nor knowledge for rescue.
How can then we expect.
To be saved in an emergency?
Hello, may I help you.
Hello.
Is it some mountaineering course?
National Social Service camp.
NSS...
We impart disaster
management related training.
What to do? What not to do?
Wow, sounds good
I saw those ropes so thought
its a mountaineering course
search and rescue is part of this training
and you
yes...
I myself...
Gauri.
Sir.
Some school people.
OK
Were interested in organizing
a mountaineering course.
Seen her somewhere.
Coincidentally I was the one
leading this operation to.
We found only one of them
alive and that was Dipankar.
Mr. Pandey,
We are trying our best.
Sir,
he is deaf... he cant hear...
just after few hours.
How can you say...
that he cannot be traced.
Dipankar shared that Kshitij
had left to bring help...
but we could not trace him even
after searching for a week...
and then one day...
yes sir,
Sir, we have found one bag...
Heart aspires to be with the birds,
Like a butterfly in the sky.
We shall fly high to catch the sun.
We will achieve our goal.
Let us fly...
Let us fly a bit.
Let us stretch our wings,
Let us fly like that.
We also wish to see all this from up there.
Let us fly...
We have started to fly...
As a team leader,
returning Kshitij's belongings was my duty.
I had tried this many times before,
but...
Number does not exist
his belongings, a bag and
diary were with me...
and Gauri was in front of me.
But then seeing her happy in
the world of deaf children,
I started thinking...
Whether these belonging
matter to her anymore
may be...
not now...
You wanted to see me.
Yes, in a camp... you had met my colleague.
Camp...!
We were impartng search
and rescue tranning,
at Kalsi.
Oh.. yes...
Please... come.
He is Kshitij.
This was his vision
to change perception of society.
Wanted to show that these children
are not disabled
but are differently abled.
Although...
we have Disabilities Act
available since 1995
but situation has not changed much.
Government and families...
both are to be blamed.
That is Gurfareen.
Her mother had given up.
Had no clue about her
schooling.
After all most schools
are for normal children.
I undersatnd that
so true.
Heart sings on the note of love.
You say and I would interpret.
Our world is the world of love.
One Sign here does all the magic.
Let the silence sing,
Let us sing the same.
Let us stretch our wings,
Let us move like the wind.
Our path leads from heart to heart.
Let us fly...
We have started to fly...
These children are lively
as long as they are here.
Back home there is no one to talk or play.
Deafness is no more a problem.
Now early detection is possible
and with proper therapy, these
children can lead a normal life.
After all something has to be done.
So that people look upon them with pride.
And that's simple. They
have to reach the top.
Have to show something.
DipankarPlease come.
Dipankar he is Kapil, Kapil he is Dipankar.
Our founder member.
Nice to meet you.
Please have a seat.
We were five.
Who began this journey with a dream
now only two are left.
Kshitij loved adventure sports.
Actually we had come here to
open an adventure academy.
Where these children could prove themselves
and give joy to their families.
But
still chasing dreams.
Let's see.
We would be blessed one day
and we await that day.
Can you help us?
May be... little bit.
Everyone wanted to go
but some were very young and
others parents were apprehensive
finally 13 children were selected.
With glittering eyes.
They have come out fully dressed.
Their hands say many stories.
If only you can understand.
Give us similar stories.
Let us also glitter.
Let us stretch our wings.
Let us step on the cloud.
Yes we have started our journey of dreams.
We have started to fly.
Welcome to NIM.
Thanks Kapil
had dreamt of this.
Welcome to Nehru Institute
of Mountaineering (NIM)
So children welcome to NIM.
Good...
after all we too have
social responsibility.
Sir
Burma bridge and trekking.
What do you say?
But sir children have
come for basic course.
Actually... Rajendra.
Special course instructor
I hope you know him.
Yes sir...
Actually, He had to join yesterday.
Got his message just now.
He won't be back soon.
Actually... his father is a heart patient.
End of 13 dreams before
they actually began.
This course... OK
after this another course
complete that as well.
Train others after these courses.
You would certainly do that
and become a great trainer
but...
There is a little dream.
That bud only wants to bloom.
Dont know why there are
obstacles everywhere.
From the little heartbeats.
Veiled in these passing moments.
It is coming from the world of aspirations.
It is the aroma of our destination.
Dear Kid, after this course, you
will not be a helpless girl.
What are you thinking Mr. Kapil?
Sir Dipankar... who is with these children.
He knows basics of mountaineering.
But his leg.
Sir, I feel... he won't have
any problem in the campus.
And once the children start to pick up,
We can take care of the
rest in training area.
Everyone around is excited
about this course
particularly the media.
So afterwards there should not be
we are there, dont worry.
Attention, get prepared. Wipe out the dust.
Dont wager. Shed tiredness.
Be brave, remain prepared. Be attentive
all the time. March on fearlessly.
March on, march on
Keep marching forward.
Keep going up.
Watch every step, Reach the sky.
March on, march on
Keep marching forward.
Watch every step.
Reach the sky.
Roar aloud. Be heard in all directions.
Such should be the battle cry.
With your shoulders up.
Lock your horns and roll on.
Be eager to accomplish.
Remove all hindrances.
You are also now the referee.
You have now to get your due share.
So you have to march forward.
You have to go up.
Watch your steps.
With resolve you have to get your goal.
Dipankar, just ask the kids, how
they found todays training?
Thank you!
She is Hima Ma'm. Has scaled many peaks.
So No communication without him.
Who is to teach?
Me or him?
Meet Dipankar.
Their sign language instructor.
Namaste.
Well children, three things
are must for mountaineering.
Courage, Technique and Passion.
Has diffused entire passion.
Where have you brought them from?
Means?
Means...!
No. It's not possible like this.
First he would learn and then...
would teach the children.
Like this... How.
What Rajendra and you, do in
adventure course is not my concern.
This is basic course.
And you know
these techniques are taught
by direct communication.
Do one thing.
Arrange video classes.
He would see and teach.
To be true, even you would not be required.
Brilliant idea Ma'm.
Why don't you share it with Principal Sir?
Sir, Director Sir has called you.
I would be back soon
you continue sharing your vast experience.
How...?
You already know.
Good morning, Sir.
Good morning...
have a seat
sir...
So... what about training.
Nice,
Children are enjoying.
Hima Ma'm is taking knotting class.
Good. Once the children
are thorough with basics.
We would invite the media.
Yes, Sir.
Would demonstrate in front of Rock no. 7
and be careful. There would
also be national media also.
Sure sir.
Hopping.
Continue hopping.
Keep doing.
Hima's funda of training -
Rough works makes one tough
otherwise all right but not
for these special children.
Dipankar, what is this going on?
What can I do?
Let me see.
What is this Ma'm?
Dont you have any emotions?
Emotions...
My foot...
Foo. t.
Seem it was a tough class.
Oh, it was short tempered madame's class...
Good... good. Think like these...
you all will go ahead...
Let's begin yoga.
Children would also join us one day, Sure.
Looking at them as mountaineers
will change people's perception
and they will get respect instead of pity.
Hello Dipankar.
How is the training going on?
They are catching up fast.
Our dream is getting realized.
Oh yes, I forgot to tell you
asking about their well being...
Really
who all...
please... talk with them
please...
Your son Ashish says
to bring home happiness
and make you feel proud.
And make you feel proud.
He has also silently woven a dream
and he has taken a vow
to fulfill this dream.
All my joys are related to you
I have always dreamt with moist eyes.
That you reply to my call and
say-What do you say, Mother.
This is Gurfareens mother speaking.
She is asking you not to cry.
What if she cannot listen,
but she understands everything.
Your silence makes me weep, How
do I overcome this sorrow?
I understand what you tell me, But how
do I tell you what I have to say?
You are my life, Wish I
could give you all joy.
Where ever you may be,
Come I want to embrace you.
Your son says that he is
doing all this for you.
He continues to run despite being tired
just for you.
So...
that you could be proud.
Time has come to show what
these kids have learnt.
To demonstrate, these kids
have prepared a small skit.
A car travelling through
mountain road
meets with an accident
and car falls in a gorge.
To rescue the passengers.
Our basic mountaineering
course trainees come.
These disabled children must
be trained differently?
Firstly... these children are not disabled
they are differently abled.
They are just hearing impaired,
but their other senses are
even more developed than us.
Sorry sir.
We had missed out that angle.
Not your mistake.
Most people think that way.
As regards to this training
complete course is designed
specially in sign language.
I'll tell you what's more.
First of this level... in the entire world.
First course of this level?
Yes...
This is the basic course on mountaineering.
After campus training of 20 days
they would be going for
high altitude expedition,
oh... that kid.
Madam... Madam...
What does report say, Doctor?
You need complete bed rest.
After how many days shall I be
fit for childrens training?
No... Not before two weeks.
Good morning Sir.
Good morning.
Hi Dipankar, How are you?
That, Doctor will tell.
Sir, shoulder is dislocated.
Also a minor fracture in collar bone.
So... complete bed rest for now.
Is referral required to higher centre?
No Sir. Bed rest is enough.
Sir.
What about your hand... Kapil.
Fine Sir.
Would take some time to recover.
So what next?
Sir... I was about to talk
to you regarding this...
Are these children ready
for the expedition?
No Sir.
Rajendra would be back next week only.
Until then.
Sir, I want some more time.
OK
What happend?
Hey what?
Why are you sitting sadly?
Ok, you are sad because Ashish and
Sir got hurt due to your mistake.
Oh no... Nothing will happen. No tension...
Smile... good boy... smile... ok.
Smile...
Your training? Your traning
shall start soon... ok.
Sad no... smile... happy OK.
Very good... good child.
I am convincing them...
but... how is the training going to start?
It was their fate.
It seemed like someone was gone.
But then they were performing quite well.
What if some casualty.
You are right Ma'm.
Sign language trainer is not around.
So... first teach him...
and then...
he will teach.
Look...
the fact is that.
These children do not deserve training.
I also had a feeling that.
Basic course going to be
very tough for children.
But they are catching things fast.
Catching things.
Mr. Matches are not won just by catching.
You require balling
and batting as well.
You all would realize
Only after some mishap.
Look...
As long as everything goes well,
everyone would cheer Kapil...
But if... anything happens to any child...
then... they would do... Kapil...
and then... how would
you face their parents?
I beg you Sir...
take care of her.
Sir... I am a poor man.
Don't really know how to converse.
Please keep this petty sum.
They don't really speak out.
Please provide if they ask for anything.
Now she is your responsibility
I have never been alone... without her
I alone know how I'm sending her.
Good morning Mr. Kapil.
Good morning.
What happened? No training today.
Training... It's over now.
What do you mean?
You were right
I took it emotionally
not realizing the consequences
of any mishap with the kids.
Then.
Then... What about those children?
Their dream?
Intentions were good...
but...
then...
So finally I am going to request
to cancel this training.
May be will take it up some other
time if its in their destiny.
But then this course is their dream.
But Mr. Kapil...
I think...
you should take another chance.
One chance...
One more chance...
but how?
How are you?
Fine...
What about the course?
Will begin again.
Never let your dreams die,
You now need your inner self.
Day or night, you never to stop.
You have to rewrite your destiny.
Should be no illusion,
Such has to be your action,
Obstructions should bow before you.
That should be your intention.
Have firm resolve.
None has courage to face you.
So you have to march forward.
You have to go up.
Watch your steps,
With resolve you have to get your goal.
So you have to march forward.
You have to go up.
Watch your steps,
With resolve you have to get your goal.
These children are wonderful.
Just have to tell once.
They are wonderful from
both heart and mind.
You just have to understand them
and this fact...
most people don't understand.
Children...
This expedition is a challenge for us.
You have to apply, what all you
have learnt in this training.
Therefore, if you wish to make
a career in mountaineering,
You should complet this
expedition seriously.
And yes...
The best performer will
receive this gorgeous trophy.
Dreams have started to
fly towards destination.
Little brush has started painting joy.
Dreams have started to
fly towards destination.
Little brush has started painting joy.
We are going to walk far,
to achieve our dreams.
There is a dream village, somewhere...
That is often visited by the clouds.
It is the well known aroma.
That I feel in the dreams
I Wanted to take children for the
expedition but my hand injury.
Anyways...
Childrens dream was getting
fulfilled I was happy.
Hima,
Whenever you feel it's not safe to proceed
or children won't be able to do.
Move back at once. Understood?
Yes Sir.
Oh... Rajendra tell them,
They have to carry their own luggage.
Sure ma'm, they will carry it.
Rough work... makes tough...
yes...
Kshitij... I am missing him a lot today.
Don't know why.
I feel something is not right.
Dont worry.
Our children are tough.
That's all right.
But, Kapil should have been with them.
Kapil, If not there
he is here...
Here? What do you mean?
You were looking pretty
cute while laughing.
I couldn't get you...
Kapil is a good man...
and complete too...
Told Kapil... so many times...
Have to be rough,
If not there... then here.
Yes get up, get going.
Should have been at the
camping site by now.
Like this we are not going
to make it before sunset.
We have not come far enough.
Those who...
are not able to continue,
can give up and return...
O Rajendra,
You tell... in their way.
They cannot do the expedition.
Have to get back tomorrow anyway...
So... why not today itself?
Children...
now its not much.
Have courage and keep going.
Soon it's going to be gentle and plain.
Ok...
We have to complete this expedition.
Have to return only after
we are successful.
Ok...
Rough work... makes tough...
To excel is your religion.
Mountain is high but not more than you.
Cross the limits,
Know yourself.
Swear by yourself, never to give up.
They may say what they want,
That should not affect you.
Your heart should reflect courage.
Even though you are alone,
You have to march on and alone.
You have to march forward.
You have to go up.
With resolve you have to get your goal.
You have to march forward.
(FOLK SONG) Fruit Beru
ripens all through the air,
(FOLK SONG) Fruit Kafal however
ripens only in March-April.
Ok, dinner will be ready in some time.
How was it today?
You must be tired.
It was really steep climb.
You are really tough.
Would send it over to us?
What? Enjoying?
Food would be ready in two minutes.
Eat and sleep silently.
And what were you talking about photos?
O... Ma'm
and don't worry about photos.
I would send those. Real good once.
Ma'm, this seems too high...
for the children?
Oh... Its high...?
Now you would tell me.
This is just the basic
course of children...
If it could be lowered a bit.
Mr. Rajendra...
This request... better addressed to Kapil.
Would have been far better
if you and Kapil
could do this in some park...
some swing activity.
All this trouble was not required?
If you agree,
we can call it off.
Ma'm you tend to take everything otherwise.
Remember.
To make them tough, You have to be rough.
Ma'm... Over here...
I don't undertand your rough - tough logic.
What if,
one of them has to summit some peak
and the ropes are equally high?
Then...
Sir... Sir...
getting late... hurry up...
Hima ma'm...
Rajendra sir...
Hello...
Hello... NIM.
Yes Hima... what is the position.
Rajendra... Has face and chest injury.
And you?
Fine Sir... Just knee...
Everything will be fine sir. No problem.
Sir please... ask about the children.
No tension sir. They are children.
Were a bit disturbed. They are normal now.
Sir, moving Rajendra.
Two porters are with him.
Would reach the road head in 7 - 8 hours.
What's your program?
Continue Sir.
Take care of children.
All the best Hima.
Right sir.
By day after, others would join you.
Then you have to complete the expedition
and hoist the flag...
ok.
Hey...
Hope you are not staying back.
And put this phone on charging.
What's the matter,
Ma'm... Got hurt.
How it happened?
Want to sing a song?
This is nothing... Solid mountaineer.
Go and get into your tents,
Nobody should get out.
Not even to piss...
get lost?
Go...
want to do expedition!
Want to do expedition!
Ramesh, just check body temperature.
Sir...
You gave me CPR
saved me...
Thank you.
You children...
how to communicate!
I love you...
Nothing... You leave.
Go... Go to your tents.
Nothing has happened.
You go... go.
Yes... Go.
What has happen to this?
There are three ways of saving
injured person in the mountains.
First provide first aid.
After that, send message for rescue.
And third...
Imediately prepare to
move the injured person.
Hello...
Hello Sir.
You have a long life.
I did not follow you.
We were talking about you only
I was telling them
anyone other then Hima,
Would have abandoned the course mid way
but It is your courage,
that despite being
injured, you are continuing the course.
Petwal with two porters
would start in a while.
By tomorrow noon they would reach you.
Till then you take rest.
Now its a challenge for you, Hima.
But Sir
There seems problem with my leg...
You have to arrange for
helicopter rescue Sir.
Please Sir, it's serious.
Hello...
Sir...
Hello Sir.
Oh, what do I do now?
Officials of the institute are
shying away from these questions.
Be what, we have to
continue the expedition.
Petwal.
Yes Sir...
when are you leaving?
Just getting things issued
I will have to leave.
If I dont leave in time...
My leg...
No... not that.
No... I would have to leave.
But... children.
Children...
I would have to move.
Another team would come by tomorrow.
You have to...
complete the expedition.
In a way that is right...
Nobody would be around now to scold you.
No children...
you stay here
but If I stay,
I will lose my leg,
and...
remember...
you are not alone.
Entire group is togther
you have to complete your expedition
we will celebrate...
ok.
And...
please click photos for me.
Smile has come back again.
Eyes have indicated.
Someone dear has come back.
One who has lost, has come back.
Heart has heard, what you said.
Love is our only language.
We are also like you, we are no different.
Why are you following me?
Don't want to complete the expedition?
That is your dream...
You have to fulfil that...
That's your future...
After a while there is a waterfall.
From there... through the caves...
there is a short cut.
After that down slope...
there come a river.
Rafters keep coming upto that place.
Your Ma'm has to reach there.
Don't get emotional, You go back now.
And there is no sign
language trainer with them.
Weather is very unpredictable
at such heights
and Hima herself is injured
and there is no communication.
And for our viewers,
and this if the weather is favorable.
Where ever you may be, come
I want to embrace you.
My life revolves round you.
I await your return.
When would you say, Hide
me in your embrace, Mother.
Petwal was sent in place
of injured Rajendra,
it was decided that expedition will
begin as soon as he reaches there.
It was a routine change of
plans for mountaineers like us
but for Gauri... it was not.
Childrens expedition...
Dreams of so many are attached to this.
Of their parents
our's...
and...
Kshitij.
You know...
I can still feel him around...
in my dreams.
Often enquires... about children
about our dreams
I know he is not going to return
but don't know why...
I still keep waiting...
had...
had they searched properly...
May be... he would have been with us
have just a few photographs of Kshitij...
taken before he was lost
and... Nothing else...
Nothing else...
Gauri...
You dont worry.
Petwal is going
and Hima is already there.
This media always exaggerates situations.
Children are safe.
Trust me.
It is the well -known aroma...
That I feel in the dreams.
Put together every bit of courage.
Leave behind all fear.
Make the best attempt.
Tear off all obstructions.
Put together every bit of courage.
Leave behind all fear.
Make the best attempt.
Tear off all obstructions.
Have sight of your goal.
And trace your path.
Mountains do move.
You have to gather strength.
Who would stop you.
Gather your strength.
Put together every bit of courage.
Leave behind all fear
face the obstructions on your path.
Exhibit your talent to the world.
March on, march on.
Don't stop, these winds can't move you.
You have now to move ahead with the storm.
March on, march on.
You have to exhibit your passion.
And have to get to your dream.
Who would stop you.
You have to gather strength.
Put together every bit of courage.
Leave behind all fear.
Make the best attempt.
Tear off all obstructions.
What if dreams are not fulfilled?
What if we are not that lucky?
We would place together our dream.
What if there is no help?
We have to reach the destination.
We have to do something innovative.
We are not incomplete.
Courage makes us complete.
If it is dark you have to invoke.
Light that is within you.
You have to find answer.
To all the questions they ask.
Challenge your destiny.
You have to have faith in your attempts.
You have to shine like sun.
And have to create history.
Make courage your tool
and you would celebrate success.
Why do you stop?
What do you fear?
Get up and have resolve.
You have to get to your goal.
Have sight of your goal.
Who would stop you.
Gather your strength.
Put together every bit of courage.
Leave behind all fear.
Make the best attempt.
Tear off all obstructions.
You all did far more then I could have
to tell you the truth...
I could't understand you...
If I was in your position...
I would have completed the expedition.
You all are really great.
You are my silent heroes.
Hima salutes you.
Come on... go get some wood,
We shall have fire. It is very cold.
Go... go...
go...
Now its all over My leg.
Now all over...
Sir, location is shown
8 km from rafting site on
Dayara Bugyal trekking route.
Over here?
But why?
Is it some other location...
Then this new location? And children?
Bisht.
Yes Sir.
You proceed with a team for recce.
Right Sir.
Be prepared for rescue.
Ok Sir.
Kapil.
You monitor Rajendra's team.
Inform me after connecting with them.
Right Sir.
Sir, can I also go till the rafting site?
Yes..
Where did you reach?
Sir crossed Harsil.
OK. How is Rajendra?
Still unconscious Sir
ok...
Call me again as you are
about to reach the hospital.
Right Sir.
Oh..You were the leader of
that search and rescue team.
That neither searched nor rescued.
You would have considered
him dead the very first day.
Search... Just a formality.
And the mission is over...
He did not die.
You murdered him.
Your negligence killed him...
It's good you were not sent
to search the children.
Otherwise once again...
Hope others are not like you...
Hope once again I am not kept in dark.
This time I would go myself...
To rescue my children...
and would return only with them...
otherwise...
What was my crime?
I should have returned
that bag in school only...
Then there would have
been neither this diary
or nor those 13 innocent dreams.
What's the matter Sir?
Many undelivered parcels these days...
I am a guide Sir,
But...
you.
From NIM.
Have come for rescue of one of our group.
Oh...
Anyway...
Ma'm...
I suggest, you wait out here...
and we proceed.
But sir, can't I proceed further with you?
Ma'm its a steep climb ahead
like this.
Let's finish the inspection.
Would decide after that...
Joshi...
Let's proceed...
Hey... Hi.
Hello... Here.
Jaideep.
Tarun...
Tarun... Look here.
My children you are very intelligent...
I love you so much.
Yes...
Ma'm, children are on
other side of the river,
Please call them... to this side...
Water current is very fast in the middle.
They would not be able to manage this.
Ma'm there is a dangerous rapid ahead.
What?
Dangerous rapid?
Call them this side fast Ma'm.
Only experienced rafters can cross that.
Tarun...
Dont cry . Dont cry.
Tarun, come this side.
Tarun.
Kapil.
Kapil...
Thanks.
Ma'm... emotions!
Emotions my foot.
First he will learn...
and then he will teach.
Everyone go inside your tents
dont come out,
not even to piss
get lost...
Come on... be fast...
want to do expedition!
And because of her unprofessional attitude,
Kshitijs dreams.
That people look upon them with pride...
You would tell better if
the same was realised.
But then...
I am dreaming right now of the next
training for these children...
These roads are the same, Same is the view.
But that time is lost somewhere.
Silence has just passed by the ears.
Perhaps something was said mildly.
These roads are the same, Same is the view.
But that time is lost somewhere.
Silence has just passed by the ears.
Perhaps something was said mildly
it is the well known aroma.
That I feel in the dreams.
There is a dream village, somewhere...
That is often visited by the clouds.
It is the well known aroma.
That I feel in the dreams.
Dreams have started to
fly towards destination.
Little brush has started painting joy.
Dreams have started to
fly towards destination.
Little brush has started painting joy.
We are going to walk far,
to achieve our dreams.
There is a dream village, somewhere...
That is often visited by the clouds.
It is the well known aroma.
One who teaches others
to save themselves is stuck himself today.
This deaf school teacher used to dream of
making these children someone special..
All this... because We really don't know
how to respond in emergency.
Search & rescue operation began
when Kshitijs group did not return.
Till date we used to organize only adventure
courses for children with special needs
but now we are going to start for the first time,
a basic mountaineering course for deaf children.
We spoke with their parents regarding this
course.
When he was very young, he used to
watch other kids go to school and cry
and today he has gone to do
this big course, all alone.
This is a concern for the parents,
school and the whole deaf community
because this course will decide whether
such courses are feasible or not.
Finally the day has arrived, which
we all have been waiting for.
Group of children has begun
their high altitude expedition.
Let us give you some details
of this expedition.
After 6 hours road journey from Uttarkashi,
Children will trek through
high Himalayan passes,
Children shall complete their training
by hoisting flags on these heights.
He is benig moved to Uttarkashi.
What caused the accident and
whether the children are safe?
There is nothing to worry.
Children are perfectly safe.
Our another team would
reach there by tomorrow.
Group of 13 deaf children is
stranded in the Himalayas.
Mr. Dipankar, right now only
team leader Hima is there.
She does not know sign language.
How will she manage them?
These children have spent some
time with her during training.
God forbid. Nothing of
that sort should happen.
Indian Mountaineering and rescue
federation has suspended Hima.
That their names would be
recommended for President's Award.
We spoke to their trainer, Kapil.
You can see this raft made by the kids. You can see
how it was made. It is not a professional raft...
I really doubt if normal children could have done
what these kids have done. They are extra ordinary.
May be this first film of it's kind and we
are all proud to be associated with it.
Group of 13 children from Bajaj Institute of Learning, Dehradun has
reached NIM, Uttarkashi, for special training and mountaineering mission.
To understand problems and safety concerns, we
spoke with their teacher who is still in hospital.
The children are 2 day trek and 6 hours
of road journey away from Uttarkashi.
Primary objective of this course is to give a direction
to these kid's lives and a new career for them.
He was very happy while leaving,
what else I need as a father.
We have to give back at least something to
the under privileged segment of the society.
I think... like adventure course these
children should be exposed to river crossing,
So... engage them in some activities
so that they are not disappointed.
You have to change your life. As it was never
before. You have to do something different.
She would tell you about knotting.
Knotting means tying ropes together.
He would be required in the beginning only.
After that children would on their own.
Yes. It happens after exercise.
You will be fine in couple of days.
Since the time kids have gone,
their parents keep coming here.
Bad news for those awaiting successful realization
of dreams of 13 deaf kids in mountaineering course.
Yesterday their sign language trainer got injured in an
accident during training and is admitted in the hospital.
We would like to tell the viewers that a group of
13 deaf children is on a mountaineering course.
In the light of what has happened, it is
likely that the course may be cancelled.
Tell me, without completing the training,
how will the kids go on the expedition?
As per the latest reports sign language trainer Rajendra has
been seriously injured on very second day of the expedition.
And I assure you that these children would
return only after completing the expedition.
Has another team gone to get back the children?
Would they be able to complete the expedition?
A dream that we all saw together...
Would that dream come true?
Have to prove that our trainees are capable
of saving themselves and also others.
So they understand each other's expressions,
body language... They can certainly communicate.
In this situation if there is an emergency
or lets say some child falls sick then?
We would be in a position to comment only after the second
team reaches there and we talk to children... I mean Hima.
Group of these 13 kids has reached
Dehradun with their teachers and trainers.
Their dream of completing
the expedition did not materialize.
Still they have been selected for the advance course based on
their courage, decision making capability and team spirit.
While felicitating 4 children involved in "Makeshift
Raft Rescue" The Minister of Youth Welfare assured.
Hope it helped -> bozxphd