These statues are made
from some kind of sand.
If we try to move them.
"They will turn into million pieces.
The statue made from Bhairo..
...we're looking for
that panicular one..
"Which is wonh millions of dollars.
It's over 300 years old.
Mr. Samar, if you can
get that statue.
...we can crack the deal..in cash.
Yes, I'll talk to him.
Hello. - Hello.
I hope we get this statues. - Yes.
What are these Englishmen saying?
They're saying the same thing, Vikram.
They want the same unique
statue made by Bhairo.
I've been trying to tell you.
Stop being so stubborn.
You won't find that statue now.
- Brother Samar!
No need to enlighten me.
Big jobs require more time.
That statue will be found,
and I will find it.
"Crazy.."
Where are you going? - This way.
"What's this restlessness?"
"Maybe..l'm about to lose my heart."
Hey mister, you forgot this.
This isn't mine.
It was with your record player.
- Show me.
1954..Rajasthani Folk Music!
Remix. Remix, man.
Fine, we'll take a look at it later.
"Your crazy lover..calls out to you."
"It's your wish..whether
you come or not."
"Your crazy lover..calls out to you."
"It's your wish..whether
you come or not."
"Crazy.."
"My eyes wonder..where's my destiny."
"l wonder..why my
arms are still empty."
"l've spent sleepless nights alone."
"What's hard to get
over..is your intoxication."
"It's difficult to forget."
Guys, how is this?
- You're a rebel, man.
"Your crazy lover..calls out to you."
"It's your wish..whether
you come or not."
"Your crazy lover..calls out to you."
"It's your wish..whether
you come or not."
"Fair boys."
Good evening, Ladies and Gentlemen!
I hope you'll have been
enjoying yourselves this evening.
Now, without further
due I present to you Andi..
...who has a special
announcement to make.
Come on, girls, we have
only 10 seconds to hit the stage.
Girls, ready?
Now for what you've
all been waiting for.
The Bollywood spectacular,
performed by..
...a supermodel,
all the way from Milan.
The beautiful, the gorgeous,
the stunning, the sizzling..
Meera!
"Fair boys."
"My rustic look.."
"My rustic look..floored
the fair boys."
"My rustic look.."
"My rustic look..floored
the fair boys."
"l wear my earrings and dance,."
"l sway my hips and dance."
"Don't stop me now."
"My rustic look.."
"My rustic look..floored
the fair boys."
"My rustic look.."
"My rustic look..floored
the fair boys."
"l want to take you along, beautiful."
Oh my, God, Andi!
She's so hot!
I never thought you'll
be able to get Meera for my show.
Nothing is impossible
for the king of fashion.
"My beautiful face..glitters
like the moon."
"So says the stars."
"So says everyone."
"All the bachelors
are crazy about me."
"One eye on me and the
other on the hook of my blouse"
My rustic look.."
"My rustic look..floored
the fair boys."
Hey, great show. - Thank you.
Well done.
Get them all locked,
they're all booked.
It's great.
Go, go.
Andi.
Hi.
What a success?
And you know what. - What?
Mr. Smith's photo-shoot contract.
- One with Showbiz?
Yes. He's cancelled
that and given it to us.
Amazing. - I know.
And the credit goes to.
Me..- Ra
Credit goes to Meera.
Yeah right. - Where is she?
She must be in her makeup room.
This way.
Meera, lwould like
to introduce you to someone.
Meet the best photographer
and best friend of Andi.
Rads? - Yeah, hi.
Andi showed me your
pictures on his phone.
What a memory.
And what a figure.
You're looking really
hot in that shon skin, Meera?
You know, babes.
In the glamour industry,
the shoncut to success.
Is shon skin! - Oh.
I think you know very
well to the fashion industry.
Why don't you clearly
say that I am a b***
Oh..supermodel from
Milan and such attitude.
Meera from Milan, later.
First Manjeet Kaur
from Mohali, Punjab.
Rads from London, later.
First Radhika Randhawa
from Kapunhala, Punjab.
Awesome!
But imagine, sand dunes, camels.
Extravagant, amazing, stunning India.
For your campaign.
It's going to be the best campaign.
...and no one would've
seen this before.
I am telling you.
Thank God I found you.
Otherwise, in panies like this.
I normally find pervens
who rape me with their eyes.
Come, Rads dear. - Where?
Let's go pany, come on.
Meera. - Come on.
Where are we going?
Let's have some beer. - Beer.
Come on, Candy. - Coming, coming.
I'm coming.
I am drunk.
I think I am drunk. - Yeah.
Because you're already
four beers down.
Four beers?
But I have a question
Why didn't I drink
the founh one directly?
Why did I drink one, two and three?
- Because.
Before four, comes three, two and one.
My rustic look..
One more question.
It's an amazing song.
Who made it? - My cousin.
He lives in India.
He makes songs for
all of Andi's shows.
Oh..lndia.
Land of the loving and the caring.
What's his name? - Karan.
Oooh!
Hi, Radhika. - Hi, Karan. How are you?
All is well, how are you?
Your song..made my life.
I am telling you, I got so
many compliments for this last show.
A supermodel has become
a big fan of yours.
Do one thing, let everyone hear this.
I'll put the phone on speaker. Okay.
Guys, Radhika has a message for you.
Hi, guys.
Hey, Radhika.
Your "Desi Look" song is a hit.
You guys are rock stars.
And how's aunty?
Speaking in Mumbai language..
...every1hing's great at home.
Give my love to her, okay. - Bye.
Is the jingle ready? - Yes.
The producer's coming
in the evening to hear it.
Hear it.
Stand straight.
Superb..now put your
hand on the shoulder.
Keep changing.
Very good.
Nice smile.
Don't hold the candy.
Hold it.
Hold it on your eye.
Okay, girls, that's lovely.
Very well done with the setup.
Okay, Meera, now quickly.
Next change. Okay.
Come on, quickly.
Come on, girls. Quickly.
Fine, I'll be right back.
Oh my, God!
Help! Someone help me!
Help me.
Please on the lights.
Someone please help me.
I can't breathe.
Help! Help me!
Meera.
Oh my, God.
Meera, are you okay.
Megan, just take her details.
And get back to me. - Okay.
Take care. Bye.
How is she, doctor? - She's fine now.
These are anti-depressant tablets.
She needs to take
it morning and evening.
But she should consult a psychiatrist.
She isn't sick,
just some fear..which is in her mind.
Fear? What fear?
I think she's claustrophobic.
She feels scared in closed,
dark spaces.
If there's a sudden power-cut,
or if the liffs stuck.
...she can suffer
a fatal attack as well.
But there must be a reason
for her fear. - Of course.
But she didn't tell me.
You're her friend, you can help her.
0K8'!-
Thank you, doctor.
When I was 10, I and my
parents werat travelling by plane.
The plane crashed.
I and an air-hostess
were the sole-survivors.
Since then..l'm scared
of dark and closed places.
Oh my, God. Meera.
But why didn't you
tell the doctor about this?
I've told so many doctors.
...that now I've lost the
interest of telling anyone else.
And second.
They give me anti-depressant tablets.
"Which I already have.
And. .third.
That doctor wasn't my friend.
Who is it? - Andi.
Hi, Andi.
How are you?
I'm good. With Rads.
Girl time.
But actually I need your passport
What is he saying? - Passport? Why?
For a visa.
But, Andi, where are we going?
We're going to India, like I told you.
You know, Rajasthamphoto-shoot.
But, Andi.. - No ifs or buts.
Send me your passpon quickly.
We need to leave next week.
Andi, I can't do this.
Let's be serious now.
I'm sending my assistant,
you send your passport
Andi, I am serious. Don't push me.
Even/thing's locked, the deal is done.
Hire some other model.
Meera.
Look.. - I am sorry.
Hello. - I can't do it.
Meera? Hello.
What happened?
You know how Andi can be?
He's a bit crazy. - Yes.
Let's go.
Oh my, God!
I didn't know Meera had
such a painful backstory.
Because she cannot fly.
She's scared. She gets panic attacks.
I'll be ruined.
This Smith. He..
He will sue me!
Andi, take a breath.
Look, Andi.
If you have a fear in your heart
you should face it.
Face our fears
I see.
You want me to go to Smith,
face him and say..
"Meera is not available."
I didn't mean you, I meant Meera.
Don't do any1hing.
I'll handle every1hing, okay.
Oh, great!
Look, I'm going to India.
I've to arrange every1hing.
I've to get the locations locked.
You get her there by hook,
or by crook.
I'll do it.
I said I'll do it. Just calm down.
Karan. - Yeah.
Here.
I've copied this.
Clean-up the sound by tomorrow.
Fine, you can do that.
But let me hear first.
I might get a new idea.
Yeah, play it.
Stop messing around.
Let's just watch
the match now. Please.
Yeah, they're all sons
of Messi here. Right.
Let's watch the match.
Fine then, let's watch the match.
Thank you.
What's that?
Guys. Look what I found.
Do you know what this is?
What?
Lemon and chilly. - Ohh!
It protects the house.
He's gone crazy. - Correct.
Stop joking all of you.
You don't know.
It keeps evil spirits out of our home.
Yeah, just like I'm
going to throw this out.
What are you doing?
I'll slap you silly.
And hang you at the door.
Look.. - Shut up.
Listen, the second
half's going to begin.
Switch on the game.
Such a bore.
"Without you..my heart's restless."
"Come back to me, beloved."
Leela.
"Without you..my heart's restless."
Leela's statue will be unique.
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir. Thank you.
He's riding the bike, I'll tell him.
Thank you, thank you.
Karan, Harpal really loved
the jingle we made for his ad.
He's coming in the evening,
with a cheque.
Karan.
Karan. Are you listening?
Rajiv, did you hear the
record I gave you for cleanup?
Yes. - One that we found in the truck.
Yes, I did.
I cleaned up the sound.
Did you feel anything
while listening to it?
Feel? It's amazing.
I even made it my ringtone.
Did you hear it? - No!
I didn't hear it.
Karan, it's a fantastic song, Karan.
We'll make a great remix of it.
"L'm in a party mood."
"Take me shopping dude."
"Give me Dollars or Pounds."
"Oh my love, don't be rude."
"l'm in a party mood."
"Take me shopping dude."
"Give me Dollars or Pounds."
"Oh my love, don't be rude."
"Rude. ."
"One, two, three, four.."
"My arms are on your waist."
"My hands are being naughty."
"Let's not go back home."
"One, two, three, four.."
"My arms on your waist."
"My hands are being naughty."
"Let's not go back home."
I've heard that a themed
restaurant just opened up.
And you know what,
it looks like an airplane.
Plane? - Plane!
But it's a restaurant, right?
- Exactly.
Shall we party in the evening?
Are you coming from
privete jet. - Yes.
Girls.
Cheers.
One more, one more.
I finished it.
Yeah!
We should get one more.
No, I think you've had enough.
No, no, cheating.
One more! One more!
Meera, shall we go eat?
Airport-themed restaurant. - Airport?
Yeah. Remember, ljust told you.
The same restaurant. - Yes.
Let's go. Come on.
Hi, girls.
How are you? - How is everybody?
'My rustic look..'
"Fair boys."
But don't drink too
much on the flight, okay?
Rads!
Rads! - What happened?
We're at the airport? - No.
Meera, remember I told you..
"There's an airpon
themed restaurant.
This is the one.
Oh..
What happened?
Meera..stop. - But are you
sure this is a themed restaurant?
Yes. - Speak up.
Okay. - Speak UP-
Yes.
Rads, let's go.
It's time to take-off. - Candy.
It's not an airport,
it's a themed restaurant, Dodo.
Right, right, okay.
Shall we go now? - Yeah, come on.
Let's go.
Careful.
Andi. - Yes.
We've boarded,
the plane will take off any minute.
This way, please.
You're so funny. - Welcome aboard.
Thank you.
Ooh, hello ma'am. Right this way.
You look like a real pilot.
I hope so.
Tell me, what's your specialty?
I can fly for 24 hours straight.
Now, right this way, ma'am. - Fly?
He meant fry.
Right?
Fly..fry..either way. - Fry.
Hey, can you get some fish and chips.
I am so hungry.
Yes, you'll get your fish and chips.
Yes, I'll get you.
One ponion fish and chips,
okay. - Rads.
I was the first one to order.
Yes, you were. - Fish and chips.
It's coming, its coming.
- Fish and chips.
I am not on a diet today.
Rads.
Rads. - It's okay.
Where am l?
- It's okay, Meera. Calm down.
Where are we? - Calm down, it's okay.
Relax.
You're safe, okay.
Meera, l..want to confess something.
We're on a flight heading to India.
But look, don't.
Welcome to Jodhpur.
Meera. Wake up.
Rads.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Where are we?
Meera, we're in India. Jaisalmer.
Rads!
Just for a contract,
you both put my life at risk.
Meera, I was only
trying to help you out.
Like this? By getting me drunk.
What if I had woken up?
I could've gotten a stroke!
It's not your help, Radhika.
It's stupidity!
What if..l had a panic-attack!
No one could've helped me.
Not you or you.
You would've watched me die,
that's it.
I want to go, right now!
B'! Plane?
Shut up, Andi.
I want to go, now.
Meera, calm down.
Okay. I am sorry.
I didn't think I was
doing anything wrong.
I swear on God!
Look..we'll do as you say. Okay.
But we need some time
to arrange every1hing.
Please, understand.
Meera. Meera.
Meera!
Andi, I'm completely famished.
Can we stop somewhere to eat?
- Yeah, yeah.
There's an eatery close-by.
Driver, let's go to the eatery.
Would you like to eat something?
Some tea or coffee?
Okay, girls,
we're going to be eating here.
Just be careful of the water.
Just have packaged water, okay.
Quickly. Quickly.
Don't you make that face at me!
Meera, it would be really
nice if you eat something.
Okay, never mind.
You don't have to.. Okay.
What are we going to do? - Just relax.
She's furious.
- It's okay, just relax.
She won't do any1hing.
Stop, calm down. - Oh my, God.
Have some water.
Forget that, Andi.
Think about how you're going
to send Meera back tomorrow.
That's what worries me, Rads.
I'm telling you, Andi.
If Meera goes, I go too. - What?
What about our friendship?
- I don't know.
What about us?
- I've said what I've said, Andi.
Who will do the shoot? - I don't know.
You can't do this to me.
What are they doing?
Madam, that's an age-old game..
"Which the girls of
Rajasthan have been playing.
I'm completely famished.
What did you eat?
"Daal-Baati"!
"Daal-Baati"?
Never heard of it before.
But..l'm sure it'll be nice.
Just like every1hing here.
Andi!
Tomorrow.
What time?
Is the call time?
Andi.
Hey, Radhika, welcome to India.
Yeah, we just arrived.
But where are you?
- Just chilling with friends.
I see.
So how about you visit us here?
We're here for another 20-25 days.
Sure.
Well, bye. Take care.
Okay see you, bye.
Hold it, please.
Bro..l gave you to hold it.
You can hold mine. Want it?
Funny, huh! - Your beer sir.
Thanks.
Hey, smart!
Take your hands off.
Take your hands off. - Really?
Run! Run. - Karan.
Karan.
Catch him.
Take him to the hospital.
Are you all at the police station?
Are they filing a case?
Is every1hing fine?
No, you can all go home.
Just handle every1hing.
Yes.
Fine.
Okay..Fine.
Nurse, is every1hing okay? - Yes.
Karan, I'll go get the medicines.
"Without you..my heart's restless."
Stop Leela.
Leela!
'Leela's statue will be unique.'
'Angel in the form of human.'
Leela..belongs to Shravan.
Leela!
'Come with me.'
Leela's statue will be unique.
'Beautiful looks.'
Excuse me. What happened?
Only Shravan.
My name's Leela. Leela.
Leela!
Karan. - Leela!
Kumar, get some water quickly.
Karan.
Sit.
Karan, what happened?
Karan.
Are you okay?
What happened?
Madam.
Are you okay?
Take your medicines.
Who is Leela?
I don't know.
You don't know?
So..where did you get that name?
Since the day I
arrived in this house.
...l've been seeing strange dreams.
What dreams?
I don't know.
Since the day I moved in here..
...l've been hearing strange sounds.
And I see the same dream all the time.
Rajiv, I've grown
so tired of all this.
Karan, somethings wrong.
Somethings definitely wrong.
We need to do something.
'Sanskrit chants'
Hey, Karan.
This house is definitely haunted.
There are no ghosts
or spirits in this house.
What about female spirits?
Like I said..he was
talking about some Leela.
No, it's not what you think.
But my dreams. What's all that?
I can't tell you about that.
But whatever it is, it's not good.
You two come see my Guru.
He can chalk out your problems,
and also find a solution.
Your Guru..
Have you heard about 'Nadi-Shashtra'?
Yes, I have.
Something written on old leaves..
They are scripts.
It contains all the details
of every human being..
...from the time of
his birth until his death.
Like..palmistry or astrology.
'Nadi-Shashtra is
no ordinary astrology.
4000 years ago,
the great sage Agustya invented this.
'Nadi-Shashtra' doesn't
make assumptions.
In fact, it tells you the truth.
So, let's go there now. - No.
We can't go there now.
Today I will only take
his thumb impression.
You can come see me four days later.
Until then, may Lord
protect you from all troubles.
Hail Lord.
"L have forsaken my throne for you."
"Come rule my heart."
"O beloved.."
"My beloved."
"..your glamorous eyes."
"They're now my best friends."
"O beloved.."
"My beloved.."
"..your glamorous eyes."
"They're now my best friends."
Okay, I think we're done
with this angle now. - Okay.
Okay. We'll stan with this one.
It's just thatihose flags. - Flags..
Listen, Andi.
No!
"My veil..flies in the breeze."
"And my beloved runs after it."
"Listen to the call of my heart."
"Don't humiliate my love."
"My hear1's..only for you."
"..your glamorous eyes."
"O beloved.."
"My beloved."
"..your glamorous eyes."
"They're now my best friends."
Hey, what's going on here?
Who is he?
Who are these people?
- Greetings, brother.
Greetings.
They are shooting here.
They are from abroad.
Who gave them permission
to shoot here?
We've permission, from the Police.
This place doesn't
belong to the police.
Oh my, God.
Flags?
Who took the flags out?
Wha..what?
What's he saying?
He means flags. - Flags?
We took them out.
It was interfering with our shot,
ruining it.
Ruining your shot?
What have you done?
Bhoop Singh, come quickly.
Boop Singh?
Sir.. Sir, I tried telling you before.
This area belongs to the Prince.
Move.
Oh my, God!
Who are these people?
Sir. - What are they doing on my land?
Sir..they are foreigners.
They claim to be shooting here.
And they say that they've
police permission.
With your permission, your highness.
...shall we chuck them out?
Let them shoot.
They're guests of Rajasthan.
Okay sir.
These Indian Prince are so strange,
aren't they?
First shooting permission.
And now dinner invitation.
"Welcome to my country."
I am Maan Singh.
"Khamba Ghani"! - What?
I say "Goodnight".
Why is he saying goodnight?
Should we go back?
Please..welcome.
Follow me. Yes.
By the way, what does the Prince do?
Ma'am, he's the Prince.
He doesn't have the
need to do any1hing.
He just returned from
London few months ago.
And his family? - Here they are.
The Prince's mother and father.
They passed away when
the Prince was just a kid.
Anyway, let it be.
I'll show you something else.
Come. - Let's go.
Come, come.
Rads, see this.
It's just a chest, Andi.
Come on, let's go.
H9'!-
Don't touch..by this hand.
It's forbidden to touch anything here.
Oh my, God! - Wow!
Look at this beautiful
'Deewan-e-khaas' (Hall).
It's so nice.
See that fountain. - Stunning.
Oh, I could live here.
Coming..Prince.
Hi, everybody. I am Ranveer Singh.
Welcome to my Motherland Jaisalmer.
Sorry, my man interrupted
your shooting.
Hi, hello. - Nice meeting you.
Hi..- I'm Andi.
Hello, nice to meet you, Andi.
I am Radhika. - Hello.
Thanks for inviting us.
Iam Meera. - Hello, Meera.
Nice meeting you. - You too.
Please come.
Cheers.
Cheers. Cheers to you.
Foreign language
You speak French.
Just a little.
I know little French.
It's not difficult.
Guys, our Prince knows all languages.
What's that? - I mean languages.
What language do you know?
I knows..Hindi, English,
Punjabi, Bengali, Portuguese, etc.
What language is that?
It's my common language.
The food was good. - A bit spicy.
You liked the food.
Now..take mine. - What is that?
'Paan' (betel-leaf)!
Pick it up slowly.
Put it in your mouth. Chew it.
And..suck it.
That's my great grandfather.
He built this palace.
He fought many battles
in his lifetime.
He was a great warrior.
But you seem a little different.
There's a huge Buddha in your palace.
Buddha gives me peace.
And you know, he was also a prince.
True.
But he also gave up his kingdom,
and lived as a poor man.
Even I was quite poor once. - Really?
Just kidding.
Wow! What a collection?
Great.
Did your dad love reading books?
Yeah, dad loved reading.
I heard about your parents.
God can't be so rude.
I believe, when Lord takes
something away from you..
...he empties both your hands,
to give you something better.
I am sad about my parent's demise.
But you can't spend your
life surrounded by grief.
You can be overwhelmed by grief..
"But you shouldn't
let it be permanent.
We should always throw it away.
Right.
It's beautiful.
Beautiful, right?
Yes.
It'll be just fantastic
if we can shoot here. - I know.
But what about Maan Singh?
He doesn't even let us touch any1hing.
Will he allow us to shoot here?
So what do we do?
I have an idea.
Meera!
You're most welcome.
And the pleasure was mine.
Meera, don't you
have something to say?
Andi. - Rads?
What?
Yeah, Meera, l..
Yes, Meera?
ActuallyRads and Andi
loved your palace. - Yeah.
Didn't you like it?
- Yes, I loved it too.
But we're here to shoot,
and they were thinking.
Be my guest.
It's all yours.
Every1hing will be just the way it is.
We won't.
I'll see you tomorrow.
"When the Lord sees you with me?"
Your highness, shall we? - Let's go.
"When the Lord sees you with me."
"He must be wondering.."
"..how could He give
me such a valuable thing."
"You're amazing."
"There are no words to describe you."
"You've descended from the sky."
"That's all I would say."
"lf someone still
asks..who or what you are."
"l would just scatter
colors in the air."
"..scatter colors in the air."
"When the Lord sees you with me?"
Mr. Lawyer,
if this case proceeds like this.
"Then it will never end.
Your highness, please see
Vikram once and talk to him.
That's the lawyer's
suggestion as well.
What does brother Vikram want?
Talk to him.
Yes, your highness.
"The land..you set foot on."
"The touch of your
feet..turns it into heaven."
"All the adornment in the world.."
"..seem faded compared to you."
"Not just me,
even the Angels are crazy about you."
"You're the breeze in summer,
the sunlight in winter."
"All the weathers owe to you."
"When the Lord sees your attitude."
"He must be wondering.."
"..how could He give
me such a valuable thing."
Meera, your tablets.
I completely forgot them.
I know why.
Some things are best forgotten.
You were right.
Sorrows can be overwhelming,
but they can't be permanent.
But I also said.. You
should always throw it away.
Okay!
Rajiv.
Where's the priest?
Guru's been waiting for you.
Come. Every1hing will be fine.
Guru..
Guru, please help me.
Since I shifted in this house,
not a moment of peace.
I know..
It's because you didn't
shift in the house alone.
You brought some
unwanted memories along.
Memories? - Yes, memories.
Of your past life.
Past life? - Yes.
You're a pan of a 300
year old incomplete story.
And you've been bestowed
this life to complete it.
Guru, what's the story?
To know that, I tried to find..
"The 'Nadi-patra' of your past life.
But I couldn't find it.
And without it the
solution of your problem.
What is that?
Is not there.
But according to your star-sign,
your binh time"
...your stars and constellations,
we've found..
...few pages,
which coincides with another woman.
And her name..was Leela!
Guru, that's the
name he keeps repeating.
That's the name he
thinks about in his dreams.
He will, because it's
an indication from Lord..
...that destiny has
to complete a full circle.
And until it's not complete,
it will keep tormenting you.
That 300 year old threat..has
now turned into a catastrophe.
Guru, what's the solution?
You mean there's no way.
There is.
There is one way..which
can take you to your destiny.
The way of Leela.
Your story is connected with Leela.
So using Leela as base.
...l'll try to show
you the story of Leela.
O Lord..today I am going against
the norms of 'Nadi-Shashtra'.
Only to help this boy.
Forgive me, Lord.
Forgive me.
'Sanskrit chants'
Don't move, boy.
Or I'll stab you right now.
What are you looking at, my tormentor.
You'll have to pay the price
of looking at Leela with your life.
I will behead you.
My head's always
bowed before you, Leela.
Behead me, or don't. I don't care.
That's my only regret.
You never stop me.
You don't care for me.
Stupid girl, aren't you ashamed.
Those who feel ashamed,
curse their fate.
If I had felt ashamed,
I wouldn't have fallen in love.
And since I'm in love,
there's bound to be fire.
Take my hand, marry me.
No, Leela.
Shravan.
I don't even have a
small home to offer you.
I feel..that my poverty
might ruin all your desires.
Your hean is my home.
You're my king. My king.
According to our customs.
...Lord Vishwakarma will
be worshiped two days later.
And this time, famous sculptor Mr. Bhairao
will also attend the veneration.
Glory to Mr. Bhairao!
"My wrists jingle..like
the golden bangles."
"As I stretchedmy counyard echoed."
"My fragrance makes
the flowers blossom."
"The moon shines its
moonlight in my lane."
"My anklets are tinkling
and conveying."
"O drummer, your drums.."
"O drummer, your drums are thumping,"
"The drums are thumping."
Glory to Mr. Bhairao!
"L've adorned my eyes with Kohl."
"l've laced my tresses with flowers."
"l've adorned my eyes with Kohl."
"The dot on my forehead claims."
"..l've stolen my own slumber."
"My anklets are tinkling
and conveying."
"O drummer, your drums are thumping,"
"The drums are thumping."
Give it here.
Hit it like this.
Here. - Okay, Bhairo sir.
Look, Bhairo sir.
I made an effon.
Beautiful.
Very beautiful.
But it lacks inspiration.
And all efforts are
vain without inspiration.
That girl at the veneration yesterday.
Leela?
She's a camel.
Jumping around in the desen all day.
Nothing more.
Leela.
Bring her here.
I will make a statue of her.
Bhairo sir,
you..will make Leela's statue.
It's been so long since
you last made a statue.
You even refused our queen.
And Leela.. - Like I said.
To make a statue..one
needs inspiration.
Go. - I get it.
I'll go call her.
Leela. - Shravan.
You didn't go to Bhairo
sir's place today,
That's where I am coming from.
And look what I made.
Statue.
Even Bhairo sir praised me.
Soon you'll be a renowned
sculptor like Bhairo.
If I can be half of what he is,
I can stan making some money.
Then I'll marry you
and bring you home.
And provide you with a square meal.
But listen. - Yes.
Bhairo sir wants to make
a statue of you. - What?
Bhairo sir wants
to make a statue of you.
I don't want to get any statue made.
Give it to me. - Here, uncle.
Leela, don't be a fool.
You know what a famous
sculptor Bhairo sir is.
And if someone makes
a statue of you in Rajasthan.
...it will create a stir all over.
I understand all that.
Go tell Bhairo.
My name's Leela. Leela.
Leela, you don't understand.
Destiny's trying to make you famous.
...and you're refusing.
Bhairo sir is a nice man.
And..l'll be there too.
Okay, since you're insisting so much,
then okay.
Come on, make my statue.
- That's more like it.
Then let's go meet
Bhairo sir tomorrow.
Fine.
Now you come with me. - Where?
Leela.
I am right here.
I'll be there with you.
Bhairo sir..Leela.
An angel in human form.
You're more beautiful
than my imagination.
Bhairo isn't God.
But I'll sculpt a statue of you..
"Which will make
you immortal in history.
Come with me.
Come on.
What is this place?
This is Bhairo sir's chamber.
Even I got to see this place,
only because of you.
And you know,
Bhairo sir made this entire chamber.
...from sand and jute.
Come.
Come. - Go on.
Come on. - I said go.
Go, sit.
Sit.
Bhairo sir, that's your seat.
From today it belongs
to my inspiration.
Shravan, I will carve
Leela's statue in a sandstone.
But sir, that's a rare stone.
And hard too.
Leela's statue will be unique.
I want solitude to make this statue.
Yes, Bhairo sir.
And until this statue isn't ready..
...you'll be my chief assistant,
and tutor all the other students.
Yes, Bhairo sir.
May Lord Vishwakarma bless you.
I'll start sculpting the statue today.
Wait.
Chief assistant.
You said you'll stay with me.
Leela..l'll go crazy.
You don't know what's
happening with me.
Let me go.
What do I understand?
Stupid girl.
Firstly Bhairo sir
is making your statue.
And he also made
me his chief assistant.
Understand?
That means you won't be here with me?
Leela..you don't understand
what will happen.
...if I become the chief assistant.
Then no one can stop
us from getting married.
Marriage? - Yes.
And don't worry, I'm right here.
And Bhairo sir needs
solitude to make the statue.
Understand.
Come on now, go and sit.
Go. Go on.
And listen..return on time.
There is no human being or animal.
No God..or the devil.
There's no Bhairo..
...or Leela!
Just an anist.
...and his inspiration.
Until they don't become one..
"Their Dream's won't become on.
An desires sacrifice.
Surrender yourself to me.
Because history was always
created from total surrender.
'Then no one can stop
us from getting married.'
"My fair beloved..
...welcome to my country."
"My nights are restless."
"The days torment me as well."
"Come back to me..beloved."
"Without you..my heart's restless."
"Without you.."
"Come back to me, beloved."
"Without you..my heart's restless."
"Without you.."
"The weathers are not the same."
"Even the rains feel different."
Beautiful looks..and
an amazing voice too.
You sing well.
Here. Wear these clothes.
Sing.
"The weathers are not the same."
"Even the rains feel different."
"Like the dried river..
...my destiny calls
out to you beloved."
"Without you..my heart's restless."
"Without you.."
"Come back to me, beloved."
"Without you..my heart's restless."
"Without you.."
"Beloved.."
"Come back to me, beloved."
"Without you..my heart's restless."
What happened, Bhairo sir?
Be patient.
Bhairo said, be patient.
No, Bhairo didn't tell her that,
it was the Destiny.
And this wait will be over..
...at the same place where
this story was left incomplete.
Whether you want it or not.
But destiny will take
you to the same place.
...where you'll be at
a similar twist of the story.
And the decision you take now..
...will decide your fate.
But getting to that twist,
won't be easy.
There will be many
obstructions on this path.
"Which will be a
matter of life and death.
Either they'll take your life,
or give their life.
King Harshvardhan staned
this Polo Tournament.
And since then, every year this
tournament is organized in his honor.
Doesn't your Prince play Polo? - No.
He likes watching, not playing.
Actually the prince
has no greed for the trophy.
That reminds me, we're hungry.
Can we eat? - Yes, of course.
I am hungry too.
You speak so much,
and don't listen at all.
I'll show you where
dinner's been served.
Come, follow me.
Let's go eat. - No, you guys go ahead.
I'll wait for Ranveer.
Okay, I'll get you a drink.
Come, Rads.
See you. - Bye.
Congrats.
Thank you.
Vikram sir, you won the match again.
Congrats.
Vikram's born to be a winner.
And there's no victory in this world,
that won't bow before Vikram.
No, thank you.
Where did this butterfly
come from in this desert?
Hello, beautiful.
Hi. Congratulations, Mr. Vikram.
First time it felt
so amazing hearing my name.
You congratulated me,
my efforts didn't go in vain.
You play really well.
That's the only think I
learned to do best, Baby Doll.
Whether it's someone
honor..or the Polo ball.
By the way, where are you from?
- London.
Wow! This is my first close
encounter with a dame from London.
Otherwise,
I only see them on the internet.
I'm sure every pan of
your body must be fair, right?
Whether every pan of
the body is fair or not.
"But the heart.
...should be.
Madam.
Why don't you come to my
manor one evening, for dinner?
You'll love the food.
I swear,
we'll leave only after breakfast.
Ranveer, you?
I was wondering only a
Rajput could stop Vikram's hand.
Don't you see,
I am busy at the moment.
We'll talk later.
Brother Vikram, behave yourself.
Meera is a guest.
I am not humiliating her.
I am only inviting
her over for dinner.
There are cenain manners to invite
someone for dinner, brother Vikram.
Vikram has his own ways.
He doesn't need to learn from anyone.
Wild animals never
learn any1hing, brother.
Ranveer.. - And they die like a dog.
Please.. - No, Vikram.
Don'tstar1 an argument here.
Or else it will affect the case.
Calm down. - Come. Come.
Come away.
Bajje..open the champagne.
I've been victorious today.
What are you thinking?
There's such a huge difference
between you and Vikram.
Doesn't seem like
you two are brothers.
Meera..Vikram was a bit
spoilt from the beginning.
After uncle and aunt's death,
he crossed all limits.
I am sorry.
But even you lost your parents
when you were quite young.
And you're a Rajput too.
But Vikram and you..are
completely different.
It's the difference in our thoughts.
For him, respect is
something to be taken.
...and I believe it should be given.
He feels proud in
displaying his strength.
...while I like being sober.
I know, because you believe
in love and affection.
I always believed in love..
"But now I've an unwavering faith.
Meaning. I didn't get it?
Look, Meera..l don't
like Misting words.
Will you marry me?
"When the Lord sees you with me."
The Lord kept my hands empty..
...SO..
...he could give me something better.
"He must be wondering.."
"..how could He give
me such a valuable thing."
"Your beloveds courtyard."
"You're now his queen.
Your beloved's courtyard."
"Your beloveds courtyard."
"You're now his queen.
Your beloved's courtyard."
"Your beloveds courtyard."
"You're now his queen.
Your beloved's courtyard."
"He's the most handsome and dashing."
"He took my heart."
"He stole my slumber..and
gave me dreams."
"He's the most handsome and dashing."
"He took my heart."
"He stole my slumber..and
gave me dreams."
"Now my eyes..keep saying.."
"No matter how much one
stops me..l will love him."
"My beloveds a superstar."
"l am a big fan of him."
"Last night when he proposed
to me in a filmy style."
"l didn't look left or right,
just gave him my heart."
"Rumors spread everywhere."
"And photos were
published in the papers."
"l don't care..l'm with a star."
"My beloveds a superstar."
"l am a big fan of him."
Thanks, Rads.
You brought me to India.
And because of you,
I found a life-partner like Ranveer.
No, Meera, it was your destiny.
I hope there are no
more sorrows in your life.
You keep smiling all the time.
And problems stay miles away.
Thank you.
You know, I am going back today.
Oh, you giving back.
No, it's going back. - Okay.
So you want to know
what's in this box. - Yes.
So open it. - What?
The box?
Lollipop? - I've got diabetes.
And no one lets me eat sweets.
S0..l Side it. - Hide it?
Yes exactly.
Suck on this, you'll love it.
Rads, we're getting late. Come on.
Disgusting!
He's behaving like he
never sucked on one of these.
What's this, brother Vikram?
What were you doing
for 25 years in London?
Can't you read?
It's a stay-order from the coun.
Can I ask the meaning of this?
Look, Ranveer.
Bhairo Viraj doesn't
only belong to you.
I've a right to it too.
You'll make decisions on your own..
...and turn it over to the government.
And expect me to watch quietly.
Look, brother Vikram.
Its best to handover Bhairo
Viraj to the archeological depanment.
Otherwise this heritage
will be reduced to dust.
Then so be it.
It belongs to me.
If you act stubborn like uncle..
"Then you too will
be ruined just like him.
We've been fighting
this case for 25 years.
What did you and uncle gain from it?
Even your manor is mongaged.
Take your stay order back.
And I'll split the
compensation money with you.
I never even took
half-day from school.
How can I accept half compensation?
Bhairo Viraj will solely be mine.
Or it will be no one's.
That's not possible, brother.
Ranveer Singh, let's settle this
matter calmly, while we still can.
Otherwise..the Rajpufs
have a history.
...of solving matter of land,
women and money by using might.
Those who are scared of the present,
talk about the past.
Rajpufs don't turn pages of history.
"They change time.
Fine, we'll decide
when I'm holding a gun.
Don't try to scare me, brother.
No bullet has the strength
to pierce Ranveer Singh's body.
And as far as your stay order goes.
...l'll get it cancelled in a month.
Ranveer Singh,you might have..
...to pay dearly for this.
I will pay whatever the price is,
brother.
You and uncle think
about paying your dues.
Vikram, if Ranveer Singh's
willing to pay few millions.
...give Bhairo Virajna to him.
At least you can repay some
of your dues. - Brother Samar.
I am not a beggar.
My father spent all his
life in finding this statue.
I Will find it.
And it'll get me at least a billion.
Petrol prices have increased.
Good days haven't arrived yet.
Go find another car. - Okay.
600..
Brother, come here.
Will you take me to Bhairo Virajna?
Why walk? It's so hot.
I have a car.
1000 for A/C, 700 for normal.
If you like it, take a seat.
Let's go.
Come. - But..you do
know Bhairo Virajna.
What are you saying?
There's no place in Rajasthan
that Basant doesn't know.
Jaipur's Hawa Mahal,
Udaipur Lake, Kota's marble..
Shall we? - Come on.
What is Bhairo Virajna?
'Viral-na' means "Home".
It's believed that
many hundred years ago..
...some guy called Bhairo lived there.
Since then the place
is known by this name.
Do you have a life insurance?
What?
Because once you go in,
you can't come out? - Why?
Dead bodies don't walk.
There's a dispute between Prince
Vikram Singh and Ranveer Singh.
Going there means inviting your death.
If Ranveer Singh gets hold of you..
...you can apologies
and save your life.
But if Vikram Singh gets you,
then..you're dead for sure.
Brother, here's Bhairo Virajna.
By the way,
my advice is that you don't go in.
Goodbye.
'Angel in the form of human.'
'What place is this?
- Bhairo sir's chamber.'
Bhairo!
Be patient.
I've heard that Bhairo sir's
going to sculpt his best statue.
We all know that,
one keeps the statue of Lord..
...in front of the main entrance.
Tomorrow is a no-moon night.
We need to see why Bhairo sir..
...wants to establish Leela's
statue at his main entrance?
Leela.
Come on.
Leela.. - It'll be fine.
Look..my statue.
Leela..the entire village
will see your statue tomorrow.
They will all be so happy.
I don't care about the villagers..
...only you.
Shravan, you wanted
my statue to be sculpted.
So I want you to see it first.
I wish that too.
So, don't suppress your desire.
Come with me.
- Leela, you don't understand.
Don't be crazy.
Leela, Bhairo sir sculpted
that statue himself.
Don't deprive him of his right.
But only you have a right on me.
Only you!
Come on. - Leela.
Leela..listen.
Leela.. - Let go.
Leela..listen to me.
Have you gone crazy?
Leela.. - Let me go.
Leela.
Bhairo sir..
Bhairo sir..l..
She brought me here.
- Yes, Bhairo sir.
With these hands I taught to sculpt.
"But now I'll use them to punish you.
Shravan.
Leela belongs to me.
Her statue, her body..
...her complexion, beauty, youth, soul.
They all belong to me.
Only me.
How dare you.. - Bhairo!
How dare you raise
your hands on my Shravan?
He's my husband!
I will not spare anyone
who dares to touch him.
I came here are your inspiration.
But you thought I was your wife.
Leela..belongs to Shravan.
Only Shravan.
Let's go. Come on.
Leela.. - Let's go. Come on.
Shravan. - Leela, move aside.
No Bhairo. - Move aside.
Leela!
Come on.
Shravan.
Look. Look.
I respected you like Goddess.
Wanted to give you a high place.
But you..lost all respect in my eyes.
Your love, made me see
the highest peak of my an.
But now..
I'll show you the
depths of my hatred!
Come on.
Go!
Catch him.
Who are you?
Let me go.
Stand up, man. Don't just lie there.
Who are you? - Karan.
Lower your eyes while talking to me.
Or else I'll gouge them out.
Who are you?
And what are you doing here?
I liked the place, so I came in.
RascaLif you like some girl,
will you barge in her home too?
What are you doing in Jaisalmer?
I have a friend. Ranveer Singh.
Ranveer Singh?
You're Ranveer Singh's friend.
You were spying on me? - No, Vikram.
Don't beat him here.
Take him to Ranveer Singh's manor.
Absolutely right, brother Samar.
And then I'll also get
a glimpse of that London girl.
Vikram, she's your sister-in-law.
I don't have any
ill intentions for her.
All I want is a little
space near her feet.
I'll show you my hospitality
at your friend's place.
Come on.
Ranveer!
Ranveer Singh!
What happened, brother Vikram?
I've a gift for you.
Your friend was taking
a stroll around Bhairo Virajna.
Didn't you explain him,
that the place is prohibited?
One only warns his friends.
I never saw him before today.
What?
He's not your friend?
- No. I don't know him.
You dare lie to Vikram!
Bhairo Virajna isn't
your father's property!
Why did you go to Bhairo Virajna?
- Ranveer, what's going on here?
Tell me.
Stop it!
You? - Yes.
You recognized me?
Yes.
Karan, right?
Ranveer, I thought he's your friend.
But he turned out
to be your wife's buddy.
Yes.
He's my friend Radhika's brother.
Now you can go.
See you, sister-in-law.
You've really lucky!
Let's go.
Meera.
Shall we go in?
Shall we?
Come on.
Let's go.
Relax.
How are you feeling now?
- Much better.
A Rajpufs used you as a punching bag.
Only Rum can cure this pain.
Thanks.
What were you doing in Bhairo Virajna?
I'm making a music
album on Rajasthani music.
So I went there looking for something.
I think you're looking
for something special.
Excuse me.
Yes, Mr. Puneet.
Where are you?
We are waiting for you?
I'm on my way, sir. - Okay, come.
0K8'!-
Excuse me. I've to go.
I'll see you later.
Hi, Radhika, Meera here.
Hi, Meera, how are you?
I've a good news for you.
Good news, so soon! Wow!
Shut up, I didn't mean that.
So? - Your brother Karan is here.
Karan?
Here, talk to her. It's Rads.
Yeah!
Hi, Radhika.
What are you doing in Jaisalmer?
Fate brought me here.
Amazing..couldn't
you come a bit earlier.
Even I would've met you.
Life had come to
a standstill back then.
And when it caught up pace.
...l found myself in front of Meera.
You're sounding like
a philosopher now.
I'm a bit confused.
How did Meera recognize me?
What do you mean by how?
She has a very sharp memory.
I showed her your photo once.
Karan, now I have to go.
But if you need any1hing,
feel free to ask Meera.
Okay? - Yeah, bye.
Take care, bye.
Thanks.
Every1hing okay? - Yeah.
By the way,
you didn't attend my wedding.
And now you're suddenly here.
Actually,
I came here looking for someone.
Some chapters from my
past are still incomplete.
...and I'm here to complete them.
But..aren't you a musician?
Yes. - So..what's all this
about books..pages..etcetera..
Meera..
How do I tell you?
L.. - Forget it.
Eat your food and
take some rest. Okay?
And then we'll talk about
your..incomplete chapters, later..
Okay?
0K8'!-
'How will destiny come full circle?'
'I don't know.'
'How will I get to that point?'
'I wonder if Meera remembers any1hing,
like I do.'
'I still don't know who's Bhairo,
where he is.'
'I'll have to talk to Meera.'
Maan Singh..look..
Actually, I can explain this.
I didn't know that was Meera's room.
Maan Singh, it's not like you think.
Please believe me.
I was actually heading
towards the kitchen.
Karan sir, get some rest.
This happens with him every day.
Maan Singh sir suffers
from sleep-walking.
Leela!
Yes?
Come fast in breakfast.
What?
Brother, come down for breakfast.
- Coming.
Leela!
Good morning, Karan. - Good morning.
Had a nice sleep?
Actually, Leela.. - Not Leela.
It's Meera Ranveer Singh.
Meera.
I don't know whether
I should tell you this or not.
What happened?
Recently I've been
getting some weird dreams.
I see faces.
I hear some names.
I feel as if that
name's calling out to me.
Has this ever happened
with you? - Yes.
It happens with me often.
Even l..can hear voices.
But..l don't see anyone.
How long has this been happening?
Every time"
...when I talk on the phone.
Get it?
Oh, come on, Meera, this is serious.
The story that began 300
years ago in Bhairo Virajna..
...l still see it in my dreams.
And the strange pan is..
What?
I see you.
And in the form of Leela.
Oh really?
Good morning. - Morning.
Hi.
So, Mr. Magician, how was your night?
He's talking about some weird dreams.
Dreams? What dreams?
It's..it's just like that.
Nothing serious.
Sir.
Sugar?
Karan? - Yes?
Two.. - Okay.
What happened, Ranveer?
Tomorrow there's a veneration
of Vishwakarma in the village.
We've been celebrating
this veneration.
...in a grand way
for hundreds of years.
And this year the villagers
want you to attend it too.
How sweet.
Why don't you join us too?
I want to talk to you.
What? - I want to talk to you.
Come with me. Come.
Leela.. - My name is Meera!
Not Leela.
In this lifetime.
But in your previous birth,
you were Leela.
And I was Shravan.
And that Ranveer, he was Bhairo.
Bhairo? - Yes.
And he also sculpted a statue of you.
Look.
Leela.
That story began on this day..
With the veneration of Vishwakarma..
...where he saw you for the first time.
And in this lifetime,
he wants to do the same thing.
Shut up, Karan.
I respect you because
you're Radhika's brother.
But I don't know
what you want to prove..
...by telling me this weird story.
Meera..try to understand.
Coming here, getting to Bhairo
Virajna is not a coincidence.
I've connected every link up to here,
only for you. - Enough!
I am married!
You've crossed the line!
Go away!
I did it.
I hit the jackpot.
You lit a torch for
me in this dark cave.
Your highness.
And its light Will
reach your home too.
Thank you.
For now..take this small token.
Thank you, Vikram sir.
By the way,
where's that long lost-traveller now?
There's a musical program
at the Prince's manor.
Come, brother Samar.
Let's go and pay our respects.
Karan..you can sing any song you like.
But to me, you'll be singing
the melody I want to hear.
"Beloved.. My beloved."
"Come home this time."
"Dwell in my eyes.."
"And show me your beautiful face."
"My hean yearns."
"My hean yearns without you."
"Don't go away again."
"My fair beloved..
...come back to my land."
"My nights are restless."
"The days torment me as well."
"Come back to me..beloved."
"l've yet to finish..
telling that imponant story."
"Come back..and listen to me, beloved."
"Without you..my heart restless."
"Without you.."
"Come back to me, beloved."
"Without you..my heart restless."
"The weathers are not the same."
"Even the rains feel different."
"Like the dried river..
...my destiny calls
out to you..beloved."
"Without you..my heart restless."
"Without you.."
"Come back to me, beloved."
"Without you..my heart restless."
"Without you.."
"O drummer, your drums are thumping,"
"The drums are thumping."
Meera!
What happened?
Thank you, doctor. - It's okay.
Come.
She shouldn't have stopped
her medication so abruptly.
Anyway, she's fine.
I'll prescribe some medicines.
- No, doctor.
The reason behind
her illness is different.
I'll take Meera back to London soon.
Goodnight doctor. - Goodnight.
Ranveer Singh!
I want to talk to Meera.
Listen to me carefully.
Don't fuel my hatred.
If anything happens to Meera,
you'll face my wrath.
No one ever got love for hatred.
Don't try to take undue
advantage of Rajpufs love, Karan.
If his hatred awakens.
...you will wish that you were dead.
I want to talk to Meera.
If I didn't care about Radhika,
you would've been long dead.
Look, the Jaisalmer border
ends at 25 kilometers.
I'll give you 20 minutes.
If I still see you around..
...then, your search
will end with your death.
If you kill him,
how will I find the statue?
Come sister-in-law. - Leave me.
And the heroine should
be in the villain's clutches.
Shall we go?
Where's the statue?
I don't even remember the name.
...of the girl I was with last night.
And you..remember your previous birth.
So..where's the statue?
I don't know.
You really don't know
where the statue is.
'Leela.'
'I don't want to get any statue made.'
I said I don't know.
'I will behead you.'
'My name's Leela.'
'Angel in the form of human.'
'I don't want a statue.'
'We can get married.. - Marriage!'
'Bhairo!'
Move aside.
'I'll show the depths of my hatred.'
'sol.
'Look..my statue.'
The statue was there.
Sister-in-law..why do you
want to save him every time?
Vikram.
Move.
Vikram sir.
Stop!
Your statue..is behind that wall!
Go get it.
RascaLyou could've told me before.
It would've saved you the thrashing.
Break down that wall.
Come.
Come fast.
Break this wall.
Fast.
Break from here.
You finally believe me..
...that I was telling the truth.
Don't you have strength in those arms.
For 300 years..l've been living..
With the wounds inflicted by Bhairo.
But maybe..the Lord's
finally taken mercy on me.
Found it. I found it.
I found the statue.
Vikram Singh!
Vikram!
Beat him!
Ranveer!
You severed all the blood
ties by shedding blood.
And also invited your
death by touching my Meera.
Now..Bhairo Virajna
belongs only to me.
Casedismissed!
This time..history won't be repeated.
In this life time..Bhairo will die.
Two lovers..won't be separated.
L..- Karan!
How dare you touch Ranveer!
He's my husband.
If you touch him,
Meera won't spare you!
Shravan and Leela were dead.
And the one who hid that
statue behind the wall..
...would know this fact.
That's the truth, Karan.
You are Bhairo.
Ranveer.
How do you know all this?
Because 300 years ago,
we died together.
Shravan?
Meera didn't remember anything
about her previous life.
Nor did I try to remind her.
Nature played a strange trick on us.
Meera was born with the same face..
"But gave us different faces.
'Now I'll use them to punish you.'
300 years ago you committed the crime.
And so you were being punished.
'Since I moved in this house..'
'..l've been seeing weird dreams.'
'You didn't move in that house alone.'
'Some unwanted memories
also entered that home with you.'
I could've killed
you and taken my revenge.
But fate had already
taken its revenge.
And so, I felt sympathetic
instead of hatred.
You are Bhairo, not Shravan, Karan.
You didn't endure that injustice,
you're the one who caused it.
You caused them so much pain..
...that, you're not even
worthy of their hatred.
Fate has brought you to this bend.
...so that you could be punished.
And you can wash off the stains
of their blood with your own blood.
Karan!
No, Karan!
Let me go, Shravan.
It's best for Bhairo to die.
You're wrong, Karan.
You're not Bhairo, nor am I Shravan.
And if you end your life like this.
...you won't gain salvation,
nor repentance.
No my.. - No, Karan.
Bhairo should've died, not Karan.
Our next binh is not
only for revenge or repentance.
The Lord gives us an opponunity
to apologies and pardon.
We forgive you for killing us.
Yes, Karan.
Come.
Yes Karan.
Rajiv.
Hey, Rajiv.
What are you listening?
It's the remix of 'Tere Bin'.
It's fantastic.
It'll be a platinum hit, for sure.
Look.
See that.
The song that reminded me of my past.
"Also fulfilled all
my dreams of this lifetime.
Let me hear it too.
Hey bro.. - Yeah!
Will be screaming "Leela" again?
Let's go.
Leela!
"My nights are restless."
"The days torment me as well."
"Come back to me..beloved."
"l've yet to finish..telling
that imponant story."
"Come back..and listen to me,
beloved."
"Without you..my heart restless."
"Without you.."
"Come back to me, beloved."
"Without you..my heart restless."
"Without you.."
"Come back to me, beloved."
"Without you..my heart restless."