Ajay..
If you think you have been wronged..
Then I will help you get justice.
Stop worrying about getting
me justice, inspector.
And use all your police
force in protecting him.
But he won't live. I will kill him.
I'll kill him today itself.
Whenever law will murder justice..
A new Ajay will be born.
Excuse me, sir..
Instead of serving
such a judicial system..
I would rather like supporting Ajay.
'After going through all
the aspects of this case..'
'..the court dismisses all other
charges made on the accused Ajay..'
'..finds him guilty
only under section 302..'
'..and sentences him
14 years of imprisonment.'
Milk helps you make a cup of coffee.
Milk helps you make cottage cheese.
Similarly, seven musical notes
help you make music.
Hey, what are you?
Tell me, is it necessary to say
'Aayo' and 'Aito' every time?
You are late, Kishore.
I had gone to look for
jewelry for Munni today.
We should buy some
now that we have the money.
If we start collecting now..
Father, why did you throw this here?
You should always
throw it in the dustbin.
You know that, right?
Sorry..
Grandpa, you won't forget
the password this time, right?
No, I won't.
"Nanacool."
"Nanacool?"
So I am cool?
So then, I can attend the party.
But there is an age limit.
I mean couple entry is compulsory.
I will be going with Anushka.
So do you have anyone to go with you?
With me..?
- Grandpa!
Yes?
- Don't shut down my machines.
My project files are rendering. Okay?
Yes. You will surely
win this competition.
Thank you.
Let's go.
- Shall we? - Let's go.
Bye, grandpa.
- Bye, grandpa.
Love you. - Bye.
- Love you.
Bye-bye.
- Let's go.
Bye.
Grandpa, Varun's grandma is single.
You want me to hook you up with her?
Imp! You will hook me up?
Varun!
Varun! Can't you hear me?
The parties these
kids attend these days..
..are just leading them
astray from their religion.
He is my son. He will have
fun but he won't go astray.
Yes, of course. I know everything.
Varun, you can break a few rules.
But never break our trust.
- Sure.
Here the key??
Brother.. Say hi to Zoya.
Zoya? Are you there?
Zoya.
I am asking you something.
- No, mom.
So irresponsible.
Did he call?
- Yes, he did.
What did he say?
Zoya? I am asking you something, Zoya.
Zoya.
Listen mom,
you have Zack's number, right?
Call him.
And ask all this crap yourself.
Okay, dear.
Now come on the camera.
Let me see your sweet face..
Before the flight takes off.
It's weird, mom.
What's weird?
We stay in the same house
but still we chat over Skype.
Come on, Zoya. Now don't begin
with the whole thing all over again.
You too must be wondering,
my mom and dad are never together..
Then how did I come into this world?
Come on, Zoya.
Yes, I got downloaded
into their life by mistake.
Am I right, Skype?
Let's go. Bye.
Go easy with the butter, Joe.
It's butter chicken, darling.
I cannot change the recipe.
Too much butter will kill you.
The thing I love cannot kill me.
Neither this, nor this and nor this.
So I am come last, huh?
Last but not the least.
Listen..
I want to go to Nanded.
I want you to come with me.
For a long drive.
For your RTR?
No.
"Come, let me take you.."
- No Joe, I have to finish this.
"To a new world.."
- No.
Good evening.
- Good evening, sir.
Good evening, sir.
Good evening.
A sensational movement
for women's security and respect.
Change it.
- But sir..
Good evening, sir.
Good evening.
You have seen our
newspaper's logo, right?
Yes. But everything
written in it is true.
Then why do you need
to use words like sensational.
Such words give more weight
to lies and not the truth.
D.C.P. Ashraf..
Okay. Thank you, Raman.
Oh God.
- Of course.
Mr. Rajguru,
Ashraf is going to create a problem.
He will approach the
media and cause a problem.
Mr. Sinha, you worry unnecessarily.
It will be an issue
if Herald makes it.
But the Herald is with you.
Let's go.
- Come on.
Come on.
- Let's go.
Mr. Sinha..
Girls from small
town want to go ahead..
But they don't know how to walk.
You are right, sir. You are absolutely right.
- No, let's go.
Come on. Let's have same fun.
- Cheers!
Why are you all clapping for me?
It's a prayer.
Ananya, why don't you
tell them the meaning?
It means: oh God,
please guide us..
From untruth to truth.
From darkness to light.
From death to eternity.
Let there be peace all over.
Right, grandma?
- Yes, dear.
You are absolutely right.
- Okay, okay. Attention everyone.
Lights off.
Come, come, come.
Blow, blow, blow.
Once more.
- Happy birthday to you.
To papa..
- Happy birthday dear Ananya.
Now to grandma.
Actually, C.M. had kept
an urgent meeting in Delhi.
I said, it's my daughter's
birthday so I need to be there.
Actually, my kids had come
to meet the film stars and cricketers.
You didn't invite them?
My Ananya knows that you
get happiness when you share them.
Look how she is sharing happiness..
..with the kids from our foundation.
- Come on.
Nice. Wow.
Nayar has been trying to hack
into our system since afternoon.
He doesn't know that all
his data is being downloaded.
You keep playing with Nayar.
Look, I have done my job.
Sir..
Your swing is too stiff, dad.
- It slipped.
But I have the perfect
thing to loosen you up.
Check this out.
Good night, dad.
What is it?
From the telecom ministry's server
they got tomorrow's bid's document.
We got the tender, Kaka Sahib.
Anything that belongs to
the government, belongs to you.
Why did you need to hack into it?
This is Kabir's first
independent project.
And as you know,
if wants something, he gets it.
Right here, right now.
- Hey bro, what's up!
Good to see you.
- Join the party.
I've been working on this
music for the past few days.
Hello, beautiful.
- Hey.
Whoa!
Hey, yo!
'Phoolchand Mehra, the second.'
'If we have a son,
we will name him Phoolchand Mehra.'
It was my grandfather's name.
I don't like it.
But I love it.
Why?
No way.
How about..
Tukaram Ganpat Rao.
No way.
No.
Ajay Mehra's son will
be called Phoolchand Mehra.
I had promised my dad.
'Varsha is dead!'
'Her son is also dead!'
'They died because of you.'
'I wanted to talk about
something important.'
'Are you listening Ajay.'
'I am worried.'
'Balwant Rai.'
'Is anybody listening?'
'They killed my brother.'
'Is anyone listening?'
Ajay, the medicine is
right in front of you and you...!
Take it.
Stop playing with your memories, Ajay.
These moments that you try
to recall with your dear ones..
Just stop it!
The nightmares that come with them
will take you somewhere from where..
..no neurologist will be able
to bring you back, let alone me.
You know that your life
isn't just yours anymore, right?
You killed her, right? Confess it.
You raped her. Confess it.
You did it, right? Tell me.
I killed her.
Good morning, sir.
Good morning.
Ajay, he is Inspector Pawar.
Sir, this is the letter.
You have to do it tomorrow.
I've already committed.
Try to understand.
Mr. Mehra, Mr. Rajguru
is waiting for you.
Please come.
Come in, sir.
Mr. Mehra..
Hi.
What brings you here?
Lokesh, all clear?
- All clear, sir.
Have a nice day.
You too, sir.
Akshay, clear?
Yup, all clear.
Wait. Let the car pass.
Can't you see?
Let's go. Let's go.
Ajay Mehra, you bastard!
You bastard!
Who the hell do you think you are?
You want to mess with me?
With Aditya Rajguru?
You will mess with the Daily Herald?
After a few exposés,
you think you are someone great?
You think you are a media mogul?
These RTA activists,
retired police officers..
You think you can challenge
me with the help of these clowns?
You wanna mess with me! You...
Your mother is a woman.
Your wife is a woman.
A daughter..
A sister..
Do you recognize her?
Read it.
'Papa, I thought...'
'...I'll come to Mumbai,
get a job and support you.'
I'll become a journalist and be the
voice of all the girls in this country.
But my boss Aditya Rajguru..
'...who is exactly your age.'
Killed my voice.
'He took advantage of my trust.'
'He raped...'
'I don't want to live anymore, papa.'
'How will I ever face you,
or my fiancé Shrikant?'
'I am sorry, papa.'
'Please forgive me.'
What does this prove?
I didn't kill her.
Doctor..
Between a rapist and
an innocent boy's DNA..
There is a difference, right?
Sorry, sir.
Please forgive me.
The three suspects of
reporter Renu Sharma's rape.
First: The owner of the Daily Herald,
the rapist, Aditya Rajguru.
The entire country is shocked by the shameful
deed of such high-profiled socialites.
Dr. Poonawala.
Instead of Rajguru's DNA sample...
...he presented Renu's
boyfriend Srikant's sample..
...and made a false report.
Police commissioner Saurabh Sinha.
He destroyed all the evidences.
He tortured Srikant..
And forced him to confess..
That he raped Renu Sharma.
S.I. Pawar was instrumental in
Ajay Mehra's unraveling of the case.
This is the biggest and most Sensational
expose done by Mr. Ajay Mehra.
He had torn the suicide note
on being pressurized by his seniors.
But later S.I. Pawar realized..
That he too has a daughter.
Ajay Mehra has done it again.
How does he do it time and again?
- May Ajay Mehra livelong.
We will disclose this secret in some time.
- So that our daughters stay safe.
This was Mumbai police's job,
but Ajay Mehra did it.
Ajay Mehra should also be in Delhi.
Only then will our girls be safe.
I will regain the trust
people have lost in Mumbai police.
'We used to give sleepless nights...
...and now Ajay Mehra
has done the same to us.'
'Our boss has been arrested...'
'...but keep listening
to Radio Herald uninterrupted.'
The market today opened
with Herald shares..
..taking a 47% dip in the value.
Experts are predicting
a further fall ahead.
That's great.
Dad, Herald media group is now ours.
That's good, Kabir.
Wow!
Butter chicken!
Ajay Mehra...
That's why you are my
favorite doctor, Ms. Riya.
Because you know how
to keep your patients happy.
Well done, my boy.
Joe!
What are you doing?
Meet them.
Hello.
- Hello.
Hi, dear.
Ajay! I am feeling so proud of you.
Come, come, come.
Every woman in this world
must be praying for you today.
Wonderful.
Let him eat.
It's okay to have it sometimes.
Sometimes?
He eats it every day.
Hey!
Sir, what's the progress
of Nanded's case?
Did RTA reply?
Yes.
I had to go there as well.
I asked the principal to come along..
..we would work as
well as romance a little.
Romance?
- So?
Eat.
You should go with him.
Long drives, outings.
Don't listen to him, Riya.
He always has a hidden agenda.
Last time he took my friends
with him to Latur for an outing.
Once there, he parked the
car outside the collectorate..
..he gave us some
plank cards to hold..
..and asked us if we could
protest with him for a while.
I was so embarrassed.
What are you saying?
- Yeah.
Did you really do that?
I killed her.
- She is lying. - What?
I humbly asked them whether
they could protest for a while.
They rudely said "no"!
I said fine. - I won't let
anything happen to you. Trust me.
I killed her, mother.
I killed her.
As you can see Srikant
who was excruciated by the police..
..has lost his mental balance
completely.
You can see that he is very scared.
And that police has
tortured him a lot.
I killed her.
- You didn't do anything.
I.. I killed her.
- I am right here with you.
Renu..
- Yes?
Renu.. you are here!
- Just relax.
I have been trying to
explain it to them..
Lie down.
I didn't kill you.
- Nothing will happen to you.
You are not Renu. - Just relax.
Where is Renu?
You are not Renu!
Relax Shrikant.
I want Renu!
Renu!
He'll get 10 more electric shocks?
It's not electric shocks.
It's a therapy which
is very important for him.
Look at Ajay.
His case was very serious.
I want to die.
Kill me. Let me die.
Die. I want to die.
Kill me. Kill me.
I want to die.
Kill me.
Be careful.
Calm down.
Are you feeling all right?
Ajay?
- Varsha?
Relax, Ajay.
- You are not Varsha.
Ward boys!
Prepare the E.C.T.
- 'Varsha! I want to go to Varsha'
Relax.
'I want to die.
I want to go to Varsha'
After the death of his wife and kids,
he turned suicidal.
But look at him now.
He is absolutely fine.
Srikant's case is not that serious.
He will get well in a few months.
But he can get well
only when you and others..
..that is, his friends and
family behave positively with him.
We will need to give him a new aim.
When he will get a new aim,
his new life with begin.
What are you thinking?
Superintendent said that
my term here is coming to an end.
I will be released next year.
What will I do once I go outside?
The things which
others can't do, Ajay.
Not everyone has the strength
to endure and to fight as you do.
He is right, Ajay.
And when we are with
you then your aim is close by.
An aim..
- Ajay..
Why don't we get out of here
and help those who are helpless..
Alone..
And feel defeated by the system.
Ajay?
They are leaving.
Your son will get well.
Just like me.
We will always be grateful to you.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Ajay, we're getting late. Shall we?
Let me call on stage,
Mr. Ajay Satyakant Mehra.
He should come here and give
the bravery award to these brave kids.
I fell into the fast flowing
water while doing river rafting..
..but these stupid kids saved my life.
Zoya Sehgal.
Varun Jain.
My son.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Rohan Kriplani.
Yeah!
Thank you. Thank you, sir.
- Anushka Kulkarni.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Please share a few
words with these kids.
All I would like to say is..
If we are going to support the truth..
..then we shouldn't
give up until we win.
Yes, sir. We won't give up.
Well said, Ajay.
You are sharing great
knowledge with these kids.
According to this, our kids
should keep doing such stupid things.
See, that wasn't so hard.
- Ajay sir..
I am Zoya.
Zoya Sehgal.
Alnoor sir knows me.
I am a blogger.
Pretending parents.
You have read my blog?
Sir, I am a big fan.
Can I get a selfie with you?
Sure.
- Hello.
Yes.
- Come on.
"Just jump and grab it."
"A delicate string.. "
"The heart sings."
"May be for others,
we don't bother."
"Everyday.."
"It's today.."
"It has nothing to do with tomorrow."
"Sadness, hold a sharp knife."
"How can we avoid
difficulties in our lives?"
"We will change the
direction of the wind."
"We will live our lives as we will."
"Friends.."
"Just jump and grab it."
"Feeling low."
"Just let it blow."
"It's useless to sulk."
"Build your own opportunities.."
"That's our funda, our principle."
"Just jump and grab happiness."
"Juice it, life is nothing
but like a fresh orange."
"We will change the
direction of the wind."
"We will live our lives as we will."
"Just jump and grab it."
"The power of our fists.."
"We will be our take."
"All the crooked rules.."
"We will break."
"We are not kids,
don't mistake."
"We are not weak, won't break."
"Whatever, whatever it is."
"Back off people."
"Don't stop us."
"Chill, don't nag us."
"Whatever, whatever it is."
"Stop bugging us like this."
"Friends, just jump and grab it."
"Just jump and grab it."
"A friend, a dear friend.."
"If becomes a special friend."
"Like a gift, godsend."
"Will be with you till the end."
"With a companion,
the journey becomes beautiful."
"How can we stay
away from each other?"
"We will change the
direction of the wind."
"We will live our lives as we will."
"Friends, just jump and grab it."
"Just jump and grab it."
"Just jump.. and grab it."
Grandpa!
My baby.
How are you?
You look tired.
I am so tired.
And now we have to spend
the whole night editing.
Order a few pizzas for us.
We will be working
through the night. Okay?
Okay, bye.
Through the night?
But you are tired.
Grandpa.. keep Skype with you.
- Okay.
Feed him.
Don't feed him grapes, okay?
How can I feed him grapes?
Strange girl.
- How are you, grandpa?
I am starving.
I am famished.
Okay. What do you want?
Order 2 cheeseburgers
and coke for me.
Order pizza.
I want to 2 burgers.
Please.
- Okay. I am your grandpa.
And not your grandma.
What are you saying?
Still, you will get everything.
- Give me the remote.
Put the match on.
There is a match going on. - Take it.
Hey can you read that?
Utterly, butterly chicken.
Exactly, it suits you perfectly.
Ajay, the accident that
took place on Pen Highway...
D'Souza sir's car was in it.
Sir, there were 8-10 more
people apart from Joe sir.
And the tanker driver
was also burnt to death.
Ajay, sister-in-law..
Joe!
I want to see Joe.
Oh, my God!
Joe!
Joe! No, Joe! No, Joe!
Joe! My Joe! I want to go..
Let me just see him once.
Let me.. oh my God.
- 'An Accident on Mumbai-Pen Highway.'
We have got information
that 8-10 died in this accident.
Former deputy commissioner
and RTI activist..
..Joe D'Souza...
'This incident..'
- Guys! Guys, he killed him.
Joe D'Souza!
- Who?
The RTI activist. Kabir shot him.
Shit, he killed him.
Shit.
I was watching this and suddenly the..
- What happened? - Look at this grandpa.
Raj Bansal.
And that's Kaka Sahib,
that's the home minister. - Shit.
I am going to blog this right now
No, Zoya.
- Why?
It will take only two seconds
to trace its IP address.
Exactly.
- Shit.
We should give it to the police.
Have you lost your mind?
The home minister himself
is involved in this.
Ajay Mehra.
We need to take this to Ajay Mehra.
- No!
No Ajay Mehra.
No!
No one will tell anything to anyone.
You guys don't know anything.
Come with me.
This is the biggest ever road
accident on Mumbai-Pen Highway so far.
8-10 people are believed
to have died in it.
What?
You saw that? - Former deputy
commissioner and RTI activist..
Are you getting it?
They turned a murder into an accident.
They killed 8-10 people.
These images might disturb you.
- Rohan, call up your father.
And ask him to come here immediately.
Yeah, my dad.
It's clear that the Pen Highway
accident in which our founder...
...and other 10 people died..
..happened due to the
mistake of the tanker driver..
..and road department's mismanagement.
- Very good.
Satyakam family prays
for Joe D'Souza and..
Mr. Bansal.. good riddance.
Troy is just great.
He killed 11 people
along with D'Souza.
That made the accident
quite convincing.
And the way Satyakam confirmed it..
Now I am relaxed.
I am relaxed.
- Good night.
'You socialist rats!'
'Bloody anarchists!'
'What is your contribution
in this country's growth?
'We are the ones who create wealth.'
'We are the ones
who provide employment.'
'We are the ones who
are feeling you all.'
'You always create hurdles for us.'
'All of you should die.'
'And I will kill all of you.'
Where is papa?
Over there.
Ananya!
- Ananya!
Slow down, dear.
Papa!
Look at this, papa.
Mom got an award.
I, too, went on the stage.
Why didn't you come here?
Dear, I was.. Prema..
Ananya, you have to
go to school in the morning.
Say good night to everyone.
Good night, papa.
- Good night.
Good night, grandma.
- Good night, dear.
Good night, mom.
Good night, Ananya.
What's wrong, son?
You look upset.
Nothing, mother.
It's just.. You should go and rest.
What is wrong, Raj?
Actually, today, I realized that
the huge empire that my dad built..
..our legacy, our son
won't be able to take it ahead.
Why do you say that?
I wish you could
witness his anger today.
He shot a man today.
And the way he shot..
Shot? What do you mean?
What do you mean by shot?
He killed someone?
Yes.
But the murder has been taken care of.
What are you saying?
- But the murder has been taken care of.
I told you not to give him a gun.
This is not about the gun.
- I had told you..
Tomorrow he kills
someone with his car..
..will you question
me why did I give him a car?
I will! I surely will!
- Please try to understand.
I am shocked by the rage
with which he killed that man.
His attitude, his thoughts..
How will he run such a
big empire with so much anger?
We have failed as parents.
What kind of an upbringing
have you given him?
Me?
- Yes, you.
I..
- You are his mother.
You never let me be a mother, Raj.
I was just a nanny to your prince.
I gave birth to him,
but he got all his values from you.
You didn't stop him when he
insulted his elders or the servants.
You gave him everything he wanted.
You made such a big
Bansal world for prince..
..that he thought that he has
a right to anything and everything.
You are responsible for it.
You have made him a..
You have made him a murderer.
This is everything?
- Yes. - Yes, dad.
There is nothing left behind with you?
- No.
You sure?
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
- Uncle..
But what are you going to do?
Dear, you know that
I am a lawyer, right?
Yes.
I will do what you want to do.
But in my own way.
Another thing:
You won't mention this to anyone.
Promise?
- Yes, uncle.
Yes, uncle.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Doomed. Oh damn..
What a piece of crap!
This makes it look as if
we are killing him on purpose.
But it was not so.
Well done, Kaka Sahib.
You invited the very person
I came here to complain about.
Mr. D'Souza..
You've made a good name for
yourself with your RTI applications.
It's time to call it quits.
Now it's time to join
hands and move ahead.
Kaka Sahib,
how many times do I have to tell you..
I don't wear a uniform anymore.
I am retired.
Hence, I am no longer
forced to follow your orders.
I have instead gotten
into a habit of following up.
Look at this.
3452 families which you have ruined.
Rehabilitate their homes, farms
and animals and the problem is solved.
Mr. D'Souza..
We have given them the compensation
government has ordered us to.
You haven't given them anything,
you have fooled them.
In exchange of a mere compensation,
you've stolen the lands of those
illiterate poor people.
Come on, Mr. D'Souza.
People will get employment
because of the project.
If they don't die due
to starvation by then.
Everything that we did was
done with government approval.
Which government
are you talking about?
The government that
dances naked to your tunes?
How dare you talk to my father
like that, you rotten slave?
What did you say?
Leave me. - This is what
your father wants to make us.
Mr. D'Souza.
- Leave me.
The government too is your slave.
Water, electricity, phone network..
- Leave me..
Everything belongs to you.
- Leave me or I'll kill you.
Everything belongs to your father.
The only thing left is
his image on the currency.
You are making this country..
Now do you understand?
Yes. I completely understand.
You are not at fault, son.
It is justified. Justified, he is.
Joe D'Souza is such a man that
this was bound to happen eventually.
Hence, I brought everything over here.
Mr. Kriplani, what do you mean to say?
That you have not
made any copies of it?
What? What are you saying?
You must have kept
one for safety sake.
You are accusing me.
You are a lawyer.
You are getting me wrong. I..
Look Mr. Raj, I am a corporate lawyer.
You know me. I did all this..
Kaka Sahib is making
an accusation on me.
Relax Kriplani.
- I did all this for you.
Relax.
He is just reassuring.
And I trust you.
And I appreciate your gesture.
- Thank you.
Very shortly, you will receive
a call from my accounts department.
No.
Why are you taking it the wrong way?
Look, you are getting it all wrong.
I didn't do all this for the money.
Mr. Kriplani, control yourself.
No, no. Mr. Kriplani, please.
This is the reason I brought
all these things with me. - Calm down.
I spoke about the money just
as a good gesture on our part.
No, I don't want any money.
You don't have to
worry about anything.
Please relax.
- Mr. Kriplani..
I hope you don't mind sharing a few
details of those four kids with us.
They won't utter a word
about this to anyone, sir.
Mr. Kriplani,
Troy is our security chief. - Okay.
It's just a regular security drill.
You don't need to feel scared.
Like you said, my son is
just like your own son.. - Absolutely.
Similarly,
your son is my life my own son.
Okay, relax.
Yeah?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
This guy..
He is too funny.
Kabir..
I'm damned..
Stop worrying about your son.
We will have to stay alert now.
You know why no one
has ever touched D'Souza?
Because he had Ajay Mehra's support.
He is very stubborn. You don't know
what kind of a person Ajay Mehra is.
Balwant Rai was once
where you are now.
He killed Ajay Mehra's brother.
The entire Mumbai police, D'Souza
and his men provided him security.
But no one was able
to stop Ajay Mehra.
He gave him 24 hours.
He went inside Balwant
Rai's house and shot him.
And he also killed all
those who were with him.
He killed all of them.
He is a crazy stubborn guy.
Mr. Bansal, he killed everyone.
Did you hear me?
You don't know what Ajay Mehra is.
Who is this Ajay Mehra?
I am thinking about my son
and you are talking about Ajay Mehra.
Who the hell is this Ajay Mehra?
'Why are you staring?'
'Honesty never dies.'
'When a corrupt person dies,
his rein ends.'
'But when an honest man dies,
his rein begins.'
'Satyakams never dies.'
Morning, mom. Morning, dad.
- Good morning.
See you in court.
- Sure, sir.
Morning.
Dad, what did you do with that video?
I mean what's the progress?
My friends were asking..
..as we haven't heard any
news about them getting arrested so..
Eat this.
- Yes, I'll eat it.
So what's the progress, dad?
Rohan, the progress is
that I have made all of you safe.
Safe? - And I am sure, this
is what other parents wanted as well.
Aren't you getting late?
- Yes. Let's go.
Dad?
Dad! Dad, wait!
Rohan.. - But what
does making us safe mean?
I gave the video to the
ones to whom it belonged.
Kabir Bansal murdered Mr. D'Souza.
And you gave the evidence to him?
Rohan, it's..
- Dad.. dad, he is wrong.
What is wrong?
Is it wrong to be a father?
Is it wrong to save your family?
No, dad. But it wrong to
be scared of the wrong people.
And you are a lawyer!
You stand for truth and justice.
Truth and justice?
You know what is
truth and justice today?
Today truth and justice is Raj Bansal.
Raj Bansal,
today, is truth and justice!
He must be having
his own reasons, Rohan.
He must be genuinely
afraid of Mr. Bansal.
He's a powerful man.
Anushka is right, Rohan.
How is she right?
If a lawyer of his stature
cannot bring justice to someone..
..then how can a common man
hope for anything in this country?
And our parents are so duplicitous.
They teach us one thing and
they do something just the opposite.
Pretending parents.
- What?
You are right, Zoya.
Pretending parents.
That day we should have
given that video to Ajay Mehra.
Then what are you waiting for?
I have taken a backup of that video.
Zoya? When? How did you do it?
What are we waiting for? Let's go.
He will now stay in the
military academy, mother.
I'm the one who spoilt him, so I'll be
the one who will get him back on track.
No.
- Call him again.
You have a problem bending
before your elders as well?
Touch her feet properly.
Go on.
Your manners help you
win the world and not your ego.
He is not answering it?
Yes, Zoya?
Hello, Alnoor sir..
Can I please speak to Ajay Mehra?
Any emergency?
Sir, Joe D'Souza didn't die
in an accident. He was murdered.
What?
And we have the evidence.
- Are you sure?
Yes, sir.
Can we please talk to Ajay Mehra?
Troy, kids have a copy of the evidence.
And they are going to Ajay Mehra.
Copy that.
Mr. Bansal, the kids
have the copy of the evidence.
And they have made
contact with Ajay Mehra.
Ajay..
There is an emergency.
Hello, Zoya..
- Sir! Ajay sir!
Raj Bansal's son,
Kabir Bansal murdered him.
We have the proof, sir.
What? Whose murder?
We went to Karnala bird
sanctuary to make a documentary.
One of our cameras captured
Kabir Bansal shooting at Joe D'Souza.
Our home minister Kaka Sahib and
Raj Bansal were also present there.
Do you know what you are saying?
Are you sure about it?
Yes, sir. We have the proof.
This incident took place
in a farmhouse in Karnala.
Where are you?
In college, sir.
Hello, sir, I am Rohan.
Rohan, do you know where my office is?
Yes, sir.
- Go there. I'm coming here.
Okay.
Let's go. Let's go, guys.
Call Kaka Sahib and Kriplani as well.
- Yes, sir.
What's happening, Raj?
You had said that
everything would be fine.
What's going on? Tell me something.
Sheetal, please. - Ajay Mehra
is at Mt. Mary Church, Bandra.
Do whatever you have to do.
Just make sure that
Kabir stays unharmed.
I don't let any harm come to my son.
Don't worry, Sheetal. - Zoya is at Pedar Road.
And we are here.
Joshi, what are you waiting for?
You didn't call Kaka saheb?
Zoya has left ?
You can catch them here.
At Senapati Bapat Road.
Keep me posted.
- Yes, sir.
I'll get the kids.
- Get them.
Yes, Mr. Bansal?
Income tax, service tax,
IT cell, narcotics department..
Use all the departments
and seize Ajay Mehra's office..
..his press and all his properties,
Immediately.
Why? What happened?
Another copy of that
video has showed up.
The kids are going
to give it to Ajay Mehra.
Why are you putting me in a fix?
Just shut up.
Just do as I say.
Kriplani,
if you had given me all the copies..
..then which copy are the
kids going to give to Ajay Mehra?
There is no other copy of it,
Mr. Bansal.
Are you playing with me?
- No, not at all.
Stop your son,
or else I will kill him.
No!
Sir. Jai Hind, sir.
Yes, Jai Hind.
Income tax,
service tax, narcotics department..
..has raided Ajay Mehra's Satyakam.
Ajay Mehra?
Yes, he has messed up big time.
Sir, Rohan is not
taking Kriplani's call.
I need your personal supervision.
Put surveillance on Ajay
Mehra and all his men right away.
Troy, you need to be faster.
Your dad is calling.
- Don't answer it.
Sir, there is only a distance of
800 yards between Troy and the kids.
Yes, Kriplani?
Hello, Kulkarni?
- Yes.
Call up Anushka right away.
Rohan is not answering my phone.
- What happened?
They have made a copy of that video.
The kids are going to give
it to Ajay Mehra. - A copy?
To Ajay Mehra?
Call her up right away,
or all of them will die.
They have taken a left
to Senapati Bapat Road.
Grandpa?
Hello, grandpa?
- What have you done!
From where did you get that copy?
You are going to give
that copy to Ajay Mehra?
You won't give that
copy to Ajay Mehra.
You will instead go straight
to Kriplani's house.
Okay, grandpa.
400 yards.
What happened?
- He is furious.
He has told me not to go
to Ajay Mehra with the hard drive.
200 yards..
I don't get one thing,
how did he learn that..
..we are going to Ajay
Mehra with the hard disk?
Obviously,
Bansal is tapping our phones.
What?
- How else would he know?
100 yards..
Troy, where are you going?
You have just crossed them.
- Stop them.
Now what?
- Who are they?
Guys, they are Bansal's men.
- Oh shit.
No!
- Rohan!
Call Ajay Mehra, now!
Yes, Zoya?
Ajay sir..
Bansal's men are attacking us.
Sir, our phones are being tapped.
What should we do?
Where are you?
Where are we?
Hang on!
Guys! Where are we, guys?
Phoenix Mall.
Phoenix Mall's parking lot, sir.
Don't worry, Zoya.
First of all, destroy your SIM cards.
I'll come there as soon as possible.
Destroy your SIM cards.
Give me your phones.
Akshay, there's an
emergency at Phoenix Mall.
Four kids are in trouble.
Send help immediately.
Okay, sir.
Bansal has foreign militants
in his security, right?
Highly trained foreigners.
We're going to die, Rohan.
I can't do anything.
Do something.
- It's stuck...it's stuck.
Rohan, the car. Rohan.
Rohan..
- It's not starting.
Skype..
Let's get out. Let's go.
- Skype..
Come on.
Oh no!
They are coming.
- Oh shit!
We need to go.
- Come on. Let's go.
Not that way.
Up..
- Run.
Guys, I am bleeding.
Shit..
Oh my God!
No, Rohan!
- No, Rohan!
No!
If we are going to support the truth..
..we aren't going
to give up until we win.
If we are going to support the truth..
..we aren't going
to give up until we win.
If we are going to support the truth..
..we aren't going
to give up until we win.
Come on. Let's go.
My leg!
Varun, hurry up. They are coming.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
- Let's go guys, come on.
Rohan come!
Have you got them, Troy?
I'll get the kids, sir.
Get the car down.
You two, you go straight.
- Okay sir.
You go up.
Yes, sir.
Give me the live feed of Phoenix Mall.
- Yes, sir.
Come, come on.
Troy, go to the security room.
Don't worry. I am on it.
What's wrong?
Stop.
- We have reached the mall, sir.
These guys are here too.
We need to keep going, guys.
Let's go. Let's go.
Come on guys let's go
- I'm coming.
Let's go. Let's go.
Who are you?
- Don't worry.
I am Satyakam.
Ajay Mehra had called.
He is on his way.
Come with me.
It's okay, guys. Come.
- It's okay, guys.
Come. Come on.
Boys, they have gone
into Mother Earth.
You think we are safe here?
Yes. Ajay Mehra will soon be here.
You are bleeding too much.
- Water.
Uncle, do you have
the first-aid box? - Yes.
Get some tissues, please.
- You all right? - Yeah.
Close the shutter.
- Yes, sir.
Hurry up.
Close the shutter.
Shit.
- Get up we need to move.
Let's go. Come on!
Come on. Come on.
Run. Run;
- Go out the back door.
Hey you!
Faster!
- Come on, guys.
Go, go, go.
Hurry up.
They are coming. Let's go.
Hurry up, Rohan!
- Go!
Go.
- Let's go.
Run, run, run.
Rohan.
Let's go.
- Go, go, go!
Come on, let's go.
- Rohan come on. Rohan.
Come on, faster.
Come on.
- Go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What happened?
- Get back!
Cameras.
- Cameras?
They are watching us.
- What?
That's how they knew
we were in that shop.
Then what should we do?
If we are together,
then we are one target. - Yes.
I think we should spilt up.
They won't be able to track us.
- That makes sense, guys.
Boys. They are all splitting up.
She is getting away. Faster.
No. No..
Leave me..
Leave me!
Leave me! Leave me!
Anushka!
Joshi, jam all the
signals from this mall. - Yes, sir.
No videos should
get uploaded from there.
Sachin, you missed him.
He's near the food court.
Leave me!
Let go of me!
Imran, she is right above you.
Leave me!
Oh shit!
Rohan!
Rohan, be careful.
Come on. Move!
- Let's go!
Get them! Faster!
Hurry up, Rohan. Hurry up.
Boys, bring in the bikes.
Watch it.
Rohan!
Leave him, I say leave him.
Zoya!
Rohan, go, go, go.
Leave me!
Don't think, Rohan. Go!
Go, Rohan!
Get her to the parking lot.
Yes!
Rohan!
- Rohan!
Can you hear me?
Rohan..
Rohan, get up.
Mr. Bansal, I have sealed
Satyakam and trammeled Ajay Mehra.
Good.
Ajay sir..
Sir..
Come on kids, let's go.
- No, I can't get up.
Troy!
Where are they?
Where did he go?
Where did they disappear?
They are outside the mall, sir.
There are no cameras outside.
Joshi.
- Yes, sir.
I want to talk to
the defense secretary. - Okay, sir.
Faster, Joshi.
- Just connecting, sir.
Akshay, call Riya.
Hello?
I want immediate access
to the satellite images of Mumbai!
What are you talking?
I am Raj Bansal here!
So what?
You could be anybody.
It's a matter of national security.
Ravi, now!
Ashok, now!
Troy, have you got them?
Troy!
Have you got them?
No, sir.
How can they be so good?
They are the mercenaries
of truth, sir.
Truth fanatics.
Ajay Mehra's soldiers, his A-team..
Your paid mercenaries can
never match these mercenaries.
What did you say?
Come again?
I've been doing cooperate..
..espionage and hacking
for you since the past five years.
That was fine.
We weren't harming any innocent being.
But what we are doing
with these kids today..
Sorry, sir.
I don't want to be a part of all this.
I am with those kids.
I am a "Satyakam".
Kabir! Kabir, stop. Stop.
Kabir! Kabir! Kabir!
Anyone else here is a "Satyakam"?
Anyone?
Keep it here. Here.
Nitin, get me some ice.
I think I've broken my leg.
- I think I've broken my leg.
Give me the antiseptic.
- It's just a little spirit, that's all.
Don't worry.
Ajay sir.. come with me for a minute.
- Varun, try to open your eyes.
It's urgent, sir. Please.
- It's paining.
It's urgent. Please.
- You'll be fine don't worry.
Open your eyes.
Many departments have raided together.
It department, central vigilance..
- What?
There is too much panic.
Have a look, sir.
They have seized the whole office.
They have arrested our people.
And look over here, sir.
Look what the news
channels are telecasting.
'Ajay Mehra exposed.'
'Sudden raids by all government departments
have put Ajay Mehra and Satyakam..'
Sir, there is a lot of confusion
among the members of Satyakam.
We are getting messages asking us,
what they should do.
Tell them not to panic.
- Sir..
How can you just sit here,
Kaka Sahib?
Call up the police
control room and ask them..
..to comb the area from
where Ajay Mehra disappeared.
Alert your cyber cell.
- Okay.
And ensure that that video
shouldn't be uploaded at any cost.
Media, judiciary, bureaucracy..
Wherever he has sympathizers,
keep them under watch.
Issue a red alert against
Ajay Mehra and those four kids.
Okay.
- Immediately.
All of you..
Hack into Ajay Mehra's
server and find out where he is.
How can he just disappear?
Akshay, where are our friends.
Sir, we are trying to contact them,
but we cannot.
Ajay sir, Rohan wants to talk to you.
Sir...
Take it easy son.
- Shit.
Give me that video.
I am sorry, sir.
But they cornered me in the shop..
So I hid the hard drive over there..
It's in the speaker section.
So that they cannot
get a hold of it.
Look after the kids.
Okay.
Mr. Bansal don't worry
filters are activated...
We won't let any comment video or
data video get uploaded against you.
Good.
Why are you guys taking so
much of time to hack into his server?
Do it faster.
It's been more than half an hour.
Look for him in every house.
We are almost here.
- Search each and every house.
If you have need to strip
everyone naked then do it.
I want Ajay Mehra. - Namdev,
who is heading the committee?
George Awasthi.
- Keep an eye on George Awasthi as well.
Yes, sir.
He's a sympathizer of Ajay Mehra.
Sir. - Yes, sir.
- Hello, control room.
Send more men.
I don't have any
idea about the location.
They took me in a dirty body bag..
..and then dumped me inside a tempo or a
truck, because I heard a shutter close.
After that it stopped at
a car park and they took me out.
Sir, he says it was a car park and
the other person says it was a school.
What's your full name?
- Ajay Vithal Gaekwad.
You are working in
the accounts department?
Since one year.
I don't know, sir.
I bloody hell don't want to see this.
Do you understand? I want
to see the bloody extortion list!
Where were you before this?
In jail.
With Ajay Mehra?
- Yes.
We are getting information
that since the past ten years..
Yes, sir?
Set up check posts at all
the roads leading out of Mumbai.
Ajay Mehra shouldn't leave Mumbai.
Sir! Sir!
- He won't. don't worry, sir.
What would you like to say?
What did you find
inside Satyakam's office?
I am Satyakam.
Ajay Mehra has asked us to keep quiet.
What are the court orders?
As you can see..
We have also heard that..
..Ajay Mehra also makes
juvenile college students...
...hack email and bank
accounts of famous people.
For not, there's been a look
out notice issued against 4 students.
What is she saying about our kids?
Yes, I, too, heard it.
Please talk softly.
Why should we talk softly?
Everything is happening
because of your son, Rohan.
Why are you blaming Rohan?
- He loves to mess around with everyone.
I kept saying that you shouldn't
get Ajay Mehra involved.
But this was Anushka's project,
wasn't it?
Yes, it is.
But Zoya is responsible for this mess.
What? - She keeps coming
up with weird ideas.
Why are you involving
my daughter into this?
If you had given even a little
attention to your daughter..
Have you ever
read your daughter's blogs?
Zoya writes blogs?
- Yes.
Why is the media saying such things
about our kids.. - So what do I do?
Who is it?
- Kriplani.
What is he saying? - He's saying that
the media is calling our kids criminals.
Search everyone's houses.
I mean everyone.
We got him, sir.
We are nearly there.
Shit!
What happened, sir?
Bansal's cyber cell was
trying to hack our server.
If it had succeeded, they would've
found out about this hideout.
But now we are safe.
Sir..
Troy wants to talk to you, sir.
Yeah, Troy.
Sir, I have tried
my best to break them.
But they are not talking.
Troy, just kill one of them.
Others will speak automatically.
- No, Troy.
Is this the best solution
you could think of?
That's the Nazi way, dad.
Fear of death is worse than death.
And next what?
Blow up this whole city with a bomb?
What do you think,
am I some god or godfather?
Are we running
a crime syndicate here?
Why are you shouting at me?
You are behaving as if
you haven't killed anybody.
What did you say?
- Raj..
- Yes, you heard me right.
You are behaving as if
you haven't killed anybody.
I didn't kill anyone with my own hands.
- What difference does it make?
It makes a difference because
we are running a business here.
We are not running a crime syndicate.
- Just keep quiet, Kabir.
I had got people killed
for tactical reasons.
You are a Harvard graduate.
- So what?
Don't you understand that
not rage but courage solves problems?
Go and think over this issue.
- Yes, I am going.
Go.
- I am going in my room.
Let me talk.
Kabir!
Hello?
Papa, food has been served.
We are waiting for you.
Give the phone to your grandma, dear.
Yes?
We got it, sir.
Here is the hard drive, sir.
See this.
Sir, I was scanning the mall's
footage and here's what I found.
Good. Very good.
Oh, we have got the drive!
My God. Inform Troy.
Troy is already in the mall, sir.
- Great.
Give me the live feed
of the shop. Give me. - Yes, sir.
Ask Troy to reach there quickly.
I want the hard drive now!
Your papa will come later.
We should start eating.
Prema?
This is the live feed from the mall.
Mr. Bansal, even Ajay Mehra
must be aware about this, right?
Doomed. He is already there.
Troy!
Where are you, Troy?
Good.
Catch him.
Troy!
Hard disk should not
go into Ajay Mehra's hand..
..even if you have to shoot him.
Kill him.
Doomed.
Go!
Watch out!
Do you have a death wish?
Hey, are you mad?
Have you gone crazy?
Watch out!
- Are you blind?
Oh, my God! He's got a gun!
Move!
Ajay Mehra.
That's Ajay Mehra.
Yes, he's wounded.
Move.
Yes Rakesh.
- Yes, sir.
What happened?
The news is true, sir.
We just found Raj Bansal's security
chief's dead body on the railway tracks.
People have also seen
Ajay Mehra fighting with him.
This means this issue directly
involves Ajay Mehra and Raj Bansal.
This is a very big story.
No, hang on.
Wait for my instructions.
Don't worry. The hospital..
- Sir..
Who..
- Mr. Kaitan.
Yes, Kaitan?
Mr. Bansal, we have been
hearing many rumors since morning..
..that you and your men are
involved in Ajay Mehra's case today.
So?
Nothing. We are not
airing any news against you.
Don't worry.
We understand that Ajay Mehra
has become a problem for all of us.
Good.
- We don't..
Rakesh, for now we
will only show the truth..
..that doesn't affect our
channel's business interest. - Okay.
Keep an eye on the situation
and keep me updated.
Got it?
Okay, sir.
Akshay!
Yes, sir.
Sir, this.. - Akshay..
Where are the kids and Riya?
Sir, the kids were in a bad condition
so Riya took them to the hospital.
But she is on her way back.
- What happened over here?
All this..
Sir, Bansal was trying
to track our location..
..so I had to disconnect everything.
Here. Connect this.
- We had no other option.
Ajay.
Riya.
What happened?
We had taken the kids
to the hospital.
Let me go! - Help me!
- How could you just barge in?
Security! Security! Stop them!
Help me!
Security!
- Leave me.
Leave me! Let go! Let me go!
Anushka!
- Leave me!
Somebody help us!
Let them go!
Anushka! Rohan!
Anushka!
- Rohan!
Why are you hitting them?
Leave them.
Rohan!
Ma'am!
Ma'am, please help us!
Ma'am! - Let them go!
Let them go! Leave me!
- Yes, sir.
Let me go!
- Talk to him.
Talk to him.
I could've killed you as well, doctor.
But I am letting you live.
- Bansal, they are just kids!
What enmity do you have with them!
Let them go! - Go and reason
it with your mental patient.
If he doesn't return the video..
..then I'll hang their dead bodies
of them at Ajay Mehra's press.
Do you understand that?
I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't do anything. Ajay..
Satyakam, our years of hard work,
our sacrifices..
In just a few hours that man
has brought us back to square one.
The entire systems and machineries..
..have become a criminal's agent.
And people are still just
watching from the sidelines.
They will side the one who wins.
They don't give a damn
about the truth or lies.
Okay, then so be it.
Akshay, upload it.
I cannot, sir. The server is dead.
Fine then make copies of it.
Yes. I will personally distribute
it across the city.
Make copies of it.
- Didn't you hear me?
Make the copies.
- They will kill the kids.
Let him kills the kids if he wants to!
He is already on a killing spree.
He killed Joe D'Souza.
He killed so many
innocent people as well.
And today,
he killed our friends in front of you.
No!
I will destroy Bansal's empire..
I will have him begging on streets!
I will expose him!
What are you waiting for?
Make copies of it.
- Stop it.
Make copies of it. No!
- What are you doing? Stop it.
I want copies.
Make copies of it.
- Stop it.
Copies. Copies
I want copies.
- Stop it.
Come to your senses!
Stop it! Stop it!
Look at me.
They are kids.
They are just kids.
They are innocent, Ajay.
They don't know that this
video could have them killed.
What do you want?
You want their photos
on that martyrs' board?
Can you live with that?
Can you?
You didn't see how
they killed Joe D'Souza.
Just look at that.
- I know.
I know, Ajay. I know.
But even Joe sir wouldn't
want us to risk the lives of kids.
And we have no right
to take such a risk with them.
Please Ajay.. try to understand.
They are not our kids.
You thought that you would
come on news channels, as heroes.
Right?
For Ajay Satyakam Mehra,
these four kids were blackmailing..
..money laundering
and hacking accounts.
The police are yet
to disclose their names.
But they say that these kids
will soon be in their custody.
Luckily, all of you are just kids.
Not you, Rohan.
You know what treatment
boys like you get in the jail.
Don't drop the soap..
No, Rohan.
She has you whipped, already.
Kabir!
Anushka!
- I will kill you!
Stop, please! No.
Leave him!
No!
- Leave him!
Kabir!
No!
- Kabir!
What?
What were you doing in there?
Teaching these slaves a lesson.
Kabir!
Have you lost your mind?
Kabir.. listen to me.
Stop.
Stop, Kabir!
Listen to me.
Listen to me, Kabir!
Kabir.. listen to me.
Son..
One should hide their children's
mistakes, not their crimes..
I heard someone scream.
What is happening?
It's nothing, mother.
Go to your room.
I am not blind or deaf, son.
It's nothing, mother. Come.
I feel as if something very bad
is going to happen. - Come with me.
Why are you hiding it from me?
- Come.
I am feeling very scared.
- Mother..
I am not feeling good..
Sir.. - Mother,
you should take care of Ananya.
Please take care of Ananya.
- I am feeling very scared.
Please, mother.
I am not feeling good about this.
Yes, tell me.
- Very good news, sir.
Ajay Mehra is going
to Kriplani's house.
Kriplani had called.
He said that Dr. Riya is coming
over to his house with Ajay Mehra.
Good.
We have our men there.
If you want we could.. - No!
No!
My leg!
Grandma.. let's pray.
Everything will be fine.
Everything will be fine, my child.
Where is my daughter?
- Ajay!
- Did you find the kids?
Ajay, give us that evidence video..
- Ajay, how dare you..?
Ajay, who has given you the right
to put my daughter's life at risk!
Give that damn thing now!
We too are concerned
about your children's safety.
Why would you be concerned? - If you are
concerned then give us the evidence.
This is not done.
- Let me at least talk.
My Varun..
- Please listen to me. Hold on. Please listen to me.
Just listen to me. Listen to me!
Once Bansal is exposed,
he will be busy saving himself.
You.. - He won't
do anything to the kids.
You just need to be patient.
He has our kids!
- You don't understand.
If anything happens to Rohan...
He won't do anything to them!
- How can you say that?
Once he is exposed, he can do nothing!
- I am worried about my kid.
He cannot do anything...
- Ajay Mehra.
You?
- Give them the evidence..
Or your daughter will die.
Daughter?
- Yes.
Anushka is your daughter.
- My daughter?!
But you said.
Varsha is dead.
And her child is also dead.
Because of you.
During delivery..
- No. You are lying!
Both of them..
- I spoke to her a few days ago.
They are dead because of you.
Both of them are dead because of you.
It's your fault.
- No!
I want to die. I want to die.
Let me die.
Ajay, drink this water.
I want to go to Varsha.
My daughter is alive.
You kept her hidden?
Why?
Why did you keep my daughter hidden?
Because I wanted to keep her alive.
Anyone who was close to you died.
Your brother.
Your sister-in-law.
Your friends.
Varsha.
D'Souza.
All of them.
All of them died.
Now look, your daughter facing death..
..as soon as she came close to you.
Why do you want to kill your daughter?
You want Anushka dead.
Enough, uncle,
you have said enough.
Calm down.
- Varun!
My son!
Mother!
Son..
How did this...
It's hurting a lot, mother.
- Where?
It's hurting a lot.
- Where does it hurt, son?
Oh God, they have hurt him so badly.
It's hurting. Move aside.
Please to listen to me.
- Ajay sir..
Listen to me, Varun. Listen to me.
Sir, they will kill my friends.
Sir, they are ruthless.
Sir, we can't take it anymore.
Please, sir. - Give them the evidence.
- Now what else do you want, Ajay?
Please give it.
- Give them the hard drive.
We can't take it anymore.
Sir, please give the hard drive.
Please sir.
Take this.
- Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Move aside.
But you got the hard drive.
- I have to save my friends.
Varun, stop. Varun..
Please go along with my son.
Zoya!
- Varun!
Rohan!
- Mom!
How are you?
- My child..
What happened?
I am so happy.
You are back. I don't want anything else.
- Ajay sir.. sir..
Anushka..
She is still there.
Sir, they were first
going to keep me back.
But as soon as they learnt that she is
your daughter, they kept her instead.
Sir, they know everything
that is happening here.
Because of my dad.
I am sorry.
Sir, Bansal has given this for you.
Are you my father?
Yes, dear.
Then where have you
been all these years?
Why was I kept away from you?
Why did grandpa always
say that my parents are no more?
I am sorry, dear.
I am sorry.
You didn't know that
you had a daughter?
You didn't know about me?
I will explain everything
when we will meet.
You are not my father.
No, dear. I am your papa.
I will explain everything.
What will you explain?
When I was small,
and I used to go to school..
..I used to think that all
my friends have parents, but I don't.
Since childhood I have been
told that I don't have anyone.
I am sorry, dear.
I did not have anyone, papa.
My child..
I thought that I am alone.
What will you explain,
that why am I here?
Why they are troubling me?
Why am I facing these problems?
What will you explain?
- Dear..
You are not my father.
No dear, you shouldn't say that.
I hate you!
Dear..
Anushka!
My child..
Don't worry. I will explain
everything to your daughter.
Bansal, I gave you the hard drive.
Give me my daughter back.
You are a smart journalist, Ajay.
- Please send her back.
I am sure you must have
made copies of this video.
I don't have any copies, Bansal.
I don't.
This is what was told
to me last time as well.
But then copies of
that video cropped up.
Hence, this time
I cannot take any risk.
Your daughter is the
guarantee of my son's safety.
Anyway, what difference
does it make to you?
She has been staying
away from you all this while.
Stop your nonsense, Bansal.
Give me my daughter back.
No!
She will stay with
me till you are alive.
And remember,
if you do anything stupid..
Anything..
Then you know what you will lose.
And the discussion ends here.
Joshi..
- Yes, sir..
Joshi, take this
girl back to her father.
Mother!
- What are you..?
You will kidnap someone's daughter?
Now this is what you will do?
Then what do you want?
That I should shoot Kabir?
Should I send him to jail?
- Yes, send him to jail.
He has committed a crime.
He should be punished.
What are you saying?
The stock market will crash if
Kabir even gets a scratch on his body.
Thousands of investors
will commit suicide.
You want to kill thousands
to save a single girl?
You too have a daughter.
What if someone does this to her?
Mother!
If someone touches my daughter,
I will kill him!
I am Raj Bansal!
What do you think?
Your daughter is valuable
and his daughter is not?
Raj, anyone's daughter
is always treated like one's own.
Let me do my work, mother.
Please. Go away from here.
I won't leave.
- Please leave, mother.
I will send this
girl back to her father.
Let me do my work. Sheetal, take her away.
- What you are doing is not right.
You keep quiet.
You too are just like him.
Please leave, mother.
- No.
Take her away, Sheetal.
- Okay..
Please. - What you
are doing is not right.
Let's go, mother.
- Please, mother.
Something bad is
going to happen to us.
Please leave.
- You are not getting it, Raj.
Everything will be over.
What does he think of himself?
- Calm down, mother.
A sin is being committed in my house.
- Come with me.
He has lost his mind.
Come on, sit down.
- This is wrong.
It is wrong.
- Sit down.
What happened, grandma? Why are
you crying? What happened, grandma?
It's nothing, dear.
It's nothing.
Joshi..
- Yes, sir.
Call the chopper. Take her
to our sea oilrig. - Right sir.
Kaka Sahib,
get Ajay Mehra arrested.
We are done with him now.
- Hello Chetan..
Get air clearance right away
and get the chopper to Bansal Mansion.
If I go...
They will kill her.
If I don't go..
He will send my daughter
somewhere far away..
And I want my daughter.
What do I do?
Ajay..
Go get your daughter.
How could he just run away?
What were you doing?
Why didn't you just shoot him?
Ajay Mehra escaped in a police van.
Your mother was right..
Why did you kidnap his daughter?
His brother was kidnapped and he had
caused havoc in the entire Mumbai city.
You have kidnapped his daughter.
His daughter!
He will tear down
the entire Mumbai city.
How can he tear down
the entire Mumbai city?
Now what do I tell you?
Set up check posts
all across the city.
Check posts..
- Issue shoot at sight orders.
If I see Ajay Mehra
anywhere near this mansion today..
Then your political career will end.
I worry more about my
life than my political career.
Joshi!
- Yes, sir!
Hello? - Take his
daughter to the helipad.
And ask Troy's team
and ground force to be ready.
Okay, sir.
Ajay Mehra wants to have war.
We will give him war!
'Ajay Mehra ran away in Bandra
Pali Hill Beats' police van..
..number MH-02-FA-7015.'
We just got the information that..
..Mumbai police has issued shoot
at sight orders against Ajay Mehra.
'Block all the roads
leading to Worli.'
We have been informed that Ajay
Mehra attacked the police team..
..and ran away in a police jeep.
Block the roads going towards
the sea-link.
Search each and every car.
These are the orders from above.
Put up tight police security.
Patil make sure.
Set up the barricades on sea-link
to Bansal mansion road.
Yes sir.
- Search each and every car.
Shoot Ajay Mehra
if he doesn't surrender.
Fast. Fast. Fast.
Hurry up. Be quick.
Hello.
Sir, after looking at the way police
are setting up barricades all around..
..the Bansal Mansion,
I feel something big about to happen.
Now we will have to
expose Bansal in this case.
Hang on
- Yes, sir.
I will let you know
what you need to do.
Move the barricades. Hurry up.
Jai Hind, sir.
- Yes, sir.
Sir you don't worry,
I am on the location itself.
Police has set up the barricades
around Bansal Mansion.
I have also arranged
the Special forces.
Do anything you have to do.
Just arrest Ajay Mehra!
I will do it, sir. I will do it.
This time he has directly
challenged Mumbai police.
Now if Ajay Mehra doesn't
surrender then he will die.
Don't let the media inside.
Move back.
Go. Hurry up.
- Hurry up.
Hello, control room.
Sir, we have found the
car Ajay Mehra ran away in.
Then why are you informing me,
you idiot?
Are we looking for
Ajay Mehra or the van?
Look for him in the area
where you found the jeep.
Find him.
Who stopped the traffic?
Clear the traffic.
- Come on.
Sir, Ajay Mehra has
hijacked our chopper.
Send Troy's team to the helipad.
- Okay, sir.
Are you mad, Ajay Mehra?
Have you lost your mind?
After stealing my
chopper you think you will..
..take your daughter
alive from my house?
I say, you should go back.
You still have time.
He will kill us.
- Shut up!
I am warning you.
I will bury your daughter alive.
Are you listening to me?
- Mr. Bansal, listen to me..
Shut up! Shut up!
- He is coming. I had told you..
Shut up!
Shut up! Go from here. Get out.
He is here.
Mom, where is papa going?
Papa!
I am sorry, papa!
For being so rude.
Fire!
- Papa!
- Shoot him to death.
No!
- Papa!
Police is shooting at
Ajay Mehra's chopper.
He's dumping fuel.
- What do you mean?
It's not safe. We have to go.
No way.
Sir, we have to go.
- How dare he!
We have to get out of here now!
- Leave me.
Sir, we need to get
you somewhere safe.
No way.
- Get him out of here.
I'll finish him.
I will ruin him.
Lord save me.
- What does he think of himself?
My family!
Ajay Mehra has taken the
chopper inside Bansal Mansion.
Move it.
Move.
Put the gun down.
Papa..
- I said, put the gun down.
Now, we are just going to kill you.
With our bad hands.
Papa..
Papa!
Dear, I am fine.
I am coming, my child.
Papa!
Don't be scared, Ananya.
Don't worry.
- Raj!
I am coming!
- Help me Papa!
Raj!
I will be there.
Don't worry. I am coming, Ananya.
- Raj!
Raj.
- Be brave, my child.
Papa.
- Help! Raj!
Get water.
Help!
- I will be there.
Raj! Help!
Move, come on.
Come on, don't be scared.
Don't be scared, son. Come on.
Come on.
Don't worry.
Come on let's go. Let's go.
Move, come.
Mom..
Papa!
- Raj!
Son..
- Papa!
Ajay Mehra!
Come out!
If you got the guts, come face me!
How dare you crash
into my house!
My child..
You have come to save
your daughter, right?
Come, save her.
- Don't touch my daughter.
Papa!
No!
Papa..
Ajay, it is my fault.
Uncle, please don't hurt my brother.
Please, don't.
Please don't hurt my brother..
Please don't..
- Please forgive us.
Please forgive us.
Please.
- Please forgive us.
Please spare him. Please..
Please.
Please spare his life.
We apologize.
Please forgive us.
- Please... sorry.
Please.
Brother!
- Kabir!
I am sorry, dear.
I am sorry.
Papa..
I've been stupid.
I am sorry.
I am sorry, I didn't know.
I had no idea.
No...
Dear ..
Love you papa.
Love you dear.
Open the gate.
Because of you...
- Forgive me, son.
Because of them..
Hi.
Hello sir.
- Hello.
Hello madam.
How are you?
- So sweet flowers.
How are you feeling?
Ajay.
Thank you.
"All you need is a spark.."
"To start a fire."
"That spark.."
"Lies dormant.."
"In your heart."
"The way this world is.."
"Let it stay that way."
"Tell me.."
"What's the fun in
leading such a life?"
"All you need is a spark.."
"To start a fire."
"That spark.."
"Lies dormant.."
"In your heart."
"Why do you complain?"
"First stop being a pain."
"To make an ocean,
every drop helps."
"The first step, you take."
"An oath, you make."
"You don't know in you God dwells."
"There are millions
excuses for failure."
"Who can you blame?"
"But it is also our responsibility."
"This I can surely claim."
"We can see what's happening."
"Why should we shy away?"
"We should be determined.."
"To change the situation."
"Listen, my dear friend, I pray."
"To what the heart says."
"The truth.."
"Is close to you."
"If you seek.."
"You shall find them.."
"In the mirror."
"The way this world is.."
"Let it stay that way."
"Tell me, what's the
fun in leading such a life?"
"Why do you complain?"
"First stop being a pain."
"To make an ocean, every drop helps."
"The first step, you take."
"An oath, you make."
"You don't know in you God dwells."