Anirudh...
I'm ready...!
Manoj, are you sure
you want to do this?
Think again, this all can
go against you"!
50 what does It affect?
Lets have It
we've to go In mud
for cleaning the mud.
If you'll go In there,
your cloths will be spoiled.
People should know what happens In
India on the name of cricket.
Dump the tension bro
here camera will on,
there his innings over.
L, Azhar ls famous for 3 things
I believe on 1 God,
and have 2 wives and 3 century.
Azhar you're away from your target,
lets see allen can stop him or not.
Everything was going perfect,
on past time I was India's captain
Mea ns, Ind ia's so n-I n-law.
Life was going cool
you've come alone?
Where's sangeeta sister?
She's on shooting.
It tells the time correctly,
and tells also that ls time right or not
I saw this watch and
It's outta my budget.
One of my fan gave me
I became commentator"
You're still there.
It's 99 test matches... now what?
Why India ls written on chest...
nisha from India times.
Congrates for your century"
I got a question, do you think after
your 99 matches you'll be captain again
I don't perform so I become captain,
but India wins.
I'm still young, don't think
about retirement"
My grandpa told me to
play atlest 100 test matches.
Chairman has call me right now.
Fathers are calling"
Remaining questions next time.
I don't understand how to say.
What sir, I thought you'll
congrate me for century"
You're accused for match fixing
hessey stated that you made
him to a bookie
and association can't ignore It,
read It.
It's totally wrong, I don't
know any m.k sha rma.
There are many players,
he has named you
I met with many peoples
In party, .scme hug, snaps..
How'd I know there's bookie
In them, why're you talking to him
I advice you to hire a lawyer.
Till this inquew completed,
you can't play cricket
you know me for many years,
can I do It.
You're strange person,
you told me that he offered 25 lacs.
Who?
Azha r?
This azhar will not be trapped,
have to fix him
angw cricket fan did violence
outside azhar's house.
Azhar had a locker
In a royal hotel.
Hensey said on 15 june that azhar
was included to fix meeting with bookie.
After this alligation on azhar,
the investigation begin
azhar ls accused for
fixing 3 matches...
we've warrant for searching
your home.
The inquew ccmmesion
has mention In their para 130..
That azhar had close relation
with m.ksharma and other bookies.
And they were include In
match fixing"
You sold our country.
My name ls azhar, I'm accused
that I sold my country!
Fans do riot an fun too
everybody ls busy with
god for complaint against me.
People used to see me by turning,
still they do but prospect ls changed.
But with I've come to meet,
he can't change.
He grew up In london,
but he's complete desi.
Salaam..
He'll say that It was
necessawtc meet here?
It was written In horoscope,
you still read this?
You're changed, not me.
I get horoscope at my home,
but I don't read It.
But I know what ls written,
time ls bad..
Today's color ls black.
I need your black coat"
whv
I've decided that we've
to fight this case..
We?
If I get In case so I'll be pointed.
You don't get me stuck..
You think others I took the money
I don't know...
I just don't want to take your case.
I'm not a big lawyer.
You're not big lawyer..
But you're my old friend.
You go and hire any big lawyer.
Your're richman, you can afford It.
Whoever has less friends..
They're not rich.
When friend ls not on my side.
50 why fight for.
Good Bye.
Told you ma ny times.
You're here raja sir.
How're you
had come to meet client,
I met with azhar.
He's strange guy"
I told him that...
I'll take your case..
50 he's asking that
do you believe that I'm not guilty
you are or not"
And he said that I don't
want to fight this case.
Free publicity ls out of my hand.
Where're you going,
and why you denied to raja.
He's top lawyer of country.
I don't want to win the case.
You were saying 5 min ago
that I've to fight the case.
If you don't want clean chit
so what?
I want my respect back.
I want my country back and people.
But how people are
looking at me I can't see.
100 right work nobody remember,
one wrong accusation, everybody forgot me
tell me everything
from begining..
Means..
You'll take the case.
It's tough, winning chances impossible.
But I saw your many innings.
Tell me from begining.
8feb 1963.
Ccngrates..
His face has shine..
Tell the name father..
Azha r.
Bringing the light ..
Not only for us..
But he'll bring the light
for entire nation.
Grandpa level people
can predict the future
when he said first time I cculd'nt
understand..when holded bat"
But grandpa was In believe.
He'll play 100 tests"
How can you do It In lat over.
I'll see It If I say it..
Your dialougue of amitabh,
and voice ls like mukhri.
You answer him by playing
not speaking.
If you'll speakwith mouth
so few people will listen
If bat will speak, so everybody
has to listen It.
You'll play 100 matches for India.
This bat will become your voice.
Just learned the bat language.
That day It became my passion.
50 I decided to do it..
Have to play for India and grandpa.
But I got late for growing up
go to mumbai,
selectors are coming there..
I can't leave you alone.
Are you doctor or nurse]
do whatever you can do.
Don't be smart.
Are you going or I hit you
I can't play..
Instead of you anybody else
will play and his grandpa will happy
the chance don't wait..
Whoever ls near the chnce will get
do one thing"
Go inside and bring the medicine..
If anybody else ls going In team,
so let him go.
Not with you but
will stay near you"
We'll do batting tll 2 days.
What happened?
Everybody got silent.
Is everything okay
If I'll not play today,
so I'll never be able to play again
grandpa said If I don't play
100 tests, so he'll hit me with bat.
I won't play less than
100 tests"
It was granpa's prayer,
that India got the azhar..
Before the england"
A young player from hyderabad.
He's hitting the ball
around the field..
Azha r's century
In his first test match..
What?
Do you know who's our against
meera, she was myjunior
In london university.
That meera sings the bhajan,
but this plays..
Once she was arguing with
defendend, judge said order.
She said shut up to judge.
You say It later"
I took that azhar case
but...what?
But I fight with many
people that azhar can't do It.
I was his biggest fan.
That's what I've to procve In court.
I'm going to India
for meeting azhar's wife.
Who can be more
better witness than her.
Do he play cricket too
have you come for that.
I want you to become
my witness In this case.
Will have tea or coffee...?
Have to pick up my
son from couching class.
I'm getting late,
cricket association felt bad.
They speaked, fan speaked.
You were his wife..
You didn't feel bad?
You didn't answer me..
You didn't too
means, you'll not help me.
It's okay I met you
In that reason.
Have you kids?
I'm single.
50 you'll never understand.
Relation never finishes
by breaking.
Ball hat my ear,
I can't hear you
marriage . .
You've to get married.
I don't want to talk
listen to me.
I was joking.
My life ls In helmet,
and her life In burka..
If you don't want to do It,
so you say no to her.
You're going for match making"
50 tell me what do I say,
talk with lvoe.
What hair you got,
and earnings"
If you've woren It so good,
or what hair you have..
I thought my daughter
ls dumb but your son too
If they'll meet thrice,
they'll talk to each other.
Kids..
What?
I'm seeing you first
time out of t.v..
Lets go outside,
leave them alone.
I didn't do It delibretly
you can keep It.
Are you agree?
Agreed"
Ccngrates..
Yes..
No.
Yes father"
Write your name on underwear.
I'll do It.
Wear that yellow shirt.
Everything from shirt
to shocks ls correct.
Check It again.
Whose phone was It.
The one I recognize by silence.
I removed 2 names, of my wives..
I don't want them
to come In court.
The other names In list
will come or not ..
You'll not call your family.
You don't know about others.
Lets go to court
with cards, we'll play there.
There must be someone
who can stand with you
tell me..will you do captaincy?
I'll do it..
You speak slowly
how can senior player
will listen to me.
If player do mistakes"
How will you handle?
Calm down"
Show your fury In ground.
It all happens, but captain
becomes by his ability.
You're new captain,
don't mind them"
3 kinda war are world famous.
Wife and husband,
water and petrol
and between India
and pakistan cricket match"
You're welcome,
this match ls between pa k-ind.
It's very important match
for India's new captain.
And everybody are
In hope with this match.
If we loose from pa kista n,
public not let us go home
and family will not
let us come In home.
Look at this pitch.
Thorow the ball here.
Kapil said sorry.
Why?
He said he can't meet
today because he's busy
we've come from so far,
how can we go back.
I said what I was told to say
sit down.
Nothing gonna happen
by torturing police made
everything recorded.
He made me do signature.
I want the info what you
didn't tell enduring torture.
I don't have any info,
If I'd know so why do I tell you
actually, I don't want
to get shot
I was looking for a guy who
direct takes me to dressing room
and I got that guy
after paying his lose do
you know what I got... info.
Everything about Indian players.
Even their personal news.
With 11 players, billions
peoples sentiments are joined"
Has to see India's religion,
who'll sale his conscience.
As you can see azhar still
ls answering In his style.
But we'll get answer
after the result of this case.
Court means truth,
the truth will be appear soon.
Azhar made his name by
his ability...
I want to call azhar
upon the witness box"
Repeat after me
that I'll say truth.
If I'm true, my god will save me,
I swear I'll say true.
If human ls changed,
so what's strange In It.
Not getting the result
of prayer people changes god
when azhar came to know
that he has less days for playing.
50 he started
playing by taking money.
What ls your score?
Only9 runs..
Azhar's score"
Onlyl score"
Your score ls telling your truth.
Meera ls presenting the
evidence by twisting"
Whatever meera ls telling
us more than hiding us.
What you means?
My client was unlucky,
his intention weren't bad.
Often cricket gets out because
of ta king wrong decision.
This was just like decision
so now you're blaiming
on umpire for saving him
I'm accused that I got
out deliebretly In this match
lock at this match, did
I hit wrong shot and lost wicket}
Or got out because of wrong decision
you're all rounder
bigger than me... your lawyer and judge.
Since when do you know
m.ksharma...
I don't know him.
We've c.b.l reports that he
had met with m.ksharma ..
I've met you 1:00..
But don't know you
so tell the court where
you met him before.
In 95 or 96
with jay...
In royal hotel.
It was daytime...
something was going on In my life.
I met hm first time there.
He's shawn..diamond trader,
and he's my friend too
he has purposal.
If you've any add or something
so I can't do it..
It's okay"
We both are here.
Can you give me 5 min so.
You're right"
We'll talk later.
Your name..
Shawn".
Tell the court complete matter
an bookie met with
a team captain"
And he just shaked your
hand and left..l didn't know that.
The truth ls you took 1 crore
for underplay...
we've ha nsey statement which
he gave to his association
truth can be pushed
but can't be hide.
Truth Is he betrayed
with his nation and his team..
Betrayer can't be caught.
But I'm here In court.
I'm speaking from public side.
He's here to tell truth
to those people"
Money ls not greater
than honor and love..
It's a court case,
not street fight"
Both of you carefull..
In the first hearing,
It's clear the he met m.k sharma.
But did he took
money from m.k sharma.
Do you want to know
did I met with m.ksharma or not?
Sometimes money ls usefull
than human being.
Association people do
whatever they like
your just bat works"
Decision they takes.
Don't you afraid.
If I shout here,
so crowd will gather.
They'll hit you so hard..
Therefor I've weight of money
when money speaks.
Nobody speaks.
If you'll not hit it..
Someone else will
this bag contains 1 crore.
And you've to work 1 thing.
Nothing.
When your demand fullfiled,
so you're silent.
I can't show you my
chest that I'm not hiding.
Whatever was ls shown"
And truth.
1 match ls remaining"
Ind vs west indies.
What had happened that match,
have your ever tried In crime branch
you should be there"
Not In black court.
What do you know about
that match
so are you sure you were
instructed to not save the match
yes, that day I feel
there's something wrong.
More than criket one more
game was beeing played.
But everybody blaimed on me.
They played badly,
and blaimed on me. x
that we told them to play slowly
turtles makes you win
In stories not In real life.
My 8 yea rs are wasted
In this case.3 years of marriage.
Telling my husband for 2 year
we'll go to honeymoon after the case.
You blaimed..
We've to procve It.
You must have many
friends, I'm not In them
tis ls prooved that whose
brain ls behind this.
But I can't fight this case anymore.
What happened to you,
I can't waste my and court's time
I can't bring sangeeta
In court... why?
Why not, because she's
the cause of your problem
you're out of limits..
I'm not but public saying
everything was good between us.
But If It's cricket or love,
you've bad timing"
50 nothing.
What girls... If you stuck In that
mess, your concentration will be bad.
To not seeing beautifull girl
how much will power ls required
she's looking cracker In
real life..
You don't understand the
diference between real and fake.
Look near her,
she's real heroin"
Don't come inside,
we've not wcren anything.
Why he's not answering.
Look, go from here, If anybody
will see, we'll be In news
I won't go taking ravi
chemistry should be
shown betweeen you both
to seeing some faces,
we shows the anger not love.
L"m not angry on being
out on zero..
You know him
yes my son ls his fan.
He have done p.h.d on girls.
Only because of you
she don't know acting,
only she do make up
the whole world ls my fan,
and I'm yours.
Because of your
bad sight, don't wet your eyes
you gave her your name,
never betray with her.
I came back home..
Noreen was with me
I was restless.
It feeIs that has near
but not with me.
I'm with you
now go to sleep, I'm afraid.
With what?
Dreams.
Why'd I see her eyes.
Do I've come here
to see her eyes.
God plays game, whatever we
wants don't gives us.
And with we go away,
It shows us on every corner.
I just found out...
It's my friends house.
I need to talk to you
tell her..
If you'll not tell her so I'll tell her
since I met you
I see only face..
Only name.
That's wrong.
Go from here.
If I'd be In control,
so I'd never come here.
Who?
Why're you hiding from me.
He's the cricket captain
of Indian team
you both are In lead
stow of my megazine.
Be carefull,
people will talk about It
If pointing someone ls crime,
so half world would In jail
I'm tryinjg to talk to
you for many days".
Did you ever think,
love never gave chance to think
ma ny things will be over,
but I'll have you
In that deal,
your lose ls greater.
Go back to your home.
Why do we not talk much.
I've come after
many days..there must be something
say something with fury
put down your collar.
Have seat son..
Salaam
I need to talk to you"
Not right now.
I'm trying to talk
to you for 4 days.
I'll be back..
There are so ma ny guest
In house, talk to them
I'm not running away.
But I'll go, to join new series.
Are you talking about packing}
You go and relax,
your new series ls important
come here ncreen
I gone out for series
without telling noreen
what I couldn't tell this
to noreen, I tell this to world.
First time I think about myself.
You should've think before
named the match to her..
That my name ls merged
with yours.
You showed this to world"
It'd be late to tell you face to face
It was right time.
I gave her up but
couldn't give up
she's just like my bad habit.
Whatever I did with
noreen, was bad.
Maybe I'm In this condition
changes ls life's reality
I'm not going ct change
my decision... sangeeta will not come
you try to hide her,
but she'll mention her..
If any stranger fell on road,
few people comes to help him
It's been 8 years of this case,
still nobody has come
his own wife..
Neither sangeeta, nor ncreen.
Nor family and fans..
Have anybody come"
He played so much cricket,
but couldn't make friends..
Who can stand near you
what ls the reason of It.
Because everybody believes
that azhar did It.
And azhar ls behind everything.
By ta king this case,
there are many haerings..
8 nov, we'll announce
the result"
Not date.
The accusation were In air
will stick on forehead
why I'm feeling that
you're my fan.
I was..
You'll be again
you can't do match fixing here.
I couldn't understand one thing.
I gave you money
before case starts"
You kept the money,
and against me.
You're saying rubbish,
this kind of anger ls In me..
In the court, the false accusation
are around here..
And true man has to
carefull about head.
This all was missing"
That's my reality
peoples crowd, the noise of my name.
You're experiecing this
after long time.
Whatever I'm because of this fans.
So move your body then.
Lets use autograph
now show some trick shots.
Is that place to do batting.
You're azhar,
you can do batting anywhere.
If you'll not show your
shots, so what's benefit to call you
now show me those good shots
hold the bat"
Answer them by playing
not speaking.
If you speakwith mouth,
I can't do it..
Anybody can give me bat,
I'm player not monkey.
I can't show you tricks.
Today nothing left.
But I'm happy
now I don't care. when we don't
care In life, then change comes.
Let us call that guy,
If you think It's misleading
so you reject the witness.
Mr. reddy you can
call your witness.
Just not have to call,
has to request you
witness name ls
miss meera verma.
Defence lawyer ls witness,
nothing ever happened..
It happened..
It's a canada's reference..
Court job ls to judge"
Dear meera, something ls
troubling me..
Before the procedure, you were
forcing azhar for take oath.
What was the reason
It's procedure so witness
don't lie.
And only true comes out.
If one man has two statments ..
One under oath and second not.
What statement ls believed
to be true...oath.
You're silent"
50 you're agreed.
May I go"
I know you're not habitual
just clear my one point"
I'm not here sitting
to say order order.
I'm noticing statement,
don't remind me.
Who did this ban on my client.
And who took action
the head of cricket association
who gives salawto mr. madhavan panel.
Cricket association
this ls my point"
Association ban It
association decided the panel.
Assocaition gives the
salawto panel.
50 how come this panel
can stay neutral.
Look they're talking
about you on news..
You should see..
We'll tell you what kapil
thinks abut azhar..
What ls the truth In alligation
100% eye seeing things
are not even true.
How can be this heared
things can be real.
In my sight, azhar ls very
good player and captain
as far as I know, he's innocent.
Listen, write down 50
on the lose of lndia..
Indian viewer are happy again.
But dangerman ls still on crease.
This captaincy ls not easy.
Judge has called you
twice, you come fast.
This case wasn't easy
people's anger and media..
Truth ls always on front.
But It takes time to reach there.
Azhar has to play
captain's inning.
Many peoples made mistake,
c.b.l mistake
bookie charge sheet wasn't made.
My grandpa told me
that I'll play 100 matchs.
But you played 99
this court case wasn't
less than a test match.
This was the biggest
test match of my lfie
It's not my mistake,
he took money
and said he will play
according to us.
This ls the stow of my
all innings... believe or not
I leave on you
I fight the case..
Because I know"
Record ls on 100,
nobody claps on 99..