Okay live 3, 2, 1..
Welcome and good evening
to one on one with me Arnab Ghosh.
I like to introduce to the man..
..the myth and the most
wanted outlaw of the world D.
"Everybody is busy battling
and life has been locked."
"Every minute selfie sis
clicked and posted on instagram."
"24 hours on phone
and life is on loan."
"He cannot do anything
and finds faults in others."
"The nation wants to know."
"There is nothing to say
but the nation wants to know."
"Your world has become useless."
"Oh God.."
"Why don't you understand?"
"Your world has become useless.
Oh God.."
"Thousands of scams happen in crores."
"Money is power and will
get anything done from anyone."
"Every hour there is breaking news.
At least million views."
"They unnecessary create
issues and main issue is ignored."
"The nation wants to know."
"There is nothing to say
but the nation wants to know."
'Your world has become useless."
"Your world has become useless."
"Your world has become useless.
Oh God.."
"Your world has become useless."
"Why don't you understand?"
"Your world has become useless.
Oh God.."
So Mr. Vachani you want to say that..
..the core committee
does not take responsibility..
..for spokes person's live comments.
Look I..
- Answer my question, Mr. Vachani.
I am..
- You will have to answer my question.
Answer me first.
Let me also...
- Answer me first, Mr. Vachani.
Let me speak.
- Answer me first.
You will have to answer Mr. Vachani.
I am speaking. Let me speak.
- Answer me.
I am giving.
Answer me.
- I am speaking.
Answer me first, Mr. Vachani.
You have to.
Okay.
Mr Vachani who is promoting
the campaign of save water..
..has wasted one glass of water here.
This means that today without
worrying about anything..
..you are publicly going against
the cause you are supporting.
Why don't you let me speak anything?
- Answer me first.
Shall I say something?
- You have to answer me.
Okay.
You have thrown the political
ideology of your party on my face.
What are you saying?
- You cannot do that.
That means you do not believe in
the political ideology of your party.
I..
- That's what you want to say.
You have insulted and made fun of
the 150 years old party, Mr. Vachani.
There is no joke..
Come on sir let's go. It is
live telecast. Everybody is listening.
Let's go sir.
Hey, he is amazing.
He is talking nonstop like
bullet train without a break.
If you call us in studio..
..then give us chance to speak.
- You answer me.
Let's go sir.
Do you know how much preparation
we do before coming here?
Let's go.
- He does not understand.
It is a limit.
Leave me.
Answer me Mr. Vachani.
He..
- You cannot leave like this.
It is matter of everyday.
Come every day and
get insulted in Prime time.
You..
- What do you have to say my friend?
You tell me.
Understand one thing that..
..even politicians have some dignity.
Understood.
Do answer me Mr. Vachani.
You cannot do that.
Mr. Vachani you have to answer.
Give the phone to Pankaj.
Pankaj, first of all cut the feed now.
And switch it to something else.
Anything.
And secondly remove Arnab
from prime time slot from Monday.
Listen, ask Neha to come to studio.
Everyone go out.
I want to talk to Arnab.
Hey, go out.
What?
Hey..
How did you get wet?
I threw water on myself.
I can give away my life.
- Yes of course.
Listen, Arnab from tomorrow
you will do the 7-8PM slot.
Now will I have to do 7-8 as well?
No, no you will have to do that only.
Only that.
What?
- Yes.
7-8 PM means.
Now will I tell people
how to cook food?
Yes. It is cookery slot so understand
what and how you will do it.
What the hell Roy?
What the hell? You tell me.
Really.
First you were saying that TRP is
not coming and losses are mounting up.
Now TRP is coming
and you have a problem.
Do you increase TRP like this?
Is this the way to increase TRP?
Okay.
Now you remember the
chapters of moral science.
Very nice.
What happened?
Burn it.
- Warning comes downstairs.
Look at Neha's shows, buddy.
Pure fashion reporting
delivered with a pinch of salt.
And ratings are good too.
Nobody is complaining.
Roy, to make shows
on lingerie and sex..
..and to openly challenge
politicians on a live show..
..is two different things.
Oh hello, mind your language.
It is not lingerie show but
India's best glamour update show.
Oh.
I am the best news
writer in the country.
I am doing this show on Roy's request.
Why are you involving
me into this debate?
Take your beauty parlor out.
There is no need to do this here.
I am here because Roy called me.
And I am getting the
prime time slot of your show.
Yeah..
What?
Yes..
Will Neha do prime
time slot on my place?
Have you literally taken
the show by its name? One on one.
If she does the show then
politicians will give fewer answers..
..and will give phone
numbers to her more.
I am leaving Roy.
Let me know when Mr.
Angry pans has cooled down.
I will come later.
- No, no Neha.
You are not going anywhere.
Wait, wait..
This man must know how important
it is to change with time.
Even you know that..
..Neha used to be the best
writer in the news business.
Okay.
She is doing this show
because the channel needs her.
You know flexibility.
Shut up.
Have cup and smell the coffee.
No one wants to see
your show nowadays.
It is okay that ratings
were fine today but at what cost.
Tomorrow RGV will come.
Again I will have to give answer about
6 cameras, 4 mikes and so many bones.
Do you know that?
It is not my fault that you
cannot handle political hooliganism.
My work was to handle heated
debates and that I was doing.
Until you..
Hello. What is it?
I said I will get the watermelon.
Watermelon, watermelon....
Yes baby..
Nothing, nothing..
I have chucked out an office boy
so he is getting angry and shouting.
Yes.
I will get it.
Sure.
Bye sweetheart.
Sorry I did not see.
I was in heated debate so I got..
It was not a heated debate.
It was hardly a debate.
You had said at 10'0clock.
Why is so much shouting
happening outside?
Stop it.
- Stop it, Pankaj.
Don't laugh, Arnab.
A 70 year old man crying on
prime time.. it was not heated debate.
It seemed as if you have snatched
a lollipop from a 6 year old child.
Did you see the way he was crying?
But it was good one, yeah..
Arnab!
You were a good news anchor.
- Thanks.
But this drama cannot
continue every day, buddy.
Even you know it. It is not feasible.
People want to see some real stuff.
Remember those days when
people would leave their dinner..
..and sit in front of the TV.
Which topic would Arnab discuss on?
Who will be court martial?
It's gone buddy.
Look!
I can't sustain like this.
Even the order from top management has
come that we have got 2 months time.
We have to make profit by them.
Otherwise everything finished.
Channel is finished. You are finished.
You are under estimating me, Roy.
Do you remember..
..that I had brought the
channel to the top position?
It was me who had made
the channel the biggest brand.
When a person talks
about past again and again..
..then one should understand
that there is some problem.
And you very well know
it what the problem is.
Do something.
You can do it.
You have done it before as well.
Think huge.
Otherwise many people
are pushing me for 7-8 slot.
So now Arnab Ghosh..
..will have to compete
with chef Kapoor for screen time.
What the hell?
- Neha, please.
Buddy, think of something.
Think of something quickly.
We just have two months time.
- Hey..
Pankaj, will this noise stop or not?
Sir I am vinod.
Vinod, is this a
studio or a fish market?
Come baby.
"Whosoever you bless Haji Ali..."
"He need not worry at all,
Haji Ali, Haji Ali.."
"Whosoever you bless Haji Ali.."
"He need not worry at all,
Haji Ali, Haji Ali.."
"Ali, Ali Haji Ali.."
"Haji Ali.."
"My Haji Ali.."
"The day is not good
so help to let it pass soon."
"Give my life a direction."
"Change my bad luck into good luck."
"Help me to come out of problems."
"Bless me; help me to find my way."
"Ali, Ali Haji Ali.."
What happened? Why have you
made face like a grilled chicken?
Many people make a mistake of removing
the chicken before it is grilled.
Look at this.
It should be of this color.
Till that time let be on grill.
I am being thrashed in
the office and you are joking.
Are you just being
thrashed and not me?
That also from my own child.
It is 4th month. Do you remember?
Sorry.
- Sorry.
Then you must be enjoying?
- What?
I mean.. sorry baby.
After making chicken roast....
I mean..now is turn of spices.
..people are happy when the
child kicks for the first time.
Like that I said. Yes.
You know everything..
..then you do it.
I am sorry.
How are you feeling?
Does someone talk like
this with pregnant woman?
Of course I am feeling awful.
Leave it.
Okay.
Now tell me what has happened?
Or you want me to read your face.
Shall I say the truth?
No, tell me the story of Harry Potter.
Of course, tell me the truth.
I have been removed
from the prime time slot.
What?
- I will do the cookery show. 7-8 PM.
Like this.
Shit.
But what happened suddenly today.
Roy said it point blankly
that we have two months.
If the ratings don't
go up we are doomed.
Channel will shut down.
You will get another assignment. I
mean there is no other Arnab in India.
It is not that easy.
I will not get a second
chance failing at my level.
And even if I get I can't
expect to be paid like before.
It is too much.
I have booked so many
thing online for the baby.
Don't worry.
We will figure something out.
Life is already going on loan.
If we do not do something quickly..
..then we will have
to come from Toyota to Tata.
If you do not have budget for
cashew nuts then there is no problem.
We can use groundnuts
to make this dish cheaper.
There will be a slight
change in taste.
Tell me, what you did the whole day.
Browsing but did not buy anything.
What were you finding?
White Sari.
What?
- What?
Don't be so surprised Arnab.
I will have to buy because
of the way you insult..
..the politicians on live TV.
Sometimes I feel..
..I should have taken the
offer of News India two years back.
They are on top of the charts now.
Relax Arnab.
Whatever happens is for good.
The important thing is that
you cannot control everything.
So just let it be.
It is very easy to talk.
You feel regretted thinking
practically about it.
You know that time I got the offer.
May be.
Listen.
I have to tell you something.
- Tell me.
Tell me.
Do you remember the night I conceived?
You came late from studio that day.
Shekhar had come home before you came.
Shekhar, your ex boyfriend.
Okay.
We just got talking and had some wine.
One thing just led to another and..
I..
You know women get stupid
and emotional sometimes.
What are you going to say?
I..
Speak.
I am not too sure
but I am just confused.
Maybe this baby is yours or his..
I don't know.
Male snake attracts the
female snake with his smell.
After the female snake agrees
they both enjoy sex for many hours.
Are you enjoying?
What do you mean by saying that?
Don't worry. It is yours.
I just wanted to say
that things can go worst.
So you learn to respect
your achievements, husband.
Relax.
I am going to sleep, good night.
Good night.
Okay, okay how old is the story?
Hot tea..
- Okay.
Are you sure it is untapped.
- Hot tea..
Hot tea..
Hot tea sir.
Hot tea sir. - Tell me
something more about the story.
More means more about it.
- Take it sir.
What.
Okay political history.
I'll call you back.
Sit down.
- What happened, sir?
Wasn't morning tea nice?
- Sit down.
Were the tea leaves more?
I had told the people in the
pantry that sir has gastric problem.
Put the tea leaves less.
Sit down.
- Okay sir.
What is this?
- This is tea sir.
It is very nice.
You are bringing tea
in every five minutes.
Give me time to drink tea.
Drink one more sir. It is very nice.
Tea is always hot and
people enjoy it while drinking.
Are you making me drink
tea or watering the plants?
Sir, you are getting angry.
You work so hard.
So you will drink more tea.
Drink it sir.
It is nice.
If you say it once again that it is
nice then I will press my throat or....
Don't get angry sir.
I will bring it later.
Don't bring it later.
Don't bring it.
You are a makeup and not a tea seller.
I don't understand
why are you after tea.
There is a difference between
profession and passion, sir.
You know it well that I love to make
others drink tea from college times.
Why are you spoiling your career?
I don't see a bright future.
You cannot make a career
by making others drink tea.
If you do hard work then one day
you will be in front of the camera.
Your mother wanted to see you on TV.
Yes sir.
She wants it but..
..what does she know about passion.
Sir, you don't seem
to be in god mood sir.
Oh really.
Are you getting angry with
me because of tasteless tea?
God, just kill me.
Today I will finish this debate.
- Okay.
Where is brother?
- He is Ranchi?
Yesterday it came in the news.
Where is your brother, idiot.
That courier man.
Okay, choosy.
I will just call him, sir.
- Call him.
Hello.
Sorry Ajay,
I got caught up with some office work.
Tell me what you were saying.
Okay.
Yes..
Correct, correct..
Okay..
Yes, will see. Sir, Choosy..
Good afternoon sir.
Do you want to courier something?
Okay.
Right.
So send it till tomorrow.
Okay.
Sir, just say yes once.
Once you said yes means
your things have gone, sir.
I will call you in five minutes.
Boss has called me. Okay.
He has called me urgently. Bye.
Sir, did sister-in-law
get the bouquet?
Did you send it?
Listen.
Do whatever you feel is right.
I just have one request to make.
What sir?
You make me drink the
entire year's tea in one day.
After that you will
never make me drink tea.
Okay. And you.
This..
This is your border.
You will courier things of others..
..and you will not courier
anything inside this.
Swear it.
Okay sir.
- Not mine but yours.
- Not of yours but of each other's.
Okay..
- Get lost from here.
Okay sir.
This is your limit.
I had told him..
..to make tea less strong
It is gas so it will
come out from somewhere.
You are right.
Yes Ajay, I was in a meeting.
Yes.
Any updates. Did Roy say anything?
Nothing new.
You tell me how your day was.
Crime Patrol 8 episodes.
Back to back.
Wow! Women crave for sweet
or sour things in pregnancy.
My wife has craving for crime.
Thank you God.
I am blessed.
- You are such a drama.
Such a drama. God.
In one episode there was a guy..
..who was caught stealing
bricks from the construction site.
Can you believe which
gang he belonged to?
No one told me.
D gang.
I mean imagine D gang
has to steal bricks.
What is so weird?
Many people of D gang are struggling.
Brother has escaped
and has left boys behind..
..to steal bricks and steel rods.
Anyways...
I have heard that he
is still active here. I mean..
People say he has
many investments here.
People say many things..
..but for me what matters
is that what you say.
Imagine..
..it would be so
cool to interview him.
I mean one on one
with the man himself.
Sensational.
Are you hypnotizing me?
You have already been hypnotized.
Keep these crime patrol
dangerous ideas with you.
Otherwise you will really
have to wear white sari.
You are such a buzz kill.
It did not go in the mouth.
Once more.
- Take this.
Clean it. I am going to bed.
I'll have two drinks and come.
Imagine it would be
so cool to interview him.
One on one with the man himself.
Sensational.
Parul.
Parul..
Baby..
What is it Arnab so late at night?
You scared me.
I came to compliment you.
For what?
You had give me a useless
idea to interview D.
So will you insult me
by waking me up from sleep?
No, it is not a bad idea at all.
Good for you.
- I am going to pitch it Roy.
All the best.
Are you excited?
Very much.
How did you like this idea?
What?
Is it risky?
Don't worry..
..your birth certificate
will have my name.
You tell me what I shall
get for you from there.
Gun.
They have the real one.
Sleep.
You are very naughty.
Remember that the flame
should not be high..
..otherwise the spoon
and wok both can burn.
Greetings, sir.
Greetings.
Sir, there is no
balance in your phone.
Do you want to get it recharged?
That will be done.
Smiling bright face.
Do you want to set a caller tune?
Black hair and golden color..
How is the weather there?
Shut up, idiot.
Girdhari, come quickly.
Brother is calling you at the pool.
How are you dear?
You do not miss me these days.
Why should I miss you?
I have found someone here.
You uncle..
Okay.
Yes brother.
Go and kill Sheela.
Now. I want to hear
the sound of the bullet.
As you say, brother.
The work will be done.
Okay fine.
Girdhari.
Meet him.
He is the owner of GML group Mr.
Arshad Ansari.
Mr. Ansari.
He is Girdhari and
takes care of my work.
Greetings..
Don't go on his face.
He is innocent to look
at but he is very clever.
So brother, get my work
done about which I had told you.
Yes.
Girdhari.
He says that he had asked..
..to threaten the builder
but we have not called.
Yes.
Tell me from there.
Tell in front of everyone.
I don't like whispering in business.
Why are you shaking the phone?
Tell me what it is.
I did not have balance in the phone.
That is why I wanted
to tell you in your ears.
Are all other phones dead?
Where was Mehmood's phone?
Sir, Mehmood's phone
is not good quality.
There are so many landlines
in the house. What are they for?
Actually brother tele marketing
people have troubled..
..people so much that
they do not pick up landline.
I tried many times.
Mr. Ansari.
You go and your work will be done.
Don't bother about what he is talking.
He has the habit of eating opium.
Okay brother, now that you
are saying then it will be done.
You should have got it recharged.
Bother you do not know.
I have to beg for
100/- to the accountant..
..and he says there is no collection.
- One minute. One minute.
Is this enough for recharge?
Yes it is enough.
Brother.
For 10 days vegetables have
not been bought leave aside mutton.
Sprinkle salt on me and eat.
We are there because of you.
Sir.
Sir, I feel to increase the TRP..
..we will have to do
something path breaking.
Roy, you are going to thank me.
Yes, you were saying something Peter.
Sir. I think we will
have to do something new sir.
You say it every time but what new.
Sir.
You must have read what I had said.
Yes. What I had said?
I want to do something for women.
What is interesting in this?
Who will see?
Listen sir.
we will put an original twist in this.
I am listening.
The headlines of our news
piece would be 'Manch Pe Kiya Bawal'
I want to do women.
It would become a rage, sir.
- Great.
Very nice, very nice..
Later we will put all
the blame on the edit, sir.
Superb.
- We are safe.
There will not be
rage but riot, idiot.
Get out.
Good for nothing.
Sir..
- Out.
Okay.
So..
- Rajat, you were saying something.
Sir, Peter spoke my idea.
This always happens, sir. I
had come here to tell you about this.
Get out.
- Sir..
Sir, my idea.
- Just leave.
Get out.
Go..
Our luck is not bad but
we have kept wrong people.
What is it? It was my idea.
Get lost.
It was my idea. Get lost.
- Rascal.
I will tell everyone
that it was my idea. Rascal...
Thief..
- Go and tell.
I have seen many people like you.
How did you like the idea?
- Rubbish idea.
What do you think, Neha?
Stupid, utter garbage
and I can go on and on..
Look, our luck is not bad.
What does Neha know?
Roy, I think you did
not hear it properly.
I heard it and imagined it in my mind.
At the end of imagination
I saw that we both are dead.
Hence.
Rubbish.
Roy, till today D
has not been interviewed.
This is going to be big.
- Big..
D has not been interviewed because
they are many reasons behind it.
He is dangerous, he is impossible.
This is a life risking idea.
Every big idea seems
to be risky in the beginning.
Don't be poetic.
I asked you to get idea
to save the channel and..
And this is what you come up with.
Tomorrow you would say that
you need Sayyed Hafiz's interview.
Day after tomorrow
you would say that..
..you need interview
of Veerappan's cousin.
Have you gone mad?
Roy, you are saying this? It is
not that no one has done this before.
Going by the history in 1959
the famous British..
..journalist Graham
Smith had done this.
Quite successfully.
Did he interview D?
In 1959 D was in nursery. Why would
anyone interview a nursery child?
He interviewed the famous
mafia king of Italy Fabio Castilana.
The one and only interview with him.
What happened of that
Graham Smith? He died.
Did you see?
He died of heart attack.
Natural death.
What to see in everything?
Whatever it was a bad idea.
Go out and get thinking.
And let me also think.
This plan of mine..
- Even you think it over Roy.
These TRP's and ratings
will be left behind.
This will make us legendary.
There will be no stopping us.
The door is that side. Forgive me.
Roy..Neha you tell him.
- I'll show you.
For the fashion segment..
Our luck is bad.
Will that be okay?
Good afternoon Mr. Chopra.
We are on it.
You don't have to worry sir.
Sir, I know I have said
this many times before..
..but this time I mean it sir.
I used to mean it earlier also
but all these things take time, sir.
I know I have less time sir.
Just 2 months.
Sir we are working on
some new ideas and I am sure..
..ratings will back up in no time.
Trust me sir.
We will turn things around.
Sir, you have already told
about this time of 2 months.
No, no sir I did not mean that.
You can say as many times as you want.
Okay, good day sir.
Yes Roy..
Arnab, go ahead with the interview.
I thought about your idea. Okay
but will what will happen with that.
I have ideas.
I am scared of those.
Listen to me. We will provoke him.
Okay. How?
What is D proud of the most?
Money, power, status and the
fact that people are scared of him.
Correct.
- So..
We will challenge him.
We will challenge everything.
Money, power, status and everything.
What will happen because of that?
That will make him angrier
and that is not good at all.
It will happen. I am telling you.
Just keep watching.
One minute, one minute..
I don't want the channel to
be in any danger, Arnab. Understood.
Wherever there is
Arnab there is danger..
..and wherever there
is danger there is Arnab.
Shut up.
I have this figured out. Come on.
Champion.
Okay.
Rami..
- Yes sir.
I was about to get tea.
Not tea but where is your brother?
He is here, sir. What happened?
Did he again couriered something?
No, no call him here in 2 minutes.
He will not be able
to come in 2 minutes.
Why?
Because he will come in 2 seconds.
He is here. Choosy.
- Greetings sir.
What are you doing here?
Sir, it had gone bad.
- Listen..
Okay.
Neha, where are you?
I need to see you immediately.
Okay, I am coming. Yes.
Parul should not come to
know about this. You know it, right.
That is about later.
First tell me that..
..why should I do it?
There is no scientific reason in it.
Just do it for old times' sake.
For old times' sake?
- Yes.
Last month when I had
asked a favor from you..
..then where had old times' gone.
You have gone mad.
You wanted to have sex with me.
And I am just telling you
to write the script of the interview.
There is a difference.
- What is the difference?
That time I was desperate
and today you are desperate.
By giving this stupid reason do not
prove yourself to be right, please.
And what the hell are you doing?
Okay I will write interview for you.
Thanks.
One minute, one minute..
That one minute has come.
Stop this striptease of yours first.
I have two conditions.
First that you will atke
me with you for the interview.
And you will mention
my name on live TV.
And give me credit for it.
What are you saying?
I am not interviewing a street dog.
Understand the seriousness of the
situation. I am going to interview D.
It is risky.
Okay, then I have other works also.
I'll see you in some time.
Listen, okay.
Good. Now second condition.
Now nothing. Done.
Nothing more.
After the interview
I want you for one night.
Are you crazy?
Just think it over.
This is the biggest
interview of your life.
I am India's biggest news writer.
No, no..
You can think over it and let me know.
Listen. Okay.
Really.
I have already put my life on stake
and now let it be my dignity as well.
I love you..you are my life
I am living because of you.
There is good news.
- Really.
I thought only I was
going to give good news.
I didn't know you also..
What?
Roy has agreed.
I am going to interview D.
What?
- Yes baby.
Oh my God.
That is so cool.
No, no..
Yes baby.
- No..
Yes..
- Go and do your work.
Go and get started.
Come on.
This is my work.
- Come on.
No, this is not your work.
That is your work, go.
Okay let me make a drink then.
- Okay.
I will have to be punished
for falling in love.
Today the weather is very pleasant.
What is this? Does the
vegetable cart look like this?
Fish and lady finger together.
What is this?
Madam, I have a rule and that..
..is I sell only female
things on my cart.
That is why fish with lady finger.
And colocasia with fish
and gourd with colocasia.
Do you want to say something else?
It will help in the
making of the video. Stupid.
What a coincidence madam.
The vegetables of my cart are
green and your dress is also green.
And I have become
excited on seeing you.
Shut up. Shut up.
The shoot has still
not started so be normal.
Uncle, you are getting too excited.
- One minute, one minute..
We are not sitting
in neighboring country.
India should be seen. India..
Is everything ready?
- Yes.
Do it nicely. Give me the mike.
Pull it.
Rolling..3, 2, 1..action.
At this time I am in
the vegetable market f Dongri.
Aslam uncle puts the biggest
cart of vegetables here.
He is with us.
Today he is put up a small cart.
Aslam uncle, shall we start if
the fishes have gained consciousness.
Yes sir.
We have heard that
famous underworld don D..
..used to buy vegetables from here.
Is this true?
But it. That rascal used
to never buy but take them for free.
So you mean to say such a great
underworld don D was a vegetable thief.
Which vegetables he used to steal?
I have a cart of 55 vegetables
but D always used to take spinach.
Oh! You want to say that
he was into green veggies.
No sir, green veggies were into D.
So you can speak Hindi Urdu.
Absolutely.
I mean he had a problem of piles.
You mean to say piles.
By changing words the
problem will not subside.
So by eating spinach piles are cured.
Not by eating sir but by applying.
As you saw Aslam uncle
said that for D it was..
..less of vegetable shop
and more of medical store.
To send your response
tweet
How much over acting do you do?
Let's go.
Sir, do you wish to say something
to Arnab about his media stand.
He definitely ahs some
connection with that D.
It is a game which they
both together are playing with me.
Sir, it is quite daring that
a reporter has openly challenged D.
Do you want to say something about it?
Please stay away. I don't
want to say anything about this.
Sir, Arnab insulted you so much and
still you do not want to say anything.
I said leave my way.
Please give me the answer, sir.
- Nonsense.
You are an inspector so sit straight.
Let me set your moustaches.
Madam..
- What?
I swear upon my mother..
I mean I swear upon my mother that when
you touch my cheeks I seem to melt.
-Shut up.
-Come on let's start.
Are you ready?
Okay let's go.
At this time I am outside Nagpada
police station and we have with us..
..senior constable Dougle.
Come let us talk to him.
Mr. Dougle we have heard
that D has spent many..
..days in this police
station when he was young.
Not when he was young but he used
to come here even in his childhood.
Sometimes he used
to puncture the cycle..
..or sometimes break
the lock of the neighbors.
I swear he was a very
different kind of a person.
So you mean to say that D
has spent a lot of time in this jail.
Not only in jail but he has spent..
..a lot of time in
the 4*4 room next to that.
What happens there?
We try to improve new and
spoilt brats there with love.
Okay, so that means you
have thrashed D many times.
One time I let him go.
I thrashed him badly.
- Okay.
One day his father
brought him here to me.
Okay. Tell us more.
Rest all is fine. Wife is unwell.
Younger has failed in 10th std.
Rest all is well.
Tell about that girl. Stop overacting.
Yes..
- Yes tell..
I remember he was brought
here once for teasing a girl.
So D had teased a girl.
He did not tease but tried to.
The girl also thrashed him
and brought her to police station.
That day I felt pity on him.
I did not feel like thrashing him.
So you did not thrash D.
No sir. That day I came
here after fighting with wife.
Yes.
Does anyone put garlic in
potato and cauliflower vegetable?
Does anyone put?
No. My mood was very bad.
I slapped..
Your wife.
I dare not slap my wife.
But I slapped D.
Okay.
- Yes..
That day I really felt
like thrashing him hard.
I missed one and
hit him under the eye.
Oh.
He wears the glasses to
hide the mark given by my hand.
Many people do not know about it.
You just heard what Dougle said.
The mark of what he gave
D under the eye still remains.
The question is that mark still there.
Tweet your response
at
Brother..
- Yes, tell me.
How shall I speak? I am feeling shy.
What is the matter?
Have you got vasectomy done?
No, no what are you
talking brother. Oh no..
Oh God....
A chaos about you
is there on social media.
About what?
The video about you.
There is a vegetable seller
who says that you stole his vegetable.
There is a policeman who says that..
Don't be poetic. Tell me clearly.
Policeman is saying that
he had thrashed you hard.
That constable is saying so.
Show me the video.
No, no..
Show it to me.
- No..
What is this?
This seems to be ammunition shop.
This is new one.
Even I had not seen this.
At this moment I am with Mr.
Zuber proprietor of Zuber arms.
Mr. Zuber I am with you.
Tell me.
Did D buy the gun for
the first time from you?
Yes sir, we needed
gun oil to repair the guns.
The picture as well as sound is good.
- he used to supply.
What?
He used to supply.
He used to supply. So how long did
this association with him continued?
It could not continue for long
but the matter is that he used to..
..steal oil from Mahalaxmi
godown and sell us at cheaper rate.
This must have continued
for 2-3 months..
..and then what could have happened.
Mr. Dougle came and arrested him.
Okay.
He thrashed him so hard that after..
..that he was hardly
seen once or twice around.
What did you talk with him
whenever you saw him once or twice?
Just tell me that does
a man speak who is injured?
He wanted to speak a lot but
could not speak with swollen lips.
Did he speak?
No, he could not speak.
- Okay.
All he could say was that he
will not be able to do this business.
Okay.
When did he but the
first gun from you?
1989. he came here with two friends.
He came here to buy three
hand guns and two pistols.
What would have been the
cost of 3 hand guns and 2 pistols?
There was no sale.
There is a ground behind
our godown where guns are tested.
I took him there to get the test done.
Believe it or not but it seemed
as if he knew nothing about it.
He did not know
anything about the gun.
Even then he was adamant to shoot.
I asked him to shoot
as even I had to make sale.
Then he picked up the
gun and started shooting..
Yes..
..and because of the weight
of the gun the wrist got twisted.
And did not hit the aim.
- The aim had to miss.
Absolutely right, sir.
But he aimed at the
ceiling of nearby shop.
The ceiling fell
and three workers died.
Against his will D
committed his first murder.
Okay then what happened?
Then I asked him to
leave before any more died.
Then Mr. Dougle came and took him.
Then..
In this way D committed
his first murder.
To give your response tweet..
..
Who is he?
Find out Girdhari.
- Okay.
I will not spare him.
Be careful brother.
Your BP will shoot.
Find out. Find out..
Okay.
Brother that..
What?
There are two more videos.
Why are you laughing?
Because you were laughing brother.
Hello..
- Hello.
Before doing the daring you
should have thought about the dangers.
Who is speaking?
Since three days you
have created a chaos on..
..twitter and you do
not know who I am speaking.
D.
Will D personally call you?
So who is speaking?
It is not important who I am speaking.
It is important that
you stop your drama.
Otherwise we will not
take much time to finish you.
This drama will not stop.
India is a free country
and we have the..
..right to speak and
show anything we wish to.
Hey, free country.
Keep a finger on the globe.
Every country is there
but none is free for us.
Whatever you are showing
is false so stop it.
What is wrong in that?
If you believe vegetable seller
and constable then everything is true.
Understand that you
and your actors will die.
You do not understand.
This drama will not end.
Kill me if you wish to.
What will you achieve by killing me.
Look, if one incident happens on social
media then its impact is for long.
Your brother is going
to be insulted for sure.
Yes, there is one option.
Quiet. Are you playing KBC with me?
Ask brother to give
me personal interview.
Whatever he wishes to
justify say in that interview.
I take the responsibility
of telecasting that interview.
Okay..
Hey you rascal..
Don't curse me but do me this favor.
Now call me next time only when
brother agrees for interview. Okay.
Hey hello..
So he has created all
this chaos for the interview.
Yes brother.
Say yes.
What are you saying?
Say yes to him.
How?
It is an opportunity Girdhari.
Enough of playing jokes.
Those who were scared till
yesterday are laughing today.
Everyone should know
that D means fear.
That means D you will
give interview and come on TV.
Bringing him here
would create trouble.
There is a security risk.
There is no security risk Girdhari.
He has just to be brought here.
What do you mean?
I mean you say yes
to him for the interview..
..and I will kill him live on TV.
Hello..
Tomorrow afternoon
3:30 at Bhendi Bazaar.
Come alone.
Who is speaking?
If you need interview
then reach there.
Tindi Bazaar..
- Bhendi Bazaar..
Aloo Bazaar..
Bhendi Bazaar. Can't you hear?
Okay, Bhendi Bazaar.
But where in Bhendi Bazaar?
Ask for 100gms cardamom
at Simar general store.
200gms.
100gms cardamom.
- Okay.
Bhendi Bazaar. Right.
Yes, Bhendi Bazaar.
- Okay.
Roy, my boy we are in cardamom!
I mean we are in business.
Yes.
I hope you had no problem
in understanding the route. - No..
Look at this cardamom.
I had called for it.
It was finished at home.
It will be of use
to make rice pudding.
You just have to take 4 people there.
Tell me before hand.
Take this.
- What is this?
These are your tickets. Do
not open them before reaching there.
You must have understood
that Haftaa brother has sent this.
But how will we go?
There is a Bahid village
near Bikaner in Rajasthan.
Reach there at 4 in the afternoon
there day after tomorrow.
Near kali Mata Chowk
you will find a tea stall.
Order for Udta Chicken
and Bullet Chaat.
Brother, give me 4 Udta Chicken chaat.
Coffee With D
If you want to live
then drink coffee with D
Brother we got message
of Hafta brother.
The boys are right.
Won't you blindfold us
so that we cannot see the way?
There is no problem if you see..
..because you will not
be able to see while returning.
Why?
Because while returning
you will be in chicken bag.
Coffee With D.
Okay, who is Arnab?
Okay, okay.
Hey, what are you selling nowadays,
vegetable seller?
I don't have a shop.
I am a makeup man sir.
Okay, keep quiet vegetable seller.
Hey madam, no photo.
- Why?
Keep your mobile inside.
No photo.
- Sorry.
You seemed to be very brave
on the phone the other day.
I felt as if you would
kill me there and then.
Today you seemed to be tensed.
I had to reach you otherwise I
am worth nothing in front of you all.
What do you mean?
I mean will D sir
meet us now or later?
He will meet you later.
Is she your wife?
- No.
Is she your sister?
I am Girdhari.
Either shake hands or give me the bag.
Hello.
Come..
Come on tell.
I swear I did not shoot.
I do not know anything.
I am saying truth.
- Egg and bread.
I don't want.
Come on I am too angry now. Come on..
Hey, make the video.
- Yes..
Come on make the video quickly.
- Making..
Straighten your hand.
- It is straight.
Come on quickly.
- Keep the focus here.
Yes keep the focus there.
- Sorry madam..
Hey Bhansali, will you
make a three and half hour movie?
Make a small love story.
Done..
- Done..
Come on now..
Come on move...
Not that side but come this side.
Ask her to pick up.
Come on get inside.
- Come on.
Come on.
- be careful of knife.
Hello.
You should have been
director in CBI Mr. Roy.
Who is this?
I am director of CBI speaking fool.
Is there some legal matter that
you have sent your people to Pakistan?
Sorry sir. I made a mistake.
I was about to call
you and then I realized..
..that you will talk that nonsense.
Get the phone of D tapped.
Or send some of his internal photos.
Or give him posion.
My boy would have got
distracted from his work, sir.
You do not know what
foolishness have you done.
Sir if we do the work that you cannot
do then it is called foolishness.
This is wrong, sir.
You idiot.
Do you know what you have done?
Because of this..
- I am sorry sir.
I will have to keep the phone.
There is lots of work here.
Sir we will talk
at ease some other time.
Why don't you do one thing?
Come to our studio.
We will take your interview as well.
- What..
Okay sir.
- Idiot.
I know that you are scared.
Anyways there is nothing
to be scared of as..
I do not unnecessarily
raise hand on someone.
Hey, can't you see it is a carpet.
How dare you bring dirty shoes inside?
Hey, I think you do
not know whose men are we.
Idiot, you are the men of that person
who sells cardamom in Bhendi bazaar.
And my husband has personally gone
to meet the person for whom he works.
Now you see what is your standing?
Keep the shoes away and sit down.
- Okay.
I am saying that..
First remove your shoes.
- Remove them, remove them..
Okay, okay..
Hey beautiful,
you are taking us too lightly.
Do you know what is this?
- It is a shoe.
Brother, gun.
Since long we were playing with knife.
Keep it straight.
- Do you know this is real gun?
Keep it on the side
otherwise you may shoot.
Why?
If you shoot then
this bulb will burst.
And if I shoot then God forbid even
I don't know what will happen of you.
I think I will have to
take permission to kill you.
Is it correct?
- It is correct.
Hello.
- Tell me.
What kind of female is she?
She is saying that she
will kill me with my gun.
Make her understand who I am?
Who I am?
Tell me who I am?
Don't mess up. You just have
to keep a watch and nothing else.
Okay, good that we talked to you.
Otherwise you know that
if would have got angry..
..this woman must have died by now.
Surely.
- Ameen.
Forget it. You cannot kill a
mosquito and you are talking so great.
Just keep a watch quietly
and for god sake..
..don't get insulted anymore.
- He is praising me.
Keep quiet.
Brother, listen to me.
- I don't want to hear anything.
Hey Afshaab.
-Yes.
Make them understand.
They are creating too much problem.
They do not know basic hygiene.
He came with dirty
shoes on the carpet.
And the other one has
spread the smell of tobacco..
..which he is chewing continuously.
He eats a lot of tobacco.
So make him understand.
Is this the way to behave
in the house of sophisticated people?
One thing more. Tell then
not do any drama in front of me.
I know they have just
come to keep a watch.
They have no orders to do anything
nor do they have that status.
Everyone knows Crime
Patrol Episode 591 Season 2
Watch it on you tube.
I shall keep the phone.
Take it.
She sees crime patrol.
- okay, come on.
I beg of you. Please..
It is matter of my dignity.
Please get scared a bit.
Let me make a video, please.
What is there?
Shall I say something?
Is it done?
Video..
Okay do.
Get scared a bit.
Arnab I am feeling very scared.
Arnab, they have kidnapped me.
Please save me Arnab.
Please I am very scared.
Arnab, they are holding my hand.
Please save me.
Leave me.
Enough.
- Get lost. Enough of it.
Brother has made a nice house.
The place where you are standing..
Is there a bomb there?
- No, no..
Those are Italian tiles. Imported.
Is it good?
- Nice.
Can you see that?
Brother cut the hand
of the person who made it.
Why?
A masterpiece remains a
masterpiece only when one is made.
Like Shah Jahan.
- Yes.
Till when will sir do interview?
Interview?
Eat something and then
we will do interview.
What will you have vegetarian
or non vegetarian food.
Nothing..
Eat something.
We had chicken on the way.
Okay.
We have a tradition that
before killing the goat we feed him.
Food.
How did you like the house?
- Nice.
Is it nice?
The house in which you live
in Mumbai is rented or your own.
It is on EMI
That house is also nice.
Curtains are also nice.
Sister-in-law is also beautiful.
You are very fond of making
comedy videos and showing them.
Watch a thriller now.
- Arnab, he is holding my hand.
Please save me..
Don't do this. What are you doing?
Leave me.
Nothing will happen. Don't worry
nothing will happen to sister-in-law.
This is just a teaser.
This is for the simple
reason that you do not..
..misbehave while taking
interview with brother.
Otherwise we will get sequel 1,
2, 3 of it.
Nothing will happen to her.
This is just for reference.
Where is he?
Rumy. There he is.
Okay..
- Where is..
Bathroom. This side.
Come, will you have tea?
Yes, I am very fond of tea.
Make me drink nice tea.
- Tanveer, get tasty tea.
And how am I looking?
You are looking very nice.
Do little bit of what you do.
- Makeup.
Yes.
So will you also go
on air for the interview?
On air.
That means brother
will go on air as well.
No, through satellite direct on TV.
Yes, yes I will come.
Call that cameraman.
Choosy, come here.
Yes tell me.
- Come here.
Am I looking okay?
- Nice, absolutely nice.
Come this side.
I am cracking jokes
so shoot that in camera.
Record.
- Yes.
Shall I speak?
Yes speak.
There was a man..
..who was taking his
newlywed wife on a horse cart.
Okay.
- Yes.
A stone came under
the foot of the horse..
..and he shook with jerk.
The wife also got jerk.
The man said one.
- Yes.
After some time the
horse again got a jerk.
The wife shook and the man said two.
- Two.
They went a little ahead.
The same stone and jerk.
The man took out the
gun and shot at the horse.
The wife shouted that
how merciless you are.
Does anyone kill an
innocent animal in this way?
The man said one.
How was it?
Nice, nice..
- Then laugh.
Nice..
- Now show how it has come.
Look brother.
It has come nice.
Nice. Now do that to it.
Delete..
- No..
Photohop..
Upload.
What do you do as you
did of brother's video?
Okay, upload it on facebook.
- Yes.
Yes, do that.
- Okay upload it on facebook.
Make an infection of it.
It is not a viral or mosquito
that I make infection of it.
How did you spread
the video of brother?
Okay Viral..
Yes, that.. now make it viral..
Yes..
- Okay we will do it.
Neha.
I just cracked a joke so listen to it.
Thanks but no thanks.
It is nice and you will enjoy it.
No, I don't listen much to jokes.
Then shall I narrate
something serious?
I am okay. Thanks.
I swear it is very hot.
What?
Tea.
Isn't it?
Yes it is hot.
Please have tea.
- No, I am okay.
Really, thank you.
Come on Rumy, going to be on air.
Come on.
I am giving you with love.
Okay please...
Please take it.
No thanks.
- Come on.
"Tell me what should I do?"
"At the back is fear and
death is standing in front."
"Tell me what should I do?"
"At the back is fear and
death is standing in front."
Hey Sarwa, just because
of an interview with hooligan..
..the entire society
has become chaotic.
Sarwa, he is sitting in Karachi..
..and here in Mumbai because
of his name he has created confusion.
Look, how people are running.
Hey, don't call him a hooligan.
Call him Don.
"If you have the courage
to live then drink Coffee With D."
"Coffee With D."
- You are getting nervous..
..and you are making me nervous too.
- Just finish this.
Okay, okay..
Okay.
- Yeah.
Okay, let us start.
- Okay.
Yeah.
Ready 3, 2..
One minute..
Mr. Girdhari, ask brother to
change the shirt. What is he wearing?
It will create so
much jitter on camera.
What? Who will kill?
No, no one minute..
Will you kill brother?
- No, no..
He said jitter.
It is hot outside so
he is becoming irritable.
Has glitter come to kill him?
Shirt is absolutely fine.
- Okay.
Please sit down.
Quiet.
- What sir?
Okay.
Alright going live. 3. 2, 1..
Welcome and good evening
to One On One with me Arnab Ghosh.
Today's interview is
special for two reasons.
One, the person whom I am
going to interview is camera shy.
He has not given interview
to anyone despite the fact..
..that he has done such
works that the world's police..
I mean media wants to interview him.
Secondly it is my birthday..
..so it might be the
last interview of my life.
Jokes apart.
I like to introduce you to the man..
..the myth and the most
wanted outlaw of the world D.
So I am giving you interview at last.
At least one of your ill
feelings are taken care of.
Today you are not giving
interview but I am taking it.
Come on let's start again.
Greetings Mr. D.
Greetings.
Brother..
- Where, where..
On TV.
Brother, brother.. worry not.
I will not spare her. Hey.
Brother.
Doesn't your channel have
any news to show other than me?
We have. But you do such big things.
You must have seen those videos.
- I have seen..
..and recognize some of the actors.
What are you saying Mr. D? Those
are the real videos of real people.
Don't call me Mr. but brother.
It brings us closer.
By addressing me Mr.
I get the feel of enmity.
Anyway your stories are
like drugs to the Indians.
We can't help it.
So you mean I should give drug as
well as entertainment brother Arnab.
Call me Mr. Arnab.
By calling me brother
I get the feel of hooligan.
And it is not entertainment.
It is called news.
Okay.
Brother Girdhari.
Girdhari, did I hear it correctly?
Yes, Girdhari.
Lovingly I call him Girdhari
Secular and he is my main associate.
In your language he is CEO,
my main man.
And she is my main lady.
But Girdhari..
I am surprised that your CEO is a..
Don't go to that side..
..otherwise the interview
will become like that..
What do you mean? How will it be?
Like a nonsense political rally.
As you wish otherwise honestly
I am interested in going there.
Girdhari...
- Yes, brother.
What news did last week come
about me on their news channel?
Breaking news.
Brother they had said that for..
..you have come to Bangkok because
Pakistan does not have this facility.
Yes.
Yes. Now tell me brother
Arnab is this right?
For last three months I
have not moved from this place.
There is nothing great in this.
That day Pakistan
bashing was necessary.
Population control guys
wanted to run a story for them.
And more rumors of you being
in Pakistan or not continue.
Yes so. I did not understand anything.
We had fewer slots.
So chief editor covered
three stories in single news.
You must have heard the headlines.
No facility in Pakistan..D
had to go to Bangkok.
What's wrong with that?
You should have called
the chief editor as well.
Brother, may I ask you a question?
- Yes.
I hope you will let
me go alive from here.
Do you have any doubt?
I am sure that you will
not do anything like that.
What will I not do?
Cheap hooligan acts.
Brother, firstly I would
like to ask you that..
..how did you become
such a big gangster?
You have said it once
so dare not say it again.
I am not gangster..
..but a Don.
What did you understand?
- Okay, what is the difference?
Have you ever seen shootout on roads?
Not really but have heard from police.
Those involved in
shootout are gangsters.
And don?
Have you ever heard about the
mastermind behind these shootouts?
Not really. Have heard rumors.
So Don is the mastermind
about whom you have heard rumors.
So basically how did you become Don?
Any problem sir.
- No problem.
Actually I had a desire
of doing business from childhood.
But business can be of any kind.
Construction, production,
transportation, real estate etc.
So what do you think all
these are not my businesses?
Let's not get involved in what I feel.
Otherwise this interview
will have pre mature climax.
Where did you begin from?
Actually I was multi
talented from childhood.
What is the called? All rounder.
But my father had problem with this.
So you mean to say that
the reason you became a Don..
..are the unresolved father issues.
What?
Only one person is responsible..
..for me to become Don and that is I.
What did you understand?
- You are right.
What a stupid question on my part?
Which father would want his
son to become a Don after growing up?
Even you are right?
Which channel would want
his best reporter to die untimely?
Let's come to your question?
Actually I loved
cricket from childhood.
I was short height with
heavy body so could not play.
But my instincts were very strong.
In your language 'Mann Ki Baat'
So from childhood you got
involved in match fixing and betting.
I said four it was four.
I said six it was a six.
I said out it was out.
So basically you want to say
that your gut feeling was very strong.
Yes, in the beginning.
Afterwards there
was no need of gut feel.
Sorry, I did not understand.
Ask something else.
Ask something interesting.
So you are saying that you
have nothing to do with match fixing.
The entire world knows this D.
you cannot deny this.
Your photographs
are seen in the stadium.
How can you say this?
Photo.
- Yes.
Photographs are seen
of film stars on grant road..
..so that means all
of them are prostitutes.
Photo of politicians is also
there in from Amar Jawan Jyoti..
..so all of them are patriots.
What are you talking, brother Arnab?
So where did all rumors come from?
Actually I had friendship
with few players.
Some had difficulty in
affording two girlfriends.
Some had to repay education loan.
I use to help them.
Oh I see and in return.
In return they used to help me.
What else?
Now..
If every batsman will
make 100 in every match then..
..how will rest of
the talent get a chance?
Growth should be inclusive.
That means whatever
we saw on TV screens..
..was actually remote
controlled by you.
Hey, you are unnecessarily
exaggerating things.
So many times..
..I have told the players
to make 100 in a match.
For which country?
- My country.
What do you mean by my country?
- My country means my country.
That's all very fine
but why don't you take a name?
What is there in a name,
brother Arnab?
A country is not made
by name but with people.
What did you understand?
- Okay.
So you were talking
about your talents.
Yes.
Other than cricket
I loved movies also.
But I had two weaknesses
with regard to movies.
One I cannot wait till the
movie is released in cinema halls.
Secondly..
..I cannot enjoy movie alone.
If the movie is nice it
should reach everyone. Isn't it?
Okay, so that is
why you started piracy.
Piracy?
What does that mean, Girdhari?
I used to travel the world.
Wherever I saw a nice movie
I used to make one copy of it.
Did you understand? - So
this according to you is not piracy.
Not forcefully, Arnab but with love.
Sometimes France and sometimes Cannes.
France and Cannes are the same Mr. D.
You understood it so
why are you going in detail.
So basically you picked
up a print from festivals.
Picked up?
Men are kidnapped.
Have you ever heard
that the film was kidnapped?
No, Have you heard?
A question to your passion for movies.
Do you invest in Bollywood?
- No.
A lot of people believe that you do.
And you have a huge
piracy racket that causes..
..losses worth crores
to film industry every year.
Which losses?
First tell me where is my money?
Which money of yours?
The money that I should get
on every film that is based on me.
Should I get it or not?
Intellectual property.
I am sure everyone wants
to know what your real business is.
Smuggling,
extortion, horse racing or what..
Nothing out of this.
Basically you are unemployed.
Shall I ask you
something brother Arnab?
Begal family in America,
Gonzalis family in South America..
..and there are so
many names in Italy.
You will keep counting till evening.
All these people work
according to their wish.
Why do you have..
..special interest in me?
What special have they done
that no one says anything to them.
Mr. D you are evading my question.
Are you saying that
you don't do smuggling?
Hey buddy, I am service provider.
Service provider.
Transport service,
courier service, mobile service..
From mobile service
I remember one thing.
Tell me one thing if a person
calls from an airtel number..
..and do kidnapping then
what is the fault of airtel.
You said courier service. So
that means are you dominoes of drugs.
Your question has two words
which I did not understand.
Okay.
If you are a service provider..
..then why don't you openly
do business just like others?
I work openly.
You tell me how much material
you want me to send to your house.
I never meant that.
Leave it.
What about extortion?
I swear upon God..
..till today I have not
got anyone's child aborted.
Mr. D I am not talking
about abortion but of extortion.
Okay, what is the meaning of this?
I do not know its meaning.
Actor..he understands
intellectual property..
..but does not understand extortion.
Extortion means to obtain
money through force or threat.
Amazing.
Why do people come to
the point of force and threat?
What is my fault in this?
So you do agree that
you extract money from people.
If I provide service then
will surely give the bill.
Do you take salary from
the channel to do this show?
Okay Mr. D I think you are
not in mood to give direct answers.
Let's shift to some lighter questions.
You have already shifted
from brother to Mr. D
Even you have shifted from Mr.
Arnab to brother Arnab.
Who is your favorite actor?
Bruce Wills and Sylvester Stallone.
So you see Hollywood as well.
I see only Hollywood.
That is strange but why not Bollywood.
I don't like movies from South and..
..you do not make
anything else except that.
Who is your favorite heroine?
No one is nice in your country.
Some have fake lips,
some do not know Hindi..
..and if you see someone
without make up..
..then you would get paralysis attack.
Where do you get all these from?
Okay, so who do you like?
Nazreena..
- But she is from Bollywood.
She is in Bollywood now. Her
actual work started in New York's bar.
Mr. D this is a family show..
..so it would be better if
you keep your responses censored.
If you were to do family show
then why are you interviewing me?
You should have done of
Sooraj Barjatya or Raju Hirani.
Believe me I tried for that
but they are busier than you nowadays.
Shall I arrange by calling them now?
Anyway, other than
Hollywood what do you like?
Other than Hollywood
I like to see porn.
There is no story in this as well
in that but action is surely there.
But nowadays many such movies
are being made in Bollywood..
..where there is so much action.
For example Jism 2, Ragini MMS 2
Extreme action.
So you had to get a porn star.
Okay, With that we take a short break.
Stay with us we will just be back.
Special LIV-IN condoms. Made from
Nigeria's special 4N TCM polyster.
You need not remove it.
You never know when
you would get a chance.
It adjusts according to your size.
So that at the time
of need you are ready.
LIV-In condoms. Keep wearing it.
Don't remove it.
Welcome back. I am still with D.
A man who is not
ready to give answer..
..but we are trying
to find answers from him.
Sir, tell me something about
your journey from Mumbai to here.
Not Mumbai.
Okay, sure.
That reminds me.
I received a call yesterday that..
..there is no water in
my area for last three days.
You cannot do such a small work.
Mr. D let me remind you
that I am not in municipality.
Not that I have remembered
then let me get it done.
Call up Gaitonde.
I will just show you
what municipality is.
Hello..
- Gaitonde...
Greetings, brother.
How are you?
- Absolutely fine.
Greetings.
All that is fine. Listen to me.
There is no water
in Dongri for three days.
Send tanker there quickly
and I will not call again.
Yes brother Arnab, tell me.
Mr. D you have still
not answered my question.
Tell me about your
journey from...to here.
Look Dongri brought me up,
waiting room helped me to grow
Wadala and Manish Market made me Don.
Your government made me fugitive.
That is all about my journey.
And how did you reach this place?
Here I have come with my wish.
Ask why?
Why?
I Karachi I feel the fragrance of....
Okay now that e are
talking of fragrance then..
..do you want to say
something about 93 blasts.
Don't go there otherwise
interview will become like that.
Mr. D it is my job to go there.
I am also a service provider like you.
I deliver truth.
Then go and find truth somewhere else.
There is no truth about this here.
So you do not want to say anything.
How did the battery
of the remote decreased?
Brother Arnab,
in childhood my mother had explained..
..that if someone has
made up his mind then..
..don't waste time
to make him understand.
Okay so if you won't
tell then let me ask.
Were you involved in 93 blasts?
- No.
Not a plain no.
I was not involved so
you want me to give a speech..
..of three and a half minutes on it.
What rubbish is this?
It is very clear from the evidences
that you had supplied bombs.
Yes I did.
When did I say that I didn't?
But you just said that
you were not involved.
Brother..
I supply the bombs
and crackers that burst.
I have a fireworks factory in....
So you are actually saying that
you own a fireworks factory in India.
Yes.
If you don't mind can you
tell me the name of that company?
You are again getting into details.
What did you say that
is was what of drugs?
Dominoes....
- Dominoes.
So understand that I am
big bazaar of bombs as well.
Let us talk about your
occupational hazards.
I mean let's talk about the problems
you face in running your business.
You must be facing problems
in running the business of bombs.
Yes, from problem I remember.
Yesterday Al-Qaida people
called and said that..
..they had sent a suicide
bomb girl in Delhi.
She was passing through petrol pump..
..and four boys noticed
and thought she was their right.
And did....
Has it been declared
as official sport in Delhi?
Can you elaborate that
suicide bomber matter?
Don't deviate from the issue.
The point is that in your country
a kind girl cannot work peacefully.
I agree....
But that so called innocent girl
had not gone there to do candle march.
Leave it. Let's just move on.
What other problems do you have?
- Attrition.
Great. He did not
understand unresolved..
..father issues but
knows of attrition.
Did you say anything?
- No nothing.
You carry on.
In last two months two hundred
people have stopped working for me.
Amazing. I had heard no
one can leave the job of Don.
You heard it right but your Baba..
..he keeps doing this.
I had sent to threaten him.
Three days they stayed in his camp and
said that they don't want to return.
Seeing them some people
left from there as well.
What SMS had come, Girdhari?
Show them.
Brother, we will not be able to do it.
Such SMS are coming.
What should we do?
Absolutely bomb.
Where?
Brother, what is her name?
Absolutely Bomb.
Where have you got lost?
Ask further, reporter.
Not reporter but senior editor.
What is the difference between both?
The same that is there
between gangster and Don.
On this note let's take a short break.
I am still sitting with
the most wanted man on the planet.
And believe me things are going to get
lot more interesting. Don't go away.
Bring water for brother.
I will just check it.
I was saying....
- Water...
I was giving it to her.
So, I was saying...
Strange man you are.
Okay drink.
Thank you.
What happened?
These rich people are so stingy.
After begging for two hours we
got this and that also without sugar.
What are you talking?
Is there no sugar in this?
What should we do now?
I have an idea.
- What?
Wait, let me think.
Idea and that also you have to think.
Bomb, bond....
Brother, let me tell you one thing.
Since long this idea
was coming to my mind.
But just could not speak.
It is the effect of the company.
What has she given?
After Duryodhan only
you have dared to insult.
What do you mean?
It means to insult someone physically.
Is there any other
way to make someone naked?
Yes brother.
Which one?
Emotionally.
Hi.
Greetings.
- Greetings.
You seem to belong to this place.
What do you mean?
I was born in Faislabad.
Okay. Don't you feel
guilty in working with D?
I mean in whatever you are
saying is not with conviction.
What is that?
You are not saying with true
heart whatever you want to say.
I am unmarried so do
not know the matter of heart.
If I was Gafur instead of Girdhari
then would you ask this question?
About guilt.
Do you want number?
No, there is a call for me.
Excuse me.
Yes sir.
Come on Arnab,
he is killing you out there.
Have you gone there to
ask questions or give answers?
Just kick him in the guts man.
Do you know what the
reaction of the public is?
You are trending globally
with a hash tag national hero.
Do you know what that means?
He is smarter than
what we had thought of.
But don't worry it
is just the interval.
I will take care. Okay.
I think we are missing
an opportunity here.
We are interviewing the
biggest interview of the century.
Do you understand? This is Arnab v/s D
Alright then 3, 2, 1 going live.
Welcome back to the most
exciting part of the interview.
The rapid fire.
Yes, this is my favorite.
- Not this one sir.
Okay, the one in which you
ask questions one after the other.
And the one who gives answers
just say anything in haste.
Is it that?
- Yes exactly.
So shall we move ahead?
You go ahead. I will speak from here.
In this round I will ask
you five questions in 1 minute.
You have to answer them quickly.
1st question.
If you are left alone
on an island for one week..
..then whom would you
like to take with you?
Anyone would do.
What do you mean that anyone would do?
Because whosoever will come with me
but only I will be alive after one week.
If you get a chance
to meet American president..
..Pakistan PM and Indian
PM then who would you like to meet.
I do not like the Indian one.
US one is scared of me.
And as far as Pakistan PM is concerned
then he is almost here all the time.
Wait for 10 minutes and
I shall make you meet him.
Virat or Shahid?
- Whoever takes the money?
AK 47 or AK 56
Brain...most dangerous.
Nazreena or Geetika.
Both....
Not both but you have to choose one.
Both have come here.
Okay.
If there is biopic on D then
whom would you want to play your role?
Shashi Kapoor.
Mr. Shashi Kapoor. Why?
Even I have bungalow,
car and money but..
..mother is still with him till today.
Okay.
Black money or white money?
I am not racist like you.
Black and white is same for me.
Okay favorite song?
"The heart still finds
those free days and nights...."
"We kept on sitting..."
You want me to dance now.....
Ask further.
I thought audience would
like to hear you singing.
Anyone can sing.
Nowadays even cricketers are singing.
If you would like to change one thing
in your life then what would it be.
Instead of Dongri I would
like to be born in Colaba.
After that life would
automatically change.
I have to say that you
have answered well and frank.
Leave all this, where is the hamper?
Which hamper?
The hamper that you
give after the rapid fire.
I did not talk about that.
That is not my problem
if you did not talk.
A hamper is always
given after rapid fire.
Everyone knows it.
Do you know or not?
Where is it?
Sir, we will get it delivered
to you once we reach India.
Hurry up and ask further.
It is time for my prayers.
So Mr. D this is our
live audience segment.
In Mumbai studio a panel
of three people is sitting.
They will directly
ask questions from you.
First of all Rohit Shukla from JNU.
Rohit, ask your question please.
Mr. D your responses till now show..
..that you do not
have illegal business..
..and till now you have
never gone against law.
Practically very hard to believe.
Hey, when did I say this sir?
No Mr D we can have
a re learn of the interview.
We are asking you something
and you are answering differently.
Instead of you if I play interview of
Chhota Bheem it would look the same.
Really..
- Yes..
Come on....
I have broken countless laws.
Now we are talking.
Tell us more please.
From last 3 years I
have not paid service tax.
So you mean you have not
broken bigger law than this.
Brother, you had said that
it is a family show so be censored.
Our next question is from Mr.
Vijay Chakraborty..
..who is our special guest tonight
from external affairs ministry.
Can you tell us Mr. D that which
country's citizenship do you have?
Don't censor this.
I will take care of it.
Take this.
This is the proof of my citizenship.
Whatever you feel is
more controversial keep it.
What the hell? What is this?
These are passport of 192 countries.
You want to say that you
are citizen of the entire world.
No, 4 still remain.
Girdhari, what happened
about those 4 countries?
Brother, we have applied
for it so it will come in 4 days.
He must have made it in tatkaal.
He is the one who was
the owner of the gun shop.
Our next question is from
Miss Neha who is our ace news writer.
Hi Mr. D
This question is from
your female audience.
Why do you always keep
moustache and what is this..
..fascination with the
same brand of sunglasses.
Why do I keep moustache?
I get a character.
I cannot keep a tail so
that is why I keep moustaches.
Without moustaches I feel
a man is standing naked on the road.
As far as sunglasses are concerned.
So all things related
to me are banned in the world.
So my glasses would be Ray Ban.
A big thanks to our
panel in Mumbai and to Neha.
World reminds me that..
..there is a rumor that you knew
in advance about the Osama killings.
I knew it? My men killed him.
Such a big joke doesn't
suit your moustaches.
I am telling you the truth Mr. Arnab.
For three months he had not
paid the EMI of protection money.
So I had no option.
What are you talking?
US did such a big cowat operation.
A movie has been made on that.
A movie has been made on Jurassic
Park as well but that is not true.
So you are saying such a big
operation by US was a video game.
Is that what you are saying?
Brother, anyone may do the operation..
..but what do you know which people
are behind the commando uniform.
Wow! It is very hard to tell
whether it is fact or fiction.
Even about 93 blasts no one
knows whether it is fact or fiction.
On that note we take a short break.
We will be back with our
final leg of the interview.
Hello, is everything fine there?
Everything is fine here.
But what are you doing?
What happened?
The problem is that
nothing has happened?
I had married a man who
was court martial on live TV
And not with a man who
would get scared of a hooligan.
Otherwise what do you think a crime
reporter like me would marry you?
Tell me what do you want to say?
Listen, it might
sound cheesy out to you
But you definitely remember
our journalism oath, right.
We will uphold the dignity of this
country and its media come what may.
Yes, it is getting cheesy and sweet.
Shut up, Arnab.
This is not a joke.
You are on the verge
of becoming national hero.
How many people get this chance?
Social media is going dessert.
Do you realize the gravity?
He must be a hooligan of somewhere.
What do we have to do?
Just remember that you are
the biggest hooligan of Indian media.
This is not just an interview
anymore to save your job.
This is that trial of D which has not
happened in court for last 22 years.
And it does not matter
if it is a media trial.
We cannot afford to lose this Arnab.
And India cannot afford to lose this.
So don't worry about me.
I am fine.
And as it is I have
done a text to police.
So you just go out there
and grab him by his fucking balls.
Bye.
I had never thought that I
would smoke a cigarette with you ever.
Have you tried a cigar?
No.
It hurts my throat.
Do you know why I didn't
ask for interview's script..
..before saying yes to the interview?
Because I thought
you are a family man..
..and would remain in your limits
because of fear of wife's death.
I thought you would
remain in your limits.
But I had forgotten that media
people never remain in their limits.
Just relax.
We both will together take
care of the interview further.
But remain in your limits.
Otherwise it is Don's interview
on live TV so anything can happen.
What did you understand?
-It is happening too much.
-Yes you are right.
Okay fine.
- Okay.
It is the last leg of the
interview so let's make it count.
This is your revised
draft for the final segment.
Just show him his place Arnab.
Welcome back to One
on One with me Arnab Ghsoh.
Now we have reached
our final segment..
..where we will ask some
inconvenient questions to MR. D
Are you ready?
- Yes.
From your talks we can make out that
your influence is on the global level.
So were you behind
the hijacking in Kandahar?
It is a limit.
Now you would say..
..that I am responsible for the
Malaysian airlines that got missing.
I won't say that but
a Gulf news report says so.
This report is right.
So are you telling
me a fact or a fiction?
I have said what I wanted to say
now understand whatever you want to.
Mr. D let me be very
categorical in my question.
So you are saying that you
are behind the disappearance..
..of two Malaysian
planes including MH 370.
There is no need to be hyper.
Relax, relax..
Is there no need to get hyper?
You are saying that
flight disappearance..
..in Malaysia have
been engineered by you.
And you are asking me to calm down.
All this has been made by media,
my brother.
Nothing of this kind had happened.
- Then what had happened?
What happened was that I had to sit in
flight from Kuala Lampur to Karachi.
And those rascals made
e sit in Beijing flight.
Tell me what my fault in this is.
I had to reach hurriedly
for my nephew's wedding..
..so we had to divert the flight.
Look, she is standing behind you.
Now you will say that passengers
of the flight are also here.
So do you think I have so many
servants in my house from beginning?
What about the second Malaysian plane?
You are too much, Arnab.
After the problem I faced am I
stupid to travel by that flight again.
No wonders your name is also
there in the top 10 list of the FBI
This is the problem.
- What is the problem?
The problem is Arnab
that I used to be number 1.
In last three years I
have come down to number 6.
Boys whom I have trained
are on top of the list.
What times have come?
You have become sentimental.
No problem. Everyone's time comes.
I think that censor
thing does not apply to you.
It does apply Mr. D but
I also get sentimental sometimes.
I am sure you must be having
plan to become number 1 again.
Yes I have a plan.
If I shoot you on live TV
then I can become number 1 overnight.
You are again talking like a hooligan.
There is a difference
between saying and doing Mr. D.
My hero.
Finally on popular
demand one last question.
Popular demand.
Will I have to dance?
You can do if you wish
to but that is not the case.
Okay.
Viewers want to know that you..
..have many fake accounts
on facebook and twitter.
Often you are being bullied on that.
What do you have to say about that?
Are you saying correct?
Of course.
One account is exactly
on your name with status update..
..check in, and share happening often.
Show it to me.
Show me which account is this?
This one.
- Yes.
What is the matter?
Why are you laughing at your own joke?
This is my account.
Girdhari takes care of it.
Show Girdhari..
Look, look..
Look.
I had gone to Malaysia and
had checked-in in that hotel. Look.
Once I was getting a philosopher
kind of feeling like..
..Danish type so I asked
him to put that status.
Look, look..
I had gone to PM's daughter's wedding
and I have put photograph of the deal.
Look Girdhari the face of
facebook has become like Doordarshan.
You had put these
on..what do you call it?
Gram Panchayat.
- Instagram.
Instagram.
Don't do anything that
will lead to thrashing.
One last question?
Why did you escape from India?
I did not escape.
I was going to settle
in Dubai to expand my business.
Unfortunately the blasts took place
and you all thought that I escaped.
Then why did you leave
your people alone in India.
Or you had planned
to settle abroad alone.
That's okay. There is no problem.
There are many people who
are not bothered about others.
And go away from home for business.
That is fine.
Arnab, this time I will
not show a trailer on mobile..
..but will show live shooting.
What trailer will you show me?
I will show you your status.
Hey, talk sensibly.
Hey, you keep quiet.
You do not have the status
to become constable in your country..
..and here you are his right hand.
Do you know what
you do with right hand?
Quiet. - Girdhari, leave it. A it
is the bullets have become expensive.
Why are you wasting it? Leave it.
D I will tell you
what your problem is.
You have kept 200 body
guards and security system..
..because you are scared.
Sitting under so much
of security in the house..
..you are talking about courage.
If you are such a big dynamic
Don then dare to come back.
Delhi is only 1100 kms away
from here but you cannot go there.
You can go to Nairobi, Malaysia..
..and even have passport
of the world with you.
But will never come to Delhi.
Shall I tell you why?
Because you belong to no one.
You neither belong to your
family nor to your country men.
The country in which you were born
you killed 257 people of that country.
The area that brought you up is going
to police and court because of you.
But you think that you are Don.
You are Bhai but your brother was
hanged six months ago in our country.
Do you remember?
You should have saved him.
You are scared of
your own criminal record.
You are so scared that for your
crime you let your brother get hanged.
Take this.
If I play this CD now..
..then it will take
only 5 minutes to prove..
..that all allegations
on you are true.
You are fond of watching movies
so let's watch this CD together.
You will not see because till today
you have been running from yourself.
Don are those who accept
their crime openly.
They either accept or deny openly.
They do not hide behind random
fantasy stories just as you do.
But what to do you are a coward.
Now rest of your life you
will escape from these allegations..
..and when you die then everyone
will run from burial place..
..because there will be no difference
between you and your crimes.
This is your luck D.
you are not Don but fraud.
Wow! Arnab.
Brother...
- What have you done?
I have not done anything.
Give me the arms.
You take care of brother.
Girdhari, he has killed brother.
I have to take revenge
for what he has done.
Take care here.
Out, get out....
Brother....
Oh god, he has made me crazy.
Brother's heart is very good.
- Come on..
so he had to get heart attack.
- Come on, come on it is time to go.
Brother's heart is very big.
- Okay..
Bye...
Come on....
Brother....
Hey, come on.
Come..
Do you know what the right hand does?
The right hand shoots, presses
the trigger, slaps and takes revenge.
Don't give me speech.
Finish it.
Come on escape.
- Please.. please..
500mts away you will find our men.
They will help you
to reach your home safely.
What are you saying?
I am saying the truth.
Come on.
I am not believer in violence now.
I believe in love.
Are you joking?
No, come on run....
Hey, good bye Neha.
Don't look behind and see.
Bye..
You are welcome in this
special edition of news.
Harsh words took away D's life.
Today's breaking news
is that our star reporter..
..Arnab Ghosh has killed
dangerous Don D in his house.
There has been turmoil in the country.
You became a star overnight, baby.
I was born as a super star.
- You are right.
Okay, I wanted to tell you something.
Tell me.
You know this interview was
very tough and challenging for me.
You know it.
I had to accept many challenges.
I know.
I had to compromise.
- You don't know.
Are you telling me that
you have to compromise with D.
No, no not that bad.
Then anything else would do.
I don't think so.
What do you mean?
Actually I will have to
sleep with Neha for one night.
What do you mean you have
to sleep for one night with Neha?
Only one night.
What rubbish is that?
- Only one.
So you have guts to tell me this.
Not to.
You have a pregnant wife.
You are a rascal.
You are such a creep.
Say sorry.
Sorry.
One more time.
Only one.
Sorry.
Only one time.
Say sorry.
Sorry.
You area such a creep.
Okay, okay I am going to the doctor.
That's it.
And listen celebration is due tonight.
If you are with me.
- Not bad.
Among so much crowd....
The biggest.. is being
offered to the country.
Hello.
Shall I call you brother
Arnab or senior editor Mr. Arnab.
Hello.
I am saying greetings Mr. Arnab.
D.
To hell with D.
You are talking to
David Adrees Kalemen.
The time has come to do that thing
which we have been planning to do.
Brother, as you say.
I will do acting of
heart attack and fall.
Okay.
And you make them
reach India safely. Okay.
So that they can make the
news of my death as breaking news.
Okay brother.
And you will be free from this life.
Yes Girdhari.
I wanted to kill him on live TV
Then I thought there
is an opportunity and..
..why should I waste it
by committing a murder.
Or give birth to a new life for me.
Did you understand?
You did not even know and you
became a chess piece of D's chess.
Today I am going to
step into my new life.
It is because of your favor.
Do remember me if you want
a promotion or money?
I will not refuse you.
What are you doing?
Have you taken the shock to heart?
Sorry buddy.
I am trying not to laugh but...
Whom are you calling buddy?
Do you know whom are you talking to?
With David Adrees Kalemen.
Buddy, I have seen many amazing
and foolish people in my media career.
But you are too great.
You are above all.
Do you know what have you done today?
With your cunningness
you have done something..
..which international police
and intelligence could not do.
You killed D with your own hands today.
You think yourself to be a remote
control but you are actually..
..a useless remote control of a TV
which is also there in my house.
Your story is amazing.
You were born in India and
then you went to Dubai.
Then because of fear of Interpol
you escaped to Pakistan.
Then you got so scared
that you disappeared..
..not only from Pakistan
but from world map.
Great.
I have to say that everyone
is in love with his own identity..
..but you destroyed your identity.
Superb, buddy.
Honestly I am grateful to you.
You freed my country
from your hangover.
Total free.
Because of our police and intelligence
your fear had already disappeared.
But you finished the fear
of your name as well.
Superb. D, D is gone.
Look what amazing thing I did.
I am sure you must be standing in the..
..ticket line of an amusement
park wearing red hat.
But my stomach is twisting
because of laughter.
Now I will take your leave.
I will keep the phone.
Okay. But one minute.
Do you know what date is today?
15th August.
No one must have thought that today you
will free us from yourself.
Now I have an important
meeting with real people.
Thanks for calling.
Hello, hello.....
Brother, he is asking for change.
Always keep change. Understood.
Do you know who I am?
D
Come on brother.
From the time he has dies
everyone think of themselves as D.
Look there.
Upcoming movie Coffee With D
Brother...
You come, please.