This Subtitle Encoded By Swagath77@Subscene.com
Bauua, you're marinating here...
Babita's coming to the Mall tonight.
- Babita, who?
Babita Kumari!
Your Mrs.
My sister-in-law.
The one who'll have henna
painted on her hands. Bauua Singh!
The irony of love!
Before I die,
she has come to meet me. In person.
Get the scooter out, Guddu.
The night is young,
full of sexy promises
A hazy wind is blowing
You always fail at love.
I burn in love
Our names are notorious
I could use you
Don't think too much
I'll leave the world behind for you.
Why worry?
The beauty conquers your heart
Bang like a drum.
work my body
Tonight I'm in charge,
so dance to my beat
Then do it slowly
Fire like a bullet.
One night only
Coz I'm feeling hot.
Tequila, no chaser
All on your lips,
you're liking my attitude
Tonight's the night.
Give me that ah ha
Might call you later
Hey you big flirt
Your love has a bitter-sweet flavour
I need you
My love is only stirred by you
Rob the treasures of the world.
Come back to me
You are a lover among lovers
The beauty conquers your heart
Bring the three Khans with you.
I'm right here, sweetheart.