How are you, brother-in-law?
I'm great. Come on in!
- I'll join you.
Certainly.
Did you get the photo?
- Photo?
I've brought her entire biodata,
sis; take a look.
Don't peep in.
Go to the kitchen.
- Get me a pancake.
Yes, uncle.
She's Shukla's daughter.
- Look.
I've got all the details on her.
She belongs to a good family.
Remember, Mom always said:
'Bring home a daughter-in-law
from a poorer family.'
Her family will remain intimidated.
- Uncle.
She's beautiful.
- Oh, great.
I think she is a little
too beautiful.
It shouldn't be that
she is always busy doing make up
while we cook for her.
She won't dare to do that.
- You think you will cook for her ever?
I don't expect you to do that, Shanti.
Of course, you expect
the worst from me!
Show me.
Child, call Sattu.
Ask him to meet the girl on Sunday.
All right, Dad.
Tell me,
why are you always so nervous
when you meet a girl?
How can one take a decision after
meeting a girl only for ten minutes
that you want to marry her and
spend the rest of your life with her?
Oh.
- Yeah.
And if you take the wrong decision,
buddy,
your whole life is ruined.
Then don't take your decision
in ten minutes. - And?
Hire an expensive Mercedes.
Go with her in the fancy car.
Check her out; totally.
Then you'll be able to
take the right decision.
I have a better idea.
Why don't I check out your girl?
I'll check her out; totally.
Shut up, you fool!
She'll be your sister-in-law.
Stay in your limit!
Oh, so your girl is my sister-in-law?
And my girl?
Forget it!
Okay listen, don't boil eggs
for me today; it's Tuesday.
Friend, you're sure to get hooked.
She's really beautiful.
I don't understand.
There's such a beautiful girl in our city
and we don't know?
Give that to me!
Yes Mom, I'll be there in time.
What dress are you wearing?
The pink suit that Aunt Guddi
had gifted me. - Good.
Listen, do wear matching earrings.
Yes Mom, I'm wearing them.
I'd worn the same earrings last time too.
Okay Mom, listen.
Tell me.
Try talking to Dad one last time.
Maybe he relents.
I'm highly qualified,
topped in my Masters. - Tea.
I don't want to get married so soon.
Let me study more,
become someone,
then I'll get married to whoever
he chooses for me.
Just try talking to him
one last time, Mom.
You know he's a stubborn man.
I supported your move to Allahabad
to do your Masters.
He taunts me for that to this day.
So just forget about further education.
Okay, listen,
talk nicely to the boy.
And like it's your habit,
don't laugh loudly in his presence.
Be a little coy.
Mom, don't ask me to pretend
to be shy, okay?
Just like he's coming to meet me
for a reason,
even I'm going to meet him
for a reason.
And if the boy is really good,
but I say I don't want to marry him,
will Dad get me married
to him forcibly?
Aarti, is there some problem?
What happened,
why did you fall silent?
Yes, Dad?
Have you chosen some guy
in your university?
No, Dad.
You are such a fool.
This boy is educated.
He's a clerk at the Collector's office,
it's a government job.
The family owns a three storey house.
They are far richer than us.
I cannot find such good proposals
for you again and again.
Don't have hopes of getting a proposal
from some senior officer, you understand?
Yes, dad.
And yes, if you reject
even this proposal,
your Jogi uncle has three
other proposals for you.
I have to get you married before
the year ends, you understand?
Yes, Dad.
So just go and meet the boy.
What happened?
Nothing.
Satyendra.
- Aarti.
Please sit.
Would you like to have something?
Yes, I...
- Waiter!
What will you have?
- Coffee.
Get two cups coffee.
Would you like to eat something with it?
A pastry maybe?
Cookies?
- No, thanks.
Just two coffees.
Okay.
Ask me whatever you wish to.
I'm ready for the interview.
Hey, no,
this is not an interview.
Like I've come here to meet you for
a reason, it's the same with you.
Even you can ask me
any questions you like.
Truly speaking,
I find this very awkward.
How can one take a life changing
decision in half an hour?
Even I find it awkward.
[Chuckles]
Dad said you have a government job.
Yes, I'm a clerk
in the excise department.
I will join next month,
I've just bagged the job.
Excise department?
They take bribes.
You want to become rich
accepting bribes? - No.
I don't believe in accepting
or giving bribes.
That's how our system works.
Even if you refuse,
people will give it to you.
I won't accept it.
- You won't be able to refuse.
I'll never accept bribes.
- We'll see.
We...
- Sir.
Ma'am.
Thank you.
- Welcome.
What are your expectations
from your would-be wife?
That she makes tea for me
when I wake up in the morning.
Then make breakfast for me.
Then pack my lunch for me.
Just like Mom has been doing for Dad
since so many years.
When I am back home from work,
she should be all dressed and waiting for.
She should massage my legs at night.
I have no such expectations from her.
I want a life partner
who can be my friend for life.
I just want her to
take care of my parents,
treat them with respect, that's all.
What expectations do
you have from your husband?
Dad has never let me work.
I've been a topper since childhood.
My only expectation from
my husband is
that he permits me to work.
You are so qualified,
you should put it to use.
In fact, it's good. If you also work,
we'll enjoy a double income.
And I won't even have to accept bribes.
- [Laughs]
I have one more expectation.
This is a tough one.
Tell me.
I want my husband to take me to
the movies every week.
You're a movie buff?
- Die hard!
We'll watch the evening show
every Sunday in Sangam theater.
You promise?
- Promise.
So, what next?
Choose a finger.
This one?
I'll call my parents in the evening.
I'll give them my consent for marriage.
- [Laughs]
You like me so much?
Why only me,
anybody will like you.
I hope you don't choose somebody else.
Even I'll call my mom in the evening.
Shall I tell you something?
Pink suits you a lot.
Thank you.
Satyendra,
what did the other finger hold?
In the restaurant,
you asked me to...
Oh that?
Instead of evening, I would go to the
men's room right away, call mom
and tell her I want to marry you.
- [Laughs]
If you don't mind,
can I tell you something?
Tell me.
I'll never mind anything you say.
It's not akward, it's awkward.
Huh? Did I say akward?
Okay.
We are going to get married now,
nothing will be akward anymore.
Awkward.
Awk...
A...
...ward.
kward
Kward... awkward.
I know. I'll learn gradually.
You want curd?
- Greetings, uncle.
Come here.
Bravo!
If you want to seek blessings,
bow down properly.
Don't just pretend to bow.
Come on, bow down again.
That's better. Bless you.
Now tell me,
prepared for the competitive exams?
I'm preparing.
I'll do well by your grace.
How will blessings help?
Greetings, aunt.
- The son wants to outdo his father.
I'm very hungry, aunt.
- Sit down.
His ancestors sold cutlery,
while he's out to become an officer.
If your son wants to do something,
why don't you support him?
Once he becomes a magistrate
or collector,
he'll make the family proud.
Come off it!
Dad, I'll surely clear the exam next year.
- Oh, really?
But if you make me sit at the
shop and sell cutlery
how will I get the time to study?
I need to focus.
Sure! I'll make you focus, kid,
just come home!
Aunt, I'd told Aarti
to attempt the exam.
She topped in the
Masters exam last year.
I'm sure she will top the
competitive exam too.
Shall even I make one attempt
on your face?
You fool!
These government officer jobs
are not for girls.
Don't give wrong advice to your sister.
By the way, that proposal
for Aarti is very good.
So when do you want
to come and meet Mr. Mishra?
They've called us at
3 O' clock tomorrow.
Be here at sharp two,
don't be late.
Arrange a bottle for me here,
brother-in-law,
and I won't leave.
[Laughs]
You'll never change.
I spoke to Mahesh.
Some members of the Shukla family
will come to meet us tomorrow.
Okay.
Shanti.
I spoke to Sattu.
We both have decided
that we won't accept any dowry.
If we don't accept any dowry,
how will we conduct the marriage?
What do you mean?
I mean,
will we be able to find a groom for
Poonam who won't accept dowry from us?
No, right?
How can we agree to marriage
without dowry?
We won't be able to save enough
from what you earn
to be able to find an
officer groom for Poonam.
Besides, we have not
made this tradition.
The dowry we get for Sattu, we'll add
some more to it and give it to Poonam.
Poonam is still two years away
from marriageable age.
Yes, and in two years,
dowry demand for her will double.
Okay, stop worrying about that
and have your milk, it's turning cold.
I've spoken to Mahesh,
he will come at 2:30pm.
I know you will not talk frankly.
We need someone worldly wise
to do the talking.
Come on now, drink your milk
and go to bed.
Sister and you have planned and decided
to give dowry of up to Rs.1200,000.
I think the boy and the family,
both are good.
Even if they demand Rs.15,00,000,
don't reject the proposal.
No, I can only pay Rs.12,00,000.
And I'll stick to that figure.
You please don't butt in there.
Rs.25,00,000.
Rs.25,00,000 is a small amount
in today's times.
We cannot accept anything less
than that for my nephew's marriage.
Shall we leave, brother-in-law?
Shall we leave?
- Wait, let me talk.
What leave? Have we come
here to leave just like that?
Mr. Mishra, I have a small plot
in Kanpur.
I will get about Rs. 300,000-400,000
if I sell it.
I've also saved some money
especially for Aarti's marriage.
For the remaining amount, I'm going to
take a personal loan from the bank.
I want to get my daughter
married into your family.
Please don't embarrass me.
You give your daughter whatever you want.
This is just an old tradition,
- [Clears throat]
or I'm against...
- Hold it, brother-in-law.
Let me talk.
I'm doing all the talking, okay?
Look, my nephew is the only son.
He's the sole heir to
this three storey house.
He's also bagged a government job now
in the excise department. - Indeed.
And my brother-in-law,
he's been working as a professor
with the University.
Hey, why are you...
They have every right
to demand that kind of dowry.
We will get him married only
if we get a good dowry, or else...
We are sorry, sir.
Rs.25,00,000 is simply
beyond our capacity.
Mr. Jogi, you don't understand math?
- Huh?
We have an offer of Rs.40,00,000.
Oh!
- Yes, Rs.40,00,000.
It's just that our Sattu
likes your daughter.
Or we wouldn't accept dowry
a penny less than that. - True.
You showed an interest,
that's why we waited.
Or by today evening, we would have
finalised his marriage to somebody else.
Sister, give me their number.
Where is my phone?
Let's go, brother-in-law. They are
meeting another family in the evening
who is giving them Rs.40,00,000.
Let's go.
I told you not to talk too much.
We can't leave.
Mr. Mishra, you are a learned man,
worldly wise.
You realise what kind of
money I can afford.
I am working as a BDO,
but I have never taken a
penny's bribe in my entire life.
You tell me,
what is your final demand?
Mr. Shukla, I am...
Mr. Shukla is demanding
as per his status.
To finalise this proposal, we demand
dowry of Rs.2500,000, not a penny less!
You get that?
We want Rs.1800,000 in cash,
Rs.700,000 worth of goods
and this is our final decision.
It's also the decision
of my sister and brother-in-law.
We cannot finalise this marriage
for anything less than this amount.
Shall we leave now,
brother-in-law?
I accept the proposal, Mr. Mishra.
We will honor your demand.
Please don't fold your hands
before me.
Shanti, get sweets!
[Laughs]
We are relatives now.
Congratulations!
You exercise your might
only on me.
'Mr. Mishra,
we will honor your demand.'
How will you arrange the
extra Rs.13,00,000?
I won't find a good groom for my daughter
for dowry less than this anywhere.
I will take a loan before
my retirement,
and repay it gradually over the years.
At least my daughter will get
married into a family of her choice;
I gave consent on that thought.
Shall I say something?
You look like Juhi Chawla in pink.
[Chuckles]
And you look like Shahrukh Khan
in every color you wear.
Really?
Shahrukh Mishra?
[Laughs]
Let's go.
Shall I move?
[Music]
"Become a street of Banaras"
"And I'll be lost in you for eternity"
"Your talk is tangy"
"Your eyes pure like the Ganges"
"I could fall asleep
staring into them forever"
"And wake up in the morning,
still lost in them"
"Become a street of Banaras"
"And I'll be lost in you for eternity"
[Music]
"We'll spend every Sunday
in Sangam Talkies"
"Watching the night show"
"Like in the films,
maybe it happens some day"
"That I become your hero"
"We'll spend every Sunday
in Sangam Talkies"
"Watching the night show"
"Like in the films,
maybe it happens some day"
"That I become your hero"
"I'll entertain you, I'll dance"
"I'll romance you"
"I'll live in your heart like joys"
"And become evident
in your every smile"
"Become a street of Banaras"
"And I'll be lost in you for eternity"
"Become a street in Banaras"
Shall I say something?
I've never been as happy in life,
as I am feeling now marrying you.
I feel the same.
Can I drink coffee out of your cup?
[Chuckles]
Where would you like to go
for our honeymoon?
Huh?
- Our honeymoon?
I want to go to
some place very cold.
Like Mussoorie...
We should go to Mussoorie!
We'll go to Mussoorie.
- Sure!
Mussoorie!
I have a secret desire.
What?
Just once, I want to go
on a drinking binge with my husband
and get really high.
I've never had alcohol.
But I've seen it in films.
And I think it could
be a lot of fun.
I've seen how the hero
gets the heroine drunk
and then they have a great time.
I want to do just that.
And then,
if...
my husband is my best friend,
I can trust him totally, right?
Of course.
Secret.
Choose a finger.
This one?
We'll have Phiskey.
- Huh?
- [Laughs]
What is Phiskey? It's Whiskey.
Yes, that's what I meant.
I'm already getting high.
What choice was on the other finger?
Barandy.
It's not Barandy, it's Brandy.
Living with you,
I'll develop a foreign accent.
[Laughs]
You know, what?
Join my family soon.
You can teach everyone English.
I'm tired of teaching them.
What?
Did I really say Barandy?
- Yes, Satyendra.
Call me Sattu.
Everyone who loves me calls me that.
There she comes!
My favorite niece!
- Uncle!
Where is our son-in-law?
Dad, he's very busy, he will
come only on the day of marriage.
Now that I am here, whatever
work you have at whatever time,
just tell me, I'll definitely not do it.
- [All laughs]
This product you will not
get anywhere else in the market.
There is padding in it?
- Yes.
It's a lovely piece.
It fits really well.
It's a two-piece night wear.
There are other colors too,
buy those. See this.
No sis, this is very pretty.
- If she could,
she would buy pink undergarments.
Neelam!
- Those, buy any color, it doesn't matter.
Sis! What crap you talk.
[Laughs]
How much longer will this take,
it feels ticklish.
Aarti will reduce your shoe size,
the amount she's scrubbing.
I'm getting married!
How can you not have pedicured feet?
What are you chatting with him,
let me see.
Now the whole bed belongs to me!
Brother is hitting me! Mummy!
Mummy, let's buy this.
Aunt, you try it on.
You'll look like a heroine. - Shut up!
If Dad spots us, he'll kill us!
You also try it.
- I don't smoke.
[Clears throat]
Ranjan!
Scram!
- [Laughs]
Round, round and stop!
Not in my plate! Dad!
- [Sneezing]
It's tasty.
Which one?
- Let's finalise the red one, Mom.
Even Aarti likes it.
- Son, girls wear red shades.
My son won't wear red.
Mummy!
[Camera clicks]
This is good. Your husband is a clerk
and my husband a junior engineer.
They are not very different.
- Sis!
Just joking!
Does brother-in-law know you smoke?
I don't hide anything from him,
nor does he hide anything from me.
We are best friends.
Even you don't hide anything from Sattu.
I won't.
I've already told him I want us to get
totally drunk on our honeymoon.
Oh, you are two steps
ahead of me.
So what did he say?
He's more excited than me.
He's never had alcohol before.
Sis, he's really cute.
Aarti, I have learnt that only two things
are most important in a marriage.
And what are those?
Lots of love and lots of money.
What nonsense, sis!
- It's the truth.
[Laughs]
- [Cellphone rings]
Sis.
What timing this boy has!
It's like this guy cannot even
use the toilet without talking to you.
How disgusting, sis!
Put it on speaker.
Let me hear what he's saying.
And let you listen in?
I'm not a fool.
I know what he's going to say,
you put it on speaker.
You will remain silent?
- Not a word!
Hi.
- Happy birthday.
You remembered?
- I remember everything about you.
Really?
Okay, listen wife,
I want to meet you.
Meet me at the temple tomorrow.
There is a room behind it.
- Huh?
We'll meet there.
I'll hit you if you go.
- I won't.
Why will we meet in a room?
Hey no, don't misunderstand.
Huh? - That we can indulge in
after marriage at home.
I've not seen you since so many days.
I want to see you so desperately!
I'm finding it difficult
to survive without you.
I will not come.
- All right, tomorrow 4pm. Bye!
Hey! Sattu, hello? Hello?
[Laughs]
I love this guy!
He's so romantic! Move!
Sis!
- He's so romantic!
He's great!
From two, you already have one thing.
Your love life will be great.
He'll be into you.
- Sis!
And I'm already imagining that.
- You're so disgusting, sis!
But one thing is amiss.
- What?
I think he is miserly.
- Why?
Just think, does one call
his would be wife to a temple?
There are so many five-star hotels.
He could have booked a room there.
What, he'll make you toll the bell
in the temple? - Come on, sis!
I don't know all that.
I'll be there before 4pm.
My poor man is finding it difficult
to survive without me.
It'll give him a breather
until our marriage.
But get this clear.
Don't let him touch you.
Men are fools.
First, he'll make a move
and then doubt your character.
I'm just warning you.
- All right, Mom!
[Laughs]
"Happy birthday to you"
"Happy birthday, dear Aarti"
Thank you, Sattu.
You did so much for me.
- This is nothing.
I have written something for you,
shall I read it?
Poetry?
- Yes. Shall I read it?
Juhi, Madhuri, Divya Bharati
You are more beautiful
than all of them, Aarti.
[Laughs]
- You are...
You're laughing.
- No, I'm not laughing, continue.
It's cute. Continue.
You are my destination, my dream.
You are God's best creation.
My only intent now.
Is to love you more than myself.
Sattu.
What do you think?
It's very, very beautiful.
Thank you.
Pink color suits you a lot.
Why do you think
I'm wearing pink color?
You mean, for me?
Of course, for you.
There are petals in your hair.
I've.. I've fallen in love with you.
Shall I say "I love you"?
Your wish.
Okay, I'll say it then.
I love you.
[Laughs]
It's your turn now.
Hey!
'I also love you.'
Say it.
Say!
It's just three words, say them.
I will not say anything.
Whatever I have to say,
I'll say after marriage.
All right.
All right, now...
shall I ask you something, you...
- Ask me.
If you don't mind?
One...
...can I kiss you once?
Can I kiss you?
How can we kiss in a temple?
God is everywhere.
- Oh, really?
I would, if you had called me
to some five-star hotel room.
Oh, I forgot!
I've bought something for you.
Happy birthday!
Bribing me, huh?
Bribing me for a kiss?
- I love you very much.
Then kiss me.
It's okay. Let it be.
Why, lost the mood?
- No, I very much want to.
[Laughs]
Then kiss me.
Shall I really?
Shall I put this down?
- I'll hold it.
Just one kiss, that's all.
No! You will kiss me
and then doubt my character.
No, I will not doubt you.
You will.
- I swear, I won't.
Everything after marriage now.
- I won't doubt you.
You have to wait for just one
more day, Sattu, bye!
I.. I will not doubt...
Sattu, it's just a small wait now.
We'll meet tomorrow
for our marriage.
[Music]
"My world started
to glitter like the stars"
"When you entered it
like a glowing moon"
"My world started
to glitter like the stars"
"When you entered it
like a glowing moon"
"I want to be so close to you"
"That I become your feeling"
"And live your every breath!"
"I set with you"
"I rise with you"
"I walk with you like your shadow"
"I intend to love you
more than myself"
"I promise myself
to be with you always"
"I spend my days,
my nights with you"
"You sleep all night,
I sit and watch you"
"You have gotten such into me"
"That even if I walk in a crowd,
but without you, I'll feel alone"
"In every mirror, I see you"
"I have become your face"
"I intend to love you
more than myself"
"I promise myself
to be with you always"
[Music]
"In your heart, love takes flight"
"In this flight, I am your wings"
"I'll get wet with you in the rain"
"When your tresses fly,
they cover me like a cloud"
"Your dark eyes
are the sea of my dream"
"I'm totally drowned in them"
"I intend to love you
more than myself"
"I promise myself
to be with you always"
"To be with you always"
Brother!
Mr. Groom, wake up!
Wake up!
Couldn't you have come
after two minutes?
Let's see that attitude when Aarti
wakes you up from tomorrow. - Scram!
Get up, Mom is calling you. Up!
- I'm coming.
[Cooker whistle blows]
[Phone chimes]
[Aarti] 'See the henna I have
applied for you.'
'Your name is etched in my life now.'
'At least in this life
I belong to you.'
[Satyendra] 'Why just this life,
I belong to you for eternity.'
'Choose a finger.'
'The right one.'
'You chose "I love you".'
'And what did the other say?'
'I love you very, very, very much!'
[Laughs]
"They are standing quietly,
something is fishy"
"It's perhaps the first meeting
of the bride and groom"
"The groom pleads with the bride
to show her face"
"The bride tells him to
get her a gold bangle first"
"They wasted away the night
in this fight"
The turmeric ceremony has begun?
- Yes, we were waiting for you.
Did you apply on him?
- I did.
I applied lots on him,
I turned him all yellow. - Good!
Brother, this is Aarti's sister,
and he's her brother. - Hello.
"They are quiet..."
Welcome to the family.
You don't have to touch my feet
to seek my blessings.
"It's perhaps their first meeting"
"The groom asks the bride
to show her face"
You look nice.
- [Laughs]
Sister, Mom is inside.
- I'll be back.
How are you?
- I'm fine, brother-in-law.
Your husband didn't come?
Aunty, you know
how busy junior engineers are.
But he will be here
on the day of marriage.
Child, get some snacks for her.
- Yes, Mom.
And Ranjan, what are you up to?
I'm preparing my thesis.
- Okay.
I've attempted twice before,
this is my third attempt.
Don't worry; work hard
and you will succeed.
Yes, I need your best wishes.
Have some.
- Sure.
Thank you. - My sister-in-law's
son works for the RTO in Indore.
Thank you.
We went last year to their house.
He enjoys a good status.
A government job gives you that.
- I agree.
Even my Sattu
has a government job now.
It's a good thing.
Sattu has a government job,
and even Aarti wants to
work after marriage.
She is lucky that you are allowing her.
My in-laws don't allow me.
We allowed it?
Who said we are allowing her?
Aunty, Aarti spoke to Sattu.
Sattu is young,
he flows with emotion and says things.
I still buy his underwear.
Look dear, daughters-in-law in
our family don't take up jobs.
It's been a tradition.
What will society say, that we are
living off our daughter-in-law's money?
In our family, daughters-in-law have
never worked, nor ever will.
At least not until I am alive.
And where a government job
is concerned,
I am the government of this house.
Let Aarti manage the house,
and treat this as a government job.
Mom.
- Yes, give me.
This is for Aarti.
Have something, you are not eating.
- We ate a lot, aunty.
[Crackers bursting]
"The couple is yet to meet."
You are looking very cute.
[Cellphone rings]
- Sattu, it's Aarti's call.
Hello.
- I'm feeling very nervous.
I have butterflies in my stomach.
- Don't worry; trust me.
Don't get tensed.
Listen, send me a picture
of you as a bride.
There should be some
suspense at least.
I want to see you, send it. - Patience!
I'm looking very hot today, by the way.
Why the suspense now,
we are almost married.
Hang up now!
I'm coming to take you.
- Bye!
Should I slap you now?
Are you foolish?
You are a fool!
- I was only talking to him on the phone.
You could have told me at least that you
have appeared for the competitive exams.
It wasn't that important.
It's wasn't important?
Are you crazy?
You... - Have you two finished?
Shall I speak now?
You've cleared the competitive exams!
You can become an officer!
Yes.
Your result has just come in,
I saw it online.
I... officer...
I can become an officer!
I have passed the exam!
[Shouts]
I want a treat!
I...
Sis, people try for years
and don't get selected.
Ranjan and I have been trying since
two years, but have failed both times.
But she cleared the exam
at first attempt!
It's a great achievement.
- It really is!
Aarti, you'll have your own residence,
a car with the beacon on top!
You'll have servants around you.
The best job in the state government,
office in the secretariat!
And so much respect,
you won't be able to digest it.
Everyone will take orders from you,
Officer Shukla.
Not Officer Shukla, I will be
Officer Aarti Satyendra Mishra.
I can't believe it, sis!
I'm going to become an officer!
Sattu is so lucky for me, sis.
Marriage is the happiest day
of one's life.
For me, it's a day
of double celebration!
Sis!
"I'm ready to take bullet wounds..."
- I'll bring home your daughter-in-law.
"...and die for love."
"I'm ready to take bullet wounds
and die for love."
"O my darling, I won't stop chasing you."
"No! No!"
"I'm ready to take bullet wounds
and die for love."
The groom is about to reach, hurry!
- Yes.
Keep it near the gate.
Dad, come here.
- What is it?
The groom will be here any minute.
- I want to say something important.
Dad, don't be angry,
just listen to me first.
Oh yes, I knew your husband
will not be able to make it.
Where is he, tell me.
- Dad... - Listen!
The groom is coming,
wear your coat, hurry.
You also get ready quickly.
- Dad, listen to me, and don't be angry.
Say it quickly,
there is no time.
Dad, Aarti had appeared for
the competitive exams.
She cleared both the levels.
She had not told us.
She qualified in the exams?
- Yes, online results have come in.
That's very good news.
It's great news.
Is Aarti ready, the groom is arriving.
Dad, you're not listening.
She has cleared the main exam,
she can be an officer.
From today, she is the
daughter-in-law of the Mishra family.
What she will become or not become,
what she will do or not do,
Mr. Mishra will decide now.
All right?
Is the welcome platter ready?
Mom, please convince Dad,
we are making a grave mistake.
The groom is on his way.
- Aarti's mother-in-law won't let her work.
We are making a big mistake
getting her married into this family.
Telling your dad anything
is not going to help.
He won't listen to anybody.
- Mom, at least you... - Manju.
Ask her to quietly go inside.
It's an auspicious day today, I don't
want to do anything inauspicious.
Dad, I know you are angry,
but think calmly... - Quiet!
Stop your nonsense!
Or I may raise my hand...
- What are you doing!
She is our guest.
- Guest indeed!
Don't say another word now.
I will speak. Why won't I?
- Keep quiet!
You want Aarti also to work
in the kitchen and look after kids
like Mom and me?
She shouldn't even try
becoming an officer?
She cleared the exam at first attempt.
She is so talented
and you are ruining her life.
Why will I not protest?
It's because of people like you
and her mother-in-law
that girls have to live
within four walls.
You want me to stall this marriage
heeding your nonsense?
You want me to tell Mr. Mishra
that my daughter can become an officer,
so I'm calling off the marriage?
- Yes, Dad.
Aabha.
- Stall this marriage.
She can get married later,
but she cannot become an officer later.
Her mother-in-law has said
she won't let her work.
She always wanted to work, Dad.
Stall this marriage.
- Aabha, quiet.
Manju, this girl has gone nuts.
Get her out of my sight
or I'll hit her.
I may do something untoward.
- Don't say that.
You are doing something
terribly untoward.
You are doing something terribly
untoward with Aarti's life.
Aabha, keep quiet.
I'm doing something untoward with
Aarti's life? - She doesn't mean that.
Listen to me carefully.
You are settled in life,
let your sister settle down too.
Don't try to be the boss of my house.
Mom, convince him.
- Enough!
Please, quiet.
Enough.
Pick up your bags and leave! [Snaps finger]
- Quiet! What...
We can get Aarti married
without your presence. Leave!
Dad, listen to me...
- Leave, I said!
How can you...
Aabha, wait.
[Music]
[Line ringing]
"I came out on the streets
with my vehicle."
"There came a turn in the journey"
"where I left my heart behind."
What happened, sis?
I just messaged Sattu.
Is everything okay?
What happened?
- Listen carefully to what I have to say.
When I went to your in-laws
house today morning,
I told her you want to work after
marriage, she flatly refused.
She said daughters-in-law in the
Mishra family don't take up jobs.
How can she say that?
Sattu himself told me...
I told her you have spoken
to Sattu about it.
You know what she said?
That Sattu is young,
and that she still buys his underwear.
You understand what that means?
She didn't tell me this,
she meant it for you.
Remember, you will never be able
to take up a job in that house.
Then why did Sattu tell me...
How does what Sattu said matter?
He will not be able to
go against his mother.
Now you decide what you want to do.
Sis, I cannot be just a housewife.
I do want to marry Sattu.
But I'd told him on our first meeting
that I want to work and he had agreed.
I cannot be just a housewife.
Sis, I'll talk to Sattu.
Why do you want to talk to Sattu?
He's my future husband.
- He's a clerk!
When you become officer, a dozen
clerks like Sattu will work under you.
I'm not saying he's bad,
he's a very good guy.
But he won't understand
even if he wants to, Aarti.
What should I do?
What do you mean
what should you do?
Look at me. Mother-in-law, father-in-law,
husband, kids, three meals
that no one cares about.
And on the other hand,
respect and independence,
and a life you have earned.
Just think!
Your future is calling you, Aarti.
Just think, why did your
results come in today?
They could have come tomorrow,
after you were married.
Right? You couldn't have done
anything then. But you can today.
Run away. Run away!
I'll call my husband,
he'll handle everything.
You go to Banaras
to my house with him.
"Dark glasses suit your fair face."
I cannot do this to Sattu.
And you can do it to yourself?
My husband and I are with you, Aarti.
Just run away.
No one will heed you here.
Run away.
Once you become officer,
Dad, Sattu, everyone will relent.
Aarti.
Aarti, it's very...
What do you want, child?
[Sobbing]
Dad, Sattu?
I'll handle them.
You want to become officer?
Then run away.
Uncle...
- There is no other option, dear.
Society is like that.
It treats men royally.
But no one respects women.
Nor does it want to give them
a life of their choice.
So whenever a daughter
gets the opportunity,
to live a life of her choice
holding her head high,
she must cross all hurdles and leave.
Run away, child. Leave.
I am with you.
[Music]
Aarti, leave, the groom is almost here.
Even I have to go down.
Someone may come.
No one should know. Leave!
I can't do it, sis.
Dad will kill me.
I won't be able to do it.
Aarti! Uncle will handle
everything; he told you.
Just remember that uncle will say you
heard about the dowry and ran away. Come!
Sis, how is Sattu at fault?
He loves me very much.
- You will find love again.
You won't get the opportunity to
become officer again. Come! - Sis.
Let me talk to him just once.
- No Aarti, not now.
And don't talk to him
until I don't tell you to.
If they come to know the
reason why you ran away,
they will blame you solely for it. Come.
- Sis, just once.
Come quickly.
Aabha, the groom has arrived.
Aabha, where is the platter of sweets?
- Mom.
[Crying]
Your brother-in-law is waiting at the
back door for you. Go.
Come. Come.
Good luck! Go quickly.
[Music]
[Crying]
Congratulations!
- To you too!
Hey! What are you doing?
- Where is Aarti?
Where is Aarti?
I'm asking you something.
She didn't want to get married, Dad.
She didn't want to get married or you
didn't want it? - What are you doing?
You are hitting your married daughter?
- Move aside!
Move aside!
What should I do if not hit her?
Worship her?
Don't hit her,
she's your married daughter.
The groom is here.
Where has she gone?
She must have told you!
- I don't know, Dad.
Sorry, Dad. Sorry, Dad. [Crying]
Sorry, Dad.
Educate your daughter even more!
Send her to Allahabad
for further education.
You cannot handle a young girl?
Why did I invite her?
She's brought me disgrace.
Uncle, why are you getting angry on her?
I have not managed to clear
the exams, but Aarti did.
If I could,
I would kill both of them.
And immolate myself too.
- Don't say that.
I've been disgraced!
My honor is in smithereens!
Come here.
Come.
I understand your pain,
brother-in-law.
This is a moment of crisis.
And we have to get out
of it somehow.
Don't think of the
society right now.
Think of how to recover Rs.1800,000
cash that we have given them.
Tell me, what should I do?
'Sorry Mr. Mishra,
forgive me for this.'
'My daughter has run away.'
'But please return the money
I gave you.'
Is this what I'll say?
See! You don't understand.
If Mahesh learns that Aarti has run away,
he won't return us a penny.
They will keep your life's savings.
So how do we make
them return the money?
We'll have to make them return it.
I beg you, brother-in-law,
let me handle this now.
Just remain silent in their presence.
We'll have tea,
but first tell us what is the matter?
Why have you called us here?
Mr. Mishra,
well, actually,
a very big crisis
has befallen upon us and you.
Crisis?
- Yes.
Mr. Jogi, what is the matter?
Well, actually Aarti...
What happened?
When we went to her room just now,
she was not there.
What do you mean?
We only found this letter.
Let me see.
Read it.
As soon as she came to know that you
demanded Rs. 25,00,000 dowry from us,
she decided not to get married
into your family.
And she left the house.
- Where did she go?
How do we know where she went?
- Let me talk to her.
We are unable to reach her,
how can we help you?
How can you say that, Mr. Shukla?
Whatever was finalised was
with the consent of both families.
Mr. Jogi, I know this is not
about dowry.
I'm sorry, Sattu,
I'd kept something from you.
I'd appeared for the
competitive exam.
The result came in today
and I have cleared the exam.
I'm going to become an officer.
You'd sent her to
Allahabad for higher education.
She must have fallen for
someone over there.
Your daughter disgraced your family honor
and ran away from home.
Go buy black paint
and rub it over your faces now!
Mind your tongue, Mahesh!
- Or what will you do?
What will we do?
I don't want to talk to you.
Mr. Mishra, you are an educated man.
I'm folding my hands
and telling you
that our daughter doesn't want to have
anything to do with your family now.
So please return our Rs. 18,00,000
cash to us without a fuss.
And return peacefully with your guests.
This marriage stands cancelled.
This is not a train ticket
that you are cancelling it.
Your daughter has run away and
you are asking us to return the money?
Have some shame.
You think this is a joke?
We won't refund a penny.
[Cellphone rings]
[Crying]
We won't refund a penny.
Let's go!
Oh, really?
It's not a piece of cake.
Don't even think of leaving
from here without refunding our money.
What can you do?
Brij, Chandu, Keshav,
close the doors!
Ranjan, get it out.
Aim it at his head...
Don't threaten me. I'm not afraid.
- You cannot leave!
Rs.18,00,000.
- Come on, shoot!
Until I don't have every penny back,
I won't let you leave from here.
Come on, shoot him!
Pump 25 bullets into him.
I'll shoot him, Dad.
- He demanded Rs. 25,00,000.
I'm standing before you,
shoot me!
Sit down, Mr. Mishra.
- Don't touch him!
And until you don't
hand me the money...
Dad, Aarti is gone. She's gone.
- What do you mean? Where did she go?
Let it be.
I'll return your money.
Don't do anything to my dad and uncle.
I'll get the money.
I'll be back.
- Son?
Aarti!
Aar... did you see Aarti?
- Huh? No.
Aarti!
Sis, where is Aarti?
I'm trying to call her since so long,
she's not answering my calls.
Where is she?
You two take the guests
and go back home.
Huh? What happened, Sattu?
I'll tell you later...
- What happened, brother?
you take everyone and go home.
- Sattu...
But...
[Aarti] 'I'm sorry, Sattu,
I'd kept something from you.'
'I'd appeared for competitive exams.'
'The result came in today
and I have cleared the exam.'
'I'm going to become an officer.'
[Crying]
Sattu.
Why did this happen?
Where is your dad and uncle?
- They are fine, don't worry.
Don't cry.
- Bring them back.
Where is the money?
I have to take back the money.
We spent Rs. 8,00,000,
I have the balance Rs. 10,00,000.
Take the Rs. 10,00,000
and get them freed quickly.
They won't accept only Rs. 10,00,000,
they want the full amount.
We will pay them later.
- They will not relent.
Where will we get money
from at this hour?
[Crying]
I'd saved this for Poonam's marriage.
I wore this when I got married.
I curse that girl
for doing this to us.
She ruined our life and ran away.
[Crying]
Hello. Sis?
- They just left.
They returned all the money to dad.
Is Dad all right?
He's not all right.
Uncle is with him.
He will stay here for a few days
until everything settles down.
Did Sattu call you?
He did, he called many times.
But like you had said,
I didn't answer.
Sis, can I call him once, please?
Yes, talk to him.
He's very hurt.
In all this, just one mistake happened;
he got hurt.
I saw him.
Stop. Stop the car.
[Brakes squeal]
What happened?
Sattu, look at him.
Brother-in-law.
Dad.
I won't die, son.
I won't die.
I'm not so weak.
I was just feeling a little suffocated.
Open your buttons.
- Wait.
I...
don't feel like going home.
I was going to take
home a daughter-in-law.
What will I go home
and do now?
Watch your mother's tears?
Everyone's eyes will be on us.
Look, there's Jugal Kishore Mishra.
Professor Jugal Kishore Mishra.
His son's marriage was planned.
We have suffered
great humiliation, son.
[Crying]
[Cellphone rings]
Come here.
What rubbish are you talking?
Look at me.
What are you talking?
Pick up, pick up, please pick up!
We won't spare them.
You are simply worrying.
[Siren wails]
And look,
as far as support is concerned,
we have started a single window
program for builders and developers.
So you will no longer
have to run around.
I hope you will now come forward
and invest in our region.
This will be beneficial
for you and for us.
[Clapping]
If you have any questions,
you can ask me.
[Knock on door]
Neelam, how many times have I told you,
don't knock, just walk in.
And I have told you equal number
of times that over here, you are senior
and I'm your junior.
See, I attempted the competitive
exam five times,
but I couldn't clear it,
whereas you cleared it
at first attempt.
By the way, Aarti,
I cannot thank you enough.
I have this job because of you,
or I'd still be in Kanpur
teaching in some school there.
Shut up.
Will you have tea?
Tea? I can have tea
anywhere, anytime.
Get two cups tea.
Aarti, the rumors I am hearing
in office, are they true?
That depends on what the rumor is.
Don't pretend now. The whole office
is talking only about one thing.
What?
Here goes.
[Laughs]
What are you doing!
- Peep!
I wasn't peeping. - Not peeping?
Your head is into my cards.
If you bend too much, you'll fall.
You have put on weight.
[Laughs]
Whenever brother-in-law is losing,
he becomes violent.
Dad, Neelam had called. Aarti is
probably going to get a promotion.
That's great!
Congratulations, brother-in-law.
Your move, Ranjan.
- It's tea-time!
Tea has come!
Sis, give me, I'll keep it.
I cannot thank God enough.
In five years,
Aarti has progressed so much.
Once she gets married,
I'll be really content.
Get up!
- Why?
Get up, quick!
- What happened?
Turn around.
Dust your clothes.
- But what happened?
But what happened?
Since five years, her thoughts
are stuck on Aarti's marriage.
I thought I'll shake them a bit
if I find them.
I'll slap you!
[All laughs]
Uncle, your turn.
What...
- Mom, why are you cheating?
I'm not cheating.
What an idiot you are.
You are cheating.
If Sonu is saying you're cheating,
then you are. - Dad, have I ever cheated?
You do cheat sometimes.
- No, I don't.
Ranjan, you take him.
- Not in the middle of the game!
Sis, you take his place.
- Come, Manju.
Come, uncle's nephew.
I guess you were born for me.
[Laughs]
- Come!
Let's continue.
Continue.
- Pick a card, it's your turn, Manju.
Yes.
- Okay.
Aabha, when are you going
to meet Aarti?
I'm thinking of going
day after tomorrow.
[Doorbell rings]
Miss Aarti Shukla, you have been
temporarily suspended from your job.
You have been accused of accepting a
bribe of 30 million for transferring
a 90-acre plot behind
Baraban railway line to Kukreja Builders.
Sir, you know me since so many years.
You think I can do such a thing?
Aarti, the question is not what
I find right or wrong.
The point is that things are against
you in the departmental enquiry.
And now, an official enquiry
has begun into the matter
assisted by ADM Finance.
Moreover, the DM is himself
heading the enquiry.
He has called you to meet him
tomorrow at 9am.
All right, sir.
Good morning, sir.
Miss Aarti Shukla.
That's your name?
- Sattu.
Call me sir.
How can you address a
senior IAS by name?
What post are you on?
Huh?
I'm a sub-registrar.
Since how long?
Four years.
And you already started
accepting bribes?
You want to accept bribes
and become rich?
But I guess it's okay.
You are a part of the system,
accepting a bribe is normal for you.
Right?
It's not like that...
- Did I ask you to sit?
Sir, I am innocent.
I can explain.
You don't have to explain
anything, Aarti Shukla.
You did what you had to.
Now I will do what I want.
The mistake you made,
you have to be punished for it.
Job suspension
and six years in prison
when found guilty.
When or if?
When I declare you guilty.
Satyendra,
at least hear me out once.
- Call me sir.
Oh great, brother-in-law.
You have been keeping
an eye on her since four years.
You even managed to convince the
minister to bring the case under you?
What do you think though?
Is she guilty?
That makes no difference to me.
I only know that I will punish her
for what I think she is guilty of.
I'll make sure she suffers.
Good day, sir.
Everything is fair in love and war.
Love is over, now war begins.
Be happy.
What happened?
- Have sweets.
Why are you so happy,
what is the good news?
See this news.
What news?
- Take a look.
Why are you showing us this
witch's photo? What happened?
Madam acted very proud.
She was against dowry
so she ran away from her marriage.
Let her try to run away now.
Why, what happened?
She is going to be in jail
very soon.
Jail? Why?
- For accepting a bribe.
And the bribe is not small.
- Oh.
The bribe amount is 30 million.
- 30 million!
We'll watch her go to jail now!
[Snaps finger]
Have sweets, brother-in-law.
Let me see the news. - Yes,
we surely deserve to celebrate this.
Take.
- Yes, I'll take it.
In Lucknow?
Even Sattu is in Lucknow.
I'll tell Sattu, he will be pleased.
- Sure, tell him.
[Cellphone rings]
Greetings, Mom.
- There's good news for you.
What happened?
I'm going to become an uncle?
No, this news is even better.
That Shukla's daughter
who left you at the altar,
has been accused of accepting
a bribe of 30 million.
She is going to go to jail.
She is in Lucknow, find out about it.
I'll call you later.
Good day.
- All right. Good day.
So Poonam, how much money
did Sattu demand
that his bride just left the
ceremony and ran away?
I can marry you without
any dowry demands.
What do you say?
- [Laughs]
Hey, where are you going?
Take, Sattu.
Don't mind, buddy.
Listen, Mahesh,
She has not run away because of dowry.
- Oh?
She has run away so that
she can become an officer. - Oh!
And hundreds of clerks like Sattu
can work under her.
She doesn't care one bit
for clerks like Sattu. - Oh, really?
[Music]
"What you filled my heart with"
"You will taste that poison"
"You will endure my pain"
"Suffer the wrath of my curse!"
"You will suffer the consequence of
your selfishness now"
"Having rejected my love"
"You will now endure my revenge"
[Music]
"You heartless woman,
you returned my love"
"with selfishness"
"You were not helpless yet"
"You cheated me"
"You will now endure my hatred
all day and night!"
"Having rejected my love"
"You will now endure my revenge"
[Music]
"Every severity that you knowingly
made me endure"
"God finally made you pay for it"
"The whole world will now watch
your public defeat!"
"Having rejected my love"
"You will now endure my revenge"
He created a ruckus in the house.
He damaged everything.
Just because he became an IAS,
he will do anything, raid anybody's house?
Bindu, get a glass.
- Yes, sis.
He has deliberately taken
the file under him
can't you see that, sis?
He has come only to
take revenge from her.
But when Aarti is innocent,
why should we all be afraid?
Because we cannot stop him.
He has all the power.
He has clearly told her
that he will have her sent to jail.
You are in deep trouble.
Behind professionalism,
he is taking personal revenge from you.
Sis, what do you suggest?
What should we do now?
Aarti.
[Sobbing]
- Hey, you don't have to cry.
Everything will be all right,
don't cry.
Drink some water.
Everything will be all right.
Aarti, I have an idea.
Go and apologise to him.
Look, he loved you very much,
maybe that's why he is so angry.
Maybe he forgives you.
And I have heard he has not
even got married yet.
Meet him somewhere outside office,
invite him for coffee.
Please have a seat,
I'll call sir. Sit.
How are you?
- How can I help you?
Listen, I'm really sorry.
For what?
For doing what I did to you.
I regret it till today.
Dowry was just an excuse.
I'd attempted the competitive exams...
- Will you have tea?
Ashok.
Ashok!
Yes, sir.
- Get two cups tea.
Okay, sir.
So, what were you saying?
I'd attempted the competitive exams.
Its result came on our marriage...
It came on our marriage day.
I didn't know what to do.
I even sent you a message.
- [Phone chimes]
My sister said your family
will never let me work.
I don't know whether I did right or wrong.
- [Chuckles]
Hmm, what?
I admit what I did to you
was very wrong.
I caused you a lot of pain.
I am genuinely sorry.
I understand why you
are so angry with me.
But what can I do now?
If you were so sorry,
why didn't you try to meet me?
I called you so many times.
You know,
I thought we loved each other.
But now that I am
handling your case,
you realise your mistake now?
Huh?
If I had not come here,
you wouldn't even think of me again.
Right?
You were practical then,
you are very practical even now.
Only, you have become hotter now.
Hmm, officer Aarti Shukla?
Very tempting.
Desirable.
Excuse me?
Are you feeling awkward?
You have come so decked up,
why me, even stone will melt.
Isn't it?
Let's first finish with the purpose
you have come here for.
Shall I shut the door quickly?
Satyendra.
Please don't talk like this.
- What?
Stop, stop talking to me in this way.
Okay.
Then how...
Then tell me how should I talk to you?
Look at yourself.
Have you come to seduce me?
Come on, I'm ready.
Come, come, fast.
- Satyendra.
Listen, Miss Aarti Shukla.
If you think that seeing
your beautiful face
I will forget my family
and my humiliation,
that will never happen.
And you don't ever forget that.
Please don't make
this personal, Satyendra.
It is personal.
It's very personal.
I can never forget
how you cheated me.
This is my life's biggest fight.
And yes, I'm not angry,
I hate you!
Now get out of here.
Satyendra...
- Get out!
I'm sorry...
Get out, move.
Miss Shukla.
Don't ever wear pink again
and come before me.
You disgust me.
Out.
[Crying]
Sir, tea.
- Keep it here.
Yes, tell me.
Sir, this is Aarti's father's
passbook,
and this is her personal passbook.
This is personal?
- Yes.
And that builder Kukreja?
He has many businesses.
He has contacts with ministers.
He bought this particular land
to put up a factory there.
He is in London now,
he will be back by next week.
Who got this deal done?
Yes sir, I got this deal finalised.
It's my job, sir.
Did he have the land papers?
How can one sell land
without the papers?
And where is the owner?
He moved to America? - Yes, sir.
And obviously
you don't have his number.
No, sir.
Any address?
I'm here, where else can I be?
I've come at 9 in the morning
and it is 5pm now.
Have you eaten anything since morning?
No. I can eat only
after I leave from here.
I am not allowed to move from here.
Okay, take care. Bye.
[Cellphone rings]
Okay listen, I'll call you back.
Okay.
Sir.
Yes sir, I spoke to him.
I have to meet him at 9:30 tomorrow.
Madam, come tomorrow at 9am.
I'll talk to him,
let me see what he has to say.
Where were these pictures taken?
Sir, I'd gone for a site visit.
This is the same plot
that Mr. Kukreja has bought.
You physically went and verified where
the land is and how much it measures?
And then knowingly transferred
government land to Kukreja's name.
No sir, I really did not know.
Who is this man?
He is Mr. Kukreja's CEO.
Mr. Segal, you must be
purchasing a lot of land.
Yes.
- This plot of land you bought,
it's market value is about 150 million.
How much did you buy it for?
Sir, actually, at that time...
- 60 million.
Yes.
You got land worth 150 million
for 60 million.
You made a direct profit of 60 million.
60... - Yes, you paid
30 million to Aarti Shukla, right?
Are they your friends?
No sir,
I only know them professionally.
He has gifted you a car.
Sir,
he bought it in my name
and gifted it to me on my birthday.
I even sent it back
but he did not take it.
Even today, it is just parked
in my parking, I have never used it.
Umesh.
- Sir.
Has anyone ever gifted you a car?
No sir, never.
- No, never?
No, sir.
- See, even they are officers.
But you seem to be someone special.
This property deal was struck
three days after your birthday.
Being in the system,
you cannot refuse bribes, right?
Isn't that what you believe?
Mr. Kukreja, you are such
a big industrialist.
Yes, sir. - You did not
verify the property papers?
That sounds impossible.
That this is government land,
I think only your officers would know.
I am only concerned with papers.
The papers were in order
so I bought the land.
Are you sure?
I am sure, Satyendra.
Aarti can never accept a bribe
from anyone.
I think there is some confusion.
- Did I ask for your advice, Mrs. Neelam?
No, sir.
Who is this?
- He is Aarti's friend.
Not yours?
Sir, how can such big people
be my friends?
Aarti used to take me
along with her to these parties,
so I went along.
What does your husband do?
- He's a school teacher.
How much do you two earn together?
How much can I earn, sir?
I only got my commission.
Mr. Kukreja said he will
handle the government office.
How am I at fault, sir?
Look, you have a right, Aarti.
If you wish, you can request a
change of the investigating officer.
But if you take my advice,
don't do that.
Because as far as I know,
DM is a good guy.
The officer you get in his place,
his reputation regarding women is not good.
So, I leave it to you.
Once we meet the CM, then we'll
decide what is to be done. - Excuse me.
Tell sir I'll have lunch and come.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
Pramod Singh.
I've done law
from Allahabad university.
Ma'am, I know you from my college days,
I was your senior.
How can I help you?
Ma'am, you tell me
how I can help you.
You see, whoever is
your investigating officer,
I will strike a deal with him for you.
He will pronounce you innocent.
But for that ma'am,
you will have to...
I am her investigation officer.
Strike a deal.
- Sir, I don't know him.
Come on.
You know her?
- Yes sir, I know her.
She is your friend?
- Yes.
Her going to jail is certain,
at least for six years.
You.. what is your name?
- Pramod, sir.
Pramod. I'll send you also
to jail along with her.
Huh? She'll have company.
Pick the pad.
Write a letter for me.
Greetings, Mom.
Greetings, Dad.
Aarti Shukla's enquiry...
Come on, write.
Aarti Shukla's enquiry
is going well.
All evidence is against her.
There is no hope of her acquittal.
There is no hope.
Tell Mom to prepare to
make an offering to God.
Prepare to make an offering...
to God.
Aarti Shukla will certainly go to jail.
What did you write?
What?
It is certain.
Full stop!
Your obedient son...
I'll write the name.
You may leave.
Sit outside.
Love is not easy.
Just know
it's a sea of fire...
You have to drown in it to cross it.
No, you have to destroy yourself in it.
You changed it.
- Understood?
Of course.
Hear this one, Priyansh.
Never make this promise to anyone
That you will love her
more than yourself
That's a good one.
Right.
Talk of love is utter nonsense.
- Really?
I want to talk to you.
- Look who has come to see me.
This couplet I just recited,
I dedicate it to my friend here,
Miss...
What's her name?
Aarti Shukla.
- Aarti! I dedicate it to Miss Aarti Shukla.
She is very famous.
She's a very practical girl.
She's quite controversial.
There was news on her
in the papers recently.
The 30 million bribe case, she's the one.
- Oh.
Now if one has to go to jail,
why just 30 million, one should
at least take 100-200 million.
[Laughs]
30 million is nothing nowadays.
This is the men's room.
I cannot bear this torture
anymore, Satyendra.
I feel suffocated. I cannot breathe.
What do you want from me?
What can I want from you?
I'm only doing my job. Move!
Doing your job or taking
advantage of the opportunity?
I am taking advantage of the opportunity?
- Yes.
I've learnt that from you.
You'd taken advantage then,
I'm taking it now.
I had not taken any advantage
of the opportunity, Satyendra.
Do you know what taking advantage
of the opportunity is? - What?
If I shout now and
say you are molesting me.
Satyendra Mishra, IAS, my investigating
officer is asking for favors from me.
That's called being an opportunist.
Go and say it.
- No, I won't.
Because I am not like that.
I wasn't like that then,
nor am I like that now.
The result came, you were at the door,
I didn't know what to do.
Your mother had told my sister
she will never let me work.
What could I have done?
You should have spoken to me.
You should have trusted me.
- How?
I loved you!
You did not think of me
even once in these five years.
[Crying]
You are shedding tears
before me now, huh?
What about what I went through?
Satyendra... - What about the
pain my parents went through?
I agree, but what can I do now?
What can I do?
What can you not bear?
That I left you?
Huh? You couldn't bear the rejection?
Did you once ever think
that if I had not left you
you would never have been at
the post you are on today?
What do you mean?
- If I had not left you,
you wouldn't be charged and wouldn't
work towards becoming an officer.
You would be a clerk even today.
Have you ever given that a thought?
[Chuckles]
Aarti Shukla, the truth is out.
Being an officer, you had a problem
marrying a clerk. - Satyen...
You found that humiliating.
- Satyendra...
I was a lowly clerk,
I lacked status.
You never understood me then,
you don't understand me now.
What's wrong with you? - You wanted
to travel in a car with a beacon.
I was never worthy of you.
- I was only...
Aarti Shukla,
you were selfish then,
you are selfish now.
You... I don't want to talk!
- Satyendra, that's not what I meant.
Satyendra, talk to...
I'm talking to you.
I am not selfish.
You want to send me to jail?
Send me to jail. Call the cops
right now and get me arrested.
Why tomorrow, I'll go to jail today.
At least I will not have to endure
this daily torture, Satyendra.
I can't take this anymore.
I'll admit I accepted a bribe.
I will... [Crying]
Go.
I can't take it anymore.
Call them right now!
- Okay, okay.
Calm down. Calm down.
- No! What calm down?
You want to talk,
we will talk.
You don't know to talk, Satyendra.
We will sit calmly and talk.
I really cannot take it
anymore, Satyendra.
I'm sorry, I think
I got a little too angry today.
I felt you are going
to kill me today.
How did you develop the habit
of smoking?
I kind of went mad after you left.
I was totally confused.
Let it be,
it's all water under the bridge now.
Choose one finger.
Choose.
If you don't mind,
shall we kiss?
What...
Just one kiss?
I will not doubt your character.
No. Satyendra!
No, not I,
you will kiss me.
A deep, passionate kiss.
And over there
is a five-star hotel.
We'll go there after.
We will spend the night there.
In a five-star hotel, you won't
mind doing anything. - Satyendra!
You only had said it, you forgot?
You know it was just a joke.
- I'm not joking.
It is the price for you
not being in jail tonight.
Come on.
Satyendra!
I misunderstood you.
Won't you ask this time
what was the choice on my other finger?
It's the 10th today.
The committee result will come
within a week.
Send the 30 million you have to us.
Bribe.
I am a part of the system.
If I refuse, force it on me.
I have not accepted any bribe,
I don't have 30 million.
Ask from Kukreja,
he won't refuse you.
You are holding many truths
about him close to your chest.
Mr. Shukla, we will not be
able to help you in this matter.
No ma'am, please don't say that.
Satyendra is not a kid.
Whatever he is doing,
he is aware of it.
If he's asking for 30 million,
pay him 30 million.
Where will I bring 30 million from?
- Look, Mr. Shukla,
we could neither say anything then,
nor can we say anything now.
I'd sold my jewelry once,
to save my husband
and my brother's life.
Now you see what you can sell
to save your daughter's life.
Even if I sell myself
I won't be able to gather 30 million.
That is your problem, Mr. Shukla.
Come ma'am,
Mr. Kukreja is waiting for you.
Yes, it will be done, I'll do it.
- Come, ma'am.
Welcome, madam.
I have been thinking since some days
that I have never met you,
although I have heard
a lot about you.
Mr. Kukreja, if I am proved guilty in
this enquiry, I could lose my job.
My parents will lose their house,
I could go to jail.
You must come forward
and tell the truth.
The world knows the truth, madam.
Don't unnecessarily act innocent
in my presence.
You have taken 30 million.
I have taken 30 million?
Didn't you share the money
with your department?
That means you took all the money?
You should have distributed some
among your colleagues.
What are you talking about?
I have not taken any money from you.
Someone from your department
has squealed.
I have lost my reputation and money
all because of you.
And now that you are in a spot,
you want me also to join you.
Oh, great! I have come across
many officers, but you...
Miss Aarti Shukla is trying
to manipulate the investigation.
Arrest her right away.
Yes, right away.
This is the worst that can happen.
He is taking his revenge.
Let us try one more time.
- Take.
I have kept everything in this.
Okay.
- Just get her released quickly.
Don't cry. Pray to God
that they release Aarti.
Come, Jogi.
Look at me.
I am where you wanted me to be.
Your revenge is taken now I hope.
Happy birthday.
This night is the best birthday
gift of my life.
Thank you.
Sir.
I wish I had never met you.
These are my house papers.
Please free our Aarti.
I'd like to present all the
necessary proof and evidence
that we need to reach a conclusion
on Miss Aarti Shukla's case.
I'd like to seek the permission
of the honorable jury to proceed.
Please proceed.
- Thank you, sir.
I want you all
to watch this video carefully.
Is it written on my head
that I am a fool?
You are an educated woman.
You so conveniently
kept the 30 million to yourself.
Now you have come
to seek more money?
All right, I'll pay you.
I'll pay you whatever sum you demand.
Just get this case that started
because of your foolishness closed.
You want to say something?
No, sir.
I don't want to say anything.
I accept whatever punishment
you announce.
Forward it.
Mr. Kukreja, I am not going
to get intimidated by your words.
If I go to jail,
I won't spare you either.
Hey, you said she has
come to settle the matter.
I think she's mad.
She threatened that she
will have me imprisoned.
We'll have to do
something about her.
Kill the stupid woman.
Her ex-boyfriend has
come to take revenge.
He's gone after her like
a hungry wolf.
And we will become victims
of his foolishness.
We will have to put an end
to the drama of their love story.
Kill her
today!
Can you explain, Mr. Mishra?
Yes sir, I can explain.
Mrs. Neelam Gupta's husband
is a school teacher.
And the broker, Mr. Rajesh Yadav,
who brokered this deal,
is her husband's childhood friend.
Mrs. Neelam retrieves information about
government land lying vacant since years
from government files
and gives it to her husband.
He forwards this message
to his broker friend Rajesh Yadav.
Then Rajesh forges the property papers
and sells them to different businessmen.
Right, Mr. Yadav?
Taking advantage of Aarti Shukla's
trust in her,
Mrs. Neelam takes her
signature on these documents.
They have been taking bribes in the
name of Aarti Shukla since many years.
And they share it amongst themselves.
Mr. Kukreja did give 30 million.
But Aarti Shukla was
totally unaware of it
because that money never reached her.
Right, Mrs. Neelam?
Thank you.
The accused, please stand up.
Thank you, Mr. Mishra.
The evidence is conclusive.
The jury is of the opinion
that Miss Aarti Shukla is not guilty.
Take them into custody.
- Yes, sir.
[Sobbing]
Come.
[Crying]
Sir.
I realise today, sir,
that it really breaks the heart when
you find out someone dear cheated you.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, sir.
You can call me Satyendra.
You can join back office
coming Monday.
Thanks, Sattu.
Mr. Saxena, how are you?
Sir, sending Aarti into custody,
you saved her life.
That's very nice of you.
- Thank you.
Mr. Pramod, good job.
- Thank you, sir.
I'm leaving for Kanpur.
I'll come back and see you. - Sure.
Sir...
Aarti is innocent.
[Cellphone rings]
Listen, is Aarti all right?
Satyendra sent back
the house papers.
Yes.
What...
[Crying]
[Music]
"I want to be with you only"
"Endure all life's sorrows with you"
"I want to live with you only"
"What I cannot tell the world"
"I want to tell only you"
"How can you be so good?"
"I want to lose myself
in your love"
"How can you be so good?"
"I want to lose myself
in your love"
"I want to lose myself!"
[Music]
Where is sir?
- He has not come yet.
What time will he come?
- I don't know.
"After many tribulations I realised"
"I am water, you are the river"
"I have to merge with you"
"After so much happening, I accept"
"My incident, your story"
"If they connect, life is set"
"You just have to look at me
once again"
After so much happening,
anyone will feel revolted, Aarti.
If I was in Sattu's place, even I would
lose faith in love and marriage.
You are right, sis.
But I know that Sattu
loves me very much even today.
If he didn't love me,
he wouldn't hate me so much to
become officer and take revenge from me.
Sattu never wanted
to become officer.
The problem is that his head has
told his heart not to love again.
Now I will silence his head
and make him listen to his heart.
Sattu.
Listen.
How much more will we run?
I'm tired.
I kept running and
became a PCS officer.
You kept running and
became an IAS officer.
Stop now, I'm tired.
We will have to stop somewhere.
If I have run, it is
away from you, Aarti Shukla.
Leave me alone,
our paths are different.
So what if our paths are different,
our destination is the same, right?
Sattu!
Run slower,
I cannot run faster than this.
Yeah, okay.
Thank you, sir.
Stop, stop!
Can you drop me home?
Please?
My car broke down.
Please.
Get in.
Thank you.
Drop her home.
- Huh?
Satyendra. Satyendra.
Go.
Where are you?
- I'll take some time.
You start drinking, I'll join you.
I'm here!
Look, I know that you
are not going to marry me.
But that does not mean
I cannot drink Whiskey with you.
Now my Mussoorie is wherever you are.
Come on now,
order a drink for me.
Okay, forget all that.
I'll start with your drink.
'Ladies first', right?
Ma'am, Whiskey on the rocks.
- Thank you. [Clears throat]
It's bitter.
I feel nothing.
Cheers.
Now I feel something.
[Laughs]
Your glasses are coming in the way.
Shall I wear them?
I look cute, don't I?
Please.
- Ma'am, your drink.
Thank you.
You know,
now I'm really feeling tizzy.
[Laughs]
You are Allahabad's Tom Cruise.
Waiter, get another drink.
- Okay, Aarti, I think...
One. Just one. Cheers!
Husband!
Please, please.
- I want to hold your hand
and roam the valleys of Mussoorie.
- Please, please, Aarti.
There are people here. Please behave.
Shall I kiss you? Just once. Allow me...
- Okay.. fine.. fine...
She's drunk.
Aarti.
[Phone chimes]
[Aarti] 'Sattu, shall I say something?'
'I am thankful to God that he made me
meet you again because of the case.'
'Or I'd probably have lost
you forever.'
Sir, are you distressed?
No.
I was distressed, but not any longer.
Move.
Satyendra!
Sattu, wait, I'm coming.
You...
Careful.
I've been looking for you.
Shall I say something, Sattu?
Satyendra. Satyendra.
Shall I?
I think I'm in love with you.
Shall I say 'I love you'?
Huh?
I love you very much.
I want to marry you.
Because I didn't send you to jail?
I freed you from jail now,
but I freed you from my heart
long ago.
I admit I made a mistake.
Satyendra.
Please relent.
Please?
[Chuckles]
Life is so strange.
There was a time when
I desperately wanted to marry you.
I would think of you all the time.
But what did you do?
You ran away.
- Sattu.
Shall I finish?
And see today.
You know, since the day I saw
my family shattered
I've begun to hate the
word 'marriage'.
And not just you,
I don't want to marry anyone
ever in my life.
Please get this clear.
Thank you.
Sattu...
"The color of love is white, pure!"
"There is no scope for cheating
and deceit in it"
"You are all colors merged in one"
"But you destroyed everything, beloved"
[Music]
"The war you are the chief of"
"I am a mere soldier of that war"
"How can you be so good?"
I want to lose myself
in your love"
"I want to spend my life only with you"
"I want to endure
life's sorrows with you"
"What I cannot tell the world"
"I want to tell only you"
Ranjan.
Yes, sis.
Are you nuts or what?
- What did I do?
What spelling is this? You don't
know your brother-in-law's name?
You wanted to become
an officer? Fool!
He's spelled Sharad as Sharda.
[Laughs]
Go get it printed right.
Time flies.
True.
But look at God's justice.
She is the one who cheated him
and he wants to remain unmarried.
Have you vowed never to
make us grandparents?
That evil woman is getting married.
Do you want to play with her children?
- Why will he do that?
Come on! Although you are right.
- [Laughs]
She is a girl, how long can
her father keep her single.
He had to get her married some day.
I am not stopping her,
I am telling him.
Son, give me the joy of becoming
a grandma before I die.
Yes son,
your mother is right.
Even we want grandchildren.
Don't you all have anything
else to speak about?
This is an important topic
for us, son. Your marriage...
Where are you going now?
- It's Tuesday, I'm going to the temple.
How are you?
- I'm fine.
I heard you are getting married.
[Chuckles]
I thought my enquiry is over.
Should I not?
No, of course not.
Do get married.
It's your life.
This...
Your stole.
I was wondering. A few days
back you told me you loved me.
That you wanted to marry me.
I was, but you refused to marry me.
You are a practical woman.
You always do the right thing
at the right time.
Did you want me to wait
for you all my life?
No, of course not.
But I'm happy
that I have decided
never to get married.
Or I would get someone like you.
- You'd never get anyone like me.
I'm unique.
And now, even I'm getting married.
Is everyone all right in the family?
- Yes.
Sharad.
He's Sharad, my fianc.
Hello.
- He is Satyendra, my very old friend.
Friend?
- I know who he is.
Actually, she has told me
everything about you.
And I want to thank you.
I didn't do anything.
- Yes, thank you for not doing anything.
I mean, if you had married Aarti,
what would I do?
Right, Aarti?
I'll just be back in a minute.
- Okay.
Sharad.
You get the car.
If you don't mind,
shall I tell you something? - Yes.
Don't marry Aarti.
She cannot be trusted.
What do you mean?
Actually, don't mind,
but she's not stable.
Until a few days ago, she was madly
trying to convince me to marry her.
And see now.
Look, as a friend, I'm telling you,
if you marry her
you will be ruined.
I leave it to you.
It's your life, your problem.
Man to man.
Thank you for this surprise too.
Have oblation.
Satyendra...
- No, thank you.
How dare you, Satyendra Mishra!
I am unstable?
Marrying me,
Sharad's life will be ruined?
What do you want from me,
Satyendra?
You don't want to marry me.
You won't let anybody else
marry me.
What should I do?
Do you love me?
- Of course, I love you.
How many times do I say
that I love you?
So you love me
and will marry someone else?
All right, I won't marry him.
Will you marry me? Huh?
Will you marry me?
You won't, because your
ego is coming in your way.
I have decided to get married.
One need not be in love
to get married, Sattu.
One can fall in love after marriage.
I'm getting married on the 10th, be there.
- I will not come.
Please do come.
I will like it.
Do come for the marriage.
Sattu.
Shanti, hurry up,
we have to leave.
We also have to pick up
Mahesh on the way.
You try once.
Call up the driver,
check where he has reached.
We are getting late.
What's going on?
Where are you going?
We are going for a marriage, son.
- Aarti's marriage?
Yes.
Why are you all going?
Son, Mr. Shukla and his wife
themselves came to invite us.
They pleaded with us,
begged us to come.
We must go.
So what? Don't go.
Hey, you are looking very beautiful.
- Thank you.
I suggest you also come along.
No, I will never go.
I wonder why even you all are going.
Hello.
- Hello aunty, hello uncle.
Hello! Hello!
Good you came, Sattu.
Aarti just asked about you.
Good you came.
- Come on, the groom is here.
Oh. Excuse me.
- Come, sis.
Come Sattu, where were you?
- Hello, son-in-law.
Oh, sorry!
Son-in-law is over there.
Congratulations Jogi,
you found a good boy for Aarti.
I just met him. - Not just the boy,
even the family is very good.
They have not made any demand.
- Oh.
Uncle.
Sattu, come, I'll introduce you
to brother-in-law. - Yes, take him.
No, it's okay.
- Come on.
Go.
Thank you so much.
- Come, Sattu.
Greetings, aunt.
- Greetings, son. Bless you.
Brother-in-law.
Come, let me introduce you.
He's Aarti's future husband.
I've met him.
Sorry, friend. You gave the
advice but I did not follow it.
No, I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have said that.
Truly speaking,
I sensed jealousy in your words.
Like if Aarti cannot belong to you, she
should not belong to anybody else, right?
Listen, I'm too embarrassed, really.
No, don't be.
Actually, I'm grateful.
It's good you let Aarti go.
Or she wouldn't be going
with me today.
Dad has booked your honeymoon
to Mussoorie.
Shall we go now?
It's time for the marriage ceremony.
Yes, let's go. Excuse me.
- Come.
Come.
- Honeymoon in Mussoorie!
Where are you?
- Look to your left.
Shall I tell you something?
You look lovely in pink.
Why do you think I'm wearing pink?
Oh, you mean, for me?
I've fallen in love with you.
You liked me so much?
Send me your picture
dressed as a bride.
How do I look?
Just like my bride.
What have I done, Aarti?
I'm really sorry.
I love you very much.
I will not be able to live without you.
I ruined everything
because of my ego.
I love you.
Shall I tell you something?
Earlier, you ran away from the
marriage for your own sake.
This time, run away for your love.
How can I run away?
Mom, Dad, Sharad, his family.
I'll talk to all of them.
I'll convince everyone,
but don't get married.
Just come with me.
Come.
What happened? What...
Choose a finger.
I cannot go with you, Satyendra.
I cannot once again break the
hearts of somebody's family.
No, Aarti,
I'm really sorry, please!
If I was wrong then,
I will be wrong today too.
You were not wrong, Aarti.
Please, I'm really sorry.
You cannot belong to anybody else,
Aarti, I love you.
What should I do?
- Aarti.
How did he come inside?
Satyendra, please.
- Wait, we are talking.
What are you doing?
Leave us alone for a few minutes.
- What are you doing?
Move back, we are talking!
- Satyendra!
Why did you push me?
- Give me two minutes.
Sharad, please.
- How dare you push me!
Why did you push me, you idiot!
- Sharad!
Stop him!
Put a gun to his temple.
Sharad.
- He's acting like a hero.
Come, Aarti.
- You stay here.
Move aside!
Sit down here!
Priest, begin!
Sit down!
Father-in-law, she has made it her
habit to run away on the day of marriage.
I have dragged her here.
Priest, begin the ceremony.
Stand up!
- Sattu, no! Sattu!
I will kill you!
- Sattu, don't.
I'm telling you I love Aarti.
Can't you understand?
Have you gone mad?
Sattu, no! - Uncle, keep quiet!
I won't listen to anybody today!
Sattu, listen to me.
- You come here.
If Aarti cannot belong to me, she won't
belong to anybody. I will shoot him!
What are you doing?
Let us talk.
I will kill you!
I'm warning the last time.
I'll kill you!
Brother-in-law,
why are you overacting?
What is he doing?
He's aimed a gun at me.
This was not in the plan.
Brother-in-law Sharad,
I'm not telling you.
I'm telling brother-in-law Sattu.
What? - What?
- What's going on?
Now what is all this about?
What do you all think?
Only you all can plan, do the drama?
I've become DM!
Tell them.
Aarti is gone.
You stay here.
It's a gun, it can go.
- You will show me the gun?
You will show me the gun?
- Sir, don't hit me.
You fish out your gun in every
marriage? - Sir, it hurts.
Don't beat me, please.
You'll show me the gun? - It hurts,
brother-in-law, don't beat me.
Calling me brother-in-law?
Are you making fun of me?
I'll tell you.
- What will you tell me?
Listen.
- What?
You are getting married.
You could have told me
that you are hand in glove with Sattu.
What could I do?
He beat me so much.
[Laughs]
- My cheeks turned red.
I'm really sorry.
Let me introduce you.
He's Aarti's brother-in-law.
Yours too.
Sorry, brother-in-law.
[Laughs]
No, but seriously,
you all did so much
for Aarti and me.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Dad.
Move away the gun!
[Laughs]
But I must say,
you all acted really well.
Give me the groom's turban.
Sure.
- Brother-in-law, the turban.
Where did the priest go?
Call the priest.
Where is the priest?
Bless you.
"Buy me a gold ring and a gold bangle."
"Give me the gifts and take me home."
"Don't underestimate me, I'm beautiful."
"I can make you go crazy."
"The end of my scarf dangles."
"Just.. just get a little naughty,
my love."
"The end of your scarf dangles."
"You've international looks
but Indian attire."
"It's an awesome combination."
"I'm popular in Bollywood,
mind your tantrums"
"Men go crazy for you as you're unique."
"There are beautiful heroines
but nobody like you."
"As your scarf slips"
"My heartbeats increase."
"Come close and show your face."
"I feel high without drinking."
"Your intentions don't seem good,
my love."
"You make me feel shy."
"Your intentions don't seem good,
my love."
"You make me feel shy."
"You've naughty plans."
"You can't be trusted."
"As you get naughty,
how do I control myself?"
"You keep staring at me."
"The end of my scarf dangles."
"Just.. just get a little naughty,
my love."
"The end of your scarf dangles."
Uncle, book tickets for Mussorie.
- Okay, I'll get it
Bless you.
We've a crazy family.
All's well that ends well.