Once upon a time
there were a Prince and a Princess...
Stories my grandma told me
as a young girl often started like that.
Everyone loves such fairy tales.
We crave stories of love,
romance and all its madness.
Like in the films.
The handsome prince,
the beautiful princess...
dance to a romantic ballad.
The first lock of eyes.
Then, lovelorn looks.
And love songs bursting
with false promises.
And finally... a happy ending.
But, that's far from the truth.
Grandma's story was true.
Once upon a time
there were a Prince and a Princess...
They both died. The End.
Gayatri and I
had an arranged marriage.
It wasn't a love match.
Last year we celebrated
our 50th wedding anniversary.
And in these 50 years,
we fell deeply in love.
We had a deal.
She'd bring me bed tea
every morning.
And every night,
I would turn off the lights
and tuck into bed with her.
But...
she left before me.
Accept our prayers.
On behalf of Thy servant.
- Hello.
- Hello, Kizie.
- Are you feeling unwell?
- I can't talk right now.
- No!
- Why are you whispering?
- Are you breathless?
- I'm fine, Ma.
What are you saying, Kizie?
Is the cylinder empty?
Mom, please take a chill pill.
I'm in a movie.
- Amen.
- Hello, hello.
Kizie?
Bye, Ma.
They're all strangers for me.
As I, to them.
But, I don't know why...
when I hug them,
I feel that I'm able
to take away some of their loneliness.
Or is it mine?
This angry young woman is my mother.
Durgesh, what time
did Kizie come here?
An hour back.
Don't lie!
- I came 15 minutes ago from the cinema.
- Really?
- After watching a film.
- Which one?
- The new one...
- New one?
It stars David Dhawan's son.
The one about dance.
Let's Dance Tonight, right?
That's right!
There's no film with that name.
Concentrate on your job.
No need to eavesdrop
on our conversation.
He's talking nonsense.
Is he?
Ma, me and the rickshaw driver, Durgesh.
The same little lanes.
The same trivial talk.
My small world in Jamshedpur.
My name's Kizie Basu.
Don't ask why.
Welcome to my boring world.
Day and night...
medicines all the time!
Dad.
Kizie, come here. Sit with me.
I start my day watching
National Geographic with dad.
I think he likes animals
more than humans.
Kizie, eat this.
Ma, what are you doing?
Open your mouth.
Why are you resisting them?
This is your favourite cheesecake.
I hate cheesecake.
How can you hate cheesecake, Kizie?
Aren't you a true Bengali?
Mom thinks just like E.T. and Elliot
had a critical bond,
so do Bengali's and their cheesecake.
I'm sure diabetes will kill me
before my cancer does.
Yes.
I have cancer. Thyroid cancer.
And this cylinder
is my best friend, Pushpinder.
The oxygen in it is my boon.
And its weight is my bane.
But, Dr Jha gives me
the deepest blues.
You're a brave girl.
And so long as you stay strong,
there's hope.
Nonsense!
I don't want to be strong.
I just want to be normal.
I want to laugh like a normal girl.
Cry for normal reasons.
I want to gossip about the girl
wearing the gaudy pink skirt.
And I want to crush on
the most handsome boy in college.
But even in my dreams
instead of a guitar,
my hero stands
with an oxygen cylinder.
I think I'm losing it.
I only have one wish.
I want to meet Abhimanyu Veer.
He's my favourite musician.
But, surely every wish
doesn't get fulfilled.
Anyway, enough for today.
Shall we meet tomorrow?
Another boring day
in the life of Kizie Basu.
Hey, Manny.
Manny!
Will this audience know
superstar Rajnikanth's song?
JP, this is just to show our love for him.
- The real show will be in Hindi.
- How?
Shall I show you? The heart...
JP, saw my killer charm?
With a chiselled face like yours,
one look is enough.
My baby boy looks just don't cut it.
Let's go, now.
What a lovely performance.
A big round of applause
for Brij Bhushan.
Louder!
Hey, don't waste plastic.
Show some respect for the talent.
And the next performer is...
Kishan Bajaj with his magic tricks!
Kishan... yay!
Now, now. Come back another time.
Hey Manny, you're back?
Did the Delhi folks boo you away?
All your batch mates are now MBAs.
And you're still lurking here?
Quiet!
Manny, get off the stage. Now!
Or else I'll call your father.
7-6-6...
He would love it, ma'am.
Lights! Music!
Immanuel Rajkumar Junior.
Kizie Basu.
Of course, I'll kiss you, Basu.
Ha-ha-ha!
I've never heard the joke before.
It wasn't a joke.
Who named you, Kissie?
- It's not Kissie.
- Then?
- It's Kizie.
- Oh.
- Z.
- Yeah.
- It's a Zambian name.
- Oh...
And which planet is that?
- Zambia's in Africa.
- Oh, okay.
I was born there.
Then it's not your fault.
I was only...
What does Kizie mean?
I'm just curious.
One that always stays with you.
You mean... a clingy latch.
Shut up.
You must be a latch.
Me? Of course... Obviously.
Ah!
My bike's working now.
Come, I'll drop you.
Thanks.
Why?
- I'll manage.
- Why?
You don't look safe.
You look like a serial killer.
I'm a serial killer
and you a serial kisser.
What a pair! No?
Kizie.
Hi, Mrs Basu.
I'm Kizie's new boy.
Friend.
Boy friend.
Sometimes I feel
like a reality show contestant.
I'm about to be eliminated
but someone votes for me
and I manage to stay on
for another week.
And when the wild card entry appears,
there's mayhem.
Immanuel Rajkumar Junior
reminds me of that wild card entry.
Irritating. Arrogant.
Narcissistic to the core.
But, I don't want him
to get eliminated.
I'm tempted to watch him perform
for another week.
So...
Hey, Manny.
Good to see so many of you here
at this session.
Who wants to start? Anyone?
Hi, everyone. I'm Omkar.
21, Hodgkin's Lymphoma.
I'm sleeping well this week.
Dr Jha has said that
my reports are better.
But, I miss my friends.
Those lectures, picnics...
Will you act in my film?
What?
JP and I are making a film.
Would you like to act in it?
You're mad.
Dr Jha's here.
Keep the faith.
He doesn't fit the bill.
It's a female role.
Look, Immanuel Rajkumar Junior...
You've learned my full name
so quickly.
Naughty girl!
Anyone else? JP?
Ah yes, sir.
What do you shoot all day?
- Sir, we're making a film.
- Really?
And we'll make such a great film
that everyone will appreciate it.
Hello.
My name is JP. Jagdish Pandey.
I have cancer of the eyes.
Optic nerve glaucoma,
isn't it doctor?
I've lost one eye.
In two months I'm scheduled for surgery
and will lose the other one, too.
I've always wanted to make
a super successful Bhojpuri film.
Starring Ravi Kishen or Manoj Tiwari.
But, that's not possible.
But, my film is shaping up well.
With Manny.
Sir, it'll be an Oscar winner.
- Really?
- Do you know who stars in it?
- Who?
- Immanuel Rajkumar Junior!
What's the film called?
'Rajni Arrives, Dreams Revive'.
Manny, would you
like to say something?
Okay.
Tell us, what are you scared of?
I'm scared of absolutely nothing.
Fine. Tell us something
about yourself.
My name is Immanuel Rajkumar Junior.
A few years ago,
I had a brush with osteosarcoma.
And because of that
I lost this baby.
But, I'm a fighter and I...
I fought well.
And sir, I want to act
like Rajni sir.
I want to beat up the bad guys.
Save the girl.
I want to risk my life for her.
I want to be a real-life hero.
Applause!
Does anybody else want to share?
Anybody else?
Kizie Basu?
This is a surprise.
First time.
Sir, I just want to say that
you don't need to be popular
to be a hero.
Even the boy-next-door
can be a hero.
Why does my bike always conk off
in front of you?
Are you really an alien?
I love you... always, forever.
- Always, forever?
- Yes!
Always, forever?
Always, forever.
What's this 'always, forever' business?
It's their 'always, forever' policy.
Their hearts beat
only for each other.
Always, forever.
Do you always say
such irritating things?
Always.
Nothing is forever.
Actually, you're right.
I can't wait for you endlessly.
Why don't you come?
I'll drop you.
I'll save you some time.
Trust me. Look at me.
Come on. Trust me.
Get in.
- Kizie Basu.
- Yes?
You shouldn't be riding
with a stranger on his bike.
What if I were to kidnap you?
Kidnap?
And where would you take me?
Shall I tell you?
This is the favourite spot for both,
serial killers and kissers.
Come.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
Not you. This place.
Yeah, of course.
But, at this very spot,
an ex told me the same thing.
You're so beautiful.
And what did you reply?
"Thank you. I know."
Do you get all your girlfriends here?
No.
Just the aliens.
Ones with these small spaceships.
The spaceship is called Pushpinder.
Pushpinder! A Punjabi!
Wassup, bro!
- Listen to this.
- What is it?
- My favourite song.
- Okay.
Which film is it from?
It's not from a film.
It's from an album by Abhimanyu Veer.
Great.
'I'm Yours.'
Oh!
Yeah.
- Did you like it?
- It's very boring.
Sorry.
- Of course.
- What?
Since it's not from a film.
Hold on. I'm into popular music.
I like all the chartbusters.
'Saturday-Saturday.'
'Girlfriend Gone Bad', 'Bad Guy.'
Such rubbish!
Oh, was it a flop album?
It was a smash hit.
Many years ago.
And for many years.
If Honey Singh would've sung it,
it would still be a hit.
My favourite.
- Really?
- What?
No... what?
I did something?
Nothing.
Then why are you giving me
the 'angry girlfriend' look?
Do you think you look cool
with the cigarette?
Millions of people
are dying with cancer, Manny.
And not being able to breathe
isn't easy.
I don't smoke.
Only a lit cigarette can kill.
And I've taken away its power.
So, it's just a metaphor.
Whatever.
It's not cool.
Yes, of course.
And I'm not your girlfriend.
Like, not now or ever?
Never ever!
Liar!
He's very arrogant.
"Liar!"
I will never meet him again.
He sat between his parents
and when I gave him a cup of tea
my hands did not shake.
But, his..
He rattled the cup
right off the saucer into his lap.
I see my family and friends
in these people sitting here.
I can't bear to see their pain.
I feel like giving them a tight hug,
to mend their broken lives.
My life feels broken, too.
Please mend it.
One son and one daughter later
our lives were whole.
Kenneth was utterly devoted
to his children.
He loved his son
but he spoilt his little girl.
- Who's the dead guy?
- Kenneth D'Costa.
I see.
- Was he Kizie's relative?
- Have you lost it?
Yours?
Are you guys here for free food?
Food doesn't get served here.
Will both of you
please shut up! Quiet.
Sorry.
You are both nuts.
Is this any place for romance?
- We are doing no such thing.
- I am. Aren't you? Feel free to.
I'm begging you. Please shut up.
I won't. Why should I?
My name's Immanuel Rajkumar Junior.
And I'm Jagdish Pandey.
And I haven't worn underpants today.
Ditto! I haven't either.
And I've never had sex!
I...
have...
Never mind, Manny.
You never told me?
Let's talk later.
Let's go from here.
Really sorry.
Manny, you almost got us into trouble.
Manny, left.
- Is your house on the left?
- Yes.
Of course.
That's it. That's it.
Thank you.
So, what have you decided?
Will you play the heroine?
I might. But, on one condition.
You will listen to this first.
Boring.
Do you want a heroine?
You don't have a choice.
The film hasn't started
but the tantrums have begun.
You're surely my heroine.
- Pushpinder bro, take care of her.
- Bye!
I'm yours...
Manny, you're croaking.
You've ruined my sleep.
I'm yours, my darling.
Here, Manny, have some milk.
- Stop it, JP.
- But, what did I do?
I don't care.
I have so many problems and you...
- Not my problem. Just stop it.
- What did I do?
- You loved me very much till yesterday.
- Now I don't!
I'm going to lose my sight...
How's the fish?
What?
Kizie, how's the fish?
It's awesome, Ma. Too sweet.
Sweet?
I'm sure it's that boy.
At this age, it's always a boy.
Manny?
Hi.
Manny!
Are you looking for me?
I love your t-shirt.
Thank you.
But, what are you doing here?
Kizie Basu, I heard your songs.
- Manny, Ma and Dad are downstairs.
- What an album!
- What amazing songs.
- Right?
This Abhimanyu's deep.
- He's so deep!
- But, tell me...
I'm yours when?
I mean, the song. 'I'm Yours'.
What's after?
What happens 'When I'm yours'?
He vanished.
Abhimanyu Veer vanished into thin air.
He never completed the song.
That's the problem with new artists.
They start but never finish.
Then there's Rajni sir.
He starts one task but finishes two.
Correct.
Of course. Rajni sir's great.
He fires a bullet
which splits in four.
If Hollywood does it... wow!
But if Tollywood does it... how?
And since when have you
started watching Rajnikant films?
Shut up. I...
Yes? Hello.
Hello.
- Yo, bro.
- I'm going in.
Hey, JP.
You won't go inside.
Or our friendship is over.
Listen.
We have to find this Abhimanyu Veer.
Yes, bro... I'm listening.
I love you, Manny.
Stop crying, please.
I'll be there in 10 minutes, okay?
- I love you, too.
- Why is he crying?
- Got eggs at home?
- What?
How many? Get them all.
I can't, Manny.
I can't come.
Ma and Dad are downstairs.
"Seize the day!"
- Stop with the film dialogues.
- "Make those 10 minutes count."
Please!
Okay.
Always, forever...
- Never ever!
- JP.
- Always, forever.
- JP!
- Come.
- Never ever.
Always, forever.
Never ever.
- Always forever.
- Break up?
- Sorry.
- No... betrayal.
She always said
that she would be my eyes.
Bro, don't stress.
It's time for revenge.
Manny, revenge isn't going
to alleviate my pain.
It's not about alleviation
but revolution.
Hold this. Come here.
- What should I do with it?
- Come here.
Throw it on her.
- No way!
- Lob it.
- Throw away all your anger.
- Did it hit?
Channel all your anger and throw.
- It's a hit!
- It hit.
Try it. Go for it.
- Go on, Kizie.
- Throw. I'm going to throw one now.
Aim for the bedroom.
- How do I know where her bedroom is?
- It's there. On the left.
Throw it.
Score!
Yes!
Oh, God.
Hello, Damania ma'am.
Manny, what are you doing here?
Ma'am, your daughter
broke my friend's heart.
Go inside.
We're here to break your house
not your heart.
But remember,
you can still call my dad.
You have his number, right?
Go inside. Go on.
- Let's get back to it, bro.
- Really?
With all your might.
Score!
Listen.
One for the...
I want to meet Abhimanyu Veer.
The song must get completed.
- It's not possible.
- Why?
I've tried desperately.
He has disappeared.
Even Invisible Man
was ultimately found.
Abhimanyu Veer is hardly a challenge.
What say?
When am I starting shoot?
Bro, we've got our heroine!
Kizie Basu.
The name's enough
to rock the country.
Rascal, are you here to avenge me
or start your own love story?
- Sorry.
- Concentrate!
Come on, Kizie. Throw them.
What an aim.
Hold this. Aim at the kitchen
I have no idea where the kitchen is.
These scenes highlighted
in yellow are Manny's.
And the orange ones are mine.
- And which is the next scene?
- This one.
We'll shoot your intro.
What say, JP?
What was it? The rain sequence.
Damsel in distress.
In rain-soaked tresses.
I'm no damsel in distress.
I'm Bengali.
And Bengali girls are dangerous.
'Rajni Arrives, Dreams Revive'.
Shot number 1. Take number 1.
Action.
And then our worst fears came true.
JP got operated
and lost his sight.
But, we had promised each other
to complete the film.
So... action.
Though the lion is called
the King of the jungle,
the lioness has all the power.
In her lifetime,
a lioness mates with multiple lions.
It is believed
that in this excited state,
a lioness can have sex
anywhere between 20-40 times
without even taking a break
for food or water.
When the lioness is away hunting...
Such stamina!
The lion is unable to mate even once.
It's all a lie.
They must be on an energy drink.
When the lioness returns from her hunt
the lion loses his cool...
What do you do?
I'm an astronaut.
I'm going to NASA next week.
You? A scientist?
Actually, my father is very rich
so I don't need to do anything.
- You should.
- Sure.
You're not that young anymore.
- Why are you joking?
- Me? It's you who's being funny.
- Is this any food to offer a guest?
- Isn't the salt less?
Stop it, dad.
More like, absent.
- What?
- Yes.
- These potatoes are like rocks.
- Immanuel says there's no salt in the food.
- What?
- Oh my God.
- What happened?
- Salt.
Didn't you like the food?
Do you know that she secretly
watches reality shows at night?
- What?
- Yes.
And she also votes
for her favourite contestants.
No, Ma. He's lying.
- That's my phone.
- That's the one she uses.
- Look. Check it.
- No!
What is this, Kizie?
And she's becoming violent.
- Ma...
- I'm very disappointed with you, Kizie.
- He's lying.
- You don't listen to me anymore.
I don't do any of that.
Honestly!
Liar!
- Why did you tell Mom?
- I didn't. Your dad did.
I've been trying
to say it since 25 years.
I saw a chance today.
There's less salt in the food.
Very good.
If you don't like the food,
don't have it.
Don't force yourself.
I'm diabetic.
Tomorrow you bring
all your reports to me, all right?
We'll have a separate consultation on...
Kizie.
Manny?
Sir.
Manny, what are you doing?
Get up.
- What happened?
- Sir, her life's in danger.
- What?
- Come, come.
- Manny!
- I'm going, sir.
Manny, what happened?
Take me along.
I want to show you something.
- But Manny, what happened?
- See, you have to help me.
Abhimanyu Veer's song is driving me mad.
- You're welcome.
- Yeah, but...
Don't you think
we need closure on it?
Shouldn't we know how it ends?
But, it's very tough to find him.
Is it?
- Yes.
- Have you tried?
I...
Here.
I think I've found Invisible Man.
"Dear Immanuel Rajkumar Junior.
"Thank you for writing to me.
"That incomplete song was my last one.
"You can't create music.
It flows from within.
"So, to answer your question...
"Forget fans, I can't even complete
the song for myself, sir."
He called me 'sir'.
"And so, your question
will remain unanswered.
"But I'm glad to know
that you and your friend Kizie Basu...
"liked my song.
"Thank you for your generous email.
Regards, Abhimanyu Veer."
Dear Mr Abhimanyu Veer.
Thank you for your reply.
I don't know why
but I feel that you will understand me.
I might not live for very long.
And your songs...
capture the loss of a loved one.
Ma, Dad, Manny...
Is there no way
of saving them from this hurt?
I want to meet you.
Please.
Love, Kizie Basu.
Elbow out.
It shouldn't slump. Like this.
Do you know how to dance?
Sure, why not?
Engineering students know it all,
but engineering.
Come here. Give me your hand.
Fine?
One, two...
Sorry, I forgot.
What?
Son, Pushpinder.
Let's dance together.
The hand goes here.
Are you going with Manny?
I told you I'm awesome.
Hello.
Kizie?
You can't leave me high and dry.
Shut up.
Manny, it's 1 am.
So?
I should sleep.
Seri.
Seri?
Is that Tamil?
Yes.
Means okay in Tamil.
I like the sound of the word.
Seri.
Manny, from now on,
'Seri' is our word.
Seri, Kizie Basu.
Seri... Immanuel Rajkumar Junior.
It's often said,
love is like falling asleep.
It happens slowly, then all at once.
It happened to me, too.
I fell asleep
while talking to Manny.
"Dear Ms Basu.
"It's tough to answer your questions
on email.
"Sometimes the right words evade you.
"But, if you're ever in Paris,
let's meet.
"Yours sincerely, Abhimanyu Veer."
- Ma!
- What happened?
- Ma... Dad!
- What's wrong?
Nothing. Sorry, Dad.
Then why did you scream?
This!
"Dear Ms Basu.
"It's tough to answer your questions
on email.
"Sometimes the right words evade you.
"But, if you're ever in Paris,
let's meet."
You can't go to Paris
with him, Kizie.
You don't even know him
well enough.
You don't know him!
What do you mean?
What are you trying to tell me?
Ma, stop over reacting.
Am I? Really?
Do you seriously think
that I'm over reacting?
Just tell me the truth.
- Is your virginity safe?
- What's wrong with you?
- What's wrong with me?
- Yes! It's safe.
I've locked it away safely
in a Swiss bank locker.
- Get it back when I'm dead.
- Kizie!
What's this?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I want to go to Paris.
I have to go.
Sweetheart, your mother is right.
How can you go alone?
Your body can't take the travel.
Dad, I'm fine.
No, you're not, Kizie.
Am I not saying that?
Okay.
Let me talk to Dr Jha.
If he gives permission then...
Kizie! Why are you saying that?
I'm speaking to my daughter.
What are you saying?
If Dr Jha gives permission will you...
- Dr Jha is the best person to...
- For what?
Does every darn thing
have to be a fight?
- I don't know.
- Why?
You said the PET scan report
was normal.
I meant the cancer
was in control for the time being.
I'm going just for a few days.
I'm not moving there permanently.
I can't give you permission
to go alone.
Alone? Manny's with me.
Manny! I'd never give you permission
to go alone with him.
You're talking like Ma now.
Only on one condition.
Only if Mrs Basu goes with you.
What?
Ma!
Me?
Ma will come with me.
It's the perfect idea.
Why me?
Ma, you've never seen Paris.
What will I do there?
- Hello, Kizie Basu.
- Hello, Junior.
Ladies and gentlemen,
hold onto your hearts.
Here's presenting...
- Manny?
- What?
I've made all the travel bookings.
Jamshedpur - Ranchi - Delhi...
And straight to...
- Paris!
Kizie Basu, Paris!
- What are you saying?
- Seriously.
Now, it's your turn...
to...
Of course, right?
But you could have given me
this information on the phone.
I could have.
But, I haven't come to give.
I've come to receive. Kissie...
I've heard that a first kiss
is very special.
Yes.
Ask me.
I've had several first kisses.
I was 15 and she, 17.
We were in the canteen...
Manny!
Why do I get the feeling
that our first kiss will be very special?
Don't you feel the same?
I do.
You do?
Okay...
Come on. Get up.
- Hey!
- Leave.
You can't get rid of me
in Paris, Kizie Basu.
- Out!
- Okay.
Manny!
Bye.
Manny...
instantly puts a smile on my face.
Makes my heart leap.
Breaking news!
Cancer can't stand your happiness.
I couldn't see clearly.
But, mom's rolling tears
made me sense her fear.
Dad's false promises
were dripping with distress.
I was scared, too.
I was scared that I would
never be able to see
Manny's stupid smile... ever again.
Hi. I'm alive.
I guess Kizie really means a latch.
But now, I've found reason
to latch on to life.
However, I was scared to meet
that reason in my current state.
I guess, we were all scared.
Ma and Dad were scared
of the medical terms.
The more experienced the doctor,
the more complicated the words.
Dad's nodding in agreement...
but isn't processing any information.
My team and I are right here.
Okay?
Okay.
All the reports by 5 o'clock, please.
Okay. Sure, sir.
Dad...
Manny?
He's waiting outside.
He wants to meet you.
How's Kizie, sir?
Better.
She doesn't want to meet you.
I'm not here to meet her, either.
I came to see you.
Really?
No... I'm lying.
I'm not going anywhere.
Kizie, love... the door's open.
Don't worry. Okay?
Thanks, Dad.
Good night.
It's Manny.
I know, Dad.
It's not fair to him.
It's my problem.
He doesn't need to suffer through it.
Correct. Absolutely.
We didn't need to suffer, too.
We should've left you
at an orphanage in Zambia.
Right?
Let him decide
whether he wants to suffer or not.
Okay?
Kizie Basu.
Immanuel.
Are you okay?
Not really.
I'm not okay.
Tell me what happened.
Manny, I want to go to Paris.
I want to meet Abhimanyu Veer.
Why is 'I'm Yours' incomplete?
And were it to get complete,
how would it end?
- I need to know.
- And where do I feature in all this?
I hope you know...
You ignoring me won't change
my feelings for you.
Manny, we can't be together.
Why not?
It can't be...
Friends?
We can be friends, right?
Friends.
- Friends.
We're all friends.
You're a friend. I'm a friend.
Okay, bro? We're all friends.
Okay?
Seri?
Seri.
She wants to go to Paris
with her ill health.
She's only thinking about Paris.
We're tired of explaining to her, doctor.
Can you please explain
the seriousness of things to her?
Kizie, it's very risky to travel.
Your immune system's very weak.
Paris has doctors.
I'll be okay.
I've given my advice.
Finally, it's a family decision, Mr Basu.
Why the deathly silence?
It's a personal family matter.
Else, I would've decided.
Come, time for bed.
Didn't hear me?
You won't be able to convince her.
You can't.
Will you have a beer?
What?
Beer.
They've gone to sleep. Want one?
Don't act silly.
You aren't allowed to drink.
I know.
But...
sometimes it's fun being silly.
So, you love Kizie, right?
Really?
But, I know...
and I really appreciate
your concern.
But don't you feel that
in her current condition...
it's a bit silly?
When my leg was operated,
I told Dad...
Please don't cut my leg.
How will I...
How will I play basketball?
And he said the same thing.
Please don't be silly.
I may have been acting silly.
But, that one moment
changed my life completely.
I played basketball
after the surgery, too.
But, it didn't have
the same magic.
When I jumped,
I didn't enjoy the flight.
When I ran,
I didn't know why I was running.
Losing a game was justified.
And in a freak case when I won,
I didn't enjoy the success.
I mean, there was a feeling
of being incomplete.
Like Abhimanyu Veer's song.
I dream big.
But, I'm not as driven
to fulfil them.
Kizie has a small dream.
And I really want
to fulfil it for her.
I know.
I know it's a bit silly.
Going to Paris in this condition,
is a bit silly.
But to fulfil Kizie's dream...
The fun in that silliness
is unparalleled.
So, Kizie Basu...
Are you going to meet
Abhimanyu Veer or Mr Manny?
You had a favourite dress
when you were eight.
You'd wear it every evening.
You loved that dress
so much, Kizie Basu.
I loved that dress
because you had stitched it for me.
Yes.
I should've stitched
this one, too.
Isn't it too revealing?
Ma, it's fine.
Is it really? Really?
It's fine?
Won't do.
AV.
Cold coffee with ice cream anybody?
- No, sir.
Come.
AV doesn't drink alcohol.
Only cold coffee.
Alcohol is bad for the liver.
You shouldn't drink.
What are you doing?
Cigarette smoking
is injurious to health.
It can lead to cancer.
Oh.
But, you already have cancer.
Go on. Smoke it.
AV, Kizie and Manny are big fans.
Actually, sir... Kizie's a big fan.
And you?
I worship Rajnikant.
Who's that?
Just joking, mate.
I love Rajnikant.
Aka Thalaiva. Woohoo!
Sir, 'I'm Yours' is my favourite album.
Mine, too. High five.
Why didn't you complete the title song?
'Cause I forgot to finish it!
No, don't worry about it.
This is his normal behaviour.
Sir.
Sir, please tell me.
My dad murdered my mom.
I'm just joking.
Mom and Dad are both
alive and kicking.
Can you stop this!
We've come from India
only to meet you.
Can you talk normally
for just two minutes?
Normally.
Sir, why is your song incomplete?
Did the reason
to complete the song end?
Who did you write the song for?
You surely loved her...
Do you still do?
Can you live happily after
the person you loved has gone?
Do you know what happens
after death?
No... what?
How would I know?
I'm still alive.
But, after my death I'll come as a ghost
and let you know.
Can you please shut up!
Enough of this nonsense.
Please stop this charade.
You guys emailed us
which is why we've come.
Kizie, let's go.
He needs help.
He needs medical treatment.
No doctor was able to help.
Yeah, sure.
When someone you love dies,
so does your own will to live.
But, death still doesn't take you.
And it is illegal to die by suicide.
So, you must continue
this sorry existence.
And because we make
stupid promises to each other
that the one left behind
will go through life with a smile...
Smile.
Smile!
Why aren't you smiling?
If you can't even smile now
what about after death?
That's what's going to happen
with you two, as well.
One of you will die.
And the other, will smile and exist.
Smile!
Why didn't I complete the song?
Because life is incomplete.
What's wrong?
He was saying the truth.
- That psycho?
- Yes.
He was saying the truth.
People can never be happy
after losing a loved one.
They lose their reason to smile.
How will Ma and Dad live?
How will you?
I'll be happy.
I'll get rid of you, after all.
Shut up.
Sorry.
Life is incomplete like his song.
I'll finish that song for you.
And 10 times better, okay?
I can sing it for you even now.
Just give me a second.
- Just... sorry...
- It's not that...
It's not funny.
Can I please just talk to you.
Look, you're smiling.
I know, but...
You were better off in Jamshedpur.
Then?
Then we went to Montmartre.
It was beautiful.
Very nice.
After that... to Notre Dame.
That was also...
And then, Manny?
- What?
- Notre Dame...
That's it.
Yes... that's it.
- That's it?
- Yes...
Yes... we were wandering the streets.
Long walk.
It was a nice long walk.
Finish your breakfast.
Long walk!
Immanuel Rajkumar Junior.
Just as Pushpinder is imperative
for my lungs,
you are for my heart.
It beats faster
every time you come closer.
I love you.
I love you, Immanuel Rajkumar Junior.
I love you so much.
Manny?
What happened?
Tell me.
Before you went to the hospital.
I just had...
an ache.
I did a PET scan.
And it lit like a Christmas tree.
Can we just pretend...
I'm not dying.
I'm not going anywhere.
- Can we just pretend?
- Yeah. Yes.
- We'll live like this, right?
- Always.
Always.
Seri.
I heard that...
you've shot the song very well.
- It's full of romance and sex.
- Shut up.
We aren't making a porn film.
Do I care, Manny?
It's not as though I can see it.
- But, Manny...
- Yes.
I really miss watching porn.
I'm sure.
And will you miss me?
Manny...
why are you saying that?
Of course.
I'm going to miss you loads.
Slowly and steadily
Manny's health was deteriorating.
We neither had anything to say
to each other, nor to hear.
And I was helpless.
Manny... Manny, get up.
- Kizie?
- Get up.
Get up.
What happened?
- You're a phony.
- What?
You promised to make me a heroine.
- Did you forget?
- No.
Who will complete JP's film?
I will, of course.
So?
Now?
Seize the day, Immanuel.
It's now or never.
The heroine must compromise.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Can you come to Payal theatre?
Why?
What happened?
I need help.
Manny!
Manny, what are you doing here?
Why?
Manny, it's infected.
- I'll have to call someone.
- No, please. Kizie, no!
Don't call them.
Please don't call them.
- Manny!
- Don't call my dad.
- I'll never talk to you.
- I'll have to call your dad.
Manny, what are you doing here?
I just... wanted to do
something for myself.
Wanted to do it on my own.
I'm...
Could you help me?
Could you please help me?
- I have to call the ambulance.
- I don't want to die.
Hello, Tata Hospital?
Please can you come
to Payal Cinema?
Ramkrishna colony, Jamshedpur.
The one who taught me to smile
was howling in pain.
He was screaming.
And I couldn't do anything.
Hi, Manny.
Please go.
I'm fine.
Really?
I don't need you right now.
My name means a latch.
You won't leave me?
Not until the very end.
Manny had come home.
But, how long he would survive,
was a looming question.
Mr Rajkumar.
Ms Basu.
I told you that when I die,
you would have to give my eulogy.
Have you written anything?
Yes.
Then hurry to the church.
Manny, are you okay?
I love you, Kizie Basu.
Five more steps. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Right turn.
Straight.
You're there. Almost.
You're late.
Welcome.
What's happening?
Tell her, bro...
I wanted to attend my own funeral.
Though I know I'm going to be
somewhere here as a ghost.
In case it doesn't work out.
- So... preview.
- Okay.
- JP.
- Yes.
I haven't prepared anything.
When Manny was 24...
I'm 23.
You're dead, Manny.
Why're you butting in?
Won't you live another year,
at least?
I met Manny when he was 19.
He had a killer smile, even then.
And when I met him, I was charmed.
I found out much later
what a jerk he really was.
My family is in Bihar.
Manny and his grandma
were my only family here.
They became closer to me
than my real family.
I sometimes feel...
it's best that I lost my sight.
Because I don't want to see a world
that doesn't have Manny.
I've lost my sight but I will always
remember Manny's face.
My best friend.
Immanuel Rajkumar Junior.
Whoa, that's too much emotion.
So... okay, bye.
Take care.
Kizie Basu.
When I moved from Zambia
to Jamshedpur, I was angry.
And scared.
I was angry because I thought, "Why me?"
Why did I need Pushpinder
so early in life?
And I was scared wondering...
what would become
of Ma and Dad after I die?
But suddenly one day,
came Manny, dancing into my life.
I haven't ever met anyone
more irritating than him.
Neither do I want to.
He made jest of everything.
Laughed at everything.
And taught me how to live life.
And slowly, he became my reason to live.
But, just as...
quickly he came into my life...
he also exited.
And left me all alone... again.
Left me all alone... again.
And two days later,
Manny left us.
He left me a letter.
Kizie, once upon a time
there were a Prince and a Princess.
They died. The End.
Every grandmother tells this story.
But, it's an incomplete one.
One that the Prince and Princess complete.
We don't get to decide
when we're born or when we die.
But we do get to decide
how we live our lives.
So, Kizie Basu, this Prince is dead.
But, his Princess lives.
And until then, our story lives on.
Kizie, I promised to complete
your favourite song.
I had to ask that madman,
Abhimanyu Veer, for help.
I'm a true lover, but a poor poet.
And he's a terrible human being,
but a talented musician.
Seri, Kizie Basu?
Seri!
Subtitles Diego Moraes(oakislandtk)
www.opensubtitles.org