This Subtitle Encoded By Swagath77@Subscene.com
Dilbar Dilbar Dilbar
Beloved, beloved, beloved...
Chadha Jo Mujhpe Suroor Hai
The intoxication that is over me...
Asar Tera Yeh Zaroor Hai
This is surely because of You...
Teri Nazar Ka Kasoor Hai
It is the fault of Your eyes...
Dilbar Dilbar Dilbar
Beloved, beloved, beloved...
Aa Paas Aa Tu Kyun Door Hai
Come close to me, why are You distant?...
Yeh Ishq Ka Jo Fitoor Hai
The madness/passion of love is over me...
Nashe Mein Dil Tere Choor Hai
My heart is intoxicated in Your love...
Dilbar Dilbar Dilbar
Beloved, beloved, beloved...
Ab Toh Hosh Na Khabar Hai
I'm not in a conscious state, I'm unaware about everything...
Yeh Kaisa Asar Hai
I don't know what kind of reaction is this...
Hosh Na Khabar Hai
I'm not in a conscious state, I'm unaware about everything...
Yeh Kaisa Asar Hai
I don't know what kind of reaction is this...
Tumse Milne Ke Baad Dilbar
After meeting You, my beloved...
Dilbar, Dilbar, Dilbar, Dilbar, Dilbar
Beloved, beloved, beloved...
This Subtitle Encoded By Swagath77@Subscene.com
Karti Qatal Na Aise Tu Chal
You cause deaths, don't walk in such a way...
Paheli Ka Iss Nikalo Koi Hal
Please find the answer to this riddle...
Husan Ka Pitara Khilta Kamal
You're a chest full of beauty, a blooming lotus...
Kar Loonga Sabar Kyunki Meetha Hai Fal
I will have patience as I know that the fruit is sweet...
Tu Mera Khwaab Hai
You are my dream...
Tu Mere Dil Ka Qaraar
You are peace of my heart...
Dekh Le Jaan-E-Mann
Look at me, O love of my heart...
Dekh Le Bas Ek Baar
Just look at me one time...
Chain Kho Gaya Hai, Kuch Toh Ho Gaya Hai
My peace is lost, Something surely has happened...
Tumse Milne Ke Baad Dilbar
After meeting You, my beloved...
Ladies...
Ab Toh Hosh Na Khabar Hai
I'm not in a conscious state, I’m unaware about everything...
Yeh Kaisa Asar Hai
I don't  know what kind of reaction is this...
Hosh Na Khabar Hai
I'm not in a conscious state, I'm unaware about everything...
Yeh Kaisa Asar Hai
I don't know what kind of reaction is this...
Tumse Milne Ke Baad Dilbar
After meeting You, my beloved...
Dilbar, Dilbar, Dilbar
Beloved, beloved, beloved...
This Subtitle Encoded By Swagath77@Subscene.com